<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304</link>
    <description>Here goes what is probably another failed attempt to suggest a social class.
_**NuclearBurrito**_ did us all a huge favor when he listed old and possible new abilities for social classes, so it helped me try again since my last attempt failed.

_**The Spy (Blue Dragon Social)**_

**Passive: Government Secrecy** - Spy visits are hidden.

**Day Ability 1: Private Matters** (2 uses) - Whispers from and to you are hidden from the court.
**Day Ability 2: I Spy with my Little Eyes** (3 uses) - Whispers from and to the target are shown to you.

**Night Ability 1: Eavesdrop** (Unlimited uses) - Check if the target talked that night. You will not know who he talked to or what he said. Framed targets appear as having spoken. This ability triggers its answer _**as soon as**_ the person speaks.
**Night Ability 2: Burn After Reading** (3 uses) - Prepare a message that will be sent at the beginning of the next morning to the target. Your name will not appear in the message. The target will receive something along the lines of &quot;**Spy**: #7 claimed Sheriff to the king but spoke last night.&quot; Only the target and the Spy will know about the existence of such a message. Activating this skill without choosing a target aims it at the Prince. The Spy will never be informed the Prince&#39;s number, however.

**Win Condition: Unseen/Cult loses**

_**The Mole (Unseen Social)**_

**Passive: Government Secrecy** - Mole visits are hidden.

**Day Ability 1: Private Matters** (2 uses) - Whispers from and to you are hidden from the court.
**Day Ability 2: Expose** (3 uses) - Reveal to the Unseen who the Prince jails tonight.

**Night Ability 1: Careless Whispers** (2 uses) - The Unseen may whisper each other without the court knowing about it during the next day.
**Night Ability 2: Noise Complaint** (3 uses) - Silence a player until the next morning. If the target is neither in the dungeon nor linked with a psychic. This player will be silenced at the beginning of the next morning. This alternative effect lasts until the night.

**Win Condition: BD loses**

So, the Spy and the Mole are another shot at getting a new Social class in. They are entirely focused on communication mechanics. The Spy is a great tool against evil kings, just like the Noble once was. He&#39;s kit revolves around finding people sending strange whispers and check them later that night. It&#39;s important to remember that people speak to the Prince and the Prince to them during nighttime and the same applies to Psychics. This skill could even be triggered by a fool who decided to talk to himself at night to lure a Spy accusation the next morning. So I don&#39;t think it&#39;s OP. Noise Complaint is a direct social attack on Unseen/Cult&#39;s face. 
And then he gets converted! The Spy becomes a Mole and the Mole is a huge weapon against the Prince (if he wasn&#39;t killed n1). He is that because he can silence a jailed player (Noise Complaint isn&#39;t prevented on jailed players) and that directly leads to lack of information to the Prince and a possible execute that could get him to lose his ability to Execute altogether. Prince players would have to be extra careful in Spy games because of the chance that he may be converted.
One of the things I like the most about these classes is that they don&#39;t depend on their alliances to win. All that matters to them is that their enemies lose. The NK can win, there could be a solo fool win or two alchemists winning by themselves. You win with them because your enemy lost.
Come on guys, it&#39;s a nice idea! Give me that juicy feedback!!

Funny note: If you think about it, Spies can actually counter Moles if they are lucky enough, which is awesome! Also, two Spies could totally work together without anyone knowing about it.

Side note: As said by 3DT_CheesyKnives, this could also work as a Noble rework if we added Royal Blood to it.

**Changelog:** 
Got rid of the Spy&#39;s second night ability Noise Complaint. Left Mole with it. (Feedback from NuclearBurrito)
Added the Side note. (Feedback from 3DT_CheesyKnives)
Added a new second night ability to the Spy, &quot;Burn After Reading&quot; and fixed &quot;Eavesdrop&quot; so they could work together. (Me)
Fixed Burn After Reading target. (Feedback from NuclearBurrito)
Fixed Burn After Reading target even further. (Me)
Updated Noise Complaint. (Feedback from NuclearBurrito)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 13:29:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i also tried making it more noble like</p>
<p>(Based on Sheepish’s Spy / Mole Idea)</p>
<p>The Noble (Blue Dragon Social)</p>
<p>Passive: Royal Blood - Can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King. You will keep this passive even if your class changes.</p>
<p>Day Ability 1: Social Status (2 uses) - Choose a target who has whispered that day. You will find out if they were royal tonight.<br>
Day Ability 2: Noble Matters (3 uses) - Whispers from and to the target are shown to you.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: Royal Hearing (2 uses) - Force your target’s next whisper to be public.</p>
<p>Night Ability 2: Messenger (3 uses) - Prepare a message that will be sent at the beginning of the next morning to the target. Your name will not appear in the message. The target will receive something along the lines of “Noble: <span class="hashtag">#7</span> claimed Sheriff to the king but spoke last night.” Only the target and the Noble will know about the existence of such a message. Activating this skill without choosing a target aims it at the Prince. The Noble will never be informed the Prince’s number, however.</p>
<p>Win Condition: Unseen/Cult loses</p>
<p>The Aristocrat (Unseen Social)<br>
Passive: Royal Blood - Can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.<br>
Passive: Secret Matter - Aristocrat visits are hidden.</p>
<p>Day Ability 1: Careless Whispers (2 uses) - The Unseen may whisper each other without the court knowing about it during the next day. The Unseen will be notified of this.<br>
Day Ability 2: Noble Matters (3 uses) - Whispers from and to the target are shown to you.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: Royal Hearing (2 uses) - Force your target’s next whisper to be public.<br>
Night Ability 2: Noise Complaint (3 uses) - Silence a player until the next morning. If the target is neither in the dungeon nor linked with a psychic. This player will be silenced at the beginning of the next morning. This alternative effect lasts until the night.</p>
<p>Win Condition: BD loses</p>
<p>Im not good at this ok</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 13:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so at what point , if the person is framed , will it show that they speak if eavesdrop is used ? If it is immediate , it might be obvious they were framed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 11:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess I understand what the Mole does, and the Spy as well, but I want to see how other people give feedback before adding mine. It’s pretty interesting though, but I think Noble should be added back anyways, regardless of your Spy getting added, as we’re in dire need of BD Social classes anyways. There are almost no Apostles ;-;</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>3 options:</p>
<p>1: Have it require a Prince to be alive to do anything. (Not the main ability anyways so whatever.)</p>
<p>2: Have it go to the potentially evil king and deal with the consequences of doing so</p>
<p>3: Have it go to a chosen starting class. It would not say who if anyone got it. (it would send it to everyone who started with the chosen class</p>
<p>Oh and by the way. Noise complaints should make is so that any edits made to the targets journal that night won’t save if he is killed that night so that it is useful without a Prince/Psychic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 22:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="6" data-topic="28304">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I suggest having it go to the king instead.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>King might be evil, but you are right. What about to the targeted player?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 22:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sheepish" data-post="1" data-topic="28304">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/sheepish/40/2553_2.png" class="avatar"> Sheepish:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night Ability 2: Burn After Reading (3 uses) - Prepare a message that will be sent at the beginning of the next morning to the Prince.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What does this do if the Prince is dead? I suggest having it go to the king instead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 22:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure, why not. Just needed to toss Royal Blood in there. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 21:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this could also work as a noble rework imo</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 21:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>
<p>Framed People would appear as if they talked during the night, regardless of if they did. Eavesdrop works like this:<br>
The Spy targets player 13. If 13 SPEAKS that night, the Spy will be notified. If 13 doesn’t speak, the Spy will receive a message saying that his target’s room was silent.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I think it’s important that the Mole has Noise Complaint at night so that he can use it with Expose. That’s almost the whole purpose of it. You find out who the Prince jailed and silence him. Swapping their places would make it so you randomly silence someone and then find out who the Prince jailed.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I both agree and disagree with your feedback on Spy’s Noise Complaint. I’ll try to think of something.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>About the whisper reading, I feel like most of the boredom brought by it in the previous versions was because of a lack of purpose. Nobles would read countless whispers in the hopes of finding 3 saying “Hey, I’m MM, you are an evil king, right?”. 99.9% of the time that didn’t happen. So the Noble ended up just copying information to his logs until he was either dead or nominated the new king.<br>
Spy’s whisper reading has a purpose. You have the tools in your kit to actually confirm those you suspect. Step one, you see a sheriff claim. Step two, you find out that the sheriff is speaking at night. Step three, you ask who was jailed and linked by the psychic. Step four, you hang the mastermind. Something along those lines. You don’t have to rely on other people to actually do something like Noble did. Once you get converted, you forget about the whisper reading and focus on hiding whispers. Which is really unseen-friendly.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Thanks for always giving me your feedback! Like really!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 20:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am Assuming that framed people show positive to the spy? How does evesdrop work exactly? Do you check if they were in a night chat or just if they SPOKE in a night chat.</p>
<p>I would also like to point out that the Spy does not need noise complaint as the only time you would use it is if you think they are unseen but in that case you just gave them an excuse to not claim to Prince/Psy. I would also recommend making it a day Ability for the mole that triggers at the start of the night.</p>
<p>Also I would like to add that people tend to dislike whisper reading. The top level players don’t have a problem with it but meny others do. I would suggest replacing it with something else such as journal reading or anynomus whispers.</p>
<p>Other than that just swap Noise Complaint and Expose and possibly give Noise complaint more uses for the mole. Feel free to give the spy something else instead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Spy and The Mole (Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here goes what is probably another failed attempt to suggest a social class.<br>
<em><strong>NuclearBurrito</strong></em> did us all a huge favor when he listed old and possible new abilities for social classes, so it helped me try again since my last attempt failed.</p>
<p><em><strong>The Spy (Blue Dragon Social)</strong></em></p>
<p><strong>Passive: Government Secrecy</strong> - Spy visits are hidden.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1: Private Matters</strong> (2 uses) - Whispers from and to you are hidden from the court.<br>
<strong>Day Ability 2: I Spy with my Little Eyes</strong> (3 uses) - Whispers from and to the target are shown to you.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1: Eavesdrop</strong> (Unlimited uses) - Check if the target talked that night. You will not know who he talked to or what he said. Framed targets appear as having spoken. This ability triggers its answer <em><strong>as soon as</strong></em> the person speaks.<br>
<strong>Night Ability 2: Burn After Reading</strong> (3 uses) - Prepare a message that will be sent at the beginning of the next morning to the target. Your name will not appear in the message. The target will receive something along the lines of “<strong>Spy</strong>: <span class="hashtag">#7</span> claimed Sheriff to the king but spoke last night.” Only the target and the Spy will know about the existence of such a message. Activating this skill without choosing a target aims it at the Prince. The Spy will never be informed the Prince’s number, however.</p>
<p><strong>Win Condition: Unseen/Cult loses</strong></p>
<p><em><strong>The Mole (Unseen Social)</strong></em></p>
<p><strong>Passive: Government Secrecy</strong> - Mole visits are hidden.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1: Private Matters</strong> (2 uses) - Whispers from and to you are hidden from the court.<br>
<strong>Day Ability 2: Expose</strong> (3 uses) - Reveal to the Unseen who the Prince jails tonight.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1: Careless Whispers</strong> (2 uses) - The Unseen may whisper each other without the court knowing about it during the next day.<br>
<strong>Night Ability 2: Noise Complaint</strong> (3 uses) - Silence a player until the next morning. If the target is neither in the dungeon nor linked with a psychic. This player will be silenced at the beginning of the next morning. This alternative effect lasts until the night.</p>
<p><strong>Win Condition: BD loses</strong></p>
<p>So, the Spy and the Mole are another shot at getting a new Social class in. They are entirely focused on communication mechanics. The Spy is a great tool against evil kings, just like the Noble once was. He’s kit revolves around finding people sending strange whispers and check them later that night. It’s important to remember that people speak to the Prince and the Prince to them during nighttime and the same applies to Psychics. This skill could even be triggered by a fool who decided to talk to himself at night to lure a Spy accusation the next morning. So I don’t think it’s OP. Noise Complaint is a direct social attack on Unseen/Cult’s face.<br>
And then he gets converted! The Spy becomes a Mole and the Mole is a huge weapon against the Prince (if he wasn’t killed n1). He is that because he can silence a jailed player (Noise Complaint isn’t prevented on jailed players) and that directly leads to lack of information to the Prince and a possible execute that could get him to lose his ability to Execute altogether. Prince players would have to be extra careful in Spy games because of the chance that he may be converted.<br>
One of the things I like the most about these classes is that they don’t depend on their alliances to win. All that matters to them is that their enemies lose. The NK can win, there could be a solo fool win or two alchemists winning by themselves. You win with them because your enemy lost.<br>
Come on guys, it’s a nice idea! Give me that juicy feedback!!</p>
<p>Funny note: If you think about it, Spies can actually counter Moles if they are lucky enough, which is awesome! Also, two Spies could totally work together without anyone knowing about it.</p>
<p>Side note: As said by 3DT_CheesyKnives, this could also work as a Noble rework if we added Royal Blood to it.</p>
<p><strong>Changelog:</strong><br>
Got rid of the Spy’s second night ability Noise Complaint. Left Mole with it. (Feedback from NuclearBurrito)<br>
Added the Side note. (Feedback from 3DT_CheesyKnives)<br>
Added a new second night ability to the Spy, “Burn After Reading” and fixed “Eavesdrop” so they could work together. (Me)<br>
Fixed Burn After Reading target. (Feedback from NuclearBurrito)<br>
Fixed Burn After Reading target even further. (Me)<br>
Updated Noise Complaint. (Feedback from NuclearBurrito)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 19:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28304-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-spy-and-the-mole-social/28304.rss">The Spy and The Mole (Social)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
