<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Throw a party sucks</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653</link>
    <description>Seasons Greetings fellow liars, spy-ers and Kings. I would like someone to explain to me the purpose behind the Butlers &quot;Throw a Party&quot; ability. Twice it has failed me, and maybe I am not using it right. So first instance...I throw a party, occupying any who visit me.....SLICE &quot;you were attacked last night&quot; ded. Second instance.....Throw a party.....&quot;you converted to unseen last night&quot;   If anyone immune to occupy slides right through butlers party, that basically leaves butler able to defend himself against....Blue Dragons?

I might be missing something here, so feel free to point it out. Also, Devs, your game is brilliant, but im seeing tons of players drop out, afk, or &quot;kill me&quot; day 1 when they get ice wizard or noble. They suck to play. Most games you randomly order or ward someone, only to die by day 3-4, and your only impact on game was 100% random choice, maybe helping evil or NK....very rarely do these classes make it to a point they can confidently use their abilities to help blue dragon. My 2 cents. Now..about how throwing a party sucks....</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 23:50:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Throw a party sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 15:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-14653-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653.rss">Throw a party sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throw a party sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not perfect immunity, nothing is.</p>
<p>In terms of attacks, it’ll save you from anything not occupy immune.  That’s Alchs, Assassins, Cult Leaders, and Reapers.  It doesn’t protect against occupy immune characters, which is Possessors. That’s still nearly all the attackers in the game.</p>
<p>In terms of conversion, the MM is occupy immune, but the Cult Leader is not, at least not normally.</p>
<p>The CL is actually kind of a special case. If he empowers the eradicate, Party Time still blocks it because he becomes occupied and the eradicate never happens.  However, if the ritualist makes the CL occupy immune instead, then he does get around party time, letting the CL convert or kill the Butler.</p>
<p>When converted to Servant, Party Time is a good way to foil investigators, since they’ll become occupied if they try to check you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 23:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-14653-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653.rss">Throw a party sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throw a party sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Possessor is occupy immune</p>
<p>Mastermind is Occupy immune</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 20:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-14653-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653.rss">Throw a party sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throw a party sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Josh_Hauze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seasons Greetings fellow liars, spy-ers and Kings. I would like someone to explain to me the purpose behind the Butlers “Throw a Party” ability. Twice it has failed me, and maybe I am not using it right. So first instance…I throw a party, occupying any who visit me…SLICE “you were attacked last night” ded. Second instance…Throw a party…“you converted to unseen last night”   If anyone immune to occupy slides right through butlers party, that basically leaves butler able to defend himself against…Blue Dragons?</p>
<p>I might be missing something here, so feel free to point it out. Also, Devs, your game is brilliant, but im seeing tons of players drop out, afk, or “kill me” day 1 when they get ice wizard or noble. They suck to play. Most games you randomly order or ward someone, only to die by day 3-4, and your only impact on game was 100% random choice, maybe helping evil or NK…very rarely do these classes make it to a point they can confidently use their abilities to help blue dragon. My 2 cents. Now…about how throwing a party sucks…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 20:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-14653-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throw-a-party-sucks/14653.rss">Throw a party sucks</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
