<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462</link>
    <description>

_Lore_: sent down by the reaper to help the Neutral killer to succeed his or her goal.

_**Faction-Neutral **_
_**Class Type- Investigative**_

**Passive 1** - slowly dying - If the NK dies then he will take your place. He is not allowed to use his abilities for a day after taking your body. Also if the NK attacks you then they will be given a message that youre the reapers apprentice. The apprentice will then know who the NK is.

**Day Ability 1** - soul snatcher - take a players night ability and use it tonight.

* This will always take the unlimited ability unless they don’t have a unlimited ability.
* If you take someone’s night ability that has unlimited then they won’t know you took one, but if there is a limit then you will be alerted that some of your soul has been taken.
* If you take someone’s soul for the third time then you gain their passive if they have one. This will count as your second passive and you can only do this once
* unlimited uses

**Night Ability 1** - full body swap - become a class of your choice(except any Unique classes) you will become that class for the next day and night.

**Notes**:
* if you become a BD member and are checked that night by an invest Ability then you will show up as BD for that night.
* if you become a fool and get killed during the day that morning then you will win still.
* 2 uses

**Win condition:** help the NK win at all cost.

Tell me what you think and if this would fit in with the game



_Lore_: The king did not want to choose sides anymore, he decided that his life is more important than the kingdom. After he made this decision the King became neutral in the battle against BD and Unseen. The Prince noticed that his king wasn’t helping BD anymore. He demanded of his father to step down and let him take the throne. The king grew in anger that day. Later that night the king sent a guard to go kill his son. A brutal slash dead center through the gut made the poor prince fall to his knees. As the Kings guard left, another shadow appeared. After the prince regained his focus, he noticed that all his wounds were cured. A friendly alchemist came to his aid saving his life. The next morning there was talk of another killer. Eventually they put the alchemist on trial. As he tried to defend himself, the king wasn’t having it. He decided that his fate was death and killed him in fear of dying. The prince heard of this and had enough. He fled the kingdom swearing of revenge on the Future. The King had a new son growing up to become the new prince.

**_**Name - Fallen prince **_
_**** Faction - neutral offense**_

**Passive 1** - hidden in the chamber - you hide in the jail the first time someone tries to attack you making you immune to death once.

**Passive 2** - taking what’s mine - when the origanl prince dies then your night ability execute will be active.

**Day Ability 1** - imprison - jail a player at night, (unlimited uses). Can jail the King but can only jail the king up the 3 times.

**Night ability 1** - execution - execute the player in jail. (3 uses) can’t exe king. This ability is only available when the prince is dead

**Night ability 2** - Lost the keys - keep a player in prison having them not participate in the day action. The player will only here people talk but can not see votes, be able to vote, or talk for the day.

**Mechanics** - this class can be jailed interrupting any day abilities. This class cannot jail the prince. You will be given a message that the player is the prince

****Win condition-** make sure there is no King by the end of the game.


_Back story_ - after wrongfully accusing someone, the prince decides to throw you in jail permanently. As the guards drag you off to jail, you give one last glance at the table and see the scorn grinning with delight

****_Name - captive _**
**_** Faction - neutral social_**

**Passive 1 -** cell mate - can hear the prince talk to the prisoner. They will come up as prince and anonymous.

**Passive 2 -** you will know the names of people who visit you

**Day Ability 1** - not going alone - bring someone to jail. It will say you were imprisoned by the prince as normal.
* The player you bring along will be able to hear the prince and that’s it
* the prince can’t hear the other person brought by the captive or doesn’t know that there is even another person there.
* the captive can also hear the player he brings along also.
* this will occupy then and make them immune to death like normal.
* the captive can choose to talk but it will show up as captive when he does.
* (3 uses)

**Day Ability 2 -** trollers box - select two players. The first selected person will send a whisper to the second selected person. You can type the whisper similar to the troll box.(unlimited uses)

**Night ability 1** - the taste of freedom - slowly dig a hole to freedom. This will take 3 days to complete. If anyone visits you then the digging will be interrupted for the night. If the prince jails you then the hole will be patched up and you will have to restart the number of days. You will know how many more days till you escape. (Unlimited uses)

**Night ability 2** - hidden in the shadows - hide in the shadows of the cell preventing anyone from visiting you. Your passives will still take affect. (4 uses)

**Win condition** - escape and win the game or have the prince die and become a “freeman”
Back story - you are finally free to do what you want. You realize that you must pick a side to survive

**_Name - free man _**
**_Faction - neutral._**

**Passive 1** - as soon as you become the freedom man, you must pick a faction(Good,neutral,Evil). The next day you will become a random class of that faction. Cannot become NK. If the cult or unseen is at its max players then you will remain a free man but will have the win condition of the cult and unseen

**Day Ability 1** - free mans motivation - instantly vote someone up for treason - will not say who voted him up.(1 use)

**Day Ability 2** - not again - instantly vote up a player to become king. - will not say who voted him up for king. (1 use)

**Night ability 1** - Potential - inject someone with royal blood. They will now have the royal blood ability(1 use)

**Win condition** - become a different faction and win with that faction.

**Changes**: the captives second day Ability changed - Day Ability 2 - Reverse psychology - you will find out a players type if they visit you. (Offensive,killer,social…etc). This was changed to trollers box.


**Back story** - the chosen one is a cult member that has been chosen to go on and complete the demons job. Gaining more power ever time he learns more knowledge

**_Name - chosen one(thinking of better name) Faction - Neutral investigative_**

**Passive 1** - hard worker - may use both day abilities during one day

**Day Ability 1** - Demons eye - send the demon to go spy on your target, knowing who they visit tonight and the following night - starts at 0 uses but gains more with quick learner ability. Read below.

**Day Ability 2** - Quick learner - pick on a character and try to guess their class
* only one time per day - unlimited uses
* when you guess a players class correctly then you gain a small buff(listed below)
* cannot guess a dead players class or a player that has been on trial
Buffs rewarded: Converted versons give the same;
* Obs or Assassin - gain 4 uses of demon eyes
* Butler or Drunk - occupy immune
* Phys or Alch - Bled/poison immune
* Inquis or Knight - death immune during the night once
* NK - death immunity during the night
* MM or CL - Learn who the Royals are
* Princess or Noble - You will gain more demon eye uses.
* Prince - Learn the identity of the harmful neuts (NK and neutral social)
* Psychic or CW - can hear dead during the night.
* Sheriff or Paladin - Learn who the Unseen/Cult are
* Fool or Scorned - find out all neutrals except NK
* Merc - Learn the classes of anyone contracted to a merc
* Starting Seeker counts as princess, Starting invoker counts as Butler and starting ritualist as Phys
* this suggestion was made by ** @NuclearBurrito**

**Night ability 1** - lots and lots of makeup - flirt with a player of your choice and know One thing about them (healer/protector,killer,magic user,investigator, master at communication, disturber)
Healer/protector- alch,phys,knight,merc,CW investigator - sheriff,princess,paladin,observor Magic user - CW,psychic,sorcerer,inquisitor Killer - any NK,prince,hunter,CL,Assassin,merc Disturber - butler,drunk Magic of communication - fool,psychic,scorn Also all converted classes and cult classes are added also

**Night ability 2** - entity’s vision - select 3 players and it will tell you how many of them players are evil. Example: “2 of the three players are evil” -if there is not enough players then this ability will be disabled -(3 uses)

**Win condition** - survive to see the BD fall

These are suggestions that I made. Tell me what you think and if they would fit in TOL. If anything gets cut out or doesn&#39;t make sense tell me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 15:56:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like helping evils win. But it needs some power to do so. It can only gain information.</p>
<p>How is everybody without the class gonna know the heck what it does without the chart as well? Also, if you need a chart in the first place it is too complex.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 15:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also the list of buffs would be placed on the right side of your screen for you to see at all times</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 15:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not necessarily designed to mess with BD but to help the evil faction win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 15:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s undoubtedly an interesting set of classes, but I still believe the NK shouldn’t have a team of any sort. It makes them more like unseen/cult, and we don’t want two informed minorities.</p>
<p>Also on the chosen one, that’s a pretty random chance ability. The goal is alright, but it is pretty hard to memorize all the buffs. We don’t want this game to become fiendishly complicated. Also, how does a solo investigative bring down the BD? Information helps the BD, and the Chosen One has to private chat to share it with evils. None of its abilities do anything to the BD, so it needs something that messes with their functions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 15:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-the-twins-neutral-killer-neutral-support/24782?u=noble1" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-the-twins-neutral-killer-neutral-support/24782?u=noble1</a></p>
<p>Take a look at this class. It implements helping the NK as much as the reapers apprentice does and both work really well</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 14:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Other then them two classes what do you think about the others?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>he is not a NK as of right now. I’m still working on him and seeing if a NK would work good with him.  I’ll tell you if he has changed</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NightX" data-post="2" data-topic="44462">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nightx/40/3104_2.png" class="avatar"> NightX:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fallen Prince has limited kills, which cannot work. NK needs a steady stream of kills.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But he isn’t NK.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 02:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The first one is a NK sided class. I have already expressed this, but being a loner is the NK experience. It should have no allies. The night ability is okay.</p>
<p>Fallen Prince has limited kills, which cannot work. NK needs a steady stream of kills.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 01:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Lore</em>: sent down by the reaper to help the Neutral killer to succeed his or her goal.</p>
<p><em>**Faction-Neutral **</em><br>
<em><strong>Class Type- Investigative</strong></em></p>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong> - slowly dying - If the NK dies then he will take your place. He is not allowed to use his abilities for a day after taking your body. Also if the NK attacks you then they will be given a message that youre the reapers apprentice. The apprentice will then know who the NK is.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong> - soul snatcher - take a players night ability and use it tonight.</p>
<ul>
<li>This will always take the unlimited ability unless they don’t have a unlimited ability.</li>
<li>If you take someone’s night ability that has unlimited then they won’t know you took one, but if there is a limit then you will be alerted that some of your soul has been taken.</li>
<li>If you take someone’s soul for the third time then you gain their passive if they have one. This will count as your second passive and you can only do this once</li>
<li>unlimited uses</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1</strong> - full body swap - become a class of your choice(except any Unique classes) you will become that class for the next day and night.</p>
<p><strong>Notes</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>if you become a BD member and are checked that night by an invest Ability then you will show up as BD for that night.</li>
<li>if you become a fool and get killed during the day that morning then you will win still.</li>
<li>2 uses</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Win condition:</strong> help the NK win at all cost.</p>
<p>Tell me what you think and if this would fit in with the game</p>
<p><em>Lore</em>: The king did not want to choose sides anymore, he decided that his life is more important than the kingdom. After he made this decision the King became neutral in the battle against BD and Unseen. The Prince noticed that his king wasn’t helping BD anymore. He demanded of his father to step down and let him take the throne. The king grew in anger that day. Later that night the king sent a guard to go kill his son. A brutal slash dead center through the gut made the poor prince fall to his knees. As the Kings guard left, another shadow appeared. After the prince regained his focus, he noticed that all his wounds were cured. A friendly alchemist came to his aid saving his life. The next morning there was talk of another killer. Eventually they put the alchemist on trial. As he tried to defend himself, the king wasn’t having it. He decided that his fate was death and killed him in fear of dying. The prince heard of this and had enough. He fled the kingdom swearing of revenge on the Future. The King had a new son growing up to become the new prince.</p>
<p><strong><em>**Name - Fallen prince **</em><br>
<em></em></strong><em>** Faction - neutral offense**</em></p>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong> - hidden in the chamber - you hide in the jail the first time someone tries to attack you making you immune to death once.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2</strong> - taking what’s mine - when the origanl prince dies then your night ability execute will be active.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong> - imprison - jail a player at night, (unlimited uses). Can jail the King but can only jail the king up the 3 times.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong> - execution - execute the player in jail. (3 uses) can’t exe king. This ability is only available when the prince is dead</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong> - Lost the keys - keep a player in prison having them not participate in the day action. The player will only here people talk but can not see votes, be able to vote, or talk for the day.</p>
<p><strong>Mechanics</strong> - this class can be jailed interrupting any day abilities. This class cannot jail the prince. You will be given a message that the player is the prince</p>
<p>**<strong>Win condition-</strong> make sure there is no King by the end of the game.</p>
<p><em>Back story</em> - after wrongfully accusing someone, the prince decides to throw you in jail permanently. As the guards drag you off to jail, you give one last glance at the table and see the scorn grinning with delight</p>
<p><strong><strong>_Name - captive _</strong><br>
<strong>_</strong> Faction - neutral social_</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive 1 -</strong> cell mate - can hear the prince talk to the prisoner. They will come up as prince and anonymous.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2 -</strong> you will know the names of people who visit you</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong> - not going alone - bring someone to jail. It will say you were imprisoned by the prince as normal.</p>
<ul>
<li>The player you bring along will be able to hear the prince and that’s it</li>
<li>the prince can’t hear the other person brought by the captive or doesn’t know that there is even another person there.</li>
<li>the captive can also hear the player he brings along also.</li>
<li>this will occupy then and make them immune to death like normal.</li>
<li>the captive can choose to talk but it will show up as captive when he does.</li>
<li>(3 uses)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2 -</strong> trollers box - select two players. The first selected person will send a whisper to the second selected person. You can type the whisper similar to the troll box.(unlimited uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong> - the taste of freedom - slowly dig a hole to freedom. This will take 3 days to complete. If anyone visits you then the digging will be interrupted for the night. If the prince jails you then the hole will be patched up and you will have to restart the number of days. You will know how many more days till you escape. (Unlimited uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong> - hidden in the shadows - hide in the shadows of the cell preventing anyone from visiting you. Your passives will still take affect. (4 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - escape and win the game or have the prince die and become a “freeman”<br>
Back story - you are finally free to do what you want. You realize that you must pick a side to survive</p>
<p><strong>_Name - free man _</strong><br>
<strong><em>Faction - neutral.</em></strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong> - as soon as you become the freedom man, you must pick a faction(Good,neutral,Evil). The next day you will become a random class of that faction. Cannot become NK. If the cult or unseen is at its max players then you will remain a free man but will have the win condition of the cult and unseen</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong> - free mans motivation - instantly vote someone up for treason - will not say who voted him up.(1 use)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2</strong> - not again - instantly vote up a player to become king. - will not say who voted him up for king. (1 use)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong> - Potential - inject someone with royal blood. They will now have the royal blood ability(1 use)</p>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - become a different faction and win with that faction.</p>
<p><strong>Changes</strong>: the captives second day Ability changed - Day Ability 2 - Reverse psychology - you will find out a players type if they visit you. (Offensive,killer,social…etc). This was changed to trollers box.</p>
<p><strong>Back story</strong> - the chosen one is a cult member that has been chosen to go on and complete the demons job. Gaining more power ever time he learns more knowledge</p>
<p><strong><em>Name - chosen one(thinking of better name) Faction - Neutral investigative</em></strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong> - hard worker - may use both day abilities during one day</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong> - Demons eye - send the demon to go spy on your target, knowing who they visit tonight and the following night - starts at 0 uses but gains more with quick learner ability. Read below.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2</strong> - Quick learner - pick on a character and try to guess their class</p>
<ul>
<li>only one time per day - unlimited uses</li>
<li>when you guess a players class correctly then you gain a small buff(listed below)</li>
<li>cannot guess a dead players class or a player that has been on trial<br>
Buffs rewarded: Converted versons give the same;</li>
<li>Obs or Assassin - gain 4 uses of demon eyes</li>
<li>Butler or Drunk - occupy immune</li>
<li>Phys or Alch - Bled/poison immune</li>
<li>Inquis or Knight - death immune during the night once</li>
<li>NK - death immunity during the night</li>
<li>MM or CL - Learn who the Royals are</li>
<li>Princess or Noble - You will gain more demon eye uses.</li>
<li>Prince - Learn the identity of the harmful neuts (NK and neutral social)</li>
<li>Psychic or CW - can hear dead during the night.</li>
<li>Sheriff or Paladin - Learn who the Unseen/Cult are</li>
<li>Fool or Scorned - find out all neutrals except NK</li>
<li>Merc - Learn the classes of anyone contracted to a merc</li>
<li>Starting Seeker counts as princess, Starting invoker counts as Butler and starting ritualist as Phys</li>
<li>this suggestion was made by ** <a class="mention" href="/u/nuclearburrito">@NuclearBurrito</a>**</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong> - lots and lots of makeup - flirt with a player of your choice and know One thing about them (healer/protector,killer,magic user,investigator, master at communication, disturber)<br>
Healer/protector- alch,phys,knight,merc,CW investigator - sheriff,princess,paladin,observor Magic user - CW,psychic,sorcerer,inquisitor Killer - any NK,prince,hunter,CL,Assassin,merc Disturber - butler,drunk Magic of communication - fool,psychic,scorn Also all converted classes and cult classes are added also</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong> - entity’s vision - select 3 players and it will tell you how many of them players are evil. Example: “2 of the three players are evil” -if there is not enough players then this ability will be disabled -(3 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - survive to see the BD fall</p>
<p>These are suggestions that I made. Tell me what you think and if they would fit in TOL. If anything gets cut out or doesn’t make sense tell me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 00:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44462-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/multiple-class-suggestion-lost-soul-chosen-one-and-much-more/44462.rss">Multiple {class suggestion} lost soul, chosen one, and much more</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
