<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870</link>
    <description>I despise whispers - but not for the reason you may expect. I understand the appeal; it&#39;s a method your players can use to secretly communicate with each other during the day. Cool. However, whispers inevitably lead to issues, and we&#39;re seeing some of them rear their head in the current King meta. Let&#39;s talk about this.

First of all, why do I dislike whispers so much? I&#39;ve been playing mafia games of all types for years, from the original party game to Forum Mafia to online video games like ToS and ToL. This means I have played many games both with and without whispers, so I have seen the effect they can have on a game. In general, what has led me to dislike whispers doesn&#39;t have anythingto do with using them in-game. They aren&#39;t overpowered on their own (although they can be in combination with other factors, as is the case with the infamous Mayor/Whisper Game meta in ToS), and they are most certainly not useless on their own either. However, it is nigh-on impossible to find a middle ground between these two extremes. Whispers are either too risky to be useful in any but the most extreme circumstances, or the single most effective for the Town/Blue Dragon to gather claims and solve the game. Nerfing them too much just leads them to be abandoned altogether. I have never seen whispers used in a way that doesn&#39;t force the meta towards one of these two outcomes, and I doubt I ever will. Their very nature leaves them in a precarious position, and neither result of their inclusion is good for game design. You don&#39;t want daytime discussion to be replaced with whispers, nor do you want a feature of your game to be basically useless. This is why I dislike whispers.

There are also some other good arguments I&#39;ve heard against whispers, but one that really hits home with me was made by @ofLegends, discussing the impact whispers can have on new players: 
[quote=&quot;ofLegends, post:1, topic:51757&quot;]

Seriously, imagine how it feels to be new right now. You’re sitting there trying to think what’s going on, then it’s like:
*whisper whisper whisper*
“oh, we’re putting up 14 I guess.”
*whisper whisper*
PARDON
“k we’re pardoning I guess…”
*whisper whisper whisper*
“now we’re putting up 5…”
*whisper… whisper whisper*
EXE THIS
“uh ok… executing…”
*more whispering*
WHISPER ME ROLES TOMORROW OR I’M VOTING YOU UP

And let’s not forget the super fun situation of actually BEING the king as a new player. Executed for being “evil”, anyone? I’m convinced I wouldn’t want all this information from people even if I actually knew the game.
[/quote]

Now, as for whether the meta of whispering all of your classes to the King is fun or not, that&#39;s up to individual opinion. Personally, I&#39;d rather have people claim and discuss during the day than everybody claiming to the King, as that leaves more than one player the ability to use social deduction, but I have seen people argue that they enjoy this meta, and more power to them. However, I believe that limiting whispers is better for the overall game health, and therefore is probably the best route to go regardless of whether you like the current meta or not.

The immediate and obvious solution to this all-or-nothing-type situation is to just remove whispers entirely, and I think that would work just fine. I&#39;ve played plenty of games where there have been no whispers, and I have never walked away from these games feeling that they would have been better with them. This is an entirely valid solution, and one I would fully support.

However, I have my doubts that the developers would ever take this route (Town of Salem sure hasn&#39;t, after all). So, I look to one of my suggestions for ToS:
![image|690x241](upload://dbX8DerVw5luYlxJuSY9Qs8pmTe.jpeg)
I feel that the same concept would work well here. Let Psychic handle secure private communication, let another Social class be able to send whispers, and either let the same Social class or maybe a different one read whispers. All non-BD classes will be able to whisper, and whispers will not be made public. This actually has far fewer problems than it may initially seem. The BD class that can send whispers isn&#39;t instantly confirmable, as all evils can send them just as easily; a BD-sided whisper-reader is also unconfirmable, because no other BD can send whispers to test them. This makes whispering a risky proposition, but also allows evils to contact each other if necessary (Unseen can reach out to an NK), while punishing bad reads (whispering a BD class you thought was evil may spell your doom). In addition, you could remove the message for a Mercenary guarding a player, and let them claim it in whispers instead.

Now, I do fully admit that this suggestion was built for a different game, and may not work as well here. For example, how does the King interact with this? Maybe all Kings can send whispers, or maybe even read them. There are many posdibilities, and I sure as heck didn&#39;t think them all through yet. So, please let me know what you think about whispers, and whether a system like the one I suggested ToS implement would be a good idea, or whether you&#39;d just remove whispers full-stop.

Thanks, and have a wonderful day. :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 16:17:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I might be in the minority here but I really wouldn’t like whispers to be eliminated or changed drastically. I wouldn’t want to lose the ability to whisper to king either. Although whisper meta is a bit annoying, I have to admit I have more fun with this current meta than with the “allies” meta.</p>
<p>If whisper meta needs to be fixed I suggest a less drastic change, such as buffing noble/aristocrat or adding a whisper reading mechanic to evil classes like NK or MM like it has been proposed by others. Or just change the starting King’s chance, I mean neutral kings usually side with BD so it basically is an 80% chance of good king right now, and they already added the fool mechanic if you hang a BD king so I don’t think the rates should be that high in favor of BD.</p>
<p>One last suggestion (a bit more drastic) would be to make it so non-unique classes have a limit of 3 instead of 2, so if you claim something and there are already 2 other claims you are not instantly hanged.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/129</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 16:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-129</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="118" data-topic="51870">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Excluding NK anyway. They are just fucked.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The Mastermind also has a bit of trouble, which is probably the most significant problem.  (The starting Assassin and CL, too, but they’re more expendable.)</p>
<p>I feel that the solution to this is to create more claimspace for them, though.  The fact is that between the Prince, the Psychic, and the King, ToL is a very claim-intensive game and was always going to be, by design.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/128</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 03:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-128</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RustyRoo" data-post="123" data-topic="51870" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/rustyroo/40/2660_2.png" class="avatar"> RustyRoo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The intention is precisely the issue.  The intention is to circumvent the anonymous whisper system.  It would be a pointless change if this is not recognised at the outset.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The problem is, they aren’t going to punish people for using blatent tools that are given. IE public chat. If you make it against the rules to reffrence anything you’ve said via an annonymous means publicly. you’ll have 3/4ths of the community banned in a week.</p>
<p>If you try to balance things by something they can beat, with the very obvious tools that they are already given, you have to use a different method, not try to force players into submission by trying to moderate it.</p>
<p>Currently there are to my knowledge only 3 rules of public chat that I know of, no spamming, no hate speach, and no directly trying to sabatoge your own or your teams objective, and that last one alone is a rediculous point of contention and arguementation among players and dev’s of what is and isn’t over that line, especially as long as fool exists.</p>
<p>A rule trying to regulate de-anonamizing anonomized messages, will tie up the moderators and players time arguing about… non-stop indefinitely. Most of us in this thread can’t see how you could define a rule for it, in which we don’t also count princes referencing jail speak, psychics identifying themselves with telepathy etc… those are all explicitly defined as anonymous chats, which players de-annonomize with the methods the game provides.</p>
<p>whether or not you can argue a difference, is irrelevant… the fact is that such a difference will have to be argued, over and over again, every game, every new batch of players. ban appeals, suspension appeals etc…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/127</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 03:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-127</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RustyRoo" data-post="125" data-topic="51870">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/rustyroo/40/2660_2.png" class="avatar"> RustyRoo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s not what I said, and you know it.  It’s information they shouldn’t have access to within the scope, world, environment, ruleset, and wishes of the dev team.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The words stated in the whisper and the words stated in the public chat are by definition known to you and should be known to you. The connection between them is gotten through induction such as with the drunk example.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/126</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 03:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-126</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RustyRoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="114" data-topic="51870" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Other examples of things that are meta gaming by your logic include:</p>
<p>Cross referencing logs.</p>
<p>Figuring out that the drunk is converted because he HHed a sheriff</p>
<p>Claiming. Like at all.</p>
<p>Being a Psychic</p>
<p>Basically the entire game outside of the night phase.</p>
<p>This is because under your reasoning it is meta gaming to tell someone something they don’t already know. ESPECIALLY if they back it up with evidence (AKA: Posting your logs. Which definitely contains Information that the other players don’t have and aren’t supposed to have).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>… and again you’re ignoring intention.</p>
<p>Other issues:</p>
<ul>
<li>logs are accessible, so you’re wrong about that</li>
<li>deducing the converted drunk is a <strong>deduction</strong> and within the environment set by the game, so you’re wrong there.  The character <strong>does</strong> have the ability to make that deduction, and the <strong>intent</strong> is within the scope and ruleset laid out for the game.</li>
<li>claiming is you personally passing on information to another player, so that’s not meta.  There’s also no reason why they <strong>have</strong> to believe your claim, and reasons why they shouldn’t.</li>
<li>being a psychic is attaining information legitimately within the world according to the behaviour of that world.  You are wrong there too.</li>
<li>the entire game out of the night phase.  That’s so silly I’m not even going to go there.  I think you’re leg-pulling with that one.</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="114" data-topic="51870">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is because under your reasoning it is meta gaming to tell someone something they don’t already know.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Strawman.  That’s not what I said, and you know it.  It’s information <strong>they shouldn’t have access to</strong> within the scope, world, environment, ruleset, and wishes of the dev team.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/125</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 02:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-125</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Precisely</p>
<p>It is pointless</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/124</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 02:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-124</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RustyRoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The intention is precisely the issue.  The intention is to circumvent the anonymous whisper system.  It would be a pointless change if this is not recognised at the outset.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/123</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 02:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-123</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Vandalay" data-post="121" data-topic="51870">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/vandalay/40/1393_2.png" class="avatar"> Vandalay:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I find it hard to imagine the current game, being competitive when we do get newish players out of the mix.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree 100%</p>
<p>No way evil stands a chance as-is without noobs in the lobby</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/122</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-122</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shrimpy" data-post="119" data-topic="51870">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shrimpy/40/15828_2.png" class="avatar"> Shrimpy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So having a bad claim in this game is not nearly as bad (and not comparable to having a bad claim in ToS) unless you are Reaper or Sorcerer</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>or MM… yes conversion is a game changer, but on the whole, the same principles apply. Good guys identifying the bad guys is the way to get ahead. yeah catching the assasain isn’t the same crippling long term effect as catching the mafioso, but that only pushes it further into the BD has extra motives to use whatever trick they can to insta identify the baddies.</p>
<p>ToL is kind of a side step with town of salem’s primary problems. They eliminated town of salem’s defined role list via basically off the bat having 7 Random towns.</p>
<p>ToL is a step easier to PoE, due to non unique classes having a cap of 2</p>
<p>Both games fall into the huge weakness of the majority of classes being more or less confirmable (or only mimicable by their exact evil counterpart).</p>
<p>Now cult games I don’t think fall into this problem as badly… Only 1 of up to 4 cult members have no ability to mimic a BD counterpart. Unseen on the other hand, 2/3rds of them have that problem, and as soon as you catch one of them… the untestable one becomes testable. Thus claims out and paying attention is almost an autowin.</p>
<p>I don’t know current winrates, but I would be willing to wager, if we get a vets or ranked mode… we are going to run into a very serious blatent issue, where we’ll see the low tiered game… with a 50%ish winrate, and the high tiered game with a 90% BD winrate.</p>
<p>Of course maybe the solution to that is what they are already dabbling with, IE different rules/skills for different skill levels of players, but I find it hard to imagine the current game, being competitive when we do get newish players out of the mix.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/121</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 23:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-121</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Encryption at its finest</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/120</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 21:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-120</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There are two things that seem to be causing confusion in this thread.</p>
<p>First, meta gaming is doing something that only makes sense if this is a game and not real life.  Using a code in jail to counter Possessor is not meta gaming, since you could do the same thing if the game were actually real life.  Concluding that the person who just died was not a poss jump because he immediately left the game, on the other hand, IS meta gaming.  Because people can’t “leave the game” in real life after they die.</p>
<p>Second, the comparisons with Town of Salem are very, very bad because there is no conversion in that game (ignoring Vampires).  So having a bad claim in this game is not nearly as bad (and not comparable to having a bad claim in ToS) unless you are Reaper or Sorcerer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/119</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-119</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t thing it should be nearly as big of a problem in ToL.</p>
<p>If everyone has everyone’s claims in ToL then Scum has a much better chance compared to in ToS.</p>
<p>Excluding NK anyway. They are just fucked.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/118</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-118</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly that whole whisper game and VFR thing was so blatantly obvious</p>
<p>I used to get all sorts of abuse from people for suggesting that stopping Mayor from whispering would just move the issue rather than fix it</p>
<p>Sure enough, I was right</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/117</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-117</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the best way to fix the whisper meta would be to rework noble so it’s focused around whispers, and change the starting king so it’s 50% good and 50% evil with no starting neutral king</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/116</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-116</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only game that considers things like posting logs as Meta game is camp cadaver (The game does not consider code words meta gaming however so long as the codes are made in game.) And that game does not have a rule against meta gaming anyways so it doesn’t matter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/115</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-115</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Other examples of things that are meta gaming by your logic include:</p>
<p>Cross referencing logs.</p>
<p>Figuring out that the drunk is converted because he HHed a sheriff</p>
<p>Claiming. Like at all.</p>
<p>Being a Psychic</p>
<p>Basically the entire game outside of the night phase.</p>
<p>This is because under your reasoning it is meta gaming to tell someone something they don’t already know. ESPECIALLY if they back it up with evidence (AKA: Posting your logs. Which definitely contains Information that the other players don’t have and aren’t supposed to have).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/114</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-114</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s all using in game Information which you are expected to have.</p>
<p>What a player said in the public chat is something that should be known to you. What was said to you in a whisper should be known to you. The fact that what was said in the public chat reveals who whispered you is something you figured you on your own using Information you are supposed to have and gotten using the intended methods.</p>
<p>No step in this prossess is rule breaking nor is the intention or the method of putting it together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/113</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-113</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RustyRoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is, if it gives the character information they <strong>should not</strong> have access to, and using a code-word in this instance is to circumvent an anonymous whisper system.  That’s the definition given for a rule-breaking meta strategy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/112</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-112</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="PokemonKidRyan" data-post="110" data-topic="51870">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/pokemonkidryan/40/17866_2.png" class="avatar"> PokemonKidRyan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is impossible to please everyone, but many are happy to be able to have whispers.</p>
<p>As it pleases well over the majority, it is only logical sense to keep them</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, here’s where it comes into debate… is the whisper game meta pleasing the majority, or is it pleasing a vocal minority in a way that makes the majority afraid not to participate due to fears of gamethrowing and getting killed.</p>
<p>Whether anyone likes it or not… a strategy with the highest chance of winning will be used. In town of salem they went through more or less this same thing in mayor games. Of which people went along with it for months.Then you started seeing “I hate mayor games” topics getting more and more common in the forums and then it hit a critical breaking point where a large enough portion of the community started gamethrowing in protest (Town roles that could kill mayor, did, and put <span class="hashtag">#nomayorgames2016</span> on the kill notes to make sure everyone could tell that they were knowingly and intentionally throwing in protest).</p>
<p>I’m not supporting their actions, and I’ll be quick to point out, after their solution, <em>mayor can no longer whisper after revealing</em>. The same segment of the community that loved mayor games (it was a known fact that mayor games had ~80% winrate), replaced it with Vote for Roles. IE put everyone up on the stand one at a time, get a claim etc…</p>
<p>Which more or less accomplished an even higher town winrate than mayor games. After that they attempted to solve that problem via reducing the amount of trials per day. Which didn’t really help much, people volunteered their claims and they could focus the VFR on just the tiny amount that didn’t.</p>
<p>After that they actually made some headway by doing a pretty major shakeup to the role list, which I do believe helped quite a bit.</p>
<p>That’s around where I burned out on the game though and came here, so I can’t say much more on the saga past that. But I will say, the majority of players seemed happier in the games when whispers/vfr weren’t the instant strategy. Not to mention the winrates weren’t in the 80-90% town sided.</p>
<p>This game is running through the same problems. let me give some of my opinions of what I think are the shortcomings, our limited class list issue.</p>
<p>While ToL does by default do almost exactly what ToS had to do (add more random towns, less hard coded classes). we also have much more rigid rules. IE 2 of each non-uniques, and quite a few unique classes. That limit does hit the point where in short a single knight dying puts huge jeopardy in all existing knight claims. as 1. if there is a real knight, he knows to insta CS any other knight claims etc…</p>
<p>Then of course we come to the classes themselves if I recall there’s about 3 very fake claimable BD classes, 3 semi-claimable but could be dangerous as they do have means to self confirm, and 6 you’d be an idiot to claim if you aren’t it, or the exact converted form of it classes.</p>
<p>So right off the bat we’ve got a shortage of claimspace… a huge danger if your claim is a duplicate of a living class, or shared with a different evil, etc… Personally I’d say the biggest thing we need, is more classes, and a good portion of them being fakable. Admitted that’s where it’s going to be toughest… as a good 90% of suggested classes, fall into the very confirmable category, as people want classes that are fun and exciting… and that rarely ever lines up with “no one can really be sure if you did your job”</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/111</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 14:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-111</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve only just seen this, but I have a bit to say.<br>
This game has been around for the best part of a year now in total with the kickstarter and all.<br>
So far, there have been many improvements to this game made, as patches have been pushed out in order to allow us to have a better experience.<br>
I am more than thankful for what we have already.</p>
<p>Now, I do also have to say that I find whispers to be important.<br>
There is the whole ‘Whisper King’ Meta and while it’s annoying, it is a valid strategy.<br>
We do have many ways to prove ourselves and claiming results to King does work.</p>
<p>The main concern with whispering King is that the King may not be your faction.<br>
As it was changed to 60% BD and 20/20 Neut/Evil before.<br>
This means that even if you claim, you may be harming your faction.<br>
Therefore it is an individual basis which is needed to be considered here.<br>
We have thousands of players here who have thousands of different tactics.<br>
Every player, every playstyle, has it’s own unique twist.</p>
<p>So to me, the question isn’t about removing whispers. As this feature is good anyway.<br>
The question is the <strong>value</strong> of whispers in the game which I believe is subjective.<br>
Therefore we cannot say that whispers are always good or always bad.<br>
It is one of many tactics which can be used and is even more useful when you have someone who can be confirmed to be on your side, without <strong>everyone</strong> having to know.</p>
<p>TL;DR:<br>
The constant improvements and patches show that the devs (and staff) have best interests.<br>
Whispers are subjective and have varying levels of importance for all players.<br>
If you don’t like whispers and don’t want to use them, then that’s your choice.<br>
However, it cannot lower the value of the game overall, when this game is about one thing…</p>
<h3>Community</h3>
<p>It is impossible to please everyone, but many are happy to be able to have whispers.<br>
As it pleases well over the majority, it is only logical sense to keep them</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/110</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-110</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UncannyLuck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s wrong in my favor though - ignoring the actions of the other players strictly favors the Unseen in the scenario I just laid out. With heals, Knight guards and ability confirmations you are far, far more likely to get a BD King.</p>
<p>Losing 2 guards and 2 OEs is a fair trade. People already poison the King day 2 with an 80% chance he’s not evil.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/109</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-109</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s nothing rule-breaking about whispering somebody a code word and then saying it out loud lmao</p>
<p>We’re just back to square one</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/108</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 03:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-108</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RustyRoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Vandalay" data-post="101" data-topic="51870">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/vandalay/40/1393_2.png" class="avatar"> Vandalay:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s a meta game, but it isn’t a rule break. They aren’t going to outlaw volunterally saying something out loud. No different than catching the just jumped possesor if you are jailor by asking him what you said in jail. Or a psychic telepathically saying “I’m number 13 stop accusing me”, etc…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes it is, and I’ll explain why there’s a difference between this, possessor, and psychic.</p>
<p>With psychic, they have the option to communicate with the room at large if they prefer to not out themselves, or are confirming they are still psychic.  It is entirely possible that a psychic, within the game environment, could share the information of who they are if they chose to.</p>
<p>With possessor, their role doesn’t allow them access to info on what the player whispered before they were possessed, so it is entirely within the game environment that they not be able to reply to the prince when questioned.</p>
<p>With the whisper meta proposed by orange for anonymous whisper system, that is entirely designed to circumvent the anonymous part and to allow players access to information that they should not have access to.</p>
<p>That makes it a rule-breaking meta by definition.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/107</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 03:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-107</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RustyRoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah, I see.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/106</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-106</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about whispers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And remember. This is also being weighed against: Having that class that would step up, Having order exe, Having an additional 6 guards, Lynching D2 and Possablely lynching D3 too. At that point an additional 4-8% chance of BD king with EKing taking the rest of that and leaving to probability of Neut king is not worth it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870/105</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 03:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51870-105</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-whispers/51870.rss">Let&#39;s talk about whispers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
