<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975</link>
    <description>So, here&#39;s the rundown... we have a Royal Adviser neutral class. Their win condition is simple: See the starting king survive the game, or become king themselves. 

The adviser has a unique passive that enables them to share a room with the king every night. This is much like the Unseen/Cult in that you can openly speak with the king at night without fear of anyone else listening in, enabling the king to communicate and coordinate with their adviser openly. The adviser&#39;s powers would primarily be built around helping their king (I&#39;ve not settled on them yet and am welcome to suggestions here) or helping themselves become king (i.e. a one time use power that gives them a few free votes toward becoming the next king if the king dies within the following day/night, etc.)

The king should always have a shred of doubt as to whether their adviser is going to remain loyal and true and stand by their side until the game ends... or turn on them and seek to take the throne themselves. Likewise, the adviser needs to weigh their odds of winning in a vote for king over the odds of them winning through standing by their king. In a perfect world, this will create an environment in which the adviser can win more easily through seeing their starter king survive, but might at times decide that they have greater odds of success if they turn on their king and try to become king themselves.

Some additional thoughts:
-The adviser should probably NOT have royal blood, to make immediately turning on their king and trying to win just by becoming king less viable. They typically will want to see their king survive, not to betray them. Betrayal should be, for the adviser, a more difficult route to victory than the king&#39;s survival (yet at the same time - a more immediate one)
-One potential idea would be to give the adviser night immunity to death (they have their own guards too, after all!), but allow the adviser to use an ability to send their guards off to someone else at the cost of their immunity for that night. This would let them further stretch a king&#39;s ability to defend critical players within a game - at the risk of enabling themselves to be killed for doing so.
-By making the adviser neutral, they don&#39;t need to be concerned with their king&#39;s faction. Whether good or neutral or evil - they win if their king survives.

Let me know what you think, and feel free to suggest any ideas around this class if you like it. This idea was a conglomeration of several ideas from the Discord, so sorry if I missed any key points!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 18:07:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like this idea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 18:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-16975-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975.rss">The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Man I didn’t even see this until now. Totally was not stealing anybody idea with my Advisor suggestion haha</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 17:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-16975-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975.rss">The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>makes king’s faction OP</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-16975-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975.rss">The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the idea tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-16975-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975.rss">The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShaneNineOne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, here’s the rundown… we have a Royal Adviser neutral class. Their win condition is simple: See the starting king survive the game, or become king themselves.</p>
<p>The adviser has a unique passive that enables them to share a room with the king every night. This is much like the Unseen/Cult in that you can openly speak with the king at night without fear of anyone else listening in, enabling the king to communicate and coordinate with their adviser openly. The adviser’s powers would primarily be built around helping their king (I’ve not settled on them yet and am welcome to suggestions here) or helping themselves become king (i.e. a one time use power that gives them a few free votes toward becoming the next king if the king dies within the following day/night, etc.)</p>
<p>The king should always have a shred of doubt as to whether their adviser is going to remain loyal and true and stand by their side until the game ends… or turn on them and seek to take the throne themselves. Likewise, the adviser needs to weigh their odds of winning in a vote for king over the odds of them winning through standing by their king. In a perfect world, this will create an environment in which the adviser can win more easily through seeing their starter king survive, but might at times decide that they have greater odds of success if they turn on their king and try to become king themselves.</p>
<p>Some additional thoughts:<br>
-The adviser should probably NOT have royal blood, to make immediately turning on their king and trying to win just by becoming king less viable. They typically will want to see their king survive, not to betray them. Betrayal should be, for the adviser, a more difficult route to victory than the king’s survival (yet at the same time - a more immediate one)<br>
-One potential idea would be to give the adviser night immunity to death (they have their own guards too, after all!), but allow the adviser to use an ability to send their guards off to someone else at the cost of their immunity for that night. This would let them further stretch a king’s ability to defend critical players within a game - at the risk of enabling themselves to be killed for doing so.<br>
-By making the adviser neutral, they don’t need to be concerned with their king’s faction. Whether good or neutral or evil - they win if their king survives.</p>
<p>Let me know what you think, and feel free to suggest any ideas around this class if you like it. This idea was a conglomeration of several ideas from the Discord, so sorry if I missed any key points!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 23:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-16975-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-royal-adviser-neutral-class/16975.rss">The Royal Adviser Neutral Class</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
