<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687</link>
    <description>There has been meny people trying to say that you can (or could anyway) claim classes that are confirmable. For example Possessor claiming Noble and assassin claiming Obs. 

First some definitions:

A class is confirmable if they have a confirmable ability that the class they are being compared to doesn&#39;t have. (Example: Drunk can confirm not assassin. He cannot confirm not Alcoholic)

An ability can be confirmed if you can check to see if the ability really happened. 

For some ability&#39;s this is as simple as the game telling specific people that the ability&#39;s effect happened. For example: Serve wine tells the target, Concentrated wine tells all visitors, Telepathy tells the whole game. The more people it tells the more confirmable it is. 

Some are less simple: Such as Flirt and Follow which don&#39;t give a message but are arguably confirmable. 

These can be confirmed based on probability. How likely is it that they guessed their results? With princess it&#39;s 1/3 at least and it&#39;s super easy to get better odds. This is why princess is a viable fake claim. Next is Follow which is extremely hard to guess and even getting someone&#39;s logs doesn&#39;t cover you for a day. This is why observer is not a viable fake claim. However, unlike with butler or noble it is possible to get the results correctly various means. For example the possessor getting everyone&#39;s whispers to the prince and thus knowing who everyone visited. 

There are 4 types of confirmability possible. From most to least confirmable:

1: Instant - Anything that can confirm you during the day. These are Noble Political Pressure/Noble Twins/Maid spy, Mystic Telepathy/Private matters, Merc&#39;s Connections and King&#39;s finger. Anyone with one of these is impossible to fake claim for any reasonable amount of time.

2: Retroactive - Any unlimited night ability that is consistantly confirmable is this. These are Prince Jail, Butler serve wine, Drunk debauchery, Mystic Link, Obs follow, Noble Gossip. You can only keep up one of these claims for 1 night unless you have a reason for the ability failing. You cannot maintain one of these claims but you can use them for a D2 accusation or similar play. Yes even Prince.

3: Proactive - Any limited night ability that is consistently confirmable is this. These are Drunk HH, CW tornado, Butler Party, Hunter wolf. It is possible to keep a fake claim like this up. The problem is when someone asks you to do the ability. However this also leaves you with a night to: Be sacrificed, Possess someone, Use an ability, or waste time somehow. This should be a possible claim so long as you have a plan for when you are asked to wolf. In other words don&#39;t claim it as sorcerer, reaper or mastermind.

4: Situational - Any night ability that can only be inconsistently confirmable. These are Phys heal, Alchemist heal, Knight CS/Defend, CW barrier, Merc stand guard, All royal blood. These ability&#39;s can be fake claimed most of the time and cannot be actively tested. However they do give distinctive results in specific situations such as if the phys target is attacked. These do not make a class a bad fake claim.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:29:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Prince seems to be in tier 1 but that is for reasons that have nothing to do with this post. Imprison is teir 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Prince may be in theory tier 2, but in practice it is tier 1</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fancy Play Syndrome stops for nobody</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Unless they were jailing you anway</p>
<p>Rip</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Claim Prince in the last 10 seconds of day, then jump as Possessor. Prince won’t have time to jail you but will almost certainly out themselves to CC you, even if you jumped.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="1" data-topic="59687">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>conformable</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2aa2dbe8d084dabe2b0a291ae4f7cefac286ddcb.png" alt="Untitled%20drawing%20(1)" data-base62-sha1="65aYBU4uiNV8d50JpQikyxcoKYH" width="666" height="500"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually claiming prince isn’t bad…</p>
<p>Wastes time for the real prince to out themselves</p>
<p>Or for them to exe you at night</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey I got a great idea!</p>
<p>Let me claim prince.</p>
<p>Hey guys I’m prince!</p>
<p>Prince:Wut you talking about</p>
<p>Me:I’m prince</p>
<p>Prince:nu u</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiers of confirmability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There has been meny people trying to say that you can (or could anyway) claim classes that are confirmable. For example Possessor claiming Noble and assassin claiming Obs.</p>
<p>First some definitions:</p>
<p>A class is confirmable if they have a confirmable ability that the class they are being compared to doesn’t have. (Example: Drunk can confirm not assassin. He cannot confirm not Alcoholic)</p>
<p>An ability can be confirmed if you can check to see if the ability really happened.</p>
<p>For some ability’s this is as simple as the game telling specific people that the ability’s effect happened. For example: Serve wine tells the target, Concentrated wine tells all visitors, Telepathy tells the whole game. The more people it tells the more confirmable it is.</p>
<p>Some are less simple: Such as Flirt and Follow which don’t give a message but are arguably confirmable.</p>
<p>These can be confirmed based on probability. How likely is it that they guessed their results? With princess it’s 1/3 at least and it’s super easy to get better odds. This is why princess is a viable fake claim. Next is Follow which is extremely hard to guess and even getting someone’s logs doesn’t cover you for a day. This is why observer is not a viable fake claim. However, unlike with butler or noble it is possible to get the results correctly various means. For example the possessor getting everyone’s whispers to the prince and thus knowing who everyone visited.</p>
<p>There are 4 types of confirmability possible. From most to least confirmable:</p>
<p>1: Instant - Anything that can confirm you during the day. These are Noble Political Pressure/Noble Twins/Maid spy, Mystic Telepathy/Private matters, Merc’s Connections and King’s finger. Anyone with one of these is impossible to fake claim for any reasonable amount of time.</p>
<p>2: Retroactive - Any unlimited night ability that is consistantly confirmable is this. These are Prince Jail, Butler serve wine, Drunk debauchery, Mystic Link, Obs follow, Noble Gossip. You can only keep up one of these claims for 1 night unless you have a reason for the ability failing. You cannot maintain one of these claims but you can use them for a D2 accusation or similar play. Yes even Prince.</p>
<p>3: Proactive - Any limited night ability that is consistently confirmable is this. These are Drunk HH, CW tornado, Butler Party, Hunter wolf. It is possible to keep a fake claim like this up. The problem is when someone asks you to do the ability. However this also leaves you with a night to: Be sacrificed, Possess someone, Use an ability, or waste time somehow. This should be a possible claim so long as you have a plan for when you are asked to wolf. In other words don’t claim it as sorcerer, reaper or mastermind.</p>
<p>4: Situational - Any night ability that can only be inconsistently confirmable. These are Phys heal, Alchemist heal, Knight CS/Defend, CW barrier, Merc stand guard, All royal blood. These ability’s can be fake claimed most of the time and cannot be actively tested. However they do give distinctive results in specific situations such as if the phys target is attacked. These do not make a class a bad fake claim.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59687-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tiers-of-confirmability/59687.rss">Tiers of confirmability</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
