<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012</link>
    <description># There will be a short period of some public testing on Steam, before the patch goes live.

## QoL:
* The buttons to open your journal, deathnote, and notes now toggle it on/off.
* The whisper and hearsay input boxes now check to make sure the message was sent before clearing the input.
* Players now have to wait 1 seconds before chaning their votes.
* There is now a confirmation box when you buy an item.
* Start early button has poofed from public games.

## General:
* Added a few new rooms for the death recap.
* Added a tutorial match for new players.
* The old tutorial is still there, but has been simplified.
* A button has been added to the journal to load a default layout.
* All healers healing a bleeding/poisoned player will now see that the player was bleeding/poisoned.
* Two new classes added. The Inquisitor and the Sorcerer.
* Royal blood now transfers when changing classes in all cases.
* New armor called Demonic Chestguard.
* New weapon called Cursed Longsword.
* Improved lobby framework.
* Improved and fixed some bugs with friends list.
* If no one could add you as a friend or be added: This is now fixed! Ask them to send you another friend invite.
* Nicknames can only be changed once/day

## Alcoholic:
* Removed Hangover.
* Added Happy Hour. 2 uses.

## Court Wizard:
* Recharge Removed.
* Added new night ability Tornado. Swap two players&#39; positions, causing all players targeting one them to target the other. Infinite uses.
* Ice ward has been changed to a self target ability. Now has 2 uses.

## Cult Leader:
* Eradicate is now a two target ability.
* Now starts with 2 uses of Eradicate.
* Sacrifice grants 2 uses of Eradicate.

## Death Knight:
* Changed Undead passive completely. Death Knight appears dead to all other players. They cannot talk to living players or vote. They will not appear in the court during the day.

## Drunk &amp; Alcoholic:
* Old Debauchery has returned. It will force players to target you instead of their original target. You will be immune to all conversion and attacks you redirect.

## Duchess:
* Slap removed.

## Inquisitor:
* New Neutral Investigative class. Will always spawn with the Sorcerer.
* To win the Inquisitor must live to see the Sorcerer die.
* Passive Holy Blessing - Immune to death at night.
* Passive Nobody Expects the Spanish Inquisition - Visits are hidden from others at night.
* Night Ability Find Magic - Check if a player is a magic user. Court Wizard, Paladin, Psychic, Illusionist, Sage, Sorcerer, and the Cult are magic users.
* Night Ability Ruthless Efficiency - Attack a player. If they are a magic user, you will kill them. Bypasses night immunity. 3 uses.

## King:
* Allies changed. All starting kings will now discover if a player has the Royal Blood passive.

## Noble &amp; Aristocrat:
* New passive Hearsay - At night a random player will be chosen and they can send anonymous messages to you.
* Royal Decree and Order have both been limited to 2 uses.

## Physician:
* Can no longer target disconnected or afk players with Reanimate.

## Ritualist:
* Removed Strength of Corax.
* Added a version of Tornado called Teleportation. 3 uses.
* Changed Brotherhood. Now makes all Cult members appear as Blue Dragon. 1 use.

## Sage:
* Removed Shock.
* Added Tornado.
* Can now target self with Wall of Fire.
* Changed type to Support.

## Sorcerer:
* New Neutral Killer class. Always spawns with Inquisitor. Counts towards the single Neutral Killer limit.
* Must live to see the Blue Dragon defeated. This means they win with the Unseen and Cult.
* Passive Mage Armor - Immune to death and occupation at night.
* Day Ability Magic Dust - Make a player appear as a magic user to the Inquisitor tonight. 3 uses.
* Night Ability Magic Missile - Fire a magic missile at a player, killing them.
* Night Ability Circle of Death - Everyone visiting target player will die. Not usable until Night 5. 3 uses.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 08:35:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Official Announcements</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 15:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After playing a bunch of games I’m not a fan of the CW ability, just adds way too much RNG on top of a game that already has a lot of RNG in it.</p>
<p>I think it makes sense for Sage/Ritualist - but not for CW.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 08:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Moleland" data-post="32" data-topic="15012">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/moleland/40/5104_2.png" class="avatar"> Moleland:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>‘I most kill king</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>itches head</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 21:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Finitethrills]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, honestly, guarding is also pretty boring.  Cold steel is also fun, but with the way this sounds, I don’t think it’s really think I’ll find it any more engaging than being dead.  Like I said, though, I’m reserving judgement until I actually get to play it.  My gut feeling is that it was a little too heavy handed an adjustment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 19:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also stops the NK strat being ‘I most kill king or Iose’</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 15:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>King’s change in ability is better.</p>
<p>Lots of Kings find “Not Ally” and straight up kill them regardless if they’re an Alchemist or whatever.</p>
<p>That and people are too reliant on the King’s ability to find factions/allies.</p>
<p>Kings die from not presenting info too. Now it’s a matter of King finding Royal Blood. Is someone claiming Princess? Are they Royal Blood?</p>
<p>A good strategy as King is to save your Royal Blood check for when someone like a Mastermind/CL is claiming Princess or an Assassin is claiming Drunk.</p>
<p>Trust me, this change is far better for the King and the friendly Neuts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How do you come and join the Public Test Realm?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 15:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Steelwhale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Look, lots of cool stuff have been changed, cool!</p>
<p>but i’m just happy that old debauch is back because people still dont know how it works</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 07:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[slappy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ellie" data-post="1" data-topic="15012">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ellie/40/8749_2.png" class="avatar"> Ellie:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Alcoholic:</p>
<p>Removed Hangover.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/ok_hand.png?v=9" title=":ok_hand:" class="emoji" alt=":ok_hand:"> in a perfect world</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 07:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That formatting.  O.o</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 04:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandy_Claws]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve played a lot of games so ima add my small peice to these changes. Overall which are good.<br>
General changes: awesome the journal default will be fun to see and the whole 1st day will not be spent making it up now and missing sherrif scouts and prince jails. It’ll also help new players get a feel of what kind if logs they need to keep and how impactful they are to the game.  The knowing if a person was poisoned is HUGE because getting DNR on a heal then outing day 3 “he did not need a heal” only to find out an all healed him then you die n3 is a big deal. New players again will be given relevant info they can use to confirm claims and not out themselves unnecessarily.<br>
Drunk/Alcaholic - did not enjoy the new changes because they either threw the game blocking crucial healers or made the game so easy as to never have anyone die. Will be interesting to see now.<br>
Court Wizard - I can’t wait to play this class. Occupy immune for 3 nights and get to swap people around? SIGN ME UP. Only downside I can see is just like the old CW is n1 n2 messing up checks for BD. It will be interesting to see how it works with other classes, and will they know if they have been swapped? And if someone healed a target will they know the target was moved? (Kind of like how drunk worked with healers “you have been redirected to #” somthing like that" or is it what ever target you inves is what it’ll show as.<br>
Cult in general: good to see that cult games are not going to last 10+ days anymore. And cult leaders will find themselves actually using sacrifice if they don’t have a full roster. Sad to see strength of the corax go but with the kill power cult has now I understand it, mixed with the new neutral class it’ll lead to some pretty fast games. Cult games just seem to add more chaos now and I like that. And ritualist actually has a claim to CW so they dont ger murderd instantly as they had no way to verify claiming anything because they could not prove. I’m guessing these changes were because Cult had the lowest winrate?<br>
King changes - I think this is good and bad. Drunk was a common claim for many cult and unseen because there wa sink real way to prove anything happened, now they can check nobility and verify them. The king changes also leads away from the expectation “King evil it’s day 3 kill him omg” also this causes the scorned to get weaker as well because it’s less investigation in the game overall but the king is going to be a more impactful IMO as they can actually lead instead of trying to find unseen cult before they get hung.<br>
Noble - always in a rough spot because there was not much to do. I have not ever seen the new noble win a game for BD. More or less they thriw the game because decree. Now that there are fewer uses forces them to use them more sparingly. The nighttime message thing may be a little wonky depending on how the RNG works out because if it’s random to where you talk to the same 2 people it’s pretty underwhelming. Bit this would need a lot more testing on my part before I come up with a valid idea of their power.<br>
Death Knights - still life after 3 days? And I’m guessing they were causing too many BD wins if there were 2 physicians late game? These need a only weaken them but the fact they can talk to the dead means the psychic can talk to him as well? If this is the case it’ll be interesting to see how it works out.<br>
Both new neutral classes - this CHANGES THE GAME IN A BIG WAY WHENEVER THIER IN THE GAME, if they affect the overall 3-4 neutral in a game that means less scorned, fool, alc and merc in the game when they are in it. And as they count as the neutral killer count no reaper or possessor. Somthing to keep an eye on if they are not/are in the game.</p>
<p>Overall I’m hyped to play the game when these hit and I’m not working all week.  Good freaking job with the constant updates and you guys are awesome. Keep doing what you do.</p>
<p>Thanks for your time.<br>
FluffyKnight</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 03:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It actually plays <em>really</em> well all around, especially since Physician is now a viable claim.</p>
<p>In addition, arguing that the new DK is “boring” is missing one key factor: you’re already dead. You can be dead and do nothing, or you can guard and kill people. Which one is more fun?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Finitethrills]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve said it before, and I’ll keep saying it… DK could stand losing either ability to talk, or ability to vote, but not both. I’ll have to wait and see how it plays, but it now sounds about as fun to play as a N1 murdered Fool.  I do have faith that if it turns out as cruddy as it sounds to me, devs will adjust it. Super happy to have devs that are willing to shake things up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 16:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eran_Shmuel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sketch" data-post="22" data-topic="15012">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/sketch/40/856_2.png" class="avatar"> Sketch:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>An Assassin who will kill them as well</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well While its not always easy to find unseen/cult, its extremly easy to find some BD members.<br>
Just kill whoever wishpering the king/ try to get progress going, have a confirmed BD status by death people logs.<br>
It’s not that hard…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Eran_Shmuel" data-post="17" data-topic="15012">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/eran_shmuel/40/2018_2.png" class="avatar"> Eran_Shmuel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its like the cult are getting a crazy-powerfull assasian that can’t  die.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>An Assassin who will kill them as well and an Assassin that is difficult to find.</p>
<p>I would wager Sorcerer is the most interesting and balanced Nature Killer at the moment, but I’ll wait until I get to play several games before a final decision.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Death Knight change was needed as it means only the psychic is able to retrieve dead-chat info now. Also allows Physician to be a valid fake-claim</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 23:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neclord]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ami" data-post="8" data-topic="15012">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ami/40/31302_2.png" class="avatar"> Ami:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sorta useless imo, lets see how it goes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Negates MM Princess claims and Invoker Drunk claims and no longer shits on neuts; it’s a fair change.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 23:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Eran_Shmuel" data-post="17" data-topic="15012">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/eran_shmuel/40/2018_2.png" class="avatar"> Eran_Shmuel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its like the cult are getting a crazy-powerfull assasian that can’t  die.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In a way, though the cult are going to have a heck of a time avoiding friendly fire. Also I’d say unseen is where it’s a bit more troubling. Inquisitor is very unlikely to kill unseen members, as it doesn’t kill MM, Assasain or 80% of possible converted roles. but he does kill all kinds of cult.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 23:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eran_Shmuel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>From fun Perspective</strong></p>
<p>The new natural killer seems Super fun!</p>
<p><strong>CW</strong> also much better…</p>
<p>I don’t like the <strong>drunk</strong> that much, it’s seems like a butler that is known to the attacker. I loved it when he could die, and we could get information. now only the targering player get the information. I do prefer this drunk better then the last patch drunk</p>
<p><strong>King:</strong> I think it’s a good change. it doesnt make sense that evil king will have so much affection on the game. I would love the king to have more then 4 uses of this power, because it’s much weaker.</p>
<p><strong>Noble</strong>: I have to see how it’s works. the noble know the random player? how can it help the noble if he doesnt know and the player just doesn’t say anything?</p>
<p><strong>DK:</strong> I really don’t like the cannot talk idea. This game is about deceit. Reading logs and faking logs is the base of this game. Remove talking is just make the game far worst. It’s good enough that they cannot vote for balancing issues</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 23:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eran_Shmuel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>From balanced prespective:</strong></p>
<p>While the new Natural killer is very cool, I don’t understand why he is against BD while the Inquisitor is against the sorccerer only.</p>
<p>Its like the cult are getting a crazy-powerfull assasian that can’t  die.</p>
<p>It would be balanced if the Inquisitor would be in the BD side, and he will not just be able to kill every magic user he can find.</p>
<p>The DK is also got alot weaker so I fear for BD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 23:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, Bos asked me if I’d be cool with him adding it to Noble</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 21:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="9" data-topic="15012" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Come to think of it, what’s the point of Ice Ward if you can self-tornado?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>occupy immune players can bypass it I think</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 21:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bus Driver HYPE!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 21:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lol is that at all influenced by your suggestion or not?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 21:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.9 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>King can still find fake drunks and princess claims</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 20:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15012-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/1-0-9-patch-notes/15012.rss">1.0.9 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
