<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949</link>
    <description>The Disciple is my version of [NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921). Credit for the idea belongs to them.


&gt;# [color = &quot;grey&quot;]The Disciple [/color] :shield: 
&gt;
&gt;**[color = &quot;gray&quot;]Neutral Support [/color]**
&gt;
&gt;**Devout Protection (Passive)** - You immune to most occupation and redirection abilities.
&gt;
&gt;**Mental Link (Passive)** - At the start of the game, you will get a list of the non-killing type neutral classes in the game not including yourself. Once you choose a class you will get 1 charge of all of their abilities and become linked with them. They will know who you are.
&gt;
&gt;**Vigilant Watch (Night)** - Prevent all players seeking to kill your linked neutral. - 3 uses
&gt;
&gt;**Conspire (Night)** - Create a chat between you and your linked neutral, allowing you to talk for the rest of the night. - Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt;**Win Condition** - Have your linked neutral complete their goal.

**Clarification of Abilities:**

**Mental Link** - If no one is selected, the game will randomly choose someone to bind them to. If there is more than one of that neutral class, the game will randomly choose one of the players to bind the Disciple to. I want to add a choice into it, but this may not be possible. I also want a different name for it as I don&#39;t think this ability name quite fits the feel of the Disciple, so if you have any suggestions, please tell me.

**Devout Protection** - Just standard occupation/redirection immunity

**Vigilant Watch** - This would have the same interaction as a Mercenary guard, but only if the person wants to kill your neutral.

**Conspire** - This chat would be like that of the mystic, except it wouldn&#39;t be anonymous. It would have a separate tab that only shows up if you are bonded to the Disciple. You can&#39;t conspire and do another night action, like all night abilities.

**Getting 1 charge of abilities from your neutral link** - This would include day abilities. For example, if you were linked with a Mercenary, you would get 1 charge of shield and 1 charge of stand guard along with your normal abilities. You would also get don armor with 1 charge. You do not get passives, however, so you would not be able to gain more bridlers with shield or stand guard.

**Extra Notes:**

* I would like a different name for Mental Link, I don&#39;t think that name fits the Disciple&#39;s flavor.

* It would be nice to get some feedback on whether they are too strong or too weak
* Do you think that they should be allowed to choose or do you think they should just be automatically linked at the beginning of the day?
* Would this class be any fun to play as, as I think it is one of the major things for the neutral class, to be more carefree and cause chaos.
.
Thank you to the NOBLE1 for letting me use their ideas</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 22:14:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NosduhYons" data-post="3" data-topic="72949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nosduhyons/40/4443_2.png" class="avatar"> NosduhYons:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I am just clarifying I am taking this just as a menu that says: Side with the NK, Side with Neutral 1, Side with Neutral 2 all on different buttons.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, I intended it to be a button based thing</p>
<p>Slight side note: make fool and disciple spawns mutually exclusive</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 22:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72949-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wait I take every thing back oh god no I don’t want a mini NK</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72949-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly IMO every neutral should be able to win with the NK. Noticed how merc and sellsword BOTH could win with the NK.</p>
<p>Also, it’s kinda BD’s fault for not killing it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 22:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72949-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NosduhYons]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you for replying and I love your idea, but I don’t know if the Disciple should be able to side with the NK. Before the Mercenary rework, having a Mercenary be contracted to the NK felt very unfun to play against, at least in my experience. Then you need to also ask, would being linked with the NK even help them? They mainly just get 2 extra kills (From you getting charges of their abilities), unless they’re Reaper, in which Vigilant Watch would come in handy if you found them early enough. I feel that NK just shouldn’t be included as a neutral you can pick because their goal is so different to other neutrals and would need separate balance.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marcus_Doodalee" data-post="2" data-topic="72949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marcus_doodalee/40/15452_2.png" class="avatar"> Marcus_Doodalee:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think he should have an ability to choose to side with A. The NK, B. Non NK neutral 1 and C. Non NK neutral 2</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marcus_Doodalee" data-post="2" data-topic="72949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marcus_doodalee/40/15452_2.png" class="avatar"> Marcus_Doodalee:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>You are only informed of your target neutrals class once you have chosen them.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am just clarifying I am taking this just as a menu that says: Side with the NK, Side with Neutral 1, Side with Neutral 2 all on different buttons. I was slightly confused what it meant at first, so if I am getting this wrong, sorry. I find the idea you need to find your linked target very intriguing, so I have decided to add it in, thank you so much for making the suggestion.</p>
<p>I want to make the Disciple more support based, and more of choosing the right abilities at the right time, but I come to a split in the road. Should I continue with getting the charge of the ability from your target, or should I make them completely support based in a more normal way?  If they continue with charges, like my original idea, I think they just might be too weak. However, if I go with the more traditional support based Disciple, I don’t know if I will be able to make it fun, which is what I was mainly going for. There are currently 3 support BDs, Chronomancer, Physician, and Court Wizard. If I just create a mixture of Physician and Court Wizard, it will be no fun. The Unseen and Cult supports are about stopping others from visiting and hiding investigative results. Neutrals only have Mercenary, which prevents visits. That is where I find my major flaw, it is really hard to make a class made to just enhance someone else feel really impactful and fun.</p>
<p>I will be editing my post to include your idea for Mental Link, thank you very much for helping me form the Disciple, even if it is just for fun. I will be thinking about adding the NK into the pool you can use, but I just need to edit the abilities first.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 22:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72949-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like the direction you’ve taken Nobles class, I have a few suggestions, mainly I think you’ve got passives that should be abilities and abilities that should be passives.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NosduhYons" data-post="1" data-topic="72949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nosduhyons/40/4443_2.png" class="avatar"> NosduhYons:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Mental Link (Passive)</strong> - At the start of the game, you will get a list of the non-killing type neutral classes in the game not including yourself. Once you choose a class you will get 1 charge of all of their abilities and become linked with them. They will know who you are.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think this should be reworked into a day ability, I don’t think the Disciple needs to know all the neutral classes in game, but I think he should have an ability to choose to side with A. The NK, B. Non NK neutral 1 and C. Non NK neutral 2 and if you if you win at the end of the game you get a certain amount of extra GP depending on which neutral you helped to win, or simply 0gp if its something like alchemist which almost always wins if outed. <strong>You are only informed of your target neutrals class once you have chosen them.</strong></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NosduhYons" data-post="1" data-topic="72949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nosduhyons/40/4443_2.png" class="avatar"> NosduhYons:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Conspire (Night)</strong> - Create a chat between you and your linked neutral, allowing you to talk for the rest of the night. - Infinite uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think a more interesting avenue for the disciple is for him to have to find his linked neutral before he can help them, say an ability that just returns feedback whether you found your neutral or not. Once you have found him/her you unlock an ability to “link” with them at night and thus confirm yourself to them or give them visit prevention.</p>
<p>Also given it is a support class it would be cool if it had some kind of cw empower or support abilty, maybe letting disciples “find my target” mechanic also be a heal? That would be interesting</p>
<p>Overall, I really like where you are taking this class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 02:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72949-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NosduhYons]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Disciple is my version of <a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921">NOBLE1’s Peace Keeper</a>. Credit for the idea belongs to them.</p>
<blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="grey">The Disciple </font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray">Neutral Support </font></strong></p>
<p><strong>Devout Protection (Passive)</strong> - You immune to most occupation and redirection abilities.</p>
<p><strong>Mental Link (Passive)</strong> - At the start of the game, you will get a list of the non-killing type neutral classes in the game not including yourself. Once you choose a class you will get 1 charge of all of their abilities and become linked with them. They will know who you are.</p>
<p><strong>Vigilant Watch (Night)</strong> - Prevent all players seeking to kill your linked neutral. - 3 uses</p>
<p><strong>Conspire (Night)</strong> - Create a chat between you and your linked neutral, allowing you to talk for the rest of the night. - Infinite uses</p>
<p><strong>Win Condition</strong> - Have your linked neutral complete their goal.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Clarification of Abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Mental Link</strong> - If no one is selected, the game will randomly choose someone to bind them to. If there is more than one of that neutral class, the game will randomly choose one of the players to bind the Disciple to. I want to add a choice into it, but this may not be possible. I also want a different name for it as I don’t think this ability name quite fits the feel of the Disciple, so if you have any suggestions, please tell me.</p>
<p><strong>Devout Protection</strong> - Just standard occupation/redirection immunity</p>
<p><strong>Vigilant Watch</strong> - This would have the same interaction as a Mercenary guard, but only if the person wants to kill your neutral.</p>
<p><strong>Conspire</strong> - This chat would be like that of the mystic, except it wouldn’t be anonymous. It would have a separate tab that only shows up if you are bonded to the Disciple. You can’t conspire and do another night action, like all night abilities.</p>
<p><strong>Getting 1 charge of abilities from your neutral link</strong> - This would include day abilities. For example, if you were linked with a Mercenary, you would get 1 charge of shield and 1 charge of stand guard along with your normal abilities. You would also get don armor with 1 charge. You do not get passives, however, so you would not be able to gain more bridlers with shield or stand guard.</p>
<p><strong>Extra Notes:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>I would like a different name for Mental Link, I don’t think that name fits the Disciple’s flavor.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It would be nice to get some feedback on whether they are too strong or too weak</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you think that they should be allowed to choose or do you think they should just be automatically linked at the beginning of the day?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Would this class be any fun to play as, as I think it is one of the major things for the neutral class, to be more carefree and cause chaos.<br>
.<br>
Thank you to the NOBLE1 for letting me use their ideas</p>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 01:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72949-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-disciple-version-of-noble1s-peace-keeper/72949.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Disciple (Version of NOBLE1&#39;s Peace Keeper)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
