<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375</link>
    <description>It&#39;s an oft forgotten and unexplored concept, but there sometimes is a need to use your enemies rather than eliminate them from play ASAP. The NK can, in some instances, be of tremendous use to the BD. Most notably in the mid-game where threat of Unseen/Cult majority is looming but not quite there. At this stage the evil faction _want_ the NK dead. The NK is the only threat to their victory, as their dominion over the BD is only a matter of time.

With this in mind, I take you to a particularly frustrating game that I played yesterday:
____________________________________
I rolled Good King. Prince died early, whispers went to me. Our sole Paladin at this point (the only Paladin claim in the game) had also died. The investigative claims were lacking. Day 5 comes along. Not a single cult had died but a lot of BD have (but not enough to lose majority, very much on the brink though). 

A Knight claims they CS&#39;d someone and they survived and so accused them of being the Reaper. The accused _**very quickly**_ gets voted up and they also claim Knight; Reaper for sure.

I decide to force pardon this Reaper, and promptly get accused (by what turned out to be a member of the cult at the time) of being an Evil King. BD and Cult collectively vote me up and execute me. I bought the Reaper 2 days, but he eventually gets executed. Cult go on to win with majority (they had a merc too so it was slightly faster than usual).
_______________________________
Was I wrong to force pardon that Reaper? Let&#39;s consider the scenarios a moment:

1. The Reaper is killed. The main investigatives are already gone and risky executions need to be made for BD to make progress. Given the 4-5 vote influence the cult has, this will very likely not pay off.
2. The Reaper lives, and gets to run free a couple of extra days and I&#39;m not executed. Odds of them hitting Cult and sapping their vote influence is fairly high depending on whether the Cult has an Invoker. If cult do, it  backfires greatly. There is, however, a bit of comfort in knowing that it&#39;s in the Reaper&#39;s interests to start thinning the Cult out to prep for their own win given the Prince is out of the picture.

Before I force pardoned, I asked myself &quot;which option creates the most likely conditions for a BD win?&quot;

To me, Option 1 just falls flat barring extraordinary luck. Option 2 has a good chance of falling flat as well, as it did in my case, but there was a route to victory hidden amongst the chaos that such a decision caused. Since there was such disagreement over my choice with the players in the game, I thought I&#39;d put it out there. Seems a fair amount of players find not killing an NK they find ASAP an alien concept.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 18:26:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Whammerist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This was Room 2, TftT V right!<br>
I remember this game, I was Invoker. I totally agreed with the force pardon, however the other element I’d have to consider is how something LOOKS in a Turbo fashion.<br>
When playing a game like this where social deduction is such a primary factor, you’ve got to consider the fact that there’s 4 Cultist all who would love nothing less than to see you voted up and killed. Often, it’s better to be “agreeable” than to make the 100% best play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 18:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59375-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss">Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just said <strong>technically</strong> we called him as evil because he want murder all of us. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59375-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss">Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He is evil</p>
<p>Just not aligned with the main evil faction</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59375-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss">Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yep this is indeed very underused with is bummer since i watch so many times when BD was just “bad” and fact you lost as NK just because someone pressed button on you is kinda frustrating.<br>
Most of players who are playing scum obviously would try push NK so that solves the problem attacking BD instead of Evils.</p>
<p>Fun Fact:<br>
Neutral Killer is techically <strong>not</strong> an  evil role so not killing him right away is not actually a missplay. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59375-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss">Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Except the inquistor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59375-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss">Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You did the right thing. The enemy of my enemy is my friend. Sometimes you got to work with the NK to win and eventually beat the NK</p>
<h2>“The enemy of my enemy is my friend” - Winston Churchill</h2>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59375-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss">Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neclord]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s an oft forgotten and unexplored concept, but there sometimes is a need to use your enemies rather than eliminate them from play ASAP. The NK can, in some instances, be of tremendous use to the BD. Most notably in the mid-game where threat of Unseen/Cult majority is looming but not quite there. At this stage the evil faction <em>want</em> the NK dead. The NK is the only threat to their victory, as their dominion over the BD is only a matter of time.</p>
<p>With this in mind, I take you to a particularly frustrating game that I played yesterday:</p>
<hr>
<p>I rolled Good King. Prince died early, whispers went to me. Our sole Paladin at this point (the only Paladin claim in the game) had also died. The investigative claims were lacking. Day 5 comes along. Not a single cult had died but a lot of BD have (but not enough to lose majority, very much on the brink though).</p>
<p>A Knight claims they CS’d someone and they survived and so accused them of being the Reaper. The accused <em><strong>very quickly</strong></em> gets voted up and they also claim Knight; Reaper for sure.</p>
<p>I decide to force pardon this Reaper, and promptly get accused (by what turned out to be a member of the cult at the time) of being an Evil King. BD and Cult collectively vote me up and execute me. I bought the Reaper 2 days, but he eventually gets executed. Cult go on to win with majority (they had a merc too so it was slightly faster than usual).</p>
<hr>
<p>Was I wrong to force pardon that Reaper? Let’s consider the scenarios a moment:</p>
<ol>
<li>The Reaper is killed. The main investigatives are already gone and risky executions need to be made for BD to make progress. Given the 4-5 vote influence the cult has, this will very likely not pay off.</li>
<li>The Reaper lives, and gets to run free a couple of extra days and I’m not executed. Odds of them hitting Cult and sapping their vote influence is fairly high depending on whether the Cult has an Invoker. If cult do, it  backfires greatly. There is, however, a bit of comfort in knowing that it’s in the Reaper’s interests to start thinning the Cult out to prep for their own win given the Prince is out of the picture.</li>
</ol>
<p>Before I force pardoned, I asked myself “which option creates the most likely conditions for a BD win?”</p>
<p>To me, Option 1 just falls flat barring extraordinary luck. Option 2 has a good chance of falling flat as well, as it did in my case, but there was a route to victory hidden amongst the chaos that such a decision caused. Since there was such disagreement over my choice with the players in the game, I thought I’d put it out there. Seems a fair amount of players find not killing an NK they find ASAP an alien concept.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59375-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/using-your-enemies-as-blue-dragon/59375.rss">Using Your Enemies as Blue Dragon</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
