<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nexus [Lore Thread]</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/nexus-lore-thread/48024</link>
    <description># Disclaimer; Nexus is a sandbox RP! So this post will be made into a wiki that anyone who joins the RP can edit and add to. 
# Locations
## Realms
_____
### Velonia
The smallest of the four realms. Mostly wildlife. Any civilization is medieval-era. There are many small kingdoms and villages scattered throughout. The largest city is Arian Spire, A large tower with a village surrounding it’s base. The government of the Spire is a democratic republic lead by an Archmage and his(or her) council of mages. 
The Church of Lyncitus originates from Velonia. They are slowly growing in popularity. One such church lies in the Capital. 

Velonia is connected to Nexus Hub by a green portal, exiting at an abandoned ruin through a similar portal at the city gate. Anyone passing through the ruins will see a forest, and crossing through will let one have reached the Capital.

**Legend of Dendar** Dendar a ancient word. Dendar is said to be the 1st Lich a necromancer of unequal power it is said he could turn a entire army into undead with a snap of his finger. while the Legend of Dendar existence&#39;s has faded with time there are still those who still know of him. perhaps this knowledge can help defeat the lichlord as many lichs become one due to siding with Dendar. those who know of dendar are bound to know of Dendar&#39;s Scythe his legendary weapon

### Callinety Falls
A realm dominated by concrete jungle, Callinety Falls technology is similar to that of the modern world. Humans with extraordinary power, dubbed Metahumans, have long been a part of society. The appearance of Metahumans date back as far as the 14th Century.

Callinety Falls is connected to Nexus Hub through an underground passage, similar to an underground passage for cars. This passage is located at the end of a  what was a dead end in a residential area. The exit in Nexus Hub is that of a gigantic tree.
### Grand Peninsula 
A world in its prime, the Grand Peninsula is in the golden age of steam, the full extent of which is not yet truly known, steam powers everything, from vehicles to entertainment and everything in between, if you can dream it, someone here can make it, providing it&#39;s powered by steam.

Ruled over by Queen Charlotte IV, a monarch who has only reigned for 5 years so far, daughter of the much beloved King Matthew II, she has deviated a bit from his vision of a perfect world, but that, she insists, is the fault of the Nexus, not herself.
### Eleos-12

The realm boasting the title of the largest realm of the four realms. Eleos-12 inhibitants have long forsaken travels of land in favour of exploration of the space. A diverse number of species and empires can be found on the limitless galaxy.

Eleos-12 is ruled over by the Intergalaxy Council, with numerous empires being part of it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 06:18:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Roleplaying</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/nexus-lore-thread/48024.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nexus [Lore Thread]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Disclaimer; Nexus is a sandbox RP! So this post will be made into a wiki that anyone who joins the RP can edit and add to.</h1>
<h1>Locations</h1>
<h2>Realms</h2>
<hr>
<h3>Velonia</h3>
<p>The smallest of the four realms. Mostly wildlife. Any civilization is medieval-era. There are many small kingdoms and villages scattered throughout. The largest city is Arian Spire, A large tower with a village surrounding it’s base. The government of the Spire is a democratic republic lead by an Archmage and his(or her) council of mages.<br>
The Church of Lyncitus originates from Velonia. They are slowly growing in popularity. One such church lies in the Capital.</p>
<p>Velonia is connected to Nexus Hub by a green portal, exiting at an abandoned ruin through a similar portal at the city gate. Anyone passing through the ruins will see a forest, and crossing through will let one have reached the Capital.</p>
<p><strong>Legend of Dendar</strong> Dendar a ancient word. Dendar is said to be the 1st Lich a necromancer of unequal power it is said he could turn a entire army into undead with a snap of his finger. while the Legend of Dendar existence’s has faded with time there are still those who still know of him. perhaps this knowledge can help defeat the lichlord as many lichs become one due to siding with Dendar. those who know of dendar are bound to know of Dendar’s Scythe his legendary weapon</p>
<h3>Callinety Falls</h3>
<p>A realm dominated by concrete jungle, Callinety Falls technology is similar to that of the modern world. Humans with extraordinary power, dubbed Metahumans, have long been a part of society. The appearance of Metahumans date back as far as the 14th Century.</p>
<p>Callinety Falls is connected to Nexus Hub through an underground passage, similar to an underground passage for cars. This passage is located at the end of a  what was a dead end in a residential area. The exit in Nexus Hub is that of a gigantic tree.</p>
<h3>Grand Peninsula</h3>
<p>A world in its prime, the Grand Peninsula is in the golden age of steam, the full extent of which is not yet truly known, steam powers everything, from vehicles to entertainment and everything in between, if you can dream it, someone here can make it, providing it’s powered by steam.</p>
<p>Ruled over by Queen Charlotte IV, a monarch who has only reigned for 5 years so far, daughter of the much beloved King Matthew II, she has deviated a bit from his vision of a perfect world, but that, she insists, is the fault of the Nexus, not herself.</p>
<h3>Eleos-12</h3>
<p>The realm boasting the title of the largest realm of the four realms. Eleos-12 inhibitants have long forsaken travels of land in favour of exploration of the space. A diverse number of species and empires can be found on the limitless galaxy.</p>
<p>Eleos-12 is ruled over by the Intergalaxy Council, with numerous empires being part of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/nexus-lore-thread/48024/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/nexus-lore-thread/48024/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 14:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-48024-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/nexus-lore-thread/48024.rss">Nexus [Lore Thread]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
