<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rated P for Plex - Feedback</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473</link>
    <description># Inquisitor + Sorcerer 

Currently, there is no true BD support. Inquisitor needs to see Sorcerer die, while Sorcerer wants to see BD fall. Both can win with Unseen or Cult. Inquisitor could win with BD if they choose to. It falls under being another Alchemist or Scorned that has won.

If a Sorcerer leaves real early, or dies around N1/N2, then it&#39;s a free win on them and they get to basically sit back while everyone bickers. It also gets to use it&#39;s abilities.

# Ideas: 
1. When Sorcerer is dead, Inquisitor abilities are disabled. This will stop Inquisitor being a threat to Court Wizard or Psychic in the long run. Had a game with one who YOLO&#39;d a CW for the sake of helping Unseen.
2. Inquisitor has to live to see Sorcerer die and then BD must win. To me it makes no sense to have Sorc be anti-BD and Inquisitor anti-Sorc but can win with everyone else. Inquisitor should be super into BD wanting to win since Sorc wanted BD to lose.
3. Inquisitor becomes Priest when Sorcerer is dead. Just a rename and re-alignment. No abilities changed.  Basically when the Sorcerer is killed, the Inquisitor is renamed to Priest and becomes BD. This doesn&#39;t seem like a good option but it&#39;s an idea regardless.

---------

# King is a crutch

Everybody is being too reliant on Kings. The King, being that they&#39;re 33% chance of being Blue Dragon, is literally every-bodies centre of attention. It&#39;s literally impossible to scum read when everybody is asking the King for Info and demanding them dead, etc.

King&#39;s Royal Blood check should return and people need to stop being so heavily reliant on the King. It should not even have a second ability.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:38:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rated P for Plex - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Id like to see a check of 2 people or so. Where it says one is investigative and it’s up to the king to deduce who. Most of the games abilities don’t actually contribute to the social deduction part of the game. They are a crutch. It literally says unseen or not sus or.some variant of that. Princesses is nice. She has to figure it out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-17473-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473.rss">Rated P for Plex - Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rated P for Plex - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel like some sort of class type check is fine ‘This guy is claiming sheriff, I checked to see if he was investigative and he is not.’ That would be fine imo</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-17473-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473.rss">Rated P for Plex - Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rated P for Plex - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Inquisitor + Sorcerer</h1>
<p>Currently, there is no true BD support. Inquisitor needs to see Sorcerer die, while Sorcerer wants to see BD fall. Both can win with Unseen or Cult. Inquisitor could win with BD if they choose to. It falls under being another Alchemist or Scorned that has won.</p>
<p>If a Sorcerer leaves real early, or dies around N1/N2, then it’s a free win on them and they get to basically sit back while everyone bickers. It also gets to use it’s abilities.</p>
<h1>Ideas:</h1>
<ol>
<li>When Sorcerer is dead, Inquisitor abilities are disabled. This will stop Inquisitor being a threat to Court Wizard or Psychic in the long run. Had a game with one who YOLO’d a CW for the sake of helping Unseen.</li>
<li>Inquisitor has to live to see Sorcerer die and then BD must win. To me it makes no sense to have Sorc be anti-BD and Inquisitor anti-Sorc but can win with everyone else. Inquisitor should be super into BD wanting to win since Sorc wanted BD to lose.</li>
<li>Inquisitor becomes Priest when Sorcerer is dead. Just a rename and re-alignment. No abilities changed.  Basically when the Sorcerer is killed, the Inquisitor is renamed to Priest and becomes BD. This doesn’t seem like a good option but it’s an idea regardless.</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<h1>King is a crutch</h1>
<p>Everybody is being too reliant on Kings. The King, being that they’re 33% chance of being Blue Dragon, is literally every-bodies centre of attention. It’s literally impossible to scum read when everybody is asking the King for Info and demanding them dead, etc.</p>
<p>King’s Royal Blood check should return and people need to stop being so heavily reliant on the King. It should not even have a second ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-17473-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rated-p-for-plex-feedback/17473.rss">Rated P for Plex - Feedback</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
