<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351</link>
    <description>Right now the game is in a fairly good state. That being said there are still some things that need changing before the game is basically perfect. 

This is in order of importance
1: Ally&#39;s needs to be replaced. I&#39;m sure it will take a few attempts to get right but the king should not be able to Investigate. This Ability could be replaced with a social or Support Ability in order to furfill it&#39;s old function.

2: The Inquisitor and sorcerer need a rework. A neutral killer does not deserve a hardcounter. Period. I suggest making the sorcerer a normal Neutral Killer and making the Inquisitor a Neutral with the current Sorcs wincon and similar night Ability&#39;s.

3: The Illusionist and the Apostle need access to dead chat. By that I mean like how the Apostle has dark words until the latest patch. The illusionist and Apostle both need that passive in order to provide engagement to dead members of that faction.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 02:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bart_Auringer" data-post="35" data-topic="34351">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bart_auringer/40/2131_2.png" class="avatar"> Bart_Auringer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Psychic feels about right now, imo.  2 was too many.  NK was a nightmare and a psychic could just suicide to get someone and come out ahead because you usually had a back up.  Now it’s an important role, but convertible, so outing yourself is a big risk.  Feels about right to be honest, though I’d love some way for Evil to see dead chat once in a while, even if it’s fairly rare.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with Psychic being perfect right now. I am only taking about changing the Illusionist and Apostle a bit</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 02:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>
<p>Problem there is… the psychic already does it and does it better most of the time.  Plus it’s not a very kingly ability.  He digs up dead bodies and talks to the corpses?  Allies is just too strong.  There is no counter claim to it other than scream Scorned target.  Neuts just die, no counter claim, no recourse.  At best you make them have the Prince kill you by playing Fool, but <em>you will die.</em> Honestly a good ability might be along the lines of the abilities that check a role.  King can see that “butler” is a killer not offense.  But it doesn’t lead to d2 “Get up 5 he’s Unseen” with no counter play.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Sorc might kill well, but she dies easily and she only wins if she lives.<br>
Even the MM can take a bullet for the team and still win.  Sorc <em>can’t</em>.  She loses if she does.<br>
She’s good at killing healers, but terrible at avoiding detection.  And the worst person for finding her is <em>the person who’s entire purpose is to kill her.</em>  Sorcs can’t claim anything.  They’re night immune, occ immune, neutral killers.  She had no escape.  Inq wins 90% of the time by just sitting around doing nothing (which also sucks since literally your first 3 MU checks are meaningless) and then you can maybe do something, but odds are you’re just waiting for the BD to inevitably find her, because if anyone looks at her, they’ll know she’s fishy.<br>
Removing Dust and making her appear to faction checks as BD would be better.  It makes the Inq feel like he’s actually doing something and makes him the best guy to find the sorc (which, remember, is literally his entire reason for existing) and opens up her claim options.  Maybe even have a message for when evil attacks her that its her if that still doesn’t work or vice versa.  Lots of options and room to work.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Psychic feels about right now, imo.  2 was too many.  NK was a nightmare and a psychic could just suicide to get someone and come out ahead because you usually had a back up.  Now it’s an important role, but convertible, so outing yourself is a big risk.  Feels about right to be honest, though I’d love some way for Evil to see dead chat once in a while, even if it’s fairly rare.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1: Maybe maybe not I’m just saying ideas that could work. Also you do realize that it’s a max of 2 night Ability’s per class right? Anyways I’m sure there is an ability that would work so we can just brainstorm until we find it.</p>
<p>2: Sure the Inquisitor is not almighty but he doesn’t need to claim to kill you. At the very least if he attacks randomly the first 3 nights he already has a decent chance of hitting you. The fact that it is so hard to make contact with the unseen is the whole reason why it’s meaningless that you can.</p>
<p>3: At this point we are disagreeing about the facts. I’ve clearly had a different experience from you so unless we get hard data we will never settle this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 14:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>
<p>I see. I don’t think an additional killing ability would be a good idea, though. There are enough killing abilities in the game already. Maybe limit allies to 2 uses, guards to 2 uses and give an 2 use additional ability.<br>
My suggestion would be. “Forensics” - “shows the result of the last ability a BD player who died the previous night used”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I disagree. The Sorc is an immensly powerful killer. The hardest part is to actually get in contact with unseen/cult. INQ claim is not almighty. He is very unlikely to get guarded or followed since BD usually look after themself.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I still believe it would buff unseen/cult way to much. I’d rather have psy not being unique than unseen/cult access to deadchat.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I actually really had 70% Unseen/cult wins and i also noticed a lot of players in game being just as bored and frustrated as i was. I really doubt its just me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 14:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-33</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1: I actually asked for it to be replaced not removed. If done right he would still be able to prove himself possablely but it wouldn’t be bland like it is now. Maybe it could be a killing ability?</p>
<p>2: The problem is that the Unseen and Cult aren’t too helpful at keeping you alive. The Inquisitor may not be able to convince the court that you are sorc but it is fairly likely that he will get you killed as anyways. Like I said a Neutral Killer does not deserve a hardcounter. Especially not one that can claim openly.</p>
<p>3: This is actually not really for the purposes of buffing evils but rather to help that problem you mentioned earlier. If a converted Psy still has access to the dead then the Possessor jumping is much less likely to be safe as the Psy needs to be dead not just converted. Even more so in Cult games with up to 3 Apostles.</p>
<p>As for the balencing problems I’m not sure how true that really is. Of the 6 games I’ve played in the latest patch (all of which were fun) 3 of them were BD wins, 2 of them were Cult wins and 1 of them was Unseen win. I’m sure that the winrates aren’t exactly 50/50 but the point is that we didn’t actually know unless the devs tell us (they really should)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 14:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No it is in a horrible state.</p>
<p>Since the patch evil won around 75% of all games i played.<br>
It’s way too easy and it lacks all the excitement it had before.</p>
<p>I noticed that i went from around 15 games a day to around 3 now because it is boring af.</p>
<p>Psy was a key investigative class and the possessors archenemy. Now poss can freely jump around midgame since unique psy is likely dead/converted by then and you don’t have to fear a second one. There is also no way contacting the dead after 1st psy is gone which ruins one of the best aspects and information sources of the game.</p>
<p>And don’t get me started on noble. Noble is the most useless BD class i have ever seen. The spy ability is basically gambling with very limited rewards since most whispers barely contain more than claims to king and merc speaking with contract. Its absolutly useless for a BD class since Cult/Unseen communicates at night.</p>
<p>The snoop is also useless if Unseen/Cult is not borderline retarded. It also ruins the fun of making snappy unseen/cult/NK notes on your second page. The private note tab is very inconvenient to use in addition to your log.</p>
<p>Regarding your suggestions:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>No, just no. It’s hard enough to tell if starting king is evil or not. If you take the invest there is nothing left for king to prove his status. If u take allies it will only lead to random King yolos and executes. It will make King an absolutly boring class to play since u have nothing to do but guard youtrself agains yolos and stabs and you are likely executed no matter what side you are on and what you do.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Mad Sorc spotted. No They don’t need chanching. Sorc is the only NK that can allie with Unseen/Cult and thats what you have to do if you want to win. If you play Sorc like you play Reaper/Poss you deserve to lose. It’s fairly hard for Inq to confirm Sorc since Sorc has 3 dusts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>No. You certainly prefer to play evil i guess but evil is strong enough as it is. Illusionist and Apostle are fairly hard to prove. Giving them access to dead chat is absolutly op.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I find it baffling that you still ask for evil buff even though they win almost any game since last patch.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 13:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To inquisitor</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 11:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It has been tested and proven worthy of its own thread <a class="mention" href="/u/nuclearburrito">@NuclearBurrito</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 05:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then we make one, and mention Boslof and Blade Everywhere</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 05:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly it deserves its own thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eh, I mean, there’s a lot of options the King can go, and I guess we all have different ideas, but Allies is not the answer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly you could just make the starting kings thing be the ability to use his day Ability’s as much as he wants</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And I’m going to be honest, I feel like the King should just have the passive where his votes always count twice, which would make room for more useful abilities. Then there could be something like Order/Royal Decree as well as PM given to the King.</p>
<p>The Mayor in ToS has permanent three votes when he reveals anyways.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Still too easy. Just give them all PM or something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or if the above would make it too easy to determine the King’s alignment;</p>
<p>Good King:<br>
Royal Heirs: Determine if a player is a Royal</p>
<p>Evil King:<br>
Conspiracy: Determine if a player is a member of the Unseen/Cult</p>
<p>Neutral King:<br>
Private Matters: All whispers from you and to you will be hidden</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Starting King:</p>
<p>Has Decide Fate, Royal Finger, and Guards as all abilities (current)</p>
<p>Good King:<br>
Order: Prevent a player from voting tomorrow.</p>
<p>Evil King:<br>
Royal Decree: Prevent a player from being accused tomorrow.</p>
<p>Neutral King:<br>
Private Matter: All whispers to you and from you will be hidden</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Great idea</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, then how about this idea?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No. Starting king HAS to be stronger than normal king. Otherwise he would be executed asap and replace with confirmed BD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I see, ok, so we have 3 options for replacing the King’s allies?</p>
<p>And I think all Kings should have all abilities, not just the starting King</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yup! Noble used to have that for a bit. Unlimited uses too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ohhh I see, it would be have all your whispers tomorrow be hidden?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No. It can be a night Ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just realized Private Matter being for the King would mean that Royal Finger or Decide Fate would have to go, both of which are pretty essential for a King role in my opinion, unlike Allies.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why not both? PM does work well with the Psychic who is based on hidden communication but it could also work on the king.</p>
<p>It wouldn’t be the only Ability that multiple classes have.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34351-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/changes-that-still-need-to-happen-1-0-15/34351.rss">Changes that still need to happen [1.0.15]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
