<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799</link>
    <description># Welcome to SFoL - Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium!

Hosted by Alice

**In a far away land, a magnanimous empire rules fairly over its land. However, familiar threats seem to be looming on the horizon…**

Welcome to Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium. This SFoL takes up a mixture of Moleland&#39;s Triple Threat Setup while also utilizing the Hand of Byzantium Class cards in order to spice things up, this in short is a HoB game that has a multiball setup. The setup here is simple. The uninformed majority needs to find and execute both the Cult and the Unseen. The only difference here is that the uninformed majority is a different faction than the Blue Dragon, and both scum factions are present rather than a single one. The King is also replaced with an Emperor that is more social and active than the classic King.

# Rules

![|20x20](/user_avatar/forum.imperium42.com/queen_alfa/40/6988_1.png) [Forum of Lies Official Hub](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/forum-of-lies-official-hub/1515?u=luxy) [Forum of Lies](/c/forum-matches/forum-of-lies)

&gt; Welcome to the wonderful wacky (And sometimes stressful) world of FoL! Useful Links [Class Cards Thread!](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fol-class-cards-clean-with-no-talking/1998) [Spreadsheet of Complete, Ongoing and Planned FoL and SFoL games! Also includes information on how to sign up to host.](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1eAoQS7saD6SL-s9v0Z6A5Fthb_XrraZt_IvBuslsoBs/edit?usp=sharing) [The Forum of Lies Discord Server!](https://discord.gg/YU7aVWd) [A friendly “how to get started” guide by one of our own players! ](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/forum-of-lies-getting-started/49368) [ New player guide by our good boy](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/forum-of-lies-new-player-guide/71790) General Gameplay Infomation Rules Follow the Global Forum Rules If you haven’t posted content in 36 hours, you’ll be prodded for inactiv…

# Gameplay

Days will be 72 hours long, or shorter if someone is executed.
Nights will be 24 hours days long.
Actions are done in your class card.
Unseen and Cult members will talk through a Discord server. They can talk there during both the day and night
The Cabalists will have a permanent private topic.
The Saint, the Blasphemer, and the Saint!Apostle with an adequate passive will have continous access to dead chat.
The Librarian, the Archivist, and the Librarian!Apostle will have their own private topic for their log network.
The Arbiter will have their own private topic that shall be usable for the entire length of the match, and they&#39;ll be allowed to invite one player to it for the entire game.
There will be one private topic per day for the Imperial Chat as different players will be allowed to enter them by night. They can only be used during the specific night.
The Unseen class cap is 4, and the Cult class cap is 5.
The maximum amount of duplicate classes is 4, barring unique class or those with the Prestige passive.
When you receive a card you will have 24 hours to reply, confirming you have received it.

# Executions

To accuse someone say “/accuse [player]” or “/vote [player]”
Should the votes reach the majority, that player will be executed and the day will end.

# Journals

Message me your entire journal, the last draft I receive before you die shall be the one displayed

# To Join

To join, simply express interest in joining by saying something like “I want to join” or “/join” or “/in” or “sign me up, coach” or whatever you want

# Class Cards


[details=Emperors]

&gt;# [color = purple]The Corrupt Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Special[/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Assassin&#39;s Brotherhood (Night)** - Sends an assassin to a player. This attack does not count as a visit and cannot be stopped, if a Coroner checks the cause of death by this attack then it will show up as killed by an Assassin. Can only be used on the second night or after that you are crowned. - One use
**Conspiracy (Night)** - Permanently makes a player be seen as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - 2 uses
_Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Unseen.

&gt;# [color = darkred]The Devout Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt;**[color = darkred]Cult Special[/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Sacrificial Offering (Night)** - Prevents healing on a player for the rest of the match. - One use
**Priest King (Night)** - Converts a player to the Cult if there is one or less Cultist alive, if there are more then the charge of Priest King will not be used. Can only be used on the second night or after that you are crowned. - One use
_Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Cult.

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]The Righteous Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]Hand of Byzantium Special[/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor. If you are executed for treason your first accuser will die alongside you.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Praetorian Guard (Night)** - Sends a guard to a player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Imperial Advisers (Night)** - Sends an adviser to a player. They will be immune to conversions for the night. - 3 uses
_Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Hand of Byzantium
&gt;* The Senex, providing they are aligned with the Hand of Byzantium.
[/details]
 



[details=&quot;Hand of Byzantium - Investigative&quot;]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Actuary [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Sharp Eyes (Day)** - Selects a player during the day. In the following night you will be notified if they have used any Day abilities. - 2 uses
&gt;**Notice to Detail (Day)** - At the beginning of the night, you will be told how many day abilities were used the previous day. - 2 uses
&gt;**Inventory (Night)** - Selects a player and you will be informed of the total number of uses they have for both their night abilities combined. Abilities with unlimited usage will count as zero. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Taxman [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Sharp Eyes): Corax&#39;s Mirror (Day)** - Along with being notified if they used a day ability, you will also learn which ability your target used. - 2 use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Arbiter [/color] :crossed_swords: :shield:  
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Special [/color]**
&gt;**Inside Knowledge (Passive)** - Once the match starts you will have a n0 green check on a Hand of Byzantium player. At the start of each night, you will know if either faction converted a player.
&gt;**Tenacity (Passive)** - You cannot be occcupied nor redirected, and both of your night abilities can be used at the same time. However, at the same time all protective abilities will fail on you and any kill that targetted you cannot be occupied or redirected. This passive cannot be removed.
&gt;**Entrust (Day)** - Selects a player during the day, this cannot be your n0 green check. They will be immune to conversions for the remainder of the game and will share a neighborhood with you. - One use
&gt;**Imperial Judgment (Night)** - Kills a player if they are a member of the Unseen or the Cult, bypassing all forms of framing, healing, and protection. You will be notified of your target&#39;s faction at the end of the night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Imperial Providence (Night)** - Heal and prevent conversions on a chosen player, the conversion protection will last for the next night as well. - Infinite uses.
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; Cannot be converted.

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Fortuneteller [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Numerology (Day)** - Tells you how many Hand of Byzantium-aligned players are still alive by the beginning of the coming night. Does not take the Emperor&amp;rsquo;s alignment into account. - 2 uses
**Shuffle Deck (Night)** - Grants an additional charge of Tarot Card. - Infinite uses
**Tarot Card (Night)** - Select three players. By the end of the night you will receive from one to three cards. Each card will tell the role of one of the selected player. Special-type classes will return the same result for Investigative-type classes and Killer-type classes will return the same result for Offensive-type classes. Tarot Card bypasses anything that would prevent visits but you can still be occupied. - 0 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Sibyl [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Shuffle Deck (Night)**
**Tarot Card (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Numerology): Divination by Blood (Day)** - Tells you of which Hand of Byzantium classes are still alive and how many. - 2 use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Governor [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Kingmaker (Passive)** - Your vote during Emperor elections silently counts as three votes.
**Certify (Day)** - Grants Royal Blood to your target. - 3 uses
**Trace Lineage (Night)** - Informs you whether your target has Royal Blood or not. - Infinite uses
**Background Check (Night)** - If an Emperor&amp;rsquo;s election was held during the previous day, then the Governor will be informed of how many votes each faction received. - 1 use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Chancellor [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Kingmaker (Passive)**
**Certify (Day)**
**Trace Lineage (Night)**
[color = darkred]**Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Background Check): Guidance of the Blood God (Night)** - If an election for Emperor happens tomorrow, then only votes for members of the Cult will count. - 1 use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Socialite [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Guest List (Day)** - By the end of the coming night, you will know how many players of each faction visited you. - 2 uses
**Social Links (Night)** - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets&amp;rsquo; class type groupings match. Groups are Special/Investigative, Social/Support, and Killer/Offensive. You will receive either no match if they are from different groups, a good match if they are in the same group, and a perfect match if they are the same class type. - Infinite uses
**Faction Links (Night)** - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets&amp;rsquo; alignments match. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Marchioness [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**Social Links (Night)**
**(Guest List): Gate of Blood (Day)** - You will learn whoever visits them the coming night. - 2 use
[color = darkred]**Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Faction Links): Blasphemous Waltz (Night)** - You will convert an additional player to the Cult if the Cult Leader converts tonight. - One use


&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Watchman [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Tracking (Day)** - You will learn if your target left their room last night. - 2 uses
&gt;**Silent Stalking (Night)** - You will learn who your target visits this night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Midnight Vigil (Night)** - You will learn who visits your target this night. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Stalker [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Hand of Byzantium - Social&quot;]

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Cabalist [/color]
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Ancient Cabal (Passive)** - Cabalists may only roll in groups of two. You will have an all-day chat with the other Cabalist. You are immune to conversion while the other Cabalist is still alive.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Letter with no Sender (Day)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Cryptic Communications (Night)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player and they will be able to post a reply. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Secretive Connections (Night)** - If alive, the other Cabalist will not be able to be voted tomorrow. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Exiled [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Ancient Cabal): Cult Traditions (Passive)** - The Cult Leader will be seen as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks while you are alive.
**Letter with no Sender (Day)**
**Cryptic Communications (Night)**
**(Secretive Connections): Influence of Anstreim (Night)** - Prevents another Cultist from being voted tomorrow. - One use


&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Coroner [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Grave Focus (Day)** - In addition to the results from Exhume or Forensics, you will also learn the class of their target&amp;rsquo;s killer. If the killer is a Psychopathic or Tyrannous Emperor then it will show their previous classes instead. - 2 uses
&gt;**Exhume (Night)** - Selects a deceased player and you will learn of all effects the target received the night they died. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Forensics (Night)** - Selects a deceased player and you will learn of every player that visited them during the entire match. Can only be used on players that died the fourth night or later. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Undertaker [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Exhume (Night)**
**Forensics (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Grave Focus): Corruption of Corax (Day)** - Causes a player to flip as another class if they are executed on trial. - One use

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Librarian [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Repository (Passive)** - You start in a public log network by yourself. Players in the network will be allowed to read the logs of any other player in the network. The Repository remains open while the Librarian is still alive regardless if they have been converted.
**Archive (Day)** - Invites a player to the log network. The player must accept before joining and can choose to leave at anytime. Can only invite two players per day. - Infinite uses
**Revoke (Night)** - Removes a player from the log network. - Infinite uses
**Shutdown (Night)** - Deactivates the Unseen or Cult day chat for the next day and night. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Archivist [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Repository): Library of Corax (Passive)** - You will be able to use Archive and Revoke along with your normal night and day abilities as an Apostle, while keeping the log network. Cult members will be able to use the network as well.
**(Shutdown): Echoes of Anstreim (Night)** - The Cult will obtain a copy of the Emperor&#39;s messages in the Imperial Chat at the end of the night. - 3 uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Magistrate [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
**Judicial Decree (Day)** - Resets the votes, allowing only you and your target to be put on trial for today. - 2 uses
**Disenfranchise (Night)** - Silently reduces the amount of votes required to execute a target by one. - Infinite uses
**Impeach (Night)** - Kills the Emperor and automatically takes their place, becoming a Righteous Emperor. Cannot be used until the third night. - 1 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Judge [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**Judicial Decree (Day)**
**Disenfranchise (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Impeach): Rise of the Blood King (Night)** - Kills the Emperor and automatically takes their place, becoming a Devout Emperor. Cannot be used until the third night. - 1 uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Saint [/color]:shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Intercession (Passive)** - You may speak with the dead during the night.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Rapture (Day)** - Will allow you to speak and vote even while dead. Can only be used after you&#39;ve died. - One use
&gt;**Mercy (Night)** - Selects a dead Hand of Byzantium-aligned player and forces them to use their primary night action on a living one. Cannot be used on Killer classes. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Spiritual Merge (Night)** - Binds a dead player to you, allowing them to speak while dead for as long as you are alive, but they will be removed from dead chat. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Blasphemer [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Intercession): Interpreter of Corax (Passive)** - All Cultists will be able to speak in Cult chat even while dead. You may also speak with the dead during the night.
**Rapture (Day)**
**(Mercy): Slave of Anstreim (Night)** - Selects a dead Cultist and forces them to use their primary night action on a living one. Cannot be used on dead Cult Leaders. - Infinite use
**Spiritual Merge (Night)**

[/details]

[details=Hand of Byzantium - Killer]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Crusader [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Providence (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the Hand of Byzantium faction visits you this coming night, they will be prevented and bled. You cannot use Hand of God after using Providence.- One use
**Hand of God (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Hand of Byzantium visits them they will be bled by you. This does not stop their actions. - Infinite uses
**Deus Vult (Night)** - Attacks and kills two targets. You will also die of exhaustion the night they use this ability regardless of the ability&amp;rsquo;s outcome. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Fanatic [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
&gt;**(Providence) Blood Providence (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the Cult visits you this coming night, they will be prevented and bled the next day. - 2 uses
&gt;**(Hand of God) Hand of Mithras (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Cult visits them they will be bled. This does not stop their actions. - Infinite uses
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Deus Vult): Incarnation of Mithras (Night)** - Allows the Cult Leader to kill an additional target if you are sacrificed. - 1 uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Duelist [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Schuld (Passive)** - If you have killed any Hand of Byzantium-aligned players in the match, then you will not be allowed to receive votes to become the Emperor.
**Versetzen (Day)** - Grants night immunity for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then you will gain a use of Zornhau. - 2 uses
**Mittelhau (Night)** - Redirects the selected player&amp;rsquo;s action to you while also granting yourself immunity to all redirected attacks and conversions, then attack the player. If you successfully kill a player then you will gain a use of Zornhau. Disables the your night abilities if the target is aligned with the Hand of Byzantium. - Infinite uses
**Zornhau (Night)** - Prevents you from being occupied or redirected, then attacks the your target and kills them, bypassing healing and night immunity. Disables your night abilities if the target is aligned with the Hand of Byzantium. - 0 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Baronet [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**(Schuld): Grausamkeit (Passive)** - If you become a Devout Emperor, then you&#39;ll gain a second use of Sacrificial Offering. 
**(Versetzen): Opfern (Day)** - Grants night immunity to you for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then the Cult Leader&#39;s next Blood of Mithras will be free of charge. - 2 uses
**(Mittelhau): **Vergeltung** (Night)** - Redirects the player onto you. If they attack you then you will counterattack and kill them. - Infinite uses
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Zornhau): Königsmord (Night)** - Kills the Emperor, bypassing everything. If the you kill a Devout Emperor, then you will commit suicide. - 1 uses

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Thaumaturge [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Thaumaturgic Focus (Passive)** - You are immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Thunder (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Thunder on your target, causing them to explode and kill the player before they are converted while also putting the conversion on cooldown. You are notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the conversion happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses
**Sigil of Fire (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Fire on your target, causing them to explode and kill any player that attacks the target, but does not prevent any actions against them. You are notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the attack happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Arcanist [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Sigil of Thunder): Thunderbolt of Corax (Night)** - If the Cult&#39;s conversion is off cooldown then you can put it on cooldown to enact an additional kill that is guaranteed to succeed. - Infinite uses
**(Sigil of Fire): Inferno of Mithras (Night)** - You will kill yourself and anyone visiting you. - One use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Warrior [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Combat Ready (Passive)** - If you are attacked during the first two nights, you will be immune and will counterattack instead of dying.
**Bloodlust (Passive)** - For every successful kill, you will gain an additional night of Combat Ready.
**Raging Axes (Night)** - Attacks and kills a player. If the target was Hand of Byzantium-aligned, then you will lose his night abilities and they will be shown as Unseen or Cult to faction checks. - Infinite uses
**Taunt (Night)** - Redirects the target&amp;rsquo;s night action to the yourself. Redirects past the second night will trigger Combat Ready. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Marauder [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Bloodlust): Blood for Blood (Passive)** - If you are sacrificed for Blood of Mithras, then the kill will bypass all forms of protection.
**(Raging Axes): Anstreim&#39;s Paranoia (Night)** - All Killer-type classes will be show as members of this Cult for this night. - One use
[/details]



[details=&quot;Hand of Byzantium - Support&quot;]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Bard [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Pure Wits (Day)** - In the coming night you will be immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. - 3 uses
&gt;**Crescendo (Night)** - If your target is redirecting, occupying, or attacking, then they will bypass immunities during this night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Allegro (Night)** - For this night, your target will be healed from Bleeding and gain both occupation immunity, conversion immunity and night immunity. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Minstrel [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Allegro): Chants of Corax (Night)** - All members of the Cult will be seen as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - 2 uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]The Eccentric [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Magus/Steam Field (Day)** - You will deploy a M/S Field around yourself, granting you night immunity and conversion protection for the coming night. - One use
**Magus/Steam Golem (Night)** - Sends out a M/S Golem to guard your target, giving them night immunity and conversion protection for this night. - Infinite uses
**Magus/Steam Mirror (Night)** - You will send a M/S Mirror onto your target&amp;rsquo;s room, causing any player visiting them to visit themselves while also bypassing redirection immunity. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Lunatic [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Magus/Steam Golem): Mithras&#39; Automaton (Night)** - Causes a Cult members to be night immune and show as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks for the night. - Infinite uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Patron [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Emergency Funds (Day)** - If your target has a limited usage ability with zero uses, then you will silently give them an additional use. Cannot target the Emperor. - One use
**Patronage (Night)** - If your target uses a limited-usage ability this coming night, then they will not consume a use of it. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Auditor [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Emergency Funds): Generosity of Mithras (Day)** - Gives an additional charge for all of the Cult&#39;s limited use abilities. - One use

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Priestess [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Confession (Day)** - If a Hand of Byzantium-aligned player is executed this day, you will have caught their soul. Once a soul is caught you will not be able to use Bind Soul. - One use
**Bind Soul (Night)** - If your target player dies this night, then you will have caught their soul and you cannot use Bind Soul nor Confession again. - Infinite uses
**Forgiveness (Night)** - Sacrifices yourself to revive a soul you have caught via Confession or Bind Soul.
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple]The Pardoner [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Confession): Anstreim&#39;s Clemency (Day)** - If a Cult member is executed this day then they will flip as a class of the Ritualist&#39;s choice and you would have caught their soul. - One use
**(Bind Soul): Cycle of Mithras (Night)** - If a selected Cultist dies this night without being sacrificed by the Cult Leader, then you will have caught their soul. The Cult Leader can use this soul for a free use of Blood of Mithras. - Infinite uses
**(Forgiveness): Anstreim&#39;s Amnesty (Night)** - Ressurects a Cultist who&#39;ve received Anstreim&#39;s Clemency by sacrificing yourself and changing your flip to a Priestess. - One uses

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Squire [/color]
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
**Cowardice (Passive)** - Grants night immunity to you for the first three nights or until the Squire remembers a class, whichever comes first.
**Pick up the Mantle (Night)** - Allows you to select a non-unique Hand of Byzantium-aligned class from the Graveyard. You will change your class to the selected one by the end of the night. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple]The Page [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Cowardice): Initiation (Passive)** - You will be seen as a member of the Hand of Byzantium for the first three nights to faction checks.
**(Pick up the Mantle): Corax&#39;s Guidance (Night)** -You will train to become like another cultist and become the non-unique class of a target deceased Cult player and may also target a dead Cult Leader, if they were a different non-unique cult class before they were Cult Leader, to become the class they used to be. (If they used any Cult Points, you receive the powers they chose with them, and if they had left over Cult Points you may take abilities that they could have taken) - 1 use


&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Surgeon [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Self-Aid (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
**Coagulant (Day)** - You will grant a player immunity to bleeding. - One use
**Surgery (Night)** - Heals a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and curing any bleeding they were suffering from. - Infinite uses
**Miracle Touch (Night)** -  You will heal a player, giving them the effect of Surgery for this and the coming night. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple]The Plague Doctor [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Self-Aid): Wells of Blood (Passive)** - You will survive the first Blood of Mithras that hits you.
**(Coagulant): Cursed Blood (Day)** - Your target will not be able to be healed for the rest of the game. - One use
**(Miracle Touch): Blood Purity (Day)** - You will permanently make a player seem Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - One use
[/details]


[details=Hand of Byzantium - Offensive]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Druid [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Isolation (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt;**Wall of Thorns (Day)** - For the following night prevents non-Hand of Byzantium classes from visiting you and will Bleed them. The Bleeding will kill them if they are not healed the next night. -One use
&gt;**Glyph of Decay (Day)** - Selects a player and all healing and removal of Bleeding on them will fail for the next two nights. - 3 uses
&gt;**Glyph of Lethargy (Night)** - You will occupy a player for tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Glyph of Sloth (Night)** - You will occupy two players for tonight. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Forest Witch [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Wall of Thorns): Vines of Mithras (Night)** - For the following night prevents non-Cult classes from visiting the Ritualist and will Bleed them. The Bleeding will kill them if they are not healed the next night. -One use

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Overseer [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Overrule (Day)** - Causes your first target to select their second target if they use any day abilities today. - 2 uses
&gt;**Red Tape (Day)** - The Emperor&#39;s night actions will fail tonight. - 2 uses
**Order of Relocation (Night)** - Forces your first target&#39;s night action to be redirected to your second target. - Infinite uses
**Order of Exchange (Night)** - Select two players and force them to target each other. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Bureaucrat [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Sentinel [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Alertness (Day)** - Grants immunity to occupation and to target changing the coming night. - 3 uses
**Detainment (Night)** - Silently removes all of the passives and night immunity from your target. The Detainment will also last until the end of the next night except when it comes to removing Royal Blood, which lasts two days. - Infinite uses
**Curfew (Night)** - Occupies your target if they attempts to attack or convert a player. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Infiltrator [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Curfew): Aid of Corax (Night)** - Causes all night actions on their target to succeed. - 2 uses


&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Warden [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Isolate (Day)** - Prevents your target from using Day Abilities. - 2 uses
**Incarcerate (Night)** - Prevents your target from visiting tomorrow while also preventing visits to them. - Infinite uses
**Divest and Removal (Night)** - Removes all limited-use abilities charges from your target. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Torturer [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**Isolate (Day)**
**Incarcerate (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(**Divest and Removal**): Offerings to Mithras (Night)** - Removes all limited-use abilities charges from their target and they will bleed in the middle of the coming day. - One use.
[/details]



[details=Unseen and Converts]
&gt;# [color = purple] The Arcanist [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Social [/color]**
**Arcane Focus (Passive)** - You are immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Illusion (Night)** - Choose a class and sets a Sigil on another Unseen player and they will show up as the chosen class to any Investigative roles that visits them. The Sigil is destroyed once the target is visited by an Investigative, requiring them to be recast. - Infinite uses
**Sigil of Madness (Night)** - Puts a Sigil of Madness on a player, permanently giving them a Mind Warp effect until you die. - 1 use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Archivist [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Social [/color]**
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only one class with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
**Concealed Access (Passive)** - Allows all Unseen members to read the logs on the public log network. Can also use both day abilities during the same day and both night abilities on the same night.
**Prosecutor&#39;s  Notes (Day)** - Allows the Unseen to gain a log on the Arbiter&#39;s posts in his chat. - 3 uses
**Archive (Day)** - Invites a player to the log network. The player must accept before joining and can choose to leave at anytime. Can only invite two players per day. - Infinite uses
**Revoke (Night)** - Removes a player from the log network. - Infinite uses
**Censorship (Night)** - Deletes a target&amp;rsquo;s logs if they die the same night. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Assassin [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Killer [/color]**
**Hidden Blade (Day)** - Cut your target, causing them to bleed. They will bleed and die in two nights if not healed. - 3 uses (shared)
**Distract (Day)** - Distract a player, rendering them unable to any day abilities for the rest of the day. - 1 use
**Assassinate (Night)** - Kill a player. - Infinite uses
**2-for-1 (Night)** - Kill two target players. - 1 use (shared)
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Auditor [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Offensive [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Black Market (Passive)** - Upon becoming the Assassin, you will gain one additional use of 2-for-1 and two additional uses of Nightshade Poison.
**Audit (Night)** - Checks if your target has the Royal Blood passive. If they have it then the target will not be able to step up during the Royalty phase while the Auditor is alive. - Infinite uses
**Confiscate (Night)** - If the target has any abilities with finite usage, then you will remove one usage from each of their abilities. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Baronet [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Gerissen (Passive)** - If you become the Emperor, then you will gain an additional use of Assassin&#39;s Brotherhood. 
**Vom Tach (Night)** - Deflects any incoming attack against all members of the Unseen and kills the attacker. - Three uses
**Missgunst (Night)** - Removes Royal Blood from a target for the remainder of the game. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Blasphemer [/color]:shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Social [/color]**
&gt;**Incantations (Passive)** - You may speak with the dead during the night.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Heretical Decree (Day)** - For the lynch today all players will be lynched at L-2. - One use
&gt;**Black Mercy (Night)** - Selects a dead Hand of Byzantium-aligned player and forces them to use their primary night action on a living one. Cannot be used on Killer classes. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Spiritual Merge (Night)** - Binds a dead player to you, allowing them to speak while dead for as long as you are alive, but they will be removed from dead chat. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Bureaucrat [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Overrule (Day)** - Causes your first target to select their second target if they use any day abilities today. - 2 uses
&gt;**Red Tape (Day)** - The Emperor&#39;s night actions will fail tonight. - 2 uses
**Order of Relocation (Night)** - Forces your first target&#39;s night action to be redirected to your second target. - Infinite uses
**Order of Exchange (Night)** - Select two players and force them to target each other. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Chancellor [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Investigative [/color]**
**Kingmaker (Passive)** - Your vote during Emperor elections silently counts as three votes.
**Forged Documents (Day)** - The Chancellor grants the Royal Blood passive to a member of the Unseen. - One use
**Overthrow (Day)** - If the Emperor at L-3, then the Chancellor can force the court to execution them. - One use
**Trace Bloodline (Night)** - Informs you whether your target has Royal Blood or not and their precise class if they do. - Infinite uses
**Stigmatize (Night)** - Removes Royal Blood from your target for two nights. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Exiled [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Social [/color]**
&gt;**Unseen Traditions (Passive)** - You will always be seen as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Letter with no Sender (Day)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Cryptic Communications (Night)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player and they will be able to post a reply. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Influence of the Black Rose (Night)** - Prevents another Unseen-aligned player from being voted tomorrow. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Fanatic [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Killer [/color]**
**Piety (Day)** - The Fanatic will be shown as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks if investigated the coming night. - 3 uses
**Martyrdom (Day)** - If a player is executed this day, the Fanatic can choose to sacrifice themselves in order to stop the execution and save the accused played while also bleeding their first accuser. - 1 use
**Malleus Maleficarum (Night)** - Bleeds any player that attempts to visit your target tonight. - 3 uses
**Regicide (Night)** - Attacks and kills the King while bypassing all forms of healing and immunities. Regicide will also kill the Fanatic the same night. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Forest Witch [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Offensive [/color]**
**Isolation (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
**Nightshade Curse (Day)** - Selects a player and for the next two nights they will not be able to be healed. - 2 uses
**Wall of Roots (Day)** - Causes all visits on the target to be prevented the following night. - 1 use
&gt;**Curse of Lethargy (Night)** - You will occupy a player for tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Curse of Sloth (Night)** - You will occupy two players for tonight. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Infiltrator [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Offensive [/color]**
**Alert (Passive)** - Grants you immunity to occupation at night and to target changing.
**Tamper (Day)** - Any day ability your target uses will be redirected to themselves. - 2 uses
**Detainment (Night)** - Silently removes all of the passives and night immunity from your target. The Detainment will also last until the end of the next night except when it comes to removing Royal Blood, which lasts two days. - Infinite uses
**Off-Limits (Night)** - Puts a barrier around their Mastermind or Assassin, causing the next Hand of Byzantium-aligned investigative role to automatically be prevented if they try to visit them. You will be informed when the barrier activates. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Judge [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Social [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only one class with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
**Judicial Decree (Day)** - Resets the votes, allowing only you and your target to be put on trial for today. - 2 uses
**Judicial Conspiracy (Day)** - If your Mastermind is executed today then you will take their place. - One use
**Disenfranchise (Night)** - Reduces the amount of votes required to execute a player by one. - Infinite uses
**Usurp (Night)** - Kills the Emperor and automatically takes their place, becoming a Corrupt Emperor. Cannot be used until the third night. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Lunatic [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Offensive [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Magus/Steam Pulse (Day)** - Release a M/S Pulse around a chosen member of the Unseen, causing all players who visit them to be prevented from visited and occupied for the next night. - One use
**Magus/Steam Irradiator (Night)** - Sends out a M/S Irradiator to a target, preventing any healing on them this night. Cannot be used on the same target twice in a row. - Infinite uses
**Magus/Steam Explosive (Night)** - For the night, the Assassin will kill all players who visit their target in addition to their target themselves. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Marauder [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Offensive [/color]**
**Carnage (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation, death at night, and will counterattack against attackers. This passive is lost once you are promoted to an Assassin.
**Aura of Dread (Day)** - All non-Killer roles will be prevented from visiting the Marauder this coming night. - One use
**Boast (Night)** - Redirects the target player to yourself - Infinite uses
**Glare (Night)** - Occupies a player for the night. If your target is successfully occupied and is also attacked the same night then they cannot be healed and their night immunity will be bypassed. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Marchioness [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**The Woman Behind the Man (Passive)** - You will appear as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks and will be promoted straight to Mastermind if the Mastermind dies, regardless of when they die or if the Assassin is still alive. This passive is not lost when you are promoted to an Assassin, only when you become the Mastermind.
**VIP List (Day)** - By the end of the next night you will know which players visited the Mastermind that night. - 3 uses
**Social Links (Night)**  - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets’ class type groupings match. Groups are Special/Investigative, Social/Support, and Killer/Offensive. You will receive either no match if they are from different groups, a good match if they are in the same group, and a perfect match if they are the same class type. - Infinite uses
**Night Waltz (Night)** - Removes the cool-down on the Mastermind&#39;s Convert the next time they successfully convert a player. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Mastermind [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Special [/color]**
**Can&amp;rsquo;t Touch This (Passive)** - Immune to death at night, occupation and target changing. Players who attempt to occupy you or change your target will believe it succeeded. Additionally, you will know who you would&amp;rsquo;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.
**Lurking Presence (Passive)** - If you die, then the starting Assassin will take your place. You appear as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks.
**Shadowy Presence (Day)** - Selects what class type you will be shown as to investigators and whether you have Royal Blood or not. Can be used alongside Foresight. - Infinite uses
**Foresight (Day)** - Determine a player&amp;rsquo;s converted class by the end of the day if they can be converted. - 4 uses
**Convert (Night)** - Change target player into the Unseen version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown
**Dirty Work (Night)** - If there are no more Unseen members left, you can become The Assassin and you will use Assassinate on your target. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Minstrel [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Support [/color]**
**Silvertongue (Passive)** - The Minstrel will appear as Hand of Byzantium for faction checks.
**Pure Wits (Day)** - In the coming night you will be immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. - 3 uses
**Ballad (Night)** - Select an Unseen player and for this night and they will be shown as Hand of Byzantium for faction checks. - Infinite uses
**Crescendo (Night)** - If your target is redirecting, occupying, or attacking, then their night actions will be guaranteed to succeed this night. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Page [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Support [/color]**
**Innocent Youth (Passive)** - Causes you to appear as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks until they remember a class.
**Ascending Villain (Night)** - Allows you to select a Hand of Byzantium-aligned class from the Graveyard. The Page in turn will become their Unseen equivalent by the end of the night. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Pardoner [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Support [/color]**
**Patience (Passive)** - While an Unseen player&#39;s soul is caught, then no promotions will happen as the player in limbo will be still considered alive.
**Amnesty (Day)** - Selects an Unseen player and if they are executed during the day then they will flip a class of your choosing and you will catch their soul. Succesful usage of this will lock Reincarnation. - 1 uses
**Reincarnation (Night)** - Selects an Unseen player. If the targeted player dies this night, then they will flip a class chosen by you and you will catch their soul. Succesful use of this will lock Amnesty and Reincarnation. - Infinite uses
**Indulgence (Night)** - Sacrifices yourself, flipping yourself as a Priestess, and revives your caught soul. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Plague Doctor [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Support [/color]**
&gt;**Self-Aid (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
**Hemophilia (Day)** - Causes a player to be unable to receive healing for the rest of the match. - One use
**Herbal Medicine (Night)** - Heals a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and curing any poison and bleeding they were suffering from. - Infinite uses
**Quarantine (Night)** -  Permantly causes an Unseen-aligned player to be seen as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Sibyl [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
**Arithmancy (Day)** - Informs you the precise number of Neutrals, Unseen, and Hand of Byzantium-aligned players are still alive by the beginning of the coming night. Does not take the Emperor&#39;s alignment into account. - 2 uses
**Fated Deck (Night)** - Grants an additional charge of Major Arcana. - Infinite uses
**Major Arcana (Night)** - Select three players. By the end of the night you will learn all of their class types. - 0 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Stalker [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Tracking (Day)** - You will learn if your target left their room last night. - 2 uses
&gt;**Eavesdrop (Day)** - You will learn who is invited to the Imperial Chat at the start of the night. - 2 uses
&gt;**Vigilant Stalking (Night)** - You will learn who your target visits along with who visits them this night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Pinpoint (Night)** - You will learn who visits the Arbiter and who will be visited by them tonight. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Taxman [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
**Precise Details (Passive)** - At the beginning of the night, you will be told how many day abilities and which abilities were used.
**Avarice (Day)** - Selects a player during the day. You will be notified if they have used any Day abilities this day and which abilities were used. - 3 uses
**Inventory (Night)** - Selects a player and you will be informed of the total number of uses they have for both their night abilities combined. Abilities with unlimited usage count as zero. - Infinite uses
**Confiscate (Night)** - If the target has any abilities with finite usage, then you will remove one usage from each of their abilities. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Torturer [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Solitary Confinement (Day)** - Prevents your target from using Day Abilities. - Infinite uses
**Incarcerate (Night)** - Prevents your target from visiting tomorrow while also preventing visits to them. - Infinite uses
**Enhanced Interrogation (Night)** - Removes all limited-use abilities charges from your target and they will bleed in the middle of the coming day. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*


&gt;# [color = purple]  The Undertaker [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Social [/color]**
**Embalm (Day)** - If a player is executed, then they will flip a class of your choosing. Usable during trials. - One use.
**Desecrate (Night)** - If the targeted player dies at night, then they will flip a class of your choosing. - Infinite uses
**Grave Robbing (Night)** - If the targeted player dies at night, then their logs will appear blank. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/details]


[details=&quot;Cult and Converts&quot;]
&gt; # [color=darkred]The Apostle[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;[color=darkred] **Cult Social**[/color]
&gt; **Eminence of Mithras (Day)**  - At the end of the day, you will learn who voted for whom during today’s king election. - 2 uses
&gt; **Influence of Corax (Night)**  - In the coming day your target will require one less vote to be executed. - 2 uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Cult Leader[/color]  :crossed_swords: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Special**[/color]
&gt; **Train (Passive)**  - At any point before the start of the first night, you may message the GM and choose the Cult alts that the Cult class that spawned with you will receive, based on a non-unique class they can be converted from. If you do not choose the Cult alts, they will receive a random valid set.
&gt; **Fanaticism (Passive)**  - You are immune to death at night until you successfully convert a player, where upon this passive is disabled. (Starting Cult Leader only)
&gt; **Disguise (Day)**  - If the target player dies tonight, they will appear as a class of your choice. - 3 uses
&gt; **Rupture (Day)**  - Cause a player to bleed. They will bleed and die in two nights if not healed. - 3 uses (shared)
&gt; **Brainwash (Night)**  - Change target player into the Cult version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown
&gt; **Blood of Mithras (Night)**  - Kill a Cult player and a non-Cult player. The first two uses of this will not kill the cult player. - Infinite uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Invoker[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Offensive**[/color]
&gt; **Fanatic (Passive)**  - Immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt; **Bewilder (Day)**  - Target player uses a day ability on themselves. - 1 use
&gt; **Strings of Corax (Night)**  - Control a player into targeting another. - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Ritualist[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Support**[/color]
&gt; **Will of Mithras (Day)**  - Make a Cult Member appear as selected BD class to investigations. - 1 use
&gt; **Strength Of Corax (Night)**  - The Cult Leader’s Blood of Mithras will bypass night immunity tonight. - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Seeker[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Investigative**[/color]
&gt; **Expose (Day)**  - Reveal who the Arbiter entrusted at the start of the night. - 1 use
&gt; **Gaze (Night)**  - Learn a player’s class type. - 2 uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/details]

# Changes from Normal HoB.
* There will be a lynch on the first day and it will last 72 hours rather than 24.
* The conversion cooldown has been increased from one day to two days to balance the fact that both factions are present.
* The Mastermind and the Cult Leader will only be able to convert starting the second night to compensate for their additional starting member.
* If both factions attempt to convert the same player, the one with less members will gain the convert.
* In the above case that both factions have the same amount of members, the Cult will gain the convert.
* The Random Unseen can also be promoted to Mastermind.
* The limit of classes with Prestige spawning is 3 rather than 2.
* To accomodate the higher number of players the Unseen cap will be raised to 4 and the Cult cap will be raised to 5. Both factions will start with 3 players each.
* The Priestess and the Saint will not roll this match nor will the Pardoner or Blasphemer roll for the Random Unseen slot. Starting Ritualists cannot select the Priestess alts.
* The Eccentric and the Bard gained some form of conversion protection in their abilities.
* The Apostle has been reworked for this SFoL in order to remove all forms of dead interaction.
* The Arbiter got completely re-vamped in order to fit in with this game mode.
# Rolelist

**[color = grey]The Emperor[/color] (60% [color = goldenrod]Righteous[/color]/20% [color = purple]Corrupt[/color]/20% [color = darkred]Devout[/color]**)
**[color = purple]The Mastermind[/color]**
**[color = purple]The Assassin[/color]**
**[color = purple]Random Unseen[/color]**
**[color = darkred]The Cult Leader[/color]**
**[color = darkred]Random Cultist[/color]**
**[color = darkred]Random Cultist[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]The Arbiter[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
# Players (26/28)

1. Geyde
2. ~~MathBlade~~ - Killed N2  - [color=darkred]**The Invoker**[/color]
3. DatBird
4. ~~HTM~~ - Lynched D1 - [color=darkred]**The Ritualist**[/color]
5. Fireslol
6. WazzaAzza
7. Priestess
8. ~~Icibalus~~ - Lynched D3 - [color=darkred]**The Cult Leader**[/color]
9. Possessed
10. H_Hjasik
11. Meteoro
12. Sam17z
13. Soulshade55r
14. ~~Firekitten~~ - Killed N2  - [color=purple]**The Judge**[/color]
15. Blizer
16. Isaac_Gonzales
17. PoisonedSquid
18. Shurian
19. Magnus
20. Marcus_Doodalee :crown: 
21. Margaret
22. SweetyCake
23. PKR
24. Twil1ight
25. Maxwell
26. Bluestorm
27. Solic
28. ~~James~~ - Killed N1 - [color=goldenrod]**The Arbiter**[/color]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 06:32:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum of Lies</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Not much good will come from keeping this topic open I fear.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9853">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9853</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 06:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9853</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9852">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9852</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9852</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>This is the exact kind of shit attitude on why I fucking canned the game in the first place, Sam.</h1>
<h1>I canned all my games here as I am fucking tired of being treated like shit by people despite the sheer amount of work that I put into creating amd hosting my setups.</h1>
<h1>Meanwhile you get people like Hjasik and Isaac who do jack squat for the forums and then mass sign-up for games and just troll them non-stop and spam axolotl pictures while calling people noobs, and you know what I got for not tolerating that bullshit?</h1>
<h1>This. I got removed from several matches and then fucking treated like a little bitch and a drama queen because I was up to here with their shit and now I’m fucking villified by the whole forums regardless of the sheer amount of work that I’ve been doing to help this FM community grow in Marl and Ashe’s absences.</h1>
<h1>Do you know how it fucking feels to be betrayed like this? I do. And I don’t fucking care about anyone in this place except Math anymore. I was fucking wrong in believing you were my friends. I was fucking wrong in wanting to help you all grow and improve in FM. I was fucking wrong in spending my time and hard work designing unique setups for you all to enjoy.</h1>
<h1>I don’t fucking care what you all think of me right now. I’m goddamn tired of being disrespected like this anymore. You all thought that you could take advantage of me, and you were right for some time. Really, goodbye and enjoy your next few FMs without me.</h1>
<h1>-Alice</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9851">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9851</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 06:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9851</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>For the record, Sam17z is uninformed of any sensitive game information.</h1>
<p>Quit talking about ongoing games, regardless of how you wish to spin it. Don’t ruin the enjoyment left in that game just because you’re pissed at Alice, regardless of how understandable that is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9850">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9850</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 05:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9850</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Soulshade55r" data-post="9848" data-topic="76799">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/soulshade55r/40/29692_2.png" class="avatar"> Soulshade55r:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>just because I don’t like using mobile to use the site the scrolling is hard to read anything I can’t really go to notepad and take notes ect.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree, mobile has been getting harder to use with every site update</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9849">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9849</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 03:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9849</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>in all seriousness I’m probably not joining a fm for a while just because I don’t like using mobile to use the site the scrolling is hard to read anything I can’t really go to notepad and take notes ect.</p>
<p>once I get a new laptop I’ll try it out but I feel like its just been a stuggle to play fm right now</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9848">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9848</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 01:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9848</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>my job here is done.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9847">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9847</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 01:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9847</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PoisonedSquid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought I was Marl’s son<br>
<s>I know I’m a girl, but ehhhhh</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9846">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9846</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9846</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve already said it.<br>
I shouldn’t need to again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9845">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9845</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9845</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shurian" data-post="9843" data-topic="76799">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shurian/40/20666_2.png" class="avatar"> Shurian:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nephew!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“It’s me Denise!”</p>
<h1>“Oh I mean Denephew”</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9844">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9844</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9844</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nephew! I have come to bargain for your daughter’s words<br>
That if she says “Die” to me I’ll be like a Motoyasu in heaven</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9843">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9843</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9843</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hai Uncle Shuri OwO</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9842">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9842</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9842</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But I am Marl’s brother<br>
I have come to bargain</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9841">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9841</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9841</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Marg-sama and Geyde-san are my son and daughter in law</p>
<p>b e g o n e</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9840">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9840</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9840</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Margaret never tells me to die!<br>
How could you still my Marg-san from me?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9839">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9839</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9839</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…</p>
<p>Die.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9838">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9838</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9838</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a> pls talk to your waifu</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9837">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9837</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9837</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yes <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9836">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9836</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9836</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Also did you magus steam mirror icibalus</em></p>
<p>because that would be LMAO</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9835">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9835</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9835</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Eccentric?</em> That’s a little strange</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9834">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9834</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9834</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eccentric</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9833">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9833</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9833</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/margaret">@Margaret</a> what were you mdear</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9832">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9832</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9832</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bazingaboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do not get mad <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/robot.png?v=9" title=":robot:" class="emoji" alt=":robot:"> Do not criticze others for any reason ever <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/robot.png?v=9" title=":robot:" class="emoji" alt=":robot:"> Beep boop beep boop</p>
<p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":joy:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9831">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9831</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9831</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t care about the rules for other forums. I care about this one</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9830">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9830</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 23:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9830</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Go to any other forum mafia site and look at their codes of conduct or rules and it should have a note about that</p>
<p>Check mafiascum or mafia universe for reference.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9829">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799/9829</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 23:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76799-9829</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-49-triple-threat-hand-of-byzantium-canned/76799.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 49: Triple Threat: Hand of Byzantium - Canned</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
