<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879</link>
    <description>I love playing Neutral Killers. You are doomed most of the time, but it&#39;s just such a great experience to play as.

Anyways, here are my theories on what you can do to win more.

# General

As a Neutral Killer, you must survive. Unlike the Unseen or the Cult, you cannot afford to lose a single member. You are the only person on your team, and if you die you lose. So claiming is key.

Unfortunately there aren&#39;t many good claims. In general, Knight and Court Wizard claims are distrusted, since they are common evil claims. I find that generally Sheriff or Paladin is a safer claim, since they are easy to fake, but less mistrusted. The problem is you have to know what faction is present, you generally have to look for signs of one of the factions. Luckily you can easily switch claims if you need to. Of course, if you are jailed night one, you can&#39;t use this, without a 50/50 chance of being screwed.

# Possessor

My favorite class by far. You have a unique advantage as Possessor, and that&#39;s the fact your Puppet Strings can fake Maid Spy. Unfortunately, if you claim Noble and are asked to use Political Pressure, you are screwed. Luckily, I find most people don&#39;t do that.

That&#39;s not the only thing, though. Possess allows you to jump into the bodies of confirmed people, which means you don&#39;t have to claim and are in a safe place. The downside, however is the fact that the Psychic will be told who you are, if you still live. So you should consider chain jumping, hoping to jump into the Psychic. Conveniently, this can also heal you of poison/bleeding.

You also don&#39;t have to worry about Knights, as the Knight will kill who you are controlling. If you do this twice, you can even kill the Knight.

Do not possess the King, as your lack of the Royal Finger is glaringly obvious.

# Reaper

Reaper lacks the advantages the Possessor has, but luckily he makes up for it.

Your souls are convenient for a couple reasons: One, you are immune to everything. You can&#39;t die of poison, bleeding, or even a King&#39;s execution (unless you run out).

In addition, they can be used to power useful abilities. Chill can lock away information, although it confirms your existence and gives them access to the dead. Still, it&#39;s also useful to avoid getting executed, as it stops votes as well. It does **not** stop day abilities, however, like the Royal Finger.

Gather Darkness can help you take out the King or the Mastermind.

Reaping also delays information getting out, so it&#39;s great to use on investigators.

# Sorcerer

Remember, the Unseen/Cult is your friend. If you ever get poisoned or bled by them, do **not** mention it, as it can signal them who you really are.

If you want to take this a step further, draft your death note like this.

&gt; Assassin, you poisoned me day three. I am the Sorcerer, so contact me.

Always kill the Inquisitor. They are your biggest enemy, and if you kill them, you are stronger than any other Neutral Killer, as you have their powers with the Unseen/Cult on your side. The extra night it takes to kill them is well worth the cost.

Use Magic Circle on confirmed Blue Dragon, such as the Prince, as this can clear out pesky protectors such as the Physician and Knight.

# Psycho King

If you managed to crown yourself, the Blue Dragon trust you and you can run rampant. No advice needed here.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 22:01:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice. Actually the first time I played this it didn’t work, but I did suspect it would be awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 22:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NightX" data-post="1" data-topic="47879">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nightx/40/3104_2.png" class="avatar"> NightX:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Assassin, you poisoned me day three. I am the Sorcerer, so contact me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is genius, just got my first sorc win in weeks thanks to this tip lol, I was a fake butler claim and got the cult to “confirm” my fake wines.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 21:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Generally, I see people ask the targets if they were occupied. If you I saw someone claim Butler, with no one to support the claim, that would be an instant red flag for me.</p>
<p>It is just simply impossible to claim an Offensive class without being converted from one, or being one.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 19:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean after you kill all the royals a butler claim is a solid claim to pass as king! I mean so how you do it is you say you occupy the people that died the night before or 2 nights before and in your will mix that up with a person being jailed and saying prevented because the alive BD do not know whether or not you actually occupied the dead person or the person jailed. This is usually my claim as NK.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 19:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Uh… No. People know when they are occupied, and generally people will notice when there is no one else to support their claim.</p>
<p>Also, how does a Butler claim help you become King?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 18:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For new players, I think when you are a neutral killer the best claim is to claim butler and choose dead and jailed people to put in your will. Additionally if you are able to kill the king a butler claim may allow you to become psycho king.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 18:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>np</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 20:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ohhh yeah i forgot thanks</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 20:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NightX" data-post="1" data-topic="47879">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nightx/40/3104_2.png" class="avatar"> NightX:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Conveniently, this can also heal you of poison/bleeding.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I put it on the post about jumping.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 18:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorc is poision and bleed immune</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 18:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>If you ever get poisoned or bled by them, do not mention it, as it can signal them who you really are.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Then aren’t you going to die?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 18:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>might also be worth pointing out in possessor. Poisons/bleeds do not follow you if you jump. So if you don’t think the BD is going to heal you (because either you claimed phys or alc, or you think there may not be a phys or alc to save you), you can always jump out of the poison/bleed. That it can be worth it to ask for a heal if you think there is a phys/alc. Healers want to think they are doing good… so them succesfully saving you will make them more hesitant to suspect that you are evil (plus it proves you aren’t the unseen/cult that would have inflicted said injury)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 17:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Guide to Neutral Killers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love playing Neutral Killers. You are doomed most of the time, but it’s just such a great experience to play as.</p>
<p>Anyways, here are my theories on what you can do to win more.</p>
<h1>General</h1>
<p>As a Neutral Killer, you must survive. Unlike the Unseen or the Cult, you cannot afford to lose a single member. You are the only person on your team, and if you die you lose. So claiming is key.</p>
<p>Unfortunately there aren’t many good claims. In general, Knight and Court Wizard claims are distrusted, since they are common evil claims. I find that generally Sheriff or Paladin is a safer claim, since they are easy to fake, but less mistrusted. The problem is you have to know what faction is present, you generally have to look for signs of one of the factions. Luckily you can easily switch claims if you need to. Of course, if you are jailed night one, you can’t use this, without a 50/50 chance of being screwed.</p>
<h1>Possessor</h1>
<p>My favorite class by far. You have a unique advantage as Possessor, and that’s the fact your Puppet Strings can fake Maid Spy. Unfortunately, if you claim Noble and are asked to use Political Pressure, you are screwed. Luckily, I find most people don’t do that.</p>
<p>That’s not the only thing, though. Possess allows you to jump into the bodies of confirmed people, which means you don’t have to claim and are in a safe place. The downside, however is the fact that the Psychic will be told who you are, if you still live. So you should consider chain jumping, hoping to jump into the Psychic. Conveniently, this can also heal you of poison/bleeding.</p>
<p>You also don’t have to worry about Knights, as the Knight will kill who you are controlling. If you do this twice, you can even kill the Knight.</p>
<p>Do not possess the King, as your lack of the Royal Finger is glaringly obvious.</p>
<h1>Reaper</h1>
<p>Reaper lacks the advantages the Possessor has, but luckily he makes up for it.</p>
<p>Your souls are convenient for a couple reasons: One, you are immune to everything. You can’t die of poison, bleeding, or even a King’s execution (unless you run out).</p>
<p>In addition, they can be used to power useful abilities. Chill can lock away information, although it confirms your existence and gives them access to the dead. Still, it’s also useful to avoid getting executed, as it stops votes as well. It does <strong>not</strong> stop day abilities, however, like the Royal Finger.</p>
<p>Gather Darkness can help you take out the King or the Mastermind.</p>
<p>Reaping also delays information getting out, so it’s great to use on investigators.</p>
<h1>Sorcerer</h1>
<p>Remember, the Unseen/Cult is your friend. If you ever get poisoned or bled by them, do <strong>not</strong> mention it, as it can signal them who you really are.</p>
<p>If you want to take this a step further, draft your death note like this.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Assassin, you poisoned me day three. I am the Sorcerer, so contact me.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Always kill the Inquisitor. They are your biggest enemy, and if you kill them, you are stronger than any other Neutral Killer, as you have their powers with the Unseen/Cult on your side. The extra night it takes to kill them is well worth the cost.</p>
<p>Use Magic Circle on confirmed Blue Dragon, such as the Prince, as this can clear out pesky protectors such as the Physician and Knight.</p>
<h1>Psycho King</h1>
<p>If you managed to crown yourself, the Blue Dragon trust you and you can run rampant. No advice needed here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 02:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47879-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-guide-to-neutral-killers/47879.rss">My Guide to Neutral Killers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
