<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[class suggestion] divine summoner (cult)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-divine-summoner-cult/8932</link>
    <description>
Name- Divine Summoner

Alignment/type-Cult/special/unique

[small chance to spawn with cult leader and ritualist]

Passive 1- Pure Evil- Divine summoner will always appear as cult to investigative abilities (mind warp etc doesn&#39;t conceal him) 

Passive 2-Summoning energy- Before using &quot;Summon Mithras&quot; ability, the cult leader must have sacrificed 1 ritualist, 1 invoker, 1 apostle, and 1 seeker to Mithras. 

Day ability 1-Telepathy- the targets next whisper will be redirected to a random player. [2 charges]


Night ability 1- Soul Gaze- see a player&#39;s class. Targets that are immune to conversion are immune to this ability as well.[3 charges]

Night ability 2-Summon Mithras- summon Mithras into the castle to unleash his rage on all remaining blue dragon, killing them instantly. 

Win requirements- Cult win


I know summon Mithras is a game ending crazy OP ability. But in order to us it, the cult leader has to at some point sacrifice the ritualist, and convert to get all 3 other classes into the cult and sacrifice one of each of them too. And also he has to not get found by BD for however long that takes to happen, and he always appears as cult so it&#39;s not terribly hard to find him. There is only a chance he would spawn in game so this wouldn&#39;t be every cult game. But if he does spawn by chance, it would make cult games so exciting. If somebody sees a whisper getting deflected, or notices different cult classes getting sacrificed, they would assume there is a divine summoner and the race is on to find him! 

I know this would change cult games a lot and it&#39;d be a big change, but I think the character is balanced and the concept is cool! 



Since 3 cult members would be spawning at the beginning, divine summoner could only be used in 16 player games.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 20:43:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-divine-summoner-cult/8932.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[class suggestion] divine summoner (cult)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Name- Divine Summoner</p>
<p>Alignment/type-Cult/special/unique</p>
<p>[small chance to spawn with cult leader and ritualist]</p>
<p>Passive 1- Pure Evil- Divine summoner will always appear as cult to investigative abilities (mind warp etc doesn’t conceal him)</p>
<p>Passive 2-Summoning energy- Before using “Summon Mithras” ability, the cult leader must have sacrificed 1 ritualist, 1 invoker, 1 apostle, and 1 seeker to Mithras.</p>
<p>Day ability 1-Telepathy- the targets next whisper will be redirected to a random player. [2 charges]</p>
<p>Night ability 1- Soul Gaze- see a player’s class. Targets that are immune to conversion are immune to this ability as well.[3 charges]</p>
<p>Night ability 2-Summon Mithras- summon Mithras into the castle to unleash his rage on all remaining blue dragon, killing them instantly.</p>
<p>Win requirements- Cult win</p>
<p>I know summon Mithras is a game ending crazy OP ability. But in order to us it, the cult leader has to at some point sacrifice the ritualist, and convert to get all 3 other classes into the cult and sacrifice one of each of them too. And also he has to not get found by BD for however long that takes to happen, and he always appears as cult so it’s not terribly hard to find him. There is only a chance he would spawn in game so this wouldn’t be every cult game. But if he does spawn by chance, it would make cult games so exciting. If somebody sees a whisper getting deflected, or notices different cult classes getting sacrificed, they would assume there is a divine summoner and the race is on to find him!</p>
<p>I know this would change cult games a lot and it’d be a big change, but I think the character is balanced and the concept is cool!</p>
<p>Since 3 cult members would be spawning at the beginning, divine summoner could only be used in 16 player games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-divine-summoner-cult/8932/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-divine-summoner-cult/8932/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8932-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-divine-summoner-cult/8932.rss">[class suggestion] divine summoner (cult)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
