<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Brawler [BD Killer] and The Hellion [Unseen Offensive]</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578</link>
    <description>&gt; # **The Brawler**
&gt; **Blue Dragon Killer**
&gt; 
&gt; **Passive:**
&gt; **Tough Skin:** The first time you Brawl with someone that has a killing ability you will be immune to their counter, then lose this passive.
&gt; **Beat &#39;em Up:** Brawling an already crippled player will kill them instead.
&gt; 
&gt; **Day:**
&gt; **Pure Muscle (2 use):** If a person you Flexed on tries to attack you tonight, they will become crippled instead.
&gt; **Fight Dirty (2 use):** Throw sand into someone&#39;s eyes making them unable to attack anyone that night and preventing them from countering your Brawl.
&gt; 
&gt; **Night:**
&gt; **Flex (inf use):** Flex on that one hater. You will be death immune the next time they try to attack you. Gain 1 use of Brawl.
&gt; **Brawl (0 use):** Cripple a player making them unable to leave their room for two nights unless healed. They will fight back if they have a killing ability. (2 use maximum)

---

&gt; # **The Helion**
&gt; **Unseen Offensive**
&gt; 
&gt; **Passive:**
&gt; **Adrenaline Rush:** You are immune to occupation and redirection when using Yawp.
&gt; 
&gt; **Day:**
&gt; **Fight Dirty (2 use):** Throw sand into someone&#39;s eyes making them unable to attack anyone that night and preventing them from countering your Brawl.
&gt; 
&gt; **Night:**
&gt; **Yawp (2 use):** Occupy two players. You will be unable to use your abilities the next night.
&gt; **Brawl (2 use):** Cripple a player making them unable to leave their room for two nights unless healed. They will fight back if they have a killing ability.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Brawler [BD Killer] and The Hellion [Unseen Offensive]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Conduit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this is ok i guess, but its utility is a bit low:<br>
Tough Skin: Doesnt need this.<br>
Beat 'em Up: harder daddy<br>
Pure Muscle: Worse bear honestly.<br>
Fight Dirty: Seems to be the most useful, throw sand in knights faces.<br>
Flex: dab on the haters<br>
Brawl: I like this the most, you have to decide whether its best to occupy a person you sus, or if its too risky.</p>
<p>Helion is ok at best too.<br>
AR: Lololol non-occupy immune occupier lolool do that lololol<br>
Fight Dirty: Worse on the Helion then Brawler.<br>
Yawp: meh<br>
Brawl: quite op</p>
<p>Brawler is ok, with atleast having some nice “Brawl them or not” decisions, which make game more interesting.</p>
<p>I don’t know how I feel about Helion.<br>
The names for Brawler/Helion are kinda weird since they don’t really fit the medieval theme that ToL has. I’m kinda a sucker for medieval names so :&lt;). You can name it whatever you want tho.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83578-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578.rss">The Brawler [BD Killer] and The Hellion [Unseen Offensive]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Brawler [BD Killer] and The Hellion [Unseen Offensive]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1><strong>The Brawler</strong></h1>
<p><strong>Blue Dragon Killer</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive:</strong><br>
<strong>Tough Skin:</strong> The first time you Brawl with someone that has a killing ability you will be immune to their counter, then lose this passive.<br>
<strong>Beat 'em Up:</strong> Brawling an already crippled player will kill them instead.</p>
<p><strong>Day:</strong><br>
<strong>Pure Muscle (2 use):</strong> If a person you Flexed on tries to attack you tonight, they will become crippled instead.<br>
<strong>Fight Dirty (2 use):</strong> Throw sand into someone’s eyes making them unable to attack anyone that night and preventing them from countering your Brawl.</p>
<p><strong>Night:</strong><br>
<strong>Flex (inf use):</strong> Flex on that one hater. You will be death immune the next time they try to attack you. Gain 1 use of Brawl.<br>
<strong>Brawl (0 use):</strong> Cripple a player making them unable to leave their room for two nights unless healed. They will fight back if they have a killing ability. (2 use maximum)</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1><strong>The Helion</strong></h1>
<p><strong>Unseen Offensive</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive:</strong><br>
<strong>Adrenaline Rush:</strong> You are immune to occupation and redirection when using Yawp.</p>
<p><strong>Day:</strong><br>
<strong>Fight Dirty (2 use):</strong> Throw sand into someone’s eyes making them unable to attack anyone that night and preventing them from countering your Brawl.</p>
<p><strong>Night:</strong><br>
<strong>Yawp (2 use):</strong> Occupy two players. You will be unable to use your abilities the next night.<br>
<strong>Brawl (2 use):</strong> Cripple a player making them unable to leave their room for two nights unless healed. They will fight back if they have a killing ability.</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 19:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83578-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-brawler-bd-killer-and-the-hellion-unseen-offensive/83578.rss">The Brawler [BD Killer] and The Hellion [Unseen Offensive]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
