<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384</link>
    <description>This started as a Priest replacement, but I think it&#39;s too different, now.

----

**Bishop** (Blue Dragon) - A trusted member of the kingdom&#39;s church.

Passive:
**Tested Faith** - After the first five days, you can no longer be converted.

Day Ability:
**Consecrated Wine** - If your target would have selected a member of the Blue Dragon that night, they will instead be occupied. (4 uses.)

Night Ability 1:
**Confessional** - Find out if a target player has attacked another player during the current round. You will be notified &quot;PlayerName has committed the sin of murder!&quot; or &quot;PlayerName has confessed nothing.&quot; _This ability actually tells you what another player has tried to do so far in the current round!_ If they&#39;re a killing class that simply hasn&#39;t tried to kill yet, you won&#39;t know. Possessor really messes with this one, since the possessed person would be shown as a killer. (Unlimited use.)

Night Ability 2:
**Healing Prayer** - Protect your target from death that night, but only if they are Blue Dragon. (Also heals bleeding/poison.) (2 uses.)

----

Converts to...

----

**Harbinger** (Unseen) - A fallen holy man with God complex.

Passive:
**Martyrdom** - If you are executed by trial, the Assassin gains occupation immunity the following night.

Day Ability:
**Spoiled Wine** - If your target would have selected a member of the Unseen that night, they will instead be occupied. (4 uses.)

Night Ability 1:
**Condemnation** - Condemn a player, reducing the number of votes needed to put them on trial the next day. (Number could change depending on how many players are left. For example, reduces by 3 if 16 players live, reduces by 2 if 10 players live, reduces by 1 if 5 players live.) (2 uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**Inverted Prayer** - Protect your target from death that night, but only if they are not Blue Dragon. (Can heal Neutrals in addition to your own team mates - Does not heal bleeding/poison.) (2 uses.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 01:21:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thor_Odinson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel like Condemnation can be extremely easy to figure out by simply seeing how many votes are next to a person’s name.</p>
<p>Now all BD has to do is check to see if the accused has been condemned, and then they are automatically pardoned.</p>
<p>In my opinion, this ability needs some way of being discreet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 01:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33384-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384.rss">[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about “If you are Executed for Trial, 1 random person who did not accuse you will become Occupation Immune. People who pardoned have priority over abstainers.”</p>
<p>This could benefit Scum or BD, much like Hunter’s passive. It can kill a BD but also a Scum.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 18:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33384-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384.rss">[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like this one. The only thing I’m not keen on is “Martyrdom” - BD shouldn’t be punished for correctly hanging scum.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 13:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33384-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384.rss">[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This started as a Priest replacement, but I think it’s too different, now.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Bishop</strong> (Blue Dragon) - A trusted member of the kingdom’s church.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Tested Faith</strong> - After the first five days, you can no longer be converted.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Consecrated Wine</strong> - If your target would have selected a member of the Blue Dragon that night, they will instead be occupied. (4 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Confessional</strong> - Find out if a target player has attacked another player during the current round. You will be notified “PlayerName has committed the sin of murder!” or “PlayerName has confessed nothing.” <em>This ability actually tells you what another player has tried to do so far in the current round!</em> If they’re a killing class that simply hasn’t tried to kill yet, you won’t know. Possessor really messes with this one, since the possessed person would be shown as a killer. (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Healing Prayer</strong> - Protect your target from death that night, but only if they are Blue Dragon. (Also heals bleeding/poison.) (2 uses.)</p>
<hr>
<p>Converts to…</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Harbinger</strong> (Unseen) - A fallen holy man with God complex.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Martyrdom</strong> - If you are executed by trial, the Assassin gains occupation immunity the following night.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Spoiled Wine</strong> - If your target would have selected a member of the Unseen that night, they will instead be occupied. (4 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Condemnation</strong> - Condemn a player, reducing the number of votes needed to put them on trial the next day. (Number could change depending on how many players are left. For example, reduces by 3 if 16 players live, reduces by 2 if 10 players live, reduces by 1 if 5 players live.) (2 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Inverted Prayer</strong> - Protect your target from death that night, but only if they are not Blue Dragon. (Can heal Neutrals in addition to your own team mates - Does not heal bleeding/poison.) (2 uses.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 09:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33384-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-bishop-blue-dragon-converts-to-harbinger-unseen/33384.rss">[Class Suggestion] Bishop (Blue Dragon) converts to Harbinger (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
