<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167</link>
    <description>**Passive 1**: Why&#39;s the ink gone?
Players will be not notified for journal theft, it will be shown as &quot;He left no journal&quot; / &quot;She left no journal&quot; upon death.

**Passive 2**: I work in darkness to serve the light. 
The Thief is always in high alert during night phase, immune to occupy

**Day Ability 1**: (1 attempt power) Now you see me, now you don&#39;t.
The Thief will publicly escape with smoke bomb and forces to end day phase

**Night Ability 1**: (1-night cooldown) Dear Diary.
The Thief enter player&#39;s room and steal the journal, cannot gain one journal if target is prevented for visit.

**The Thief&#39;s Lore**: During the day on tavern somewhere in realm of Adiart, whispers has been told about royal castle is dealing with corruption within their ranks, however without proof of solid evidence that may be contained only in journals about their activities day and night, interest of acquiring the journals starts to perk up under anonymous black market begin to start posting bounty with promise of riches that will make any mercenary that need money to feed their family or other desires, can make them retire for the rest of their lives--the catch is, they need to get out of the royal castle alive and deliver the journals here let alone getting in is also the hard part. Men and woman for hire would appears to be losing interest in taking the job before returning taking their seats to drink away their past sorrows and troubled present, among the crowded customers there is one mysterious figure in cloak and cloth mask that hasn&#39;t taking off...it&#39;s eyes on the bounty that has been posted at the wooden pillar supporting the tavern&#39;s second floor, the mysterious figure stand up from the seat they occupied earlier is searching for one noble that is responsible for asking people in the tavern for hire that returned to his room upstairs, the mysterious figure has either get through crowded lower tables or pass the bar tables occupied with scum and villainy that cause trouble when ever feel like it and that happened quite a lot that even the bar maid is sexually assaulted recently by huge-build mercenary at age of 41 that has likely seen action in previous war against the realm since royal castle is united to fight against one common foe--the cult of Mithras that used to have thousands of followers and dozens of the leaders, 
but that&#39;s story of another time about the previous war. 

The mysterious figure would walk through the open spaces that has been presented without trying to bump into each other&#39;s shoulders, the movement is surprisingly fluid and smooth for the figure that has been only here for first time in this tavern and the customers by the lower tables didn&#39;t seem to get bothered at all, fewer mobs by the bar tables couldn&#39;t think but glare at the mysterious figure for acting up like this person owns the place, they tend to learn the figure a lesson soon. Upstairs appear to be guarded by the soldiers from the noble he hired not likely from the royal castle itself. The mysterious figure below observe when the bar maid walk up to the stairs as the guard on the left gestures with open palm towards the bar maid to halt, the right guard begin to speak up &quot;What ish yur bushness here -hic- pretty leydy?&quot; that appears to be drunk without question, the bar maid dismissively wave her free hand to make stench of alcohol coming out of guard&#39;s breath go away &quot;I am delivering the bread and blocks of cheese to the guests of far right room, shall you let me pass?&quot; The bar maid is tapping on her feet that notify she&#39;s in a hurry to delivering &quot;Urr um...the masterrr did nut order sucs -hic-&quot; The left guard clear his throat and look at the bar maid &quot;Sorry for this lad giving you grief, you can go pass delivering the food for someone else you have mentioned, we&#39;re making sure our noble is safe within his different room.&quot; The left guard make shuffle the open gap for the bar maid immediately walk through and take turn to the right, the right guard isn&#39;t looking down the stairs but forward the bar maid that has turned her back marching towards the room that has ordered the food, the left guard also turn around to give a bonk at the back of the right guard&#39;s head &quot;I am surprised you sod is even hired to do guard duty...&quot; The mysterious figure took his sweet time to climb on the wooden pillar as they grab the bounty paper with them, is now hanging on the edge of second floor that causes the chatting nearly die down while the guards by the stairs is too occupied to do their job. &quot;We are fortunate that we&#39;re standing at the very stairs and nobody can sneak past us to the hall by second left room wi..&quot; The mysterious figure nod themselves as the guard is talking to himself, they lift up to climb to the second floor and casually walk past the guards while the drunken right guard hasn&#39;t been recovered from the bonk yet receives rather a stomp from the bar maid&#39;s feet that has come out of the room not without change of appearance that she look more worked up than before, she walk past the other guard and climb down and the crowd below starting to laugh to notice there has been rips to her clothing, especially they look down.

-Knock Knock!- 

Softly bonking can be heard to other side of the room freezes the noble before looking towards the door &quot;Who goes there?&quot; Silence occurs by the door before the lock starting to click as metal pin tips coming out from the other side of lock for the noble to see, he reaches for the rapier as he stands ready to counter-strike the possible foe by the other side of the door. The mysterious figure hide it&#39;s metal pins they used for pick locking the door, reach for the bounty paper he grabbed by the pillar earlier, pushes the door softly without making the creaking too obvious for the guards it wasn&#39;t their man that opened the door, lean his free hand holding the bounty paper towards the gap for the noble to see. The noble is skeptical about the approach from the stranger &quot;What happened to my guards without knowing your presence?&quot; demanded the noble towards the door. The mysterious figure took no time to fully open the door just enough to get them through before shutting behind them. &quot;You need to hire guards that don&#39;t make them drunk easily or start accusing the drunk they forgot about the job&quot; as the ominous voice comes out from the lips of the mysterious figure in cloak do expose the green-colored eye contact towards the noble in envy expression &quot;They pose no issue for me, you can dissolve them from your services, they will sober soon after I am done talking to you about this job.&quot; said the mysterious figure ending their sentence, apparently they are voiced like a man. &quot;...these cheap idiots are still alive and they didn&#39;t saw you approaching to me...I gave them clear instructions to watch the stairs!&quot; nearly cause the noble to shout in self-destructing fashion. &quot;That cost you extra if you want to know my answer. However let&#39;s talk business instead.&quot; as the mysterious figure start to walk and pick a seat to sit while the noble is still pointing his rapier at the stranger if they pull anything they will regret &quot;What about this business, hmm? Are you really going to throw your life away for mere journals that I--&quot; &quot;...Black market.&quot; as the mysterious figure interrupted the noble that causes to scowl at the person &quot;Yes, black market can provide the payment of sixty gold coins for one journal.&quot; The silent broke the conversation between the employer and potential hired man before releasing soft laughter through the lips of the figure &quot;It is not even worth the coins to live in retirement if I come out alive and with the same amount of coins, you can get one week supplies with nothing but bread, whale soap, ink bottles, one fresh feather, pay the rest of the coins to the landlord that has to pay taxes to the royal family so I can scribe how poor my life is,&quot; the figure is not finished to speak by looks of it &quot;Judging by this, you get the bigger share for like sixty-six procent of the profit while I get thirty-three for this worthless trip while your pulse bag will be fat and happy.&quot; the words spoken from the mysterious figure didn&#39;t seem to convince the noble about the true motivation behind the bounty he&#39;s eagerly to take &quot;Take your best bet.&quot; said the noble with grimace expression on his face, before the figure dismissively wave his hand &quot;You want complete set of four journals so you can blackmail the royal family with hefty sum in return for evidence who the conspirators are that want Blue Dragon faction dead, even if it means the journals belong to conspirators themselves that misdirect to execute the innocent, and I won&#39;t be surprised you want the throne for yourself too.&quot; the mysterious figure glaring at the noble to imitate the same expression through their eyes that the noble wore earlier before, the noble slowly sheath his rapier back placed by his belt by his satisfaction &quot;That&#39;s right,&quot; said the noble before he takes a seat as well, close to the figure &quot;so here&#39;s the deal: You bring four journals and I will set up the price twenty times much as the original price being put, your procent as you have figured out will be thirty-three while I keep sixty-six procent.&quot; The noble take a good look towards the figure like he&#39;s playing game of poker cards, The Thief give deadpan expression towards the noble as he&#39;s not convinced with the price he&#39;s being offered &quot;triple the price even more by the black market and I&#39;d like to have forty procent of the profits and you have sixty procent, considered the risk of getting caught stealing the evidence...you also need to pay something extra from the black market I can put of good use, I want smoke bombs with your money as advancement pay for me.&quot; the noble perking his eyebrow towards The Thief &quot;But these cost like two-hundred-and-fifty gold coins--&quot;, but The Thief interrupts before the noble could finish &quot;Then bribe guards from the royal armory inside the Castle of Adiart itself and I take it from here, since you are invited as royal guest and is allowed to bring servants anyway, deal?&quot; as The Thief extend their hand towards the noble, the expressions tensed between both beam of glaring from the unsung noble and The Thief, in his defeat--the noble couldn&#39;t keep the stare going and sighs before accepting the extending hand before giving a shake in *ancient classical times fashion &quot;Deal.&quot;
(*The Roman handshake)

**More lore added soon...**

**Objective**: Stay alive to steal at least four journals and then escape!


**Comments**:


Other suggestions of The Thief can be posted here :grinning:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 20:09:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Abilities has been updated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 20:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Done, making The Thief less high-profile. (Since The Fool shares same night ability)</p>
<p>And instead of making the smoke bomb being immune to execution and untraceable for the day when ability is used, it is now ability being used in order to escape and win after the condition to collecting four journals is met.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>alright then but that day ability to strong if people are smart enough to figure out your the thief and convince other people it is you should be killed for it not have a way to escape I think no classes should be able to survive the day makes your more annoying to kill since everyone has to spend 2 days killing you and that’s just not fun at all</p>
<p>and he has night immune and is immune to Occupy so please just make it possible to kill him</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 23:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The reason why smoke bomb attempt power has one extra use is that even if Blue Dragon doesn’t have the jailer anymore, they can still decide to execute on trial to get their stolen journals back if they figure out who the thief is and removing one attempt power, it’s odd night and then the next day doing so again because reasons?</p>
<p>It’s correct that doing so in just four nights flawless is too easy and too early and if people figure out this player is the thief, it’s confirmed. People that are confirmed can still communicate about their (false) findings without the journal scribed inside but should the rest of blue dragon trust them at point they were ‘confirmed’?  Then they have to use their wits, almost all neutrals can’t be converted.</p>
<p>deadfrien’s version seem to belong by blue dragon faction rather than neutral which can figure other player’s role and instant confirm them or at least narrow them down by hinting which classes uses their items, making The Thief look like most of the games the deputy sheriff (Or like The Investigator from Town of Salem–oops you said before me) and also use same said item to someone like testing waters.<br>
They can side with Black Rose without getting converted at start I’m afraid if they are still neutral and Black Rose can use mirrored classes to have their abilities to put use for them, you know my meaning? That’s where converted system is for, it’s like giving a role that can do almost everything when it comes to items and yeah I know that deadfrien said it’s converted version will be nerfed but if their goal is to survive with other survivors - then Black Rose doesn’t need to dumb The Thief down and carry on.</p>
<p>if changed from my take, the night ability with immunity can affect all nights but otherwise nerf a bit,</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 15:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so if the thief needs 8 nights and that is gonna be highly unlucky in itself, therefore, making it more luck based instead of skilled<br>
and with the Now you see me, now you don’t why have it be usable twice? if people fiqure out your the theif they are probably never gonna talk or do anything to you thefore speeding up the game and making it harder for you to win and since you can’t do anything about it your dead in the water</p>
<p>hell your also probably gonna killed on Night 4 since every odd night your immune and if your lucky enough not to be killed to get 8 nights in</p>
<p>I still belive that deadfrien ability set is more useful and cool set and if we set the theif objectice to survive it becomes a more easy class since your version is likey gonna be really hard to win as based on the luck aspect</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 14:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have changed the passive that thief doesn’t need to read from other journals, just collecting is their job. In flawless run, the thief need more than <strong>eight</strong> nights to win for themselves and won’t show up anymore, ‘eliminating’ the voter in the progress and there are chances The Thief can be killed or occupied by roleblocker during the night they will steal beforehand that The Thief need even more nights to reach the winning condition, should the game end without meeting the condition, the game is a loss to The Thief - Meaning the survival with the others wouldn’t count. The reason will be added to my The Thief’s lore coming soon.</p>
<p>The only way to get the journals back is executed on day or by The Prince, other means getting killed will discard the journals.</p>
<p>Also The Thief is wildcard, meaning they necessarily doesn’t need ‘anyone’ to help their goal unless opposing factions profit from prolonging their lives enough to secure their own win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 13:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think the thief needs to steal anything to win. The way you have made it is simply an another way to say survive 4 nights.</p>
<p>still stealing Journals can’t help the thief in any good way it can only help those who ally with him and they should already have ways to get info without the aid of a neutral</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 13:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you, deadfrien. I will think for night ability 1’s alternatives, The Thief is careful character but not on least expecting moments.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[deadfrien]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s actually quite a solid idea, and it makes survival a bit easier.<br>
I still think his Night Ability 1 should be changed, but overall  it sounds good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 21:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds to me The Thief as neutral need unique objective as mentioned above.</p>
<p>My idea to steal journals that unable players to write again for the rest of the game, still stands. Starting to steal on Night 2, Night 4, Night 6 and then Night 8 (and so on) to complete the objective. Although the other winning condition to win with other survivors with still not able to steal all four journals wouldn’t make sense if the condition is not met. That causes Thief’s game to lose and should The Thief met the objective with the journals, they should able to escape the Castle of Adiart at immediately effect for example (or on next ‘odd’ night,) and by next day, it will be known on announcement like: “The Thief escapes with evidence of treason against the realm!”, sealing the victory for The Thief since it’s presence is no longer needed during the game at this point, because of his wildcard nature and can cause nuisance to everyone like The Fool, hanging on day or killing The Thief on ‘even’ nights will put end of this class for the match. The Prince or other killers that can bypass night immunity can also finish the job.</p>
<p>That is my explanation for the winning conditions, The Thief is allowed to steal any journal they see fit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 10:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I suggest that you make his theft ability so it does not work for om Unique classes</p>
<p>like the king, since he has guards and well how to you steal a guard? trust me I tried once did not work. still trying to find a way to do it<br>
it would also make sure he can’t take the priest and the paladin power and that would make sense holy powers and all that<br>
also since all the evil killers at the moment are Unique he definitely won’t kill anyone…definitely won’t <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
I’m talking about the knight<br>
And what would do if he targeted the cult leader or the mastermind? Nothing good I can say that much</p>
<p>need I keep going? why not what would happen if he targeted the prince? no one for him to kill so nothing useful once again<br>
the only ability that may still help yet unlikely would be the sheriff’s windows peak but how much would that really help the thief?</p>
<p>anyway name the ability whatever the power is normally called but add :stolen: in front of it. still need to know what power you stole like<br>
:Stolen: Drug</p>
<p>: Edit: It turns out this thief is more powerful than I 1st thought it’s not just a thief but a consig from tos. Consider adding a 2-day cooldown to his theif power but he gets to keep his stolen item until he changes it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 06:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[deadfrien]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the journal-stealing is a bit underpowered, especially with the Thief being Neutral, so here’s a heavy revamp.</p>
<p>Day Ability 1: Theft … During the day phase, the Thief infiltrates another player’s room and steals one of their items representing an ability. The Thief can use this item’s power on an appropriate target at night, but the item is discarded from his bag after use. If the item represents an ability that has limited attempts, the character loses that attempt.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: (1-day cooldown) We Work In The Darkness … Same ability, but can be used more than once. Maybe the headstart just makes it so he can’t be seen interacting with other characters/doesn’t show up to watchers?</p>
<p>Night Ability 2: ??? (couldn’t think of name) … Use the ability of one of your items. The item is discarded after use. Only non-killing night abilities can be used, maybe (ie; Nightshade can be stolen, but not used.)</p>
<p>Special [Passive]: Item Pouch - The Thief can hold onto items that represent abilities. He needs at least 1 to use ??? (Night Ability 2).</p>
<p>If the Thief could be converted, than his abilities would be nerfed to prevent the Black Rose from becoming too powerful. But I think it’d be more fun if the Thief remained a random factor <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>(This was discussed more in depth on the ToL Discord, so look there if you want to see the full discussion.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 21:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Passive 1</strong>: Why’s the ink gone?<br>
Players will be not notified for journal theft, it will be shown as “He left no journal” / “She left no journal” upon death.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2</strong>: I work in darkness to serve the light.<br>
The Thief is always in high alert during night phase, immune to occupy</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong>: (1 attempt power) Now you see me, now you don’t.<br>
The Thief will publicly escape with smoke bomb and forces to end day phase</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1</strong>: (1-night cooldown) Dear Diary.<br>
The Thief enter player’s room and steal the journal, cannot gain one journal if target is prevented for visit.</p>
<p><strong>The Thief’s Lore</strong>: During the day on tavern somewhere in realm of Adiart, whispers has been told about royal castle is dealing with corruption within their ranks, however without proof of solid evidence that may be contained only in journals about their activities day and night, interest of acquiring the journals starts to perk up under anonymous black market begin to start posting bounty with promise of riches that will make any mercenary that need money to feed their family or other desires, can make them retire for the rest of their lives–the catch is, they need to get out of the royal castle alive and deliver the journals here let alone getting in is also the hard part. Men and woman for hire would appears to be losing interest in taking the job before returning taking their seats to drink away their past sorrows and troubled present, among the crowded customers there is one mysterious figure in cloak and cloth mask that hasn’t taking off…it’s eyes on the bounty that has been posted at the wooden pillar supporting the tavern’s second floor, the mysterious figure stand up from the seat they occupied earlier is searching for one noble that is responsible for asking people in the tavern for hire that returned to his room upstairs, the mysterious figure has either get through crowded lower tables or pass the bar tables occupied with scum and villainy that cause trouble when ever feel like it and that happened quite a lot that even the bar maid is sexually assaulted recently by huge-build mercenary at age of 41 that has likely seen action in previous war against the realm since royal castle is united to fight against one common foe–the cult of Mithras that used to have thousands of followers and dozens of the leaders,<br>
but that’s story of another time about the previous war.</p>
<p>The mysterious figure would walk through the open spaces that has been presented without trying to bump into each other’s shoulders, the movement is surprisingly fluid and smooth for the figure that has been only here for first time in this tavern and the customers by the lower tables didn’t seem to get bothered at all, fewer mobs by the bar tables couldn’t think but glare at the mysterious figure for acting up like this person owns the place, they tend to learn the figure a lesson soon. Upstairs appear to be guarded by the soldiers from the noble he hired not likely from the royal castle itself. The mysterious figure below observe when the bar maid walk up to the stairs as the guard on the left gestures with open palm towards the bar maid to halt, the right guard begin to speak up “What ish yur bushness here -hic- pretty leydy?” that appears to be drunk without question, the bar maid dismissively wave her free hand to make stench of alcohol coming out of guard’s breath go away “I am delivering the bread and blocks of cheese to the guests of far right room, shall you let me pass?” The bar maid is tapping on her feet that notify she’s in a hurry to delivering “Urr um…the masterrr did nut order sucs -hic-” The left guard clear his throat and look at the bar maid “Sorry for this lad giving you grief, you can go pass delivering the food for someone else you have mentioned, we’re making sure our noble is safe within his different room.” The left guard make shuffle the open gap for the bar maid immediately walk through and take turn to the right, the right guard isn’t looking down the stairs but forward the bar maid that has turned her back marching towards the room that has ordered the food, the left guard also turn around to give a bonk at the back of the right guard’s head “I am surprised you sod is even hired to do guard duty…” The mysterious figure took his sweet time to climb on the wooden pillar as they grab the bounty paper with them, is now hanging on the edge of second floor that causes the chatting nearly die down while the guards by the stairs is too occupied to do their job. “We are fortunate that we’re standing at the very stairs and nobody can sneak past us to the hall by second left room wi…” The mysterious figure nod themselves as the guard is talking to himself, they lift up to climb to the second floor and casually walk past the guards while the drunken right guard hasn’t been recovered from the bonk yet receives rather a stomp from the bar maid’s feet that has come out of the room not without change of appearance that she look more worked up than before, she walk past the other guard and climb down and the crowd below starting to laugh to notice there has been rips to her clothing, especially they look down.</p>
<p>-Knock Knock!-</p>
<p>Softly bonking can be heard to other side of the room freezes the noble before looking towards the door “Who goes there?” Silence occurs by the door before the lock starting to click as metal pin tips coming out from the other side of lock for the noble to see, he reaches for the rapier as he stands ready to counter-strike the possible foe by the other side of the door. The mysterious figure hide it’s metal pins they used for pick locking the door, reach for the bounty paper he grabbed by the pillar earlier, pushes the door softly without making the creaking too obvious for the guards it wasn’t their man that opened the door, lean his free hand holding the bounty paper towards the gap for the noble to see. The noble is skeptical about the approach from the stranger “What happened to my guards without knowing your presence?” demanded the noble towards the door. The mysterious figure took no time to fully open the door just enough to get them through before shutting behind them. “You need to hire guards that don’t make them drunk easily or start accusing the drunk they forgot about the job” as the ominous voice comes out from the lips of the mysterious figure in cloak do expose the green-colored eye contact towards the noble in envy expression “They pose no issue for me, you can dissolve them from your services, they will sober soon after I am done talking to you about this job.” said the mysterious figure ending their sentence, apparently they are voiced like a man. “…these cheap idiots are still alive and they didn’t saw you approaching to me…I gave them clear instructions to watch the stairs!” nearly cause the noble to shout in self-destructing fashion. “That cost you extra if you want to know my answer. However let’s talk business instead.” as the mysterious figure start to walk and pick a seat to sit while the noble is still pointing his rapier at the stranger if they pull anything they will regret “What about this business, hmm? Are you really going to throw your life away for mere journals that I–” “…Black market.” as the mysterious figure interrupted the noble that causes to scowl at the person “Yes, black market can provide the payment of sixty gold coins for one journal.” The silent broke the conversation between the employer and potential hired man before releasing soft laughter through the lips of the figure “It is not even worth the coins to live in retirement if I come out alive and with the same amount of coins, you can get one week supplies with nothing but bread, whale soap, ink bottles, one fresh feather, pay the rest of the coins to the landlord that has to pay taxes to the royal family so I can scribe how poor my life is,” the figure is not finished to speak by looks of it “Judging by this, you get the bigger share for like sixty-six procent of the profit while I get thirty-three for this worthless trip while your pulse bag will be fat and happy.” the words spoken from the mysterious figure didn’t seem to convince the noble about the true motivation behind the bounty he’s eagerly to take “Take your best bet.” said the noble with grimace expression on his face, before the figure dismissively wave his hand “You want complete set of four journals so you can blackmail the royal family with hefty sum in return for evidence who the conspirators are that want Blue Dragon faction dead, even if it means the journals belong to conspirators themselves that misdirect to execute the innocent, and I won’t be surprised you want the throne for yourself too.” the mysterious figure glaring at the noble to imitate the same expression through their eyes that the noble wore earlier before, the noble slowly sheath his rapier back placed by his belt by his satisfaction “That’s right,” said the noble before he takes a seat as well, close to the figure “so here’s the deal: You bring four journals and I will set up the price twenty times much as the original price being put, your procent as you have figured out will be thirty-three while I keep sixty-six procent.” The noble take a good look towards the figure like he’s playing game of poker cards, The Thief give deadpan expression towards the noble as he’s not convinced with the price he’s being offered “triple the price even more by the black market and I’d like to have forty procent of the profits and you have sixty procent, considered the risk of getting caught stealing the evidence…you also need to pay something extra from the black market I can put of good use, I want smoke bombs with your money as advancement pay for me.” the noble perking his eyebrow towards The Thief “But these cost like two-hundred-and-fifty gold coins–”, but The Thief interrupts before the noble could finish “Then bribe guards from the royal armory inside the Castle of Adiart itself and I take it from here, since you are invited as royal guest and is allowed to bring servants anyway, deal?” as The Thief extend their hand towards the noble, the expressions tensed between both beam of glaring from the unsung noble and The Thief, in his defeat–the noble couldn’t keep the stare going and sighs before accepting the extending hand before giving a shake in *ancient classical times fashion “Deal.”<br>
(*The Roman handshake)</p>
<p><strong>More lore added soon…</strong></p>
<p><strong>Objective</strong>: Stay alive to steal at least four journals and then escape!</p>
<p><strong>Comments</strong>:</p>
<p>Other suggestions of The Thief can be posted here <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/grinning.png?v=9" title=":grinning:" class="emoji" alt=":grinning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 23:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-167-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-thief-neutral-wildcard-immune-to-convert-updated/167.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Thief (Neutral Wildcard) (Immune to convert) -UPDATED-</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
