<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How About Some Introductions</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366</link>
    <description>Just thought I&#39;d start a topic for Introductions. Not that we all really need one. But I&#39;ll start off first. 

Hello, My name is David but you guys can call me D1g1By3, or D1g1 for short...(Long story). I am just a regular Guy that enjoys gaming. (trying not to give out too much personal info). I was introduced to TOL ironically through TOS (Town f Salem). I will try not to mention them too much due to being the competition. Apologies if that was considered advertising... I&#39;m Not advertising them just saying that&#39;s where I came from.........Anyways I am really looking forward to this game to become a reality. The whole Idea of having much more interaction in a 3D universe. (So unlike all of it&#39;s predecessors.) Is intriguing to me. What originally started as pretty much a Text based, use your imagination type Genre, has turned into something truly remarkable. I am having High hopes for this and hope to see it continue to grow, even after Development. Anyways, not really much of an Intro. It&#39;s turned into a &quot;My hopes for what to come&quot; I guess. But I look forward to seeing other peoples &quot;Introductions&quot; as well. 

~ D1g1 signing out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 17:38:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How About Some Introductions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="http://forum.imperium42.com/t/newbie-introductions/288" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://forum.imperium42.com/t/newbie-introductions/288</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 19:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-366-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366.rss">How About Some Introductions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How About Some Introductions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D1g1Byt3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just thought I’d start a topic for Introductions. Not that we all really need one. But I’ll start off first.</p>
<p>Hello, My name is David but you guys can call me D1g1By3, or D1g1 for short…(Long story). I am just a regular Guy that enjoys gaming. (trying not to give out too much personal info). I was introduced to TOL ironically through TOS (Town f Salem). I will try not to mention them too much due to being the competition. Apologies if that was considered advertising… I’m Not advertising them just saying that’s where I came from…Anyways I am really looking forward to this game to become a reality. The whole Idea of having much more interaction in a 3D universe. (So unlike all of it’s predecessors.) Is intriguing to me. What originally started as pretty much a Text based, use your imagination type Genre, has turned into something truly remarkable. I am having High hopes for this and hope to see it continue to grow, even after Development. Anyways, not really much of an Intro. It’s turned into a “My hopes for what to come” I guess. But I look forward to seeing other peoples “Introductions” as well.</p>
<p>~ D1g1 signing out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 19:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-366-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-about-some-introductions/366.rss">How About Some Introductions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
