<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657</link>
    <description>“Deep in the frozen wastes of Svalbard an abandoned complex has been brought back to life. A group of ultimates from all ages and walks of life have been captured by a mysterious hag and her assistant. It seems another killing game has begun, although it seems the tables have turned. For now the mastermind is being hunted!”

“A game of hope, a game of despair. A game of truth, a game of lies. A game of life, a game of death. Welcome to **DanganR**- I mean **Blood on the Forums: Clown Fiesta**!”

Bienvenue losers and (hopefully) winners, this game is hosted by myself and @EliThePsycho ! I&#39;m the ~~cringy~~ fun and quirky mod as you can tell. So this one’s gonna be a shitshow cause there isn&#39;t actually a script technically. We&#39;re playing Fishbucket!

What is Fishbucket you may ask? Why it&#39;s only the best script in Clocktower (because it isnt one)! You may roll any character from Trouble Brewing, Bad Moon Rising, Sects and Violets, Laissez un Faire, or Deadly Penance Day. The normal townsfolk/outsider/minion/demon ratios are still the same.


[details=&quot;Character Lists&quot;]
https://imgur.com/a/wJmGSIC (link for base 3 because discourse stopped working)
(it contains Trouble Brewing, Sects and Violets, and Bad Moon Rising)

Laissez Un Faire: 

![laissezunfaire.PNG|583x500](upload://AjqI5Cn3OGR4TJxVp5RNk721cDV.jpeg) 

Deadly Penance Day:


![deadlypenanceday|353x500](upload://zDvtsbYO4zQCMzpi25YzXZsJ0RY.jpeg) 
[/details]


If you have any questions about things such as Madness/Character Transformations I will gladly go over them.

Anyways, this game has flavour. And by flavour I mean offensively bad flavour. So you weebs will be really happy with this state of affairs I&#39;m guessing.

If you have no idea what&#39;s going on right now, continue reading.


[details=&quot;The Basics&quot;]
This game is designed for a variable number of players, and thus the composition of the game is able to change depending on how many players join. The following list denotes the standard composition of the game at each possible player count.

Total Players: Townsfolk/Outsiders/Minions/Demons
5: 3/0/1/1
6: 3/1/1/1
7: 5/0/1/1
8: 5/1/1/1
9: 5/2/1/1
10: 7/0/2/1
11: 7/1/2/1
12: 7/2/2/1
13: 9/0/3/1
14: 9/1/3/1
15: 9/2/3/1

Every character in-game is unique in that more than one of the same character will never appear at the start of the game (there can never be two Chefs at the start, for example).

Certain characters may contain parts of their ability which modify the game setup; some add character types (and subtract others to compensate), while others change elements of the game entirely. Be sure to take notice of these. You’ll find them in [square brackets], like those ones.
[/details]


[details=&quot;Phase Length&quot;]
Each day phase will last for no longer than 48 hours.
12 hours: Discussion phase. Nominations may not be cast at this time.
12 hours: Nomination phase. Players who wish to nominate may do so at this time, and votes may begun to be cast during this time as well.
24 hours: Vote finalization. During this time, votes may be cast freely on any existing nomination, but no new nominations may be made. Once this time ends or all votes have been locked in, the day will resolve.

The night phase will last for no more than 24 hours. If all relevant actions have been submitted and processed, Storytellers reserve the right to begin the next day early.
Storyteller

The Storyteller is the key moderator for the game; All ability uses at night must be sent to the Storyteller via private message, and Storyteller will have the final say on any open-ended ability behaviors. Storyteller’s goal is to keep the game both fun and balanced, and they’ll often be trying to make it last as long as possible; however, the Storyteller may not alter any existing rules to accomplish this.
[/details]


[details=&quot;The Fabled&quot;]
The Fabled aren’t really characters so much as special modifiers that the Storyteller can put in play to tweak the game. For example, the Angel can be put into play to help keep newer players from being targeted, or the Buddhist can be put into play to keep the more experienced players from dominating the discussion. Fabled will always be announced when they are in play, along with their effect upon gamestate. A breakdown of Fabled characters can be found below.

Angel: Something bad might happen to whomever is most responsible for the death of a new player.
Buddhist: Veteran players may not speak for the first six hours of the day phase.
Doomsayer: If more than four players live, each living player may publicly invoke the Doomsayer once per game to cause a player of their own alignment to die.
Fiddler: Once per game, at night, the Demon secretly chooses a player of an opposing alignment; All players then choose which of these two wins the game.
Hell’s Librarian: Something bad might happen to whomever speaks when the Storyteller calls for silence.
The following Fabled character must be added before the game begins; please speak to the Storyteller if you wish to see it added.
Revolutionary: Two neighboring players are known to be the same alignment. Once per game, one of them may register falsely.
[/details]



[details=&quot;Malfunctioning&quot;]
The primary source of interference with abilities in this game is the malfunction. A class that is malfunctioning is not told that they are malfunctioning; if the character is one that gathers information, then the information they receive that night is arbitrary (open-ended, Storyteller may resolve at their discretion), otherwise, the malfunctioning character’s ability simply does not have any effect.
Nominations and Voting
[/details]



[details=&quot;Voting&quot;]
Once the discussion phase has ended, the Storyteller will formally announce the opening of the nomination phase. Players must be nominated before they may be voted on that day. Each player may only be nominated once per day, and each player may only nominate once per day.
When a nomination is opened, the storyteller begins to track votes for that nomination. The players may precast votes, but the votes will lock in a clockhand format. Starting with the player below the nominee on the list, and working downwards, the votes will be locked if they are cast. As an example, take the following five players;

    Alex
    Brianna
    Cameron
    Derek
    Ellen

Brianna is nominated. Cameron’s vote will be locked as soon as he places it, because he is the first person below Brianna on the list. Derek may cast his vote before Cameron, and may alter his vote if Cameron has not yet voted, but once Cameron has voted and had his vote locked, Derek’s vote will be the next to lock, and if it is placed when Cameron’s vote locks, then Derek’s vote will lock as the vote cast by Derek at that time.
Any votes that are not cast by EoD will be considered votes to pardon. If the count of votes to execute is more than half of the number of living players (not half+1, that’s an important distinction), and is the highest count of votes against any player that day, the accused will be considered “about to die”. At the end of the day or when all votes on all nominations have been cast, the player who is “about to die” will be executed. If there is a tie between two or more players for the highest count of votes, the day will end with no execution. The Storyteller may only declare an early end to voting if it is no longer possible to tie or exceed the highest nomination.
[/details]


[details=&quot;Whispers&quot;]
Players may whisper each other in-game through private messages. Whispers must, however, be publicly announced, typically by requesting permission to whisper (a standard format is /whisper [Player]). Whispers to your neighbors (those seated next to you) do not have to be announced. Once a whisper has been declared and accepted, the two players may whisper via private message until one of them speaks publicly in the game chat, at which point the whisper is considered over and the players must declare whispers again if they wish to whisper.
[/details]


[details=&quot;Death&quot;]
When a player dies, nothing is revealed about their character and they are allowed to stay in the game and speak. They may not nominate and they will have only one vote token (this will allow them to cast a vote to execute) for the entire game. Evil players who die may thus continue to help their allies by keeping up their claim and spreading misinformation, and good players may similarly help their allies by retaining relevant info that others may have forgotten in the heat of the game. Once a player dies, their ability stops working, which means that a player killed before they would perform their ability will not perform their ability, and any ability with a persistent effect will end upon the player’s death.
[/details]


[details=&quot;Victory&quot;]
Good wins by eliminating all Demons (Minions do not necessarily need to die for Good to win, but eliminating Minions can be helpful). Evil wins by reducing the game to two living players (irrespective of either player’s alignment). The Storyteller may also declare a victory for Evil if Good may no longer possibly win (for example, if only evil players are left alive and thus no one would nominate the Demon). Certain class abilities may present alternate routes to victory; these classes, if able to appear, will be made known on the class list. In the event of a tie (both teams would win simultaneously), Good wins.
[/details]


[details=&quot;Madness&quot;]
Certain character abilities in Blood on the Clocktower reference a status known as “madness”. What madness means, in the simplest terms, is that when a player is “mad” about something, they are trying to convince the other players that it is true, even if it is not (especially if it is not). Ultimately, the Storyteller is the one who judges whether the “mad” player’s efforts are sufficient to avoid punishment, but this allows the Storyteller to be more lenient toward players who are unfamiliar with the concept, and by the same token, to expect more from an experienced player.
[/details]



[details=&quot;SHENANIGANS&quot;]
And finally, the Pit-Hag may not turn evil players into alignment changing characters. A Pit-Hag that has been killed by the Vigormortis may not create a Leviathan. I may also add more exceptions if they come up during pre-game. Otherwise everything goes. If anything else gamebreaking comes up during pre-game it gets added here. Also all Djinn jinxes will be in effect if both characters roll.
[/details]


The player list can be found below; just ping myself or Eli with /in and the seat you want (if you dont choose I pick one for you.).

1 - 
2 - Gorta
3 -
4 - 
5 - 
6 - Cantaloupe
7 - Intensify
8 -  PokemonKidRyan
9 - Leafia
10 - Windward
11 -  Marshal ([color=purple]Traveler[/color])
12 -  Marl
13 - Amelia
14 - 
15 -

Spectators - 

Katze - Informed

Backups -
Whysper
CRichard</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 15:08:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Signups</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/682">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/682</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-682</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>signups have closed</h1>
<h1>the rand begins</h1>
<h1>the game is now on the forge</h1>
<h1>classcards going out this evening (EST)</h1>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/an_gorta_pratai">@an_gorta_pratai</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/cantaloupe">@cantaloupe</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/intensify">@Intensify</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/pokemonkidryan">@PokemonKidRyan</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/leafia">@Leafia</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/windwardaway">@WindwardAway</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/marshal">@Marshal</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/marluxion">@Marluxion</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/amelia">@Amelia</a></p>
<p><span class="mention">@mods</span> lock this thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/681">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/681</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 15:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-681</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>replacements are for when someone can’t play the game</h1>
<h1>replacements are not “haha i dont have time i’m just gonna play because screw everyone else”</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/680">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/680</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-680</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>i wont</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/679">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/679</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-679</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>they’re about as potentially damaging as a surprise mid-game traveler, or even more damaging (if a slot that was about to be yeeted suddenly isnt thanks to a replacement that changes the game state massively</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/678">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/678</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-678</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m still not speccing in case you change your mind</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/677">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/677</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-677</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>no they are not</h1>
<h1>replacements fuck with game balance massively</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/676">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/676</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-676</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>Isn’t that what replacements are for?</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/675">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/675</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-675</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>are you actually saying this when someone is travelling because they might have to leave early</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/674">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/674</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-674</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Like why allow any Travelers then? What are they for if not for midgame join?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/673">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/673</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-673</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>We’re exhiling any traveller d1 that isn’t Deviant, Butcher or Begger</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/672">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/672</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-672</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel not only scammed, but double scammed</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/671">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/671</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-671</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>yes they can</h1>
<h1>but im the host and im not allowing it</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/670">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/670</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-670</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>I would prefer to only have travelers at the start of the game</h1>
<h1>this game is gonna be fucky wucky, i dont want any surprise travelers ruining that balance further</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/669">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/669</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-669</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can’t travelers join at any time?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/668">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/668</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-668</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>Clearly we end the game before any Travellers get to join</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/667">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/667</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-667</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="thepigeonnyc" data-post="663" data-topic="86657">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/thepigeonnyc/40/32596_2.png" class="avatar"> thepigeonnyc:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ll travel over the weekend</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>the game is starting before then</p>
<p>just an fyi</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/666">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/666</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-666</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/thepigeonnyc">@thepigeonnyc</a> is that an <strong>/in</strong>?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/665">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/665</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-665</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(By travel, I mean become a BotC traveler</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/664">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/664</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-664</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wait a minute, <strong>/I don’t want to be an informed spec</strong></p>
<p>I’ll travel over the weekend</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/663">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/663</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-663</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>EST</h1>
<h1>and I still need to clear it with dat/eli first</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/662">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/662</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-662</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GGhana" data-post="660" data-topic="86657">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/gghana/40/33120_2.png" class="avatar"> GGhana:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lunchtime today</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Imagine knowing what timezone this is</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/661">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/661</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-661</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>signups closing by lunchtime today</h1>
<h1>just need to clear everything with Eli/Dat first</h1>
<h1>signups are still open</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/660">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/660</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-660</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yup. Mwahahaha!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/659">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/659</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 05:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-659</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>welcome to the house… of DOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/658">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657/658</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 04:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-86657-658</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bruh-on-the-cringetower-clown-fiesta-signups-9-15/86657.rss">Bruh on the Cringetower: Clown Fiesta - Signups (9/15)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
