<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529</link>
    <description>**The Bounty Hunter**
_Unique Neutral, Offensive_

**Lore:** I&#39;m not good at writing proper lore, but basically the bounty hunter was a knight who accidentally killed an innocent person and lost his job. There was a trial but his actions were forgiven by the King himself. However, many people still hated him for what he did and wanted him dead, so he decided to become a bounty hunter in order to get enough money to leave the castle with his family and start a new life. 

**Victory condition**
Kill your target and collect the bounty.

**Passive Ability 1: Your last job**
You are immune to death at night. You will be given a random target at the beginning of the game. That target&#39;s exact class and faction will be revealed to you. If your target dies on trial or is killed by anyone else you will commit suicide the following night.

&gt;_**Notes**: Your target can be any class from any faction except for the following: the King, the Mastermind, the Inquisitor, the Scorned or a Neutral Killer). A message will appear in chat telling everyone that there is a bounty hunter trying to kill said player, and there will be a small symbol next to their name that everyone can see. (Example: &quot;There is a bounty for John Smith&#39;s [12] head!&quot;)_

**Passive Ability 2: A new life**
One day after you successfully kill your target you will collect your bounty. After you collect your bounty you will win and leave the castle along with your family.

&gt;_**Notes:** Your &quot;family&quot; will be two living players chosen at random (except the king), who will also leave the castle. Leaving the castle will make your name and number disappear, and It works similar to death with the difference that you cannot see or write in dead chat or be revived, and no one will be able to know your previous class or see your logs._
&gt;_Also, you do not immediately win after killing your target, you need to survive one more day before you can win, which means you need to take observers into account before killing your target._

**Day Ability 1: Intimidate**
Select a player. He will be unable to visit your target for the next two nights. You can use this ability on your target to prevent him from using any self-targeting abilities until tomorrow. 3 uses.

&gt;_**Notes:** If used on your target it will prevent any self-targeted abilities, even if they are day abilities and even if your target is occupy immune. Prevents things like &quot;Stoneskin potion&quot;, &quot;Concentrated wine&quot;, &quot;Bear Companion&quot;, &quot;Ice ward&quot; or &quot;Hide&quot;._

**Night Ability 1: The Perfect Chance**
Attempt to kill your target. If your target is still alive after using this ability, you will commit suicide the following night. 1 use. 

**Night Ability 2: This is MY job**
Your target will be immune to death tonight and cannot be accused for treason tomorrow. You will also heal any poison or bleeding on them. 3 uses.
________________
________________

**Gameplay and strategy:**
The bounty hunter needs to kill his target, but he only has one chance to do it so he has to be careful and wait for the perfect moment. Everyone knows who the target is, so they will try to protect them because if the bounty hunter wins he will remove two random players from the game and their class and logs will be lost forever.

The bounty hunter knows the exact class and faction of his target, since he has to adapt his play style depending on his target&#39;s class (Trying to kill a sheriff is not the same as trying to kill a hunter).
He can use his day ability &quot;Intimidate&quot; to prevent a physician or knight from protecting his target for the next two nights, or he can use it on his target to prevent them from using any self-targeted abilities until the next day. (which is useful if your target is a hunter or court wizard).
His night ability &quot;This is MY job&quot; can prevent his target from being killed by someone else or being executed if they are suspicious.

Finally, his most important ability &quot;The Perfect Chance&quot; only has one use, which means he cant just randomly use it night one and win (it can still happen but you must be extremely lucky). There are many things the bounty hunter has to take into account before attempting to kill his target. Not only does he have to make sure his target isn&#39;t being healed or guarded, but he also needs to make sure that they are not in jail or that you are not going to be occupied or debauched. Not only that, but you also have to stay hidden and be careful of observers who might be watching your target, since even if you kill your target you need to wait one day before claiming your bounty.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 19:41:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Vandalay" data-post="5" data-topic="28529" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/vandalay/40/1393_2.png" class="avatar"> Vandalay:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="psychoneirik" data-post="1" data-topic="28529">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/psychoneirik/40/12950_2.png" class="avatar"> psychoneirik:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The bounty hunter has no reason to reveal his target’s class or faction to others, so revealing it  would count as gamethrowing (even in logs). Asking a bounty hunter for his target’s class would also be worthy of a report.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t see how this is valid to report or claim. Gamethrowing litterally means that giving this information lowers your chances of winning.</p>
<p>You can’t define it as gamethrowing to ask, but he’s also under no obligation to tell the truth obviously.</p>
<p>While of course as a living bountyhunter if he started as BD, yes it could be seen as gamethrowing to out them as a legitimate BD class, that’s about it really, and if he is unseen/cult/NK, logically speaking people wouldn’t believe it, because any rational bounty hunter that wanted the protectives not to cover the target, would want to convince people the target is evil.</p>
<p>In logs, you really can’t cover that by gamethrowing, by definition you can’t gamethrow after you’ve lost.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>An earlier version of the Bounty Hunter could get NK or MM as his target, I mean yeah the bounty hunter could be lying but still outing them would be extremely bad for them and it wouldn’t benefit you since they will try to execute them. However you can no longer get any targets with passive death immunity like MM or NK so I agree this makes little sense now. Will remove it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 19:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28529-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss">[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lily" data-post="2" data-topic="28529" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/lily/40/19089_2.png" class="avatar"> Lily:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have 2 questions</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>If one of your family members is the Alchemist they leave with you do they automaticly win cause they did surivive the same goes for fool.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Can one of your family members be the MM CL Or a Nk if yes then that would be an easy bd win</p>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<ol>
<li>Leaving the castle counts as dying for the game’s purposes, which means alchemist would lose.</li>
<li>The family target selection is the same as the one for his bounty (cannot pick any roles with passive death immunity like MM or NK, however it can pick Cult Leader).</li>
</ol>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KyoDaz" data-post="4" data-topic="28529" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kyodaz/40/30587_2.png" class="avatar"> KyoDaz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Isn’t this just an inquisitor just instead of the Sorcerer it’s random and much harder?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Inquisitor has to find the sorcerer while the bounty hunter already knows who he has to kill. They differ in gameplay by the fact that inquisitor/sorcerer is a game of cat and mouse while bounty hunter needs to wait for the right moment (or create it himself with the help of his abilities) before striking his target. He can prevent a player from visiting his target for two nights, which can help him get rid of physicians or knight if he finds them. He could also just bait heals the night before he tries to kill his target by claiming he is poisoned or something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 19:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28529-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss">[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="psychoneirik" data-post="1" data-topic="28529">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/psychoneirik/40/12950_2.png" class="avatar"> psychoneirik:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The bounty hunter has no reason to reveal his target’s class or faction to others, so revealing it  would count as gamethrowing (even in logs). Asking a bounty hunter for his target’s class would also be worthy of a report.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t see how this is valid to report or claim. Gamethrowing litterally means that giving this information lowers your chances of winning.</p>
<p>You can’t define it as gamethrowing to ask, but he’s also under no obligation to tell the truth obviously.</p>
<p>While of course as a living bountyhunter if he started as BD, yes it could be seen as gamethrowing to out them as a legitimate BD class, that’s about it really, and if he is unseen/cult/NK, logically speaking people wouldn’t believe it, because any rational bounty hunter that wanted the protectives not to cover the target, would want to convince people the target is evil.</p>
<p>In logs, you really can’t cover that by gamethrowing, by definition you can’t gamethrow after you’ve lost.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 16:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28529-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss">[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Isn’t this just an inquisitor just instead of the Sorcerer it’s random and much harder?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 15:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28529-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss">[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devin_Colp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this I got a suggestion.</p>
<p>Instead of losing 2 players, how about losing 1 other player but to make up for it the Bounty Hunter has the occupy immune status of the MM. He would be able to hide better and it would lessen the burden on BD when the Bounty Hunter wins.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 14:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28529-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss">[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lily]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have 2 questions</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>If one of your family members is the Alchemist they leave with you do they automaticly win cause they did surivive the same goes for fool.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Can one of your family members be the MM CL Or a Nk if yes then that would be an easy bd win</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 13:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28529-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss">[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Bounty Hunter</strong><br>
<em>Unique Neutral, Offensive</em></p>
<p><strong>Lore:</strong> I’m not good at writing proper lore, but basically the bounty hunter was a knight who accidentally killed an innocent person and lost his job. There was a trial but his actions were forgiven by the King himself. However, many people still hated him for what he did and wanted him dead, so he decided to become a bounty hunter in order to get enough money to leave the castle with his family and start a new life.</p>
<p><strong>Victory condition</strong><br>
Kill your target and collect the bounty.</p>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 1: Your last job</strong><br>
You are immune to death at night. You will be given a random target at the beginning of the game. That target’s exact class and faction will be revealed to you. If your target dies on trial or is killed by anyone else you will commit suicide the following night.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em><strong>Notes</strong>: Your target can be any class from any faction except for the following: the King, the Mastermind, the Inquisitor, the Scorned or a Neutral Killer). A message will appear in chat telling everyone that there is a bounty hunter trying to kill said player, and there will be a small symbol next to their name that everyone can see. (Example: “There is a bounty for John Smith’s [12] head!”)</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 2: A new life</strong><br>
One day after you successfully kill your target you will collect your bounty. After you collect your bounty you will win and leave the castle along with your family.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em><strong>Notes:</strong> Your “family” will be two living players chosen at random (except the king), who will also leave the castle. Leaving the castle will make your name and number disappear, and It works similar to death with the difference that you cannot see or write in dead chat or be revived, and no one will be able to know your previous class or see your logs.</em><br>
<em>Also, you do not immediately win after killing your target, you need to survive one more day before you can win, which means you need to take observers into account before killing your target.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1: Intimidate</strong><br>
Select a player. He will be unable to visit your target for the next two nights. You can use this ability on your target to prevent him from using any self-targeting abilities until tomorrow. 3 uses.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em><strong>Notes:</strong> If used on your target it will prevent any self-targeted abilities, even if they are day abilities and even if your target is occupy immune. Prevents things like “Stoneskin potion”, “Concentrated wine”, “Bear Companion”, “Ice ward” or “Hide”.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1: The Perfect Chance</strong><br>
Attempt to kill your target. If your target is still alive after using this ability, you will commit suicide the following night. 1 use.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2: This is MY job</strong><br>
Your target will be immune to death tonight and cannot be accused for treason tomorrow. You will also heal any poison or bleeding on them. 3 uses.</p>
<hr>
<hr>
<p><strong>Gameplay and strategy:</strong><br>
The bounty hunter needs to kill his target, but he only has one chance to do it so he has to be careful and wait for the perfect moment. Everyone knows who the target is, so they will try to protect them because if the bounty hunter wins he will remove two random players from the game and their class and logs will be lost forever.</p>
<p>The bounty hunter knows the exact class and faction of his target, since he has to adapt his play style depending on his target’s class (Trying to kill a sheriff is not the same as trying to kill a hunter).<br>
He can use his day ability “Intimidate” to prevent a physician or knight from protecting his target for the next two nights, or he can use it on his target to prevent them from using any self-targeted abilities until the next day. (which is useful if your target is a hunter or court wizard).<br>
His night ability “This is MY job” can prevent his target from being killed by someone else or being executed if they are suspicious.</p>
<p>Finally, his most important ability “The Perfect Chance” only has one use, which means he cant just randomly use it night one and win (it can still happen but you must be extremely lucky). There are many things the bounty hunter has to take into account before attempting to kill his target. Not only does he have to make sure his target isn’t being healed or guarded, but he also needs to make sure that they are not in jail or that you are not going to be occupied or debauched. Not only that, but you also have to stay hidden and be careful of observers who might be watching your target, since even if you kill your target you need to wait one day before claiming your bounty.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 05:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28529-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bounty-hunter-unique-neutral-offensive/28529.rss">[Class suggestion] The Bounty Hunter (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
