<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Change to Sorcerer/Inquisitor pair suggestion</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-to-sorcerer-inquisitor-pair-suggestion/27000</link>
    <description>Hi the problem with the couple classes right now is inquisitor win too easy because Blue Dragon are hunting for neutral killer and he only need sorcerer to die in anyway possible. 
Sorcerer is harder to win because not only she need to kill inquisitor and make Blue Dragon lose, she need to survive to end game too. If neutral killer isn&#39;t dead yet blue dragon is increasingly intolerant to neutral classes as game go on.

So my suggestion is this change both to sorcerer(Sun sorcerer/Moon sorcerer) which objective is to kill each other themselves. 
They have night immune but not to each other kill ability.
They have 2 night abilitys and no day ability.
1. A single targeted kill ability. Sun sorcerer can kill on even-numbered nights and Moon sorcerer can kill on odd numbered nights. This is to reduce their overall kill-rates to equal other neutral killers.
2. A check to 2 targets each night.Tell them that their targets are magic or not. The sorcerer will use this ability the night they can&#39;t kill or don&#39;t want to kill.

If one sorcerer kill another they won the game and lose their night abilitys. They become harmless neutral with only vote rights. 
If somehow one sorcerer die any other ways the living one objective will change to survive and win with evil side.
If one step up they become evil king and the other one can still kill him to win the game.

It&#39;s like a hidden war game between the two with both blue dragon and evil side taking collateral damages.
They are neutral killers that are hunting other neutral claimed classes.
They would not want to out themselve because the other one will kill them. If Blue Dragon got lucky and hanged one of them just make the other siding with evil. Evil has very little chance of harming them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 07:16:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-to-sorcerer-inquisitor-pair-suggestion/27000.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Change to Sorcerer/Inquisitor pair suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spotshooter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi the problem with the couple classes right now is inquisitor win too easy because Blue Dragon are hunting for neutral killer and he only need sorcerer to die in anyway possible.<br>
Sorcerer is harder to win because not only she need to kill inquisitor and make Blue Dragon lose, she need to survive to end game too. If neutral killer isn’t dead yet blue dragon is increasingly intolerant to neutral classes as game go on.</p>
<p>So my suggestion is this change both to sorcerer(Sun sorcerer/Moon sorcerer) which objective is to kill each other themselves.<br>
They have night immune but not to each other kill ability.<br>
They have 2 night abilitys and no day ability.</p>
<ol>
<li>A single targeted kill ability. Sun sorcerer can kill on even-numbered nights and Moon sorcerer can kill on odd numbered nights. This is to reduce their overall kill-rates to equal other neutral killers.</li>
<li>A check to 2 targets each night.Tell them that their targets are magic or not. The sorcerer will use this ability the night they can’t kill or don’t want to kill.</li>
</ol>
<p>If one sorcerer kill another they won the game and lose their night abilitys. They become harmless neutral with only vote rights.<br>
If somehow one sorcerer die any other ways the living one objective will change to survive and win with evil side.<br>
If one step up they become evil king and the other one can still kill him to win the game.</p>
<p>It’s like a hidden war game between the two with both blue dragon and evil side taking collateral damages.<br>
They are neutral killers that are hunting other neutral claimed classes.<br>
They would not want to out themselve because the other one will kill them. If Blue Dragon got lucky and hanged one of them just make the other siding with evil. Evil has very little chance of harming them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-to-sorcerer-inquisitor-pair-suggestion/27000/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-to-sorcerer-inquisitor-pair-suggestion/27000/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 07:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27000-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-to-sorcerer-inquisitor-pair-suggestion/27000.rss">Change to Sorcerer/Inquisitor pair suggestion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
