<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634</link>
    <description>*The Castle of Regalia. A magnificent castle, one surrounded in riches and grandeur. The inhabitants of the castle all live in relative harmony, as even the commonfolk have enough money to stay out of poverty. The castle is also known for quite a few popular individuals, ones who have extraordinary powers and talents. They all band together under the banner of the Regal Lions. But it just isn’t enough for some, or that’s what the Lord’s wife said… before she was found dead in her quarters. A well known topic amongst the citizens of Castle Regalia is the revolutionaries that once plagued Castle Adiart, an ally of the Lions. However, the Blue Dragon of Adiart managed to defeat these revolutionaries… or so was thought until the heinous act of regicide was committed. It’s clear that the Unseen and the Cult are not completely gone… in blood on the wall of the quarters spells “Your riches and your talents cover up the true corruption within this castle. We will liberate this castle and spread your coin across those who deserve it!” Can the Regal Lions silence these familiar foes, or will they consume the castle within their iron fists? Only time will tell…*





### SFoL 62: [color=lightgreen] Regal Lions[/color], hosted by @Amelia 

## Rules
Follow the https://forum.imperium42.com/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244, and the https://forum.imperium42.com/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926. 

## Gameplay

* Days are 48 hours long or until an execution ends it, Nights last 24 hours. The first day is an exception, it lasts only 24 hours and has no execution.
* You will be provided a DM with your classcard by the host, send your actions there.
* Unseen/Cult will talk through a special Discord server or forum message.
* Commoners, Serfs, and Commoner!Apostles will talk with their guests in a separate forum message.
* Those in The Oneiromancer’s Dream Sphere will talk in a separate forum message.
* If the Lord uses Trial By Council, this will be publically announced.
* Alts will be allowed this game, however I must be notified of your identity before the game starts and you must apply through the alt mod, aka DatBird.

## Executions

* To accuse someone say “/vote [player]”. Please make the life of the hosts easier by bolding it (by putting ** ** around it)
* Should the votes reach the majority, that player will be executed and the day will end.
* When the day ends, the player with the most votes will be executed.
* Voting &quot;/no execution&quot; is an option.

## Picking a New Lord

* If there are less than 4 players a new Lord will not be selected.
* When the Lord dies a 12 hour period starts. In this, players may vote in their class PM for who they want to become the next Lord.
* Whoever receives the most votes in this period will be crowned Lord. If votes are tied, a Lord election will be held the next day to determine it.

## Journals

DM the host what you want on your journal. When you die, the last update to your journal will be revealed to everyone. It has a character limit of 1000 characters.

## Classlist



**Lord** **(65% [color = lightgreen]Venerable[/color], 35% [color = purple]Draconian[/color] / [color = darkred]Devout[/color])**
**[color = purple]Mastermind[/color]** / **[color = darkred]Cult Leader[/color]**
**[color = purple]Assassin[/color]** / **[color = darkred]Random Cult[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Executioner[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]**
**[color = lightgreen]Random Regal Lion[/color]** / **[color = grey]Random Neutral Non-Killer[/color]**
**[color = grey]Random Neutral Non-Killer[/color]**
**[color = grey]Neutral Killer[/color]**

## Classes

[details=&quot;Regal Lions&quot;]
&gt; # [color=lightgreen]The Venerable Lord[/color] :shield: :crown: :fire:
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Special**[/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. If you are executed during the day, all healing will fail tonight and all investigations will return Regal Lion tonight.
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day.
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Venerable Law (Day) -** Choose a player and make them immune to conversion for the rest of the game. 1 use (starting Lord only)
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Personal Guard (Night) -** Send your guards to protect a player and make them death immune tonight. 2 uses :crown:
**Adviser (Night) -** Make a player immune to occupation, redirection, and visit prevention tonight. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Executioner [/color] :fire: :crossed_swords: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Ruthless (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation, redirection and visit prevention.
&gt; **Throwing Axe (Day) -** Cause a player to start bleeding. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. 2 uses
&gt; **Hasty Sentence (Day) -** Tonight, your target will be occupied and all visitors to them aside from you will be prevented. You will additionally sentence them to death, making them a valid target for Execution and sending them a message you did so. 1 use
&gt; **Condemnation (Night) -** Sentence a player to death, sending them a message you did so. They are then a valid target for Execution. Infinite uses
&gt; **Execution (Night) -** Prevent all visitors to a player, then kill them. This attack will always kill them, no matter the circumstances and no matter their defenses. You may only target those who have been sentenced to die before. 3 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Constable [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Investigative** [/color]
&gt; **Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled.
&gt; **Royal Service (Day) -** Send your servants to keep tabs on a player. You will know if they visit the target of your ability tonight. 1 use
&gt; **Profile (Night) -** Choose a player and a class name from each of Unseen/Cult/Neutral. You will know if that player is one of these three classes, but not which. You may only choose each class name once before you choose every other class name in the faction. Infinite uses
&gt; **Thorough Inspection (Night) -** Learn if your target is a member of the Unseen or Cult. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Agent [/color] or [color=darkred] The Seeker[/color]**

&gt; **[color=darkred] Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs 1 [/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Royal Service** - **Dark Service (Day) -** Send a servant to follow a player. You will learn who they visit tonight. 2 uses
**Profile** - **Seek Out (Night) -** Choose any number of players and a Regal Lion class. You will know if at least one of them is that class. Infinite uses
**Thorough Inspection** - **Identify (Night) -** Learn your target’s exact class if they are a member of the Regal Lions. 1 use

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Clockmaker [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Investigative** [/color]
**Fated Night (Day) -** Prevent all Unseen and Cult visitors to your target of your night abilities tonight. 1 use
**Clockworks (Night) -** Learn if your target is visited by a member of the Unseen or Cult tonight. Infinite uses 
**The Hands of Time (Night) -** Learn if your target is visited by the Unseen or Cult tonight, and which Unseen or Cult classes visited them last night. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Chronologer [/color] or [color=darkred] The Seeker [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Fated Night - Night of The Harvest (Day) -** In addition to your normal results tonight, learn which ability each class used tonight on your target. 1 use
**Clockworks - Mithras’s Time (Night) -** Learn the Regal Lion classes that your target is visited by tonight. Infinite uses 
**The Hands of Time - Corax’s Judgement (Night) -** Learn every class that visits a player tonight. 2 uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Diviner [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Investigative** [/color]
**Tarot Card (Day) -** Slip a player a tarot card, telling you if they have negative effects happen to them tonight, but not which. 2 uses 
**Divination (Night) -** Learn if a player has any passives tonight. Infinite uses
**Divine Prophecy (Night) -** Learn how many players visit you tonight. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Onmyoji [/color] or [color=darkred] The Seeker [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Tarot Card - Corax’s Fortune (Day) -** Learn which negative effects happen to a player tonight. 3 uses
**Divination - Corruption (Night) -** Learn if a player has any passives, if they do, learn their immunities and if they have Royal Blood. Infinite uses
**Divine Prophecy - Prophetic Doom (Night) -** Choose a Cult member and learn who visits them as well as their factions. This can target yourself. 2 uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Scribe [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Investigative** [/color]
**Sigil of Sight (Day) -** Learn if a player has any day abilities used on them today. 2 uses :crown:
**Record Observations (Night) -** Follow a player and learn who they visit tonight. Infinite uses
**Runic Eye (Night) -** Learn a player’s faction. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Scholar [/color] or [color=darkred] The Seeker [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Runic Eye - Gaze of Corax (Night) -** Attempt to guess a player’s class type grouping. Class type groupings are Special/Investigative, Killer/Offensive and Social/Support. If you are correct, learn their exact class. 2 uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Mage [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Support** [/color]
**Magic Ward (Passive) -** You are immune to bleeding.
**Stubborn Spell (Day) -** Make a player immune to conversion tonight. 2 uses
**Healing Magic (Night) -** Heal a player and cure any bleeding they may have. Infinite uses :crown:
**Wormhole (Night) -** Choose a player and redirect anyone targetting you tonight to that player. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Enchantress [/color] or [color=darkred] The Ritualist [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
&gt; **Stubborn Spell - Void Spell (Day) -** Anyone who dies by the Cult’s hand tonight will be hurled into the void, hiding their flip and destroying their logs. 1 use
&gt; **Wormhole - Blood Portal (Night) -** Redirect anyone targetting a member of the Cult to another player. This can target yourself. 2 uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Marquess [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Support** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled.
**Certify (Day) -** Grant someone the Royal Blood passive. 2 uses
**Charity Fund (Night) -** Refund someone a use in their limited use abilities silently. This cannot make their abilities go above maximum. Infinite uses
**Gateway (Night) -** Ensure players visiting your target successfully perform their actions. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Count [/color] or [color=darkred] The Ritualist [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Charity Fund - Patronage (Night) -** Restore 1 use to every non Cult Leader Cult member’s limited usage abilities. 1 use
**Gateway - Terror (Night) -** Prevent anyone but the Cult from visiting a player tonight. 1 use

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Orator [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Support** [/color]
**Confident Speech (Night) -** Make someone immune to negative effects barring attacks tonight. Infinite uses
**Inspire (Night) -** Cause your target to bypass immunities if they are attacking, occupying, or redirecting tonight. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Activist [/color] or [color=darkred] The Ritualist [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Confident Speech - Accursed Words (Night) -** Frame a player as a class of your choice tonight. Infinite uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Commoner [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Social** [/color]
**House Party (Passive) -** You start in a neighborhood chat by yourself. People in this chat may speak freely with each other until you die. Keep this passive on class change.
**Commonfolk (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are nullified if a Royal is alive.
**Greetings (Night) -** If your target visits you tonight, add them to the neighborhood chat. Infinite uses
**Small Talk (Night) -** Redirect target player to yourself tomorrow night. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Serf [/color] or [color=darkred] The Apostle [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Commonfolk - Semi Royalty (Passive) -** Votes for you to become Lord are nullified if a Royal is alive, however all other Cult will receive double votes for Lord.
**Greetings - Mithras’s Invitations (Night) -** If your target visits you tonight, add them to your neighborhood chat. Targetting a member of the Cult with this ability will add them to the chat regardless if they visited you. Infinite uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Resurrectionist [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Social** [/color]
&gt; **Rite of Ascension (Day) -** You may speak in the main thread today while dead. 1 use
&gt; **Channel (Night) -** Use the unlimited usage night ability of a dead non-Killer Regal Lion player on an alive player. Each corpse can only be used once. Infinite uses :crown:
&gt; **Incomplete Resurrection (Night) -** Add the limited use night ability of a non-Killer Regal Lion player onto your class card, and remove this one. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Necromancer [/color] or [color=darkred] The Apostle [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Rite of Ascension - Dark Arts (Day) -** Cause a player to believe they started bleeding. 2 uses :crown:
**Incomplete Resurrection - Bloody Corpse (Night) -** Gain the Cult Alt of a non-Killer Regal Lion player’s limited usage night ability, or the normal form of it if it does not have a cult alt. 1 use

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Martyr [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Social** [/color]
&gt; **Ultimate Sacrifice (Day) -** If the target of the execution today is a member of the Regal Lions, you will die in their place. 2 uses
&gt; **Penitence (Night) -** All votes on your target will silently not count tomorrow. This can’t target the same player twice in a row. Infinite uses :crown:
&gt; **Absolution (Night) -** Commit suicide tonight and make everyone else death immune tonight. This cannot be stopped in any way, but will fail if you die in any other way tonight. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Retributionist [/color] or [color=darkred] The Apostle [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Ultimate Sacrifice - Corax’s Embrace (Day) -** If a member of the Cult is to be executed today, die in their place and flip as The Martyr. 2 uses
**Absolution - Mithras’s Kindness (Night) -** Commit suicide tonight and flip as The Martyr. This action cannot be stopped in any way, but will fail if you die in any other way tonight. If the Cult Leader’s next conversion would fail, the pity conversion will be triggered no matter what. 1 use

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Dancer [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Offensive** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled.
**Lecherous (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection at night.
**Ballot Ballet (Day) -** Cause a player to require 1 less vote to be executed. 2 uses :crown:
**Tempting Tango (Night) -** Occupy a player for the night. Infinite uses
**Devilish Duet (Night) -** Occupy 2 separate players tonight. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Showstopper [/color] or [color=darkred] The Invoker [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Florist [/color]
&gt; 
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Offensive** [/color]
**Dedicated (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection during the night.
**Rafflesia (Day) -** Day abilities targetting your target will secretly fail today. 2 uses :crown:
**Sweet Scent (Night) -** Redirect your first target to your second target tonight. Infinite uses
**Thorny Vines (Night) -** Prevent all visitors to a player. 2 uses :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Flowergirl [/color] or [color=darkred] The Invoker [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Tailor [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Offensive** [/color]
**Your New Clothes (Passive) -** If a player visits someone dressed as their class, their visit will be guaranteed to succeed.
**Tripwire (Day) -** Occupy target player for this day. 1 use
**Dress Up (Night) -** Choose two players. Dress the first as the second. If anyone else visits one of your targets tonight you will occupy that target. Infinite uses
**Silver Strings (Night) -** Redirect two players to each other tonight. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Seamstress [/color] or [color=darkred] The Invoker [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Your New Clothes - Woven Curses (Passive) -** If a player visits someone while dressed as their class, their visit will be prevented.

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Exorcist [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Killer** [/color]
**Soul Melt (Passive) -** For every player that dies at night, you will gain a soul. You will always be aware of how many souls you have.
**Guilty Conscience (Passive) -** If you kill a member of the Regal Lions, the ability you used to do it will be disabled.
**Soul Link (Day) -** Spend 1 soul and choose two players. If 1 dies tonight, kill the other player as well. Infinite uses
**Haughty Wall (Night) -** Spend 2 souls to make yourself death immune tonight. You will also kill any attackers to yourself. This can’t be used two nights in a row. Infinite uses
**Wraith (Night) -** Spend 2 souls and send a wraith to kill a player. Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Mortician [/color] or [color=darkred] The Acolyte [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: Varies** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**1 Point Alts**
**Soul Melt**
**Soul Link - Blood Bonds (Day) -** Choose 2 players. If one is executed today, the other will die tonight. This will cost 2 souls if you have Soul Melt, otherwise 1 use
**Haughty Wall - Corax Phantom (Night) -** Prevent all visitors to a member of the Cult. Costs 2 souls if you have Soul Melt, otherwise 1 use
**2 Point Alts**
**Guilty Conscience - Murderous Intent (Passive) -** The next time the Cult Leader uses Eradicate, they will not consume a charge of it.
**Wraith - Summon Demon (Night) -** Summon a Demon to kill a player. 1 use :crown:

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Draketamer [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Killer** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled.
**Maul (Day) -** Cause a player to begin bleeding. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. 1 use
**Drake Attack (Night) -** Send your drake companion to kill a player. You will lose access to your abilities if this kills a member of the Regal Lions. 3 uses
**The Hunt Begins (Night) -** Cause a player to become permanently unhealable until you die or your class changes. 2 uses
&gt; 
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Dracorider [/color] or [color=darkred] The Acolyte [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Drake Attack - Phantasmal Strike (Night) -** Disguise yourself and every Cult member who is attacking as Regal Lion tonight. 2 uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Summoner [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Killer** [/color]
**Gale Beast (Day) -** Any day abilities targetting you today will be redirected to their users. 1 use
**Ignoble’s Dust (Day) -** Send a Vagrant’s phantom to kill the Lord tonight. He will not know this was done, and will die even if he is defended, but will survive if healed. If the Lord was a Venerable Lord, you will commit suicide. 1 use
**Duelist’s Phantom (Night) -** Summon a phantom to duel your target. You will bleed and occupy the target if they attempt to attack anyone tonight. 3 uses
**Warden’s Ghost (Night) -** Summon a ghost to defend a player. This ghost will kill any attackers to that player. If you successfully kill someone then your abilities will secretly do nothing the next night. Infinite uses :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Cantor [/color] or [color=darkred] The Acolyte [/color]**

&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult points: 2, Each ability costs: 1** [/color]
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Alts** [/color]
**Gale Beast - Blood on the Wind (Day) -** All day abilities targetting a selected Cult member will be redirected to their users. This can target yourself. 1 use
**Ignoble’s Dust - Dark Prominence (Day) -** Curse the Lord to die tonight if not healed. You will commit suicide if he was a Devout Lord. 1 use
**Duelist’s Phantom - Gladiator’s Demon (Night) -** Occupy and kill your target if they attempt to visit a member of the Cult tonight. 2 uses
**Warden’s Ghost - Angel of Mithras (Night) -** Deflects any oncoming attack to the Cult and kills the attacker. 3 uses

&gt; # [color=lightgreen] The Stargazer [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightgreen] **Regal Lion Special** [/color]
**Reach into the Void (Day) -** Conjure a power to use at night with Star’s Blessing. Each power must be used before conjuring the same one again. Infinite uses
**Star’s Blessing (Night) -** Use the power you have conjured. Infinite uses
**Rising Star -** Learn your target’s possible class types. 
**Cosmolight -** Learn which class types visit your target.
**Portal -** Redirect everyone targetting a player to another player.
**Falling Star -** The night after this one, kill your target. This power is disabled and removed from the rotation if you kill a Regal Lion with it.
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and Cult as well as any neutrals who stand in your way.*

&gt; **Converts to [color=purple] The Zodiac [/color] or [color=darkred] The Cabalist [/color]**

&gt; **The Cabalist has no Cult Alts**
[/details]

[details=&quot;Unseen&quot;]
&gt; # [color=purple] The Draconian Lord [/color] :crown: :fire: :shield: :crossed_swords: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Special** [/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. 
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day.
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Draconian Law (Day) -** Target player is permanently framed for the rest of the game. 1 use
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Enforcer (Night) -** Make a player unhealable tonight. 2 uses
**Corrupt Adviser (Night) -** Make a player immune to occupation, redirection, and visit prevention tonight. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Mastermind [/color] :crossed_swords: :shield: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Special** [/color]
&gt; **In the Shadows (Passive) -** You appear as a member of the Regal Lions to all investigations. 
&gt; **Can’t Touch This (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation, redirection, death, and bleeding. You will be notified if there is an attempt to bleed you.
&gt; **Dirty Work (Day) -** Swap places with the Assassin if they have the Apprentice passive, or become the Assassin and turn them into their previous converted class if they do not have it at the beginning of the night.1 use
&gt; **Convert (Night) -** Attempt to convert someone to the Unseen. If you fail 3 conversions, a random convertible player is converted instead. Infinite uses, with a 1-night cooldown on success.
&gt; **Foresight (Night) -** Learn a player’s class type if they were converted, or if they are conversion immune. 3 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Assassin [/color] :shield: :fire: :crossed_swords:   
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Apprentice (Passive) -** Take the Mastermind’s place if they die, become Lord, or use Dirty Work. You will pass this passive down to the current convert if you become Lord.
&gt; **Lacerate (Day) -** Slice a player’s artery, causing them to start bleeding. They will die in 2 nights if not healed. 3 uses (shared) :crown: 
&gt; **Distract (Day) -** Occupy target player for this day. 1 use (shared)
&gt; **Assassinate (Night) -** Attack and kill your target. Infinite uses :crown: 
&gt; **2-for-1 (Night) -** Kill two players. 1 use (Shared) :crown: 
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Agent [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled.
**Undercover Rebel (Passive) -** You will appear as The Constable to investigations, even if your class changes.
**Secret Service (Day) -** Send your Royal Service to keep tabs on a player. You will learn who they visit tonight. 2 uses
**Extensive Filing (Night) -** Choose any number of players and a Regal Lion class. You will learn if any of them are that class. Infinite uses
**Probe (Night) -** Learn target player’s class. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Chronologer [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**Darkest Night (Day) -** Choose a member of the Unseen. They will appear as a class of your choice to investigations tonight. 1 use
**Chronology (Night) -** Learn the Regal Lion classes that a player is visited by tonight. Infinite uses 
**The Hands of Fate (Night) -** Learn every class a player is visited by tonight, as well as which abilities they used. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Onmyoji [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**A Tale Unfolds (Passive) -** If the Mastermind dies and the Assassin is unable to take their place, you will become the new Mastermind. Keep this passive if you become the Assassin.
**Tarot Card (Day) -** Learn which negative effects happen to a player tonight. 3 uses
**Wind’s Calling (Night) -** Learn if a player has any passives, and if they have Royal Blood as well as any immunities they have. Infinite uses
**Doomsday Prophecy (Night) -** Learn who visits a member of the Unseen tonight and their factions. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Scholar [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**Fated Sigil (Day) -** Learn if any day abilities are used on your target and which ones. 2 uses :crown:
**Detailed Observations (Night) -** Learn who a player visits and who visits them. Infinite uses
**Bloodshot Eye (Night) -** Guess a player’s class type grouping. Class type groupings are Special/Investigative, Killer/Offensive, and Social/Support. If you are correct you will learn their class. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Enchantress [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Support** [/color]
**Magic Ward (Passive) -** You are immune to bleeding.
**Shadow Spell (Day) -** Tonight, the Assassin’s victims will be hurled into the void, hiding their flip and destroying their logs. 1 use
**Restoration Magic (Night) -** Heal a member of the Unseen and grant them Magic Ward for the next day. Infinite uses
**Black Hole (Night) -** Choose a player and redirect everyone targetting an Unseen member tonight to that player. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Count [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Support** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled.
**Black Market (Passive) -** If you become the Assassin, Lacerate and 2-for-1 will be replenished if they are used.
**Certify (Day) -** Grant someone the Royal Blood passive. 2 uses
**Extort (Night) -** Remove 1 use of a player’s limited usage abilities from them silently. 3 uses
**The Scapegoat (Night) -** Prevent all visits to a player aside from the Assassin’s. 1 use :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Activist [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Harsh Words (Night) -** Redirect a player to themself. Infinite uses
**Activism (Night) -** Remove a player’s immunities tonight, then occupy them. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Serf [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Social** [/color]
**Pseudo Lords (Passive) -** If a Royal is alive, all votes for you to become Lord are nullified. Votes for the other Unseen members to become Lord are doubled, however.
**House Party (Passive) -** You start in a neighborhood chat by yourself. People in this chat may speak freely with each other until you die. Keep this passive on class change.
**Uninvited Guests (Night) -** If your target visits you tonight, add them to the neighborhood chat. Unseen members will be added regardless if they visit you or not. Infinite uses
**Small Talk (Night) -** Redirect a player to yourself tomorrow night. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Necromancer [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Social** [/color]
**Grave Danger (Day) -** Your night abilities tonight will pull off of the Unseen versions of the dead target’s class. 2 uses
**Channel (Night) -** Use the unlimited usage ability of a deceased non-Killer Regal Lion player on an alive player. Each corpse can only be used once. Infinite uses :crown:
**Incomplete Resurrection (Night) -** Add the limited usage ability of a deceased non-Killer Regal Lion player to your class card, and remove this ability. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Retributionist [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Social** [/color]
**Ultimate Sacrifce (Day) -** If an Unseen member is being executed, sacrifice yourself to save them. You will flip as The Martyr. 2 uses
**Penitence (Night) -** Silently make all votes on your target tomorrow not count. Can’t target the same person twice in a row. Infinite uses :crown:
**Memento Mori (Night) -** Commit suicide tonight, killing you without fail, while also flipping as The Martyr. If the Mastermind’s next conversion would fail, the pity conversion will always be triggered. This ability will not work if you die by any other means tonight. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Showstopper [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled.
**Lecherous (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection at night. 
**Ballot Ballet (Day) -** Cause a player to require 1 less vote to be executed. 2 uses :crown:
**Tempting Tango (Night) -** Occupy a player for tonight. Infinite uses
**Devilish Duet (Night) -** Occupy 2 players tonight. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Flowergirl [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Dedicated (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection at night.
**Rafflesia (Day) -** All day abilities used on your target today will secretly fail. 2 uses :crown:
**Beehive! (Day) -** If your target uses a day ability today, they will be forced to target themself with it. 1 use
**Bitter Scent (Night) -** Redirect your first target to your second target tonight. Infinite uses
**Thorny Vines (Night) -** Prevent all visitors to a player. 2 uses :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Seamstress [/color] :fire: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Repulsive Attire (Passive) -** If a player visits someone dressed as their class, they will be prevented from visiting. 
**Tripwire (Day) -** Occupy target player for this day. 2 uses
**Dress Up (Night) -** Choose two players. Dress the first as the second. If anyone else visits one of your targets tonight you will occupy that target. Infinite uses
**Purple Strings (Night) -** Redirect two players to each other tonight. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Mortician [/color] :fire:
&gt; 
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Support** [/color]
**Soul Melt (Passive) -** You get a soul for everyone that dies at night. You retain the souls you had as an Exorcist. You are always aware of how many souls you have.
**Mortal Bonds (Day) -** Choose 2 players. Spend 2 souls to bind them together. If one is executed today the other will die tonight. Infinite uses
**Ectoplasmic Ritual (Night) -** Spend Souls to restore uses of The Assassin’s day abilities. Each use costs 2 souls. Infinite uses
**Possession (Night) -** Spend 2 souls to defile the Assassin’s kill as a class of your choice. Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Dracorider [/color] :fire:
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive) -** Votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled. 
**Dragon’s Hoard (Passive) -** If you become Lord, the Assassin will gain an additional use of 2-for-1.
**Maul (Day) -** Cause a player to begin bleeding. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. 1 use :crown:
**Drake Flame (Night) -** Kill anyone visiting the Assassin’s targets tonight. 1 use
**Wyvern in Hiding (Night) -** Kill 1 random visitor to a member of the Unseen. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Cantor [/color] :fire:
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Gale Fiend (Day) -** Choose a member of the Unseen and redirect all day abilities targetting them today to their users. 1 use
**Despot’s Shadow (Day) -** Send an accursed phantom after the Lord. He will not know this, and will die tonight if not healed. You will trigger the Tenacity penalty if they were Venerable, but will commit suicide if they were Draconian.
**Marauder Phantom (Night) -** If your target attempts to visit a member of the Unseen tonight, occupy and kill them. 2 uses
**Enforcer Apparition (Night) -** Deflect any oncoming attacks to members of the Unseen and kill the attackers. 3 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=purple] The Zodiac [/color] :fire: 
&gt; 
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Special** [/color]
**Reach into the Void (Day) -** Conjure a power to use tonight with Star’s Curse. Each power must be used once before it can be conjured again. Infinite uses
**Star’s Curse (Night) -** Use the power you have conjured. Infinite uses
**Nuclear Fission -** Tomorrow, the Assassin can use 2 day abilities.
**Event Horizon -** The Assassin will hurl his victims into the void tonight, hiding their flip and destroying their logs.
**Quasar -** Learn a player’s class type and the class types that visit them tonight.
**Comet -** Redirect anyone targetting an Unseen member to another player.
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Cult”]
&gt; # [color=darkred] The Devout Lord [/color] :crown: :fire: :crossed_swords: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Special** [/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. 
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day. 
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Blasphemous Law (Day) -** If your target is Cult, restock 1 use in all of their limited usage abilities tonight silently. 1 use (Starting Devout Lord only)
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Priest Lord (Night) -** If 1 or less Cult members aside from you remain, convert your target to the Cult. This ability is refunded if there are multiple Cult members alive and it fails. 1 use (starting Devout Lord only)
**Heretical Decree (Night) -** Use an unlimited usage ability held by a deceased non-Cult Leader Cult member on an alive player. You may only use each corpse once. Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=darkred] The Cult Leader [/color] :shield: :fire: :crossed_swords: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Special** [/color]
**Train (Passive) -** At the start of the game, you may choose your starting Cultist’s Cult Alts. This passive does not apply if The Cabalist spawned, and if you do not choose by Night 1 it will be randomized. Starting Cult Leader only.
**Rupture (Day) -** Cause a player to begin bleeding. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. 1 use
**Transfer Essence (Day) -** Swap places with a member of the Cult, inheriting their Cult Point selections. 2 uses (shared)
**Sacrifice (Day) -** Sacrifice yourself to Mithras, flipping as a class of your choice and restoring 2 uses of Eradicate. This only works if you don’t die by other means tonight. 1 use
**Brainwash (Night) -** Convert a player to the Cult. If you have failed 2 conversions before and fail another one, a random player will be converted instead. Infinite uses, with a 1 night cooldown on success
**Eradicate (Night) -** Channel the power of Mithras to attack 2 players. 2 uses (shared)
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=darkred] The Seeker [/color] :crossed_swords: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Investigative** [/color]
**Expose (Day) -** Learn who has been sentenced by the Executioner. 1 use
**Gaze (Night) -** Get a player’s class type grouping. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=darkred] The Ritualist [/color] :crossed_swords: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Support** [/color]
**Will of Mithras (Day) -** Tonight, a selected Cult member will appear as Regal Lion to investigations. 1 use
**Strength of Corax (Night) -** The Cult Leader is guaranteed to visit their targets tonight. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=darkred] The Apostle [/color] :crossed_swords: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Social** [/color]
**Dark Words (Passive) -** Dead Cult members may speak in the Cult chat while you live.
**Mind Warp (Night) -** Frame a player tonight. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=darkred] The Invoker [/color] :crossed_swords: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Offensive** [/color]
**Unhinged (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection at night.
**Bewilder (Day) -** If your target uses a day ability today, they will be forced to target themself. 1 use
**Strings of Corax (Night) -** Redirect a player to themself. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=darkred] The Acolyte [/color] :crossed_swords: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Killer** [/color]
**Eminence of Mithras (Day) -** Target player will be unhealable tonight. 1 use
**Curse of Mithras (Night) -** If target player is bled tomorrow, they will die a night early. 1 use :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*

&gt; # [color=darkred] The Cabalist [/color] :crossed_swords: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred] **Cult Special** [/color]
**Shape Flesh (Night) -** Shape flesh into one of four powers to use. Each one can only be used once.
**Voodoo Doll -** The Cult Leader can choose a third target of Eradicate tonight at the cost of bleeding you if they do.
**Corrupt Intervention -** Redirect everyone targetting a player to another.
**Jinx -** Learn which class types visit a player.
**Blood Moon -** If target player dies tonight, hurl them into the void, hiding their flip and destroying their logs. :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Regal Lions and any neutrals who would oppose your cause.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Neutral non-Killers&quot;]
&gt; # [color=savannah] The Worshipper [/color] :fire: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=savannah] **Neutral Support** [/color]
&gt; **You Are my Everything (Passive) -** Before the end of Night 1, you must choose a player to worship. They will become your target. If you do not, it will be randomized. If this player is ever unable to win or wins early, you will commit suicide.
&gt; **Sweet Talk (Passive) -** If the one you worship is not aligned with the Regal Lions, you will survive the first attack on you. 
&gt;
&gt; **Comparison (Day) -** Choose a player and see if they can win with your target as their current class. Unusable Day 1, and unusable if your target is dead. You will receive the results at the end of the night. 3 uses
&gt; **Ambush (Day) -** Slice a player with a dagger and bleed them. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. 1 use :crown:
&gt;
&gt; **Watchful Eye (Night) -** Prevent all non-conversion visits to your target. If your target is dead, you may target anyone you have identified as able to win with your target. 3 uses :crown:
&gt; **True Fanaticism (Night) -** Kill 1 random visitor to your target that is not of their faction. 1 use :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Ensure your target wins the game*

&gt; # [color=savannah] The Obedient Lord [/color] :crown: :fire: :shield:
&gt;
&gt; [color=savannah] **Neutral Special** [/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. 
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day. 
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Fanatical Law (Day) -** Relinquish the throne, reverting to The Worshipper. Your target will instantly become the new Lord. 1 use
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Merciless Dagger (Night) -** Prevent all non-conversion visits to your target tonight, and kill 1 random visitor to them not of their faction. This can target those who you’ve identified as able to win with your target if your target is dead. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Ensure your target wins the game.*

&gt; # [color=orange] The Fiddler [/color] :fire: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=orange] **Neutral Social** [/color]
**The Fiddle Plays For Thee (Passive)**  - If you are executed, all of the players who voted to execute you will gain death immunity and occupation and redirection immunity for the current night. If you were executed by majority, then there will be a second lynch for the day.
**Last Gift of the Fiddler (Passive)**  - Upon achieving your win condition at the end of the day, you will leave the match, all members of the Regal Lions that voted for you will be occupied for the night, and all Neutral, and Cult or Unseen players will gain an additional usage of their limited-use abilities. You cannot die to attacks by players who are not members of the Regal Lions.
**Brown Note (Day) -** Make a player believe they are bleeding. 2 uses :crown: 
**Sojourn (Night) -** Visit a player. This does absolutely nothing. Infinite uses :crown: 
&gt;
&gt; *Have at least 2/3 of the votes needed to execute you or be at L-1 during a day and survive that day.*

&gt; # [color=orange] The Fiddling Lord [/color] :fire: :shield: :crown:   
&gt;
&gt; [color=orange] **Neutral Special** [/color]
**Fiddle as Regalia Burns (Passive) -** If you die at night or by execution, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. You will retain The Fiddle Plays for Thee and Last Gift of the Fiddler. If you achieve your win condition, there will be no more Lords.
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day. 
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Foolish Law (Day) -** Cause a player to believe they started bleeding. 2 uses
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt; *Have at least 2/3 of the votes needed to lynch you or be at L-1 during a day and survive that day.*

&gt; # [color=deeporange] The Chancellor [/color] :shield: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=deeporange] **Neutral Social** [/color]
&gt; **Malevolent Tutor (Passive)**  - At the start of the game, you will have two random Regal Lion players who are not the Executioner assigned to you as your Protégés. Neither Protégé will know that they are your Protégé and you will know which classes they are, and if they get converted or not. In addition, a Regal Lion-aligned Protégé that becomes Lord while you are alive will become a Spiteful Lord instead of a Venerable Lord.
**Behind the Scenes (Passive)**  - You cannot be killed at night by players who are not members of the Regal Lions, and votes to you for Lord count as 0.
**Sinister Negotiations (Day)**  - Sends an anonymous message to the Unseen or Cult chat. - Three uses
**Defamatory Propaganda (Day)**  - Removes Royal Blood from a player. - 2 uses
**Bodyguards (Night)**  - Prevents a Protégé from dying at night. - 3 uses :crown: 
**Nightshade Tea (Night)**  - If you are in the Lord’s nightchat tonight, poison them, killing them bypassing everything - One use :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to see a Protègè becomes Lord, then ensure a Protègè who is Lord survives the game.*

&gt; **While the Chancellor normally cannot become Lord, if an Obedient Lord forces him onto the throne, the Chancellor will become a Spiteful Lord.**

&gt; # [color=skyblue] The Oneiromancer [/color] :fire: :shield:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=skyblue] **Neutral Social** [/color]
**Dream Sphere (Passive) -** You will create an empty neighborhood known as the Dream Sphere at the start of the match (you aren’t in it).
**Sleep Paralysis (Passive) -** You cannot die at night for the first three nights. If you die, anyone in the Dream Sphere will also die with you.
**Deep Slumber (Day) -** Add a player to the Dream Sphere. Infinite uses
**Lucid Dreams (Day) -** Send an anonymous message to the Dream Sphere. This can be done up to three times per day and is usable alongside Deep Slumber. Infinite uses
**Dreamscape (Night) -** Choose between healing, occupying, redirecting, or learning the class type of a player in the Dream Sphere. Infinite uses
**Somnabulist’s Fog (Night) -** All votes on you from players in the Dream Sphere will silently not count tomorrow. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Survive whilst the majority of players besides yourself are in the Dream Sphere at the end of the game.*

&gt; # [color=skyblue] The Dreaming Lord [/color] :fire: :shield: :crown:   
&gt;
&gt; [color=skyblue] **Neutral Special** [/color]
**Forlorn Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. All players within the Dream Sphere will die should you die. You may send three anonymous messages to the Dream Sphere every day.
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use both day abilities in the same day. 
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Allies and Dreams (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with yourself for tonight, and choose a third player to add to the Dream Sphere. Infinite uses
**Forlorn Law (Night) -** Heal, occupy, redirect or learn the class type of a player in the Dream Sphere. Infinite uses
**Somnabulist’s Fog (Night) -** All votes on you from players in the Dream Sphere will silently not count tomorrow. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Survive whilst the majority of players besides yourself are in the Dream Sphere at the end of the game.*

&gt; # [color=sienna] The Umbraphile [/color] :fire: :shield:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=sienna] **Neutral Offensive** [/color]
**Paranoia (Passive) -** You will survive the first non Regal Lion attack on yourself. You will appear as a member of the Unseen or Cult to investigations on yourself.
**Pure Wits (Day) -** Learn if a player uses Pure Magic. The Diviner, Mage, Scribe, Florist, Exorcist, Draketamer, Stargazer, Resurrectionist, and Martyr use Pure Magic. If you check a converted form of these classes, you learn that they use Dark Magic instead. 3 uses
**Vengeful Strike (Day) -** Kill a Pure Magic user you’ve found in broad daylight. 1 use
**Menacing Stance (Night) -** Prevent all non attacking and non converting visits to a player. If that player uses Pure Magic, occupy them as well. 3 uses
**Dark Shroud (Night) -** Make an identified Dark Magic user appear as Regal Lion to investigations tonight. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Ensure the Regal Lions lose*

&gt; # [color=lavender] The Hex Master [/color] :fire: :shield:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=lavender] **Neutral Offensive** [/color]
**Forbidden Magic (Passive) -** You are immune to the first non Regal Lion attack on you and are immune to occupation and redirection at night. You appear as the evil faction to investigations.
**Vulnerability Hex (Day) -** All healing on your target will fail tonight. 2 uses
**Meticulous Trick (Night) -** Choose 2 players. Occupy them both if someone visits either of them. Infinite uses
**Finale Hex (Night) -** The first person you vote tomorrow will be instantly executed. You will also commit suicide upon voting. The day will still go on normally, however. 1 use
&gt;
&gt; *Ensure the Regal Lions lose.*

&gt; # [color=turquoise] The Spiteful Lord [/color] :fire: :shield: :crown:   
&gt;
&gt; [color=turquoise] **Neutral Special** [/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. 
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day. 
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Spiteful Law (Day) -** Occupy target player for this day. 1 use
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Vulnerability Hex (Night) -** Target player will be unhealable tonight. 2 uses
**Stonewall (Night) -** Prevent all non attacking and non converting visitors to a player. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Ensure the Regal Lions lose*

&gt; # [color=pink] The Comic [/color] :fire: :shield:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=pink] **Neutral Social** [/color]
**Crazed (Passive) -** You are immune to non Regal Lion attacks. If you win early you will leave the game.
**Stalk (Day) -** Learn target player’s faction instantly. 1 use
**Unsettle (Night) -** Cause a player to receive incorrect feedback from their abilities tonight. Infinite uses
**Distorted Time (Night) -** If target player is executed tomorrow, they will flip as a class of your choice, and you may give them false logs. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Ensure 3 or more Regal Lion players are executed or survive to see the Regal Lions lose.*

&gt; # [color=pink] The Comical Lord [/color] :fire: :shield: :crown:   
&gt;
&gt; [color=pink] **Neutral Special** [/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. 
**Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day. 
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Unhinged Law (Day) -** Silently add a vote to a player. 1 use
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Manifested Hatred (Night) -** Cause 2 players to receive incorrect feedback from their abilities tonight. Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt; *Ensure 3 or more Regal Lion players are executed or survive to see the Regal Lions lose.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Neutral Killers&quot;]

&gt; # [color=violet] **The Astromancer** [/color] :shield: :fire:  
&gt; 
&gt; [color=violet] **Neutral Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Untouchable (Passive) -** You are immune to death, bleeding, occupation, and redirection, and will not be seen visiting your targets. You will be informed if any of these are attempted on you.
&gt; **Omniscient (Passive) -** You will learn the true classes of defiled and voided players.
&gt; **Outer Void (Day) -** Anyone killed by your hand tonight will be hurled into the void, hiding their flip and destroying their logs. 2 uses
&gt; **Inner Cosmos (Day) -** Cover yourself in a veil of stardust, allowing you to appear as a class of your choice tonight to investigations. Additionally, you may submit a player you will be appearing to visit tonight. 2 uses
&gt; **Stargaze (Night) -** Summon a meteor upon a player, killing them. Infinite uses :crown: 
&gt; **Doomsday (Night) -** Condemn a player to death. You may choose a night past this one where that player will die bypassing anything that would save them. Additionally, all visitors to that player upon that night are attacked as well. 2 uses :crown: 
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to be in the final 4 players while the evil faction cannot execute you on their own.*

&gt; # [color=gold] The Imperialist [/color] :shield: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=gold] **Neutral Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Last of a Dynasty (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation, redirection, bleeding and death, and will be informed if someone tries to bleed you. Additionally, votes for you to become the next Lord are doubled. You will crown into the Imperialistic Lord instead of the Psychopathic Lord.
&gt; **Imperial Providence (Day) -** If there is a Lord nomination tomorrow, only your vote will count for it. 1 use
&gt; **Imposing Presence (Day) -** Silently make a player require 2 less votes to be executed. If 7 or less players are alive, make them require 1 less vote. 2 uses :crown: 
&gt; **Champion’s Slash (Night) -** Attack a player with a greatsword, killing them. Infinite uses :crown: 
&gt; **Imperial Judgment (Night) -** Attack two players tonight. Only usable if a member of the Regal Lions was executed yesterday. 2 uses :crown: 
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to the final 4 players while the evil faction cannot execute you on their own.*

&gt; # [color=lightblue] The Zealot [/color] :fire: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightblue] **Neutral Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Zealous Pursuit (Passive) -** At the start of the game 2 players are chosen as heathens. If one dies, a new player is chosen as a heathen. You will always know the heathen’s classes.
&gt; **Holy Blessing (Passive) -** You cannot die at night, other than to the Executioner’s execution.
&gt; **Interrogate (Day) -** Discover if a player is a heathen. Infinite uses :crown: 
&gt; **Sentence (Day) -** Choose someone who has been found as a heathen. They will be kidnapped and will be occupied bypassing occupation immunity. Additionally, they and you may send 2 10000 character messages to each other through the host. 3 uses
&gt; **Dispose of Filth (Night) -** Attack a player, this attack is unhealable. Unusable if you used Sentence today. Infinite uses :crown: 
&gt; **Pyre’s Flames (Night) -** Ignite the player you have sentenced, killing them and any visitors they may have. This will bypass death immunity. You will destroy their logs and may insert new logs in their place. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to the final 4 players while the evil faction cannot execute you on their own.*

&gt; # [color=lightcyan] The Frostweaver [/color] :shield: :fire:
&gt;
&gt; [color=lightcyan] **Neutral Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Frozen Guard (Passive) -** You are immune to bleeding and death, and you will be notified if someone tries to bleed you.
&gt; **Gangrenous Wounds (Passive) -** Anyone bled during the day will die 1 day earlier while you live.
&gt; **Snap Freeze (Day) -** Cause a player to begin bleeding. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. 2 uses :crown:
&gt; **Impassable Blizzard (Day) -** Prevent all visitors to yourself tonight. 2 uses
&gt; **Ice Spike (Night) -** Impale a player with spikes made of ice, killing them. You will also learn who visited your target that night, and may bleed one of these players the next day whenever you wish. Infinite uses :crown:
&gt; **Absolute Zero (Night) -** Put a player’s room into cryo-stasis, killing them and any visitors they had, as well as occupying the target bypassing immunity to occupation, and preventing all visitors. 2 uses :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to the final 4 players while the evil faction cannot execute you on their own.*

&gt; # [color=indigo] The Darkstalker [/color] :fire: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=indigo] **Neutral Killer** [/color]
**In Darkness I Reside (Passive) -** You are immune to bleeding and death, and will be informed if somebody tries to bleed you. All visits to you at night by a cursed player are prevented.
**Shackles of the Damned (Passive) -** If somebody ever claims their true class, you may quote that post in your class card and curse them. All healing will fail on cursed players, and they will not know they are cursed.
**Damnation (Day) -** Choose a cursed player. They will die tonight. This is a normal kill that will not benefit from the effects of a curse. Infinite uses
**Cloak of Shadows (Day) -** In the coming night you will be immune to occupation and redirection. 2 uses
**Phantom Force (Night) -** Strike from the shadows and kill a player. Attacking a cursed player will hide your visits. Infinite uses :crown: 
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to the final 4 players while the evil faction cannot execute you on their own.*

&gt; # [color=rainbow] The Psychopathic Lord [/color] :shield: :crown: :fire:  
&gt;
&gt; [color=rainbow] **Neutral Special** [/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. 
**Deadly Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation, death, bleeding, and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use both day abilities in the same day. You will be notified if someone tries to bleed you.
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Private Execution (Night) -** Send a guard to kill a player. Infinite uses
**Psychopathic Law (Night) -** Kill a player, bypassing anything that could stop you. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to the final 4 players while the evil faction cannot execute you on their own.*

&gt; # [color=gold] The Imperialistic Lord [/color] :fire: :shield: :crown:   
&gt;
&gt; [color=gold] **Neutral Special** [/color]
**Inheritance (Passive) -** If you die, there will be a vote to nominate a new Lord. 
**Deadly Tenacity (Passive) -** You are immune to occupation, death, bleeding, and redirection. Your abilities do not count as visits. You can use all day abilities in the same day. You will be notified if someone tries to bleed you.
**Trial By Council (Day) -** Choose 4 players other than yourself. They will be unable to be executed today, and must unanimously decide who will be executed today amongst themselves. 1 use
**Imperialistic Law (Day) -** Cause someone to require 2 less votes to be executed. If 7 or less players remain, make them require 1 less vote. 2 uses
**Allies (Day) -** Choose two players who will share a night chat with you tonight. Infinite uses
**Royal Slash (Night) -** Kill a player, bypassing anything that would stop the kill. Infinite uses
**The Lord’s Judgment (Night) -** Kill two players without fail. Only usable if a member of the Regal Lions was executed yesterday. 2 uses
&gt;
&gt; *Survive to the final 4 players while the evil faction cannot execute you on their own.*
[/details]

## Playerlist 
1. an_gorta_pratai (Pre-In)
2. Chloe
3. Jane
4. Wazza
5. PsychoKang
6. Blizer
7. Centuries
8. CRichard564
9. EightySecond
10. highway_101
11. mathmods
12. Apprentice
13. UnknownTraveler
14. PokemonKidRyan
15. Anstreim
16. Arete
17. ModeShifter
18. Magnus

## Backups
1. TheBlueElixir
2. 

## Spectators
Spectators are not informed, but they will have access to a thread where they can discuss the game state.
1. Astand
2. DatBird
3. Marshal
4. katze
5. sulit
6. Italy
7. KyoDaz
8. Appelsiini
9. Frostwolf103</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 19:37:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Signups</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Napoleon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/uninformed spec</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/224">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/224</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 19:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-224</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Ffs I ran out of new topics and have to wait 6 hours</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/223">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/223</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 14:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-223</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>All class cards have been sent out and a new thread for the game will be created imminently. If you did not receive a class card, DM me. Do not say so in the thread.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/222">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/222</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 14:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-222</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Class cards will now be sent out</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/221">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/221</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 14:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-221</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Well it seems this filled while I was sleeping. The randing process will now begin. Please do not speak anymore in this thread.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/220">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/220</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 13:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-220</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Blizer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i know the game is being randed but i noticed something that bothered me slightly, and that was infinite Allies lol.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/219">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/219</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 12:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-219</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/spectate</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/218">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/218</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 12:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-218</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Appelsiini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/spectate</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/217">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/217</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 10:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-217</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/Amelia">@Amelia</a></p>
<p>game filled.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/216">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/216</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 10:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-216</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/In</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/215">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/215</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 10:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-215</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CRichard564]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That is when the wait is longest. I mean if I get EK that would be a nice change <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> .</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/214">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/214</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 08:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-214</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1 more 1 more</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/213">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/213</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-213</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>there is no meme<br>
get out of my image folder</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/212">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/212</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 06:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-212</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Italy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i see how it is</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/211">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/211</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 06:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-211</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Amelia" data-post="1" data-topic="82634">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/amelia/40/35432_2.png" class="avatar"> Amelia:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>katze</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>nooooooo kat <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/210">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/210</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 06:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-210</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/In</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/209">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/209</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 05:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-209</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CRichard564]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Two more slots left reeeeeee.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/208">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/208</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 04:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-208</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/spectate</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/207">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/207</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 03:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-207</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Italy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/spectate</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/206">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/206</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-206</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Italy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it will be full of nothing but memes</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/205">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/205</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-205</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chloe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>can we give italy a post requirement</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/204">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/204</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-204</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>join regularly reeee</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/203">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/203</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-203</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Italy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>do i join backup or spectate<br>
hmmmm</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/202">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/202</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-202</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>how different is this from regular FoL classes?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/201">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/201</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-201</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>no</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/200">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634/200</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 01:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82634-200</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-62-regal-lions-signups-18-18-full/82634.rss">SFoL 62: Regal Lions - Signups (18/18) - FULL</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
