<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A life full of hatred. [Lore Suggestion for The Scorned]</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-life-full-of-hatred-lore-suggestion-for-the-scorned/73244</link>
    <description>Every human should have the same chances when they are born.

 She didn&#39;t get what she deserved, and now she is pointing at others. When she was a child, no one helped the poor orphan. They didn&#39;t even give her some food. She tried to learn how to hunt, but the Hunter caught her and kicked her out of the forest. She was hungry, so she stole a loaf of bread from a Noble.
 
The Prince imprisoned her, and told her &quot;this is for the good of the people&quot;. He didn&#39;t execute her, because she was young. When she was released, she was hungry yet again. The Prince didn&#39;t give her food, because &quot;she has to learn a lesson&quot;. 

The torture of hunger damaged her sanity, and only her instincts remained. Everything she has seen, she stole and ate. Once she got caught, she didn&#39;t care, so the Prince let the people of the castle throw anything at her, punish her as much as they want to. That broke her mind. 

Everyone was surprised, after all of this, she wasn&#39;t angry. No one saw any emotions from her, until one of her tormentors got executed. Then she smiled. And gained a new life goal: to see the ones that hurt her die. This new kind of feeling kept her going. Nowadays - it is told by rumours - she doesn&#39;t even have to eat and only pure hatred remained in her eyes. 

**&quot;I do this only because I enjoy it. If I die, it doesn&#39;t matter. I already lost everything.&quot;** - _The Scorned_</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-life-full-of-hatred-lore-suggestion-for-the-scorned/73244.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A life full of hatred. [Lore Suggestion for The Scorned]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markneu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Every human should have the same chances when they are born.</p>
<p>She didn’t get what she deserved, and now she is pointing at others. When she was a child, no one helped the poor orphan. They didn’t even give her some food. She tried to learn how to hunt, but the Hunter caught her and kicked her out of the forest. She was hungry, so she stole a loaf of bread from a Noble.</p>
<p>The Prince imprisoned her, and told her “this is for the good of the people”. He didn’t execute her, because she was young. When she was released, she was hungry yet again. The Prince didn’t give her food, because “she has to learn a lesson”.</p>
<p>The torture of hunger damaged her sanity, and only her instincts remained. Everything she has seen, she stole and ate. Once she got caught, she didn’t care, so the Prince let the people of the castle throw anything at her, punish her as much as they want to. That broke her mind.</p>
<p>Everyone was surprised, after all of this, she wasn’t angry. No one saw any emotions from her, until one of her tormentors got executed. Then she smiled. And gained a new life goal: to see the ones that hurt her die. This new kind of feeling kept her going. Nowadays - it is told by rumours - she doesn’t even have to eat and only pure hatred remained in her eyes.</p>
<p><strong>"I do this only because I enjoy it. If I die, it doesn’t matter. I already lost everything."</strong> - <em>The Scorned</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-life-full-of-hatred-lore-suggestion-for-the-scorned/73244/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-life-full-of-hatred-lore-suggestion-for-the-scorned/73244/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73244-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-life-full-of-hatred-lore-suggestion-for-the-scorned/73244.rss">A life full of hatred. [Lore Suggestion for The Scorned]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
