<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stuck at main menu</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176</link>
    <description>#### What happened?

I just bought the game yesterday, and after looking at the tutorial, the rules, the guide, and the classes, I went to find a game and clicked start solo. I then got the message &quot;Timed Out (Reconnecting...)&quot;. It never reconnected. I then tried creating a group, but got the message &quot;Verifying Version...&quot;. It never changed. I then tried to enter an invite code, but got the message &quot;Something&#39;s Wrong: Tell a Dev in Discord&quot;. I verified integrity of game files through steam and it said &quot;1 file failed to validate and will be required&quot;. Tried finding a match, same thing happens. Re-verify the game integrity, same message again. I tried re-verifying the game integrity once more before trying again, and this time it said &quot;All files successfully validated&quot;.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?

The game should have let me found a match solo, create a group, and join a game through the enter an invite code.

#### Steps to reproduce:

I open the game
Login with Steam
See that the find match box has ? players online, ? rooms(matches), and ? in Lobby.
Click start solo (it is flashing immediately after login with steam) or find game, the Ready text sometimes stays the same or changes to timed out.
Try clicking create group, it returns verifying version...
If I find a code through the discord, I enter it in the enter invite code, and I get an error message.
Exit game and verify integrity of the game files twice.
The first try it repairs a file, the second try it says everything is validated.
Repeat steps.

#### Comments:
I&#39;ve tried restarting my computer and turning off and on my wifi.
I am on v1.0.7b at the time of writing this, and prior to running all these steps again today, I received a new update to this game (the game wasn&#39;t working prior to the update today). I can post images if needed.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 18:34:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Stuck at main menu</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TryphonX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is an issue the devs are working on fixing. It’s currently confirmed that there is something wrong (not for everyone) and the devs are looking into it. Thanks for the report, I hope it gets fixed soon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 18:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8176-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176.rss">Stuck at main menu</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Stuck at main menu</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[phillies27]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>I just bought the game yesterday, and after looking at the tutorial, the rules, the guide, and the classes, I went to find a game and clicked start solo. I then got the message “Timed Out (Reconnecting…)”. It never reconnected. I then tried creating a group, but got the message “Verifying Version…”. It never changed. I then tried to enter an invite code, but got the message “Something’s Wrong: Tell a Dev in Discord”. I verified integrity of game files through steam and it said “1 file failed to validate and will be required”. Tried finding a match, same thing happens. Re-verify the game integrity, same message again. I tried re-verifying the game integrity once more before trying again, and this time it said “All files successfully validated”.</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>The game should have let me found a match solo, create a group, and join a game through the enter an invite code.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<p>I open the game<br>
Login with Steam<br>
See that the find match box has ? players online, ? rooms(matches), and ? in Lobby.<br>
Click start solo (it is flashing immediately after login with steam) or find game, the Ready text sometimes stays the same or changes to timed out.<br>
Try clicking create group, it returns verifying version…<br>
If I find a code through the discord, I enter it in the enter invite code, and I get an error message.<br>
Exit game and verify integrity of the game files twice.<br>
The first try it repairs a file, the second try it says everything is validated.<br>
Repeat steps.</p>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>I’ve tried restarting my computer and turning off and on my wifi.<br>
I am on v1.0.7b at the time of writing this, and prior to running all these steps again today, I received a new update to this game (the game wasn’t working prior to the update today). I can post images if needed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 17:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8176-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/stuck-at-main-menu/8176.rss">Stuck at main menu</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
