<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Friendly Reminder about Attitudes and the Influx of New People</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881</link>
    <description>

This game is exploding in popularity and we have an influx of new people. This is great for the health of the community and the game itself.

Three things:

1) **This is quite the complex game and knowing the mechanics and intricacies can take time.**

I was just in a game where they immediately killed a Sheriff because he was the last person the Drunk Debauched.

The Sheriff didn&#39;t understand why he was being accused and didn&#39;t do a good job defending himself because he didn&#39;t understand how Drunk works and it was his first game.

The people in the game were assholes to him, logs called him &quot;Bad Sheriff&quot; or &quot;Dumb Sheriff.&quot;

While this is particularly difficult because sometimes people *will* strategically pretend to be a new player but for now, let&#39;s give people the benefit of the doubt and be a little more understanding and welcoming.

-------------------------------------


2) **If you&#39;re new don&#39;t be afraid to introduce yourself and let people know it&#39;s one of your first games and you might need help/pointers/tips.**

It would also help to watch streamers play on twitch - there will usually be people live who are happy to answer your questions.

The discord is an active happy space to discuss the game and ask questions.

-------------------------------------

3) **Stop being so salty!** 

This is a game where you murder and backstab and lie and trick people but for the most part, it&#39;s all in good fun and we&#39;re in character during the game.

But after the match is over it&#39;s pretty lame to say &quot;omg prince you were terrible&quot; or &quot;i can&#39;t believe what a worthless king we had&quot; etc. 

Take that time to provide people constructive criticism. I had a game just now where we would have won if the Prince jailed the last convertable target but he messed up and we ended up losing. I&#39;m not sure he even realized what he did wrong because he was just getting flamed like crazy at the end and he left. 

I love telling people their plays were clever or awesome, even if lost the game.

Let&#39;s be a welcoming and understanding community and educate people on what they can do better so we can have clever and entertaining games.

I look forward to killing all of you baddies.

Love,

livejamie</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 21:38:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Friendly Reminder about Attitudes and the Influx of New People</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t want people to be good at the game, if they are bad they are easier to manipulate/lead</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 21:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7881-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881.rss">Friendly Reminder about Attitudes and the Influx of New People</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Friendly Reminder about Attitudes and the Influx of New People</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m curious to see how this community will evolve now that the game is public and “live”.</p>
<p>It definitely causes a lot of salt when teammates don’t act the way you want them to, but remember that that is part of the game. The only way baddies can win is if the good guys make mistakes. Everyone makes those mistakes, even you, dear reader.</p>
<p>The amount of trolling and salt has definitely increased lately, but that’s to be expected with an increase in population. I had a Merc and a Neutral King flame me in night chat (the Butler) after getting them both killed. I poisoned the King and pushed a lynch on the possibly converted Merc since he hadn’t guarded me in 3 nights. Both were besides themselves with anger afterward. A Blue Dragon killing Neutral players is not gamethrowing, nor is it even a bad idea.</p>
<p>Prepare yourself for the salt mines, and bring a pickax.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 21:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7881-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881.rss">Friendly Reminder about Attitudes and the Influx of New People</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Friendly Reminder about Attitudes and the Influx of New People</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This game is exploding in popularity and we have an influx of new people. This is great for the health of the community and the game itself.</p>
<p>Three things:</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>This is quite the complex game and knowing the mechanics and intricacies can take time.</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>I was just in a game where they immediately killed a Sheriff because he was the last person the Drunk Debauched.</p>
<p>The Sheriff didn’t understand why he was being accused and didn’t do a good job defending himself because he didn’t understand how Drunk works and it was his first game.</p>
<p>The people in the game were assholes to him, logs called him “Bad Sheriff” or “Dumb Sheriff.”</p>
<p>While this is particularly difficult because sometimes people <em>will</em> strategically pretend to be a new player but for now, let’s give people the benefit of the doubt and be a little more understanding and welcoming.</p>
<hr>
<ol start="2">
<li><strong>If you’re new don’t be afraid to introduce yourself and let people know it’s one of your first games and you might need help/pointers/tips.</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>It would also help to watch streamers play on twitch - there will usually be people live who are happy to answer your questions.</p>
<p>The discord is an active happy space to discuss the game and ask questions.</p>
<hr>
<ol start="3">
<li><strong>Stop being so salty!</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>This is a game where you murder and backstab and lie and trick people but for the most part, it’s all in good fun and we’re in character during the game.</p>
<p>But after the match is over it’s pretty lame to say “omg prince you were terrible” or “i can’t believe what a worthless king we had” etc.</p>
<p>Take that time to provide people constructive criticism. I had a game just now where we would have won if the Prince jailed the last convertable target but he messed up and we ended up losing. I’m not sure he even realized what he did wrong because he was just getting flamed like crazy at the end and he left.</p>
<p>I love telling people their plays were clever or awesome, even if lost the game.</p>
<p>Let’s be a welcoming and understanding community and educate people on what they can do better so we can have clever and entertaining games.</p>
<p>I look forward to killing all of you baddies.</p>
<p>Love,</p>
<p>livejamie</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 20:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7881-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friendly-reminder-about-attitudes-and-the-influx-of-new-people/7881.rss">Friendly Reminder about Attitudes and the Influx of New People</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
