<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore suggestion] The Noble (Class bio)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-noble-class-bio/6820</link>
    <description>Page: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Noble

Lore topic: The noble, noble

Lore:

Castle Adiart has often housed a fair amount of what could only ever be considered as &quot;Guests of honour&quot;. While this also contains those such as the drunk who have given up on their pursuit of the throne, The noble is here because their pursuit of the throne knows no bounds. Their influence in their respective villages have earned the right to be close to the king, yet still family, they lack the heart to slit their throats. Thus the noble has put their power into the art of espionage and sabotage. Hoping that throwing themselves headfirst into the dangers of politics and corruption of state will eventually lead to their ascension through heroics of pen and paper. Through blackmail, treaties, subpoenas, childhood promises and even promises of love and affection the Noble controls the flow of democracy and the small inner working of the castle. Servants will report to them, Criers will relay their messages at morning breakfast and even other members of the court respect their wishes when silence is the preferable option. 

Last in line to the throne, But first in line with the people. The noble utilises the delicate touch that only those without the stigma of blood and violence can ever uphold. And with Adiart rife with murder and intrigue the Blue Dragon may just need a quill and parchment to stem the injustices of the unseen.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 16:00:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-noble-class-bio/6820.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] The Noble (Class bio)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Page: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Noble" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Noble</a></p>
<p>Lore topic: The noble, noble</p>
<p>Lore:</p>
<p>Castle Adiart has often housed a fair amount of what could only ever be considered as “Guests of honour”. While this also contains those such as the drunk who have given up on their pursuit of the throne, The noble is here because their pursuit of the throne knows no bounds. Their influence in their respective villages have earned the right to be close to the king, yet still family, they lack the heart to slit their throats. Thus the noble has put their power into the art of espionage and sabotage. Hoping that throwing themselves headfirst into the dangers of politics and corruption of state will eventually lead to their ascension through heroics of pen and paper. Through blackmail, treaties, subpoenas, childhood promises and even promises of love and affection the Noble controls the flow of democracy and the small inner working of the castle. Servants will report to them, Criers will relay their messages at morning breakfast and even other members of the court respect their wishes when silence is the preferable option.</p>
<p>Last in line to the throne, But first in line with the people. The noble utilises the delicate touch that only those without the stigma of blood and violence can ever uphold. And with Adiart rife with murder and intrigue the Blue Dragon may just need a quill and parchment to stem the injustices of the unseen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-noble-class-bio/6820/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-noble-class-bio/6820/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 15:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6820-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-noble-class-bio/6820.rss">[Lore suggestion] The Noble (Class bio)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
