<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720</link>
    <description>**Father Time - (Neutral Killer)** This NK manipulates the aspect of time in ToL in interesting ways.

**Win Condition:** Same as reaper/possessor.

**Passive 1:** 
Groundhog Night - Father Time will upon being attacked, reset the night timer back to full, having every player choose their action again. They will obtain their original night results, but their actions will reset. Whoever attempted to attack Father Time cannot attack Father Time again that night. Father Time&#39;s original action will not reset and he can attack again after the reset.

**Passive 2:**
All the Time in the World - Father Time is immune to occupation, retargeting and conversion.

**Day Ability:** 
Skip to the Good Part - The day timer will lose 80 seconds. If it is 80 seconds or less night time will immediately begin. (2 uses)

**Night Ability 1:**
Your Time is Now - Attack targeted player and rapidly age him towards his death. (Unlimited uses)

**Night Ability 2:**
Chronic Corruption - Corrupt past selves of targeted player, attacking every player the target has visited in the game so far, including the player the targeted player visits tonight, bypasses night immunity. (2 uses)

**Lore:** Pending

**Comments:** Father Time&#39;s most unique trait is Skip to the Good Part that ensures BD must act soon if Father Time is found out. Father Time can however easily frame someone by using this too. Skip the day when someone is found out as neutral and that person shall surely be executed. Groundhog Night gives him the needed night immunity in an unique form that does give him away entirely to his attacker, much like reaper&#39;s night immunity. These both have great synergy with Chronic Corruption. There will be more nightly visits if days are skipped and the abilities used prior to a Groundhog Night activation still count as a visit. This makes targeting players who have visited many alive players the most important deduction step for Father Time. Father Time shouldn&#39;t target players like knights or physicians that generally visit the same key player with this ability. The mere existence of Chronic Corruption also makes having a log full of dead people less suspicious, giving scum an easier time to fake-claim in a Father Time&#39;s game. Conversely this also makes BD players amazingly less credible. &quot;This drunk log only contains dead people and he didn&#39;t step up for royal blood, exe!&quot;. Lastly he has the standard attack targeted player this night ability.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 23:30:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I took your comments to heart and made some changes addressing them. I think it’s one of the core things that makes him unique, so I’m reluctant to completely take it out. Players now do get their results. This is only still possibly tedious for prince. The rest of the players receive feedback from the night before it resets. So a sheriff can investigate another target for instance, or a butler hitting an occupy immune, can choose to occupy someone else. This is obviously bad for Father Time, but to compensate for that he gets to use a kill ability twice. Also buffed Chronic Corruption slightly for that extra framing ability. The player that is targeted, will show as killer to wisps/watching observers now, similar to possessor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 23:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with people who’ve said the night resets are a problem.  It doesn’t actually give most people more time, since nothing actually <span class="bbcode-i">changes</span> (beyond them knowing that Father Time was attacked…  by someone.)  It’d just be an irritation to everyone else in the game.</p>
<p>How about this?  Out of Time:  Anyone who tries to kill Father Time is occupied that night and for the next night.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 22:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The possible longer nights are offset by lack of days. Skip to the Good Part and Groundhog Night complement each other. Resetting a night is an unique mechanic that alerts the whole court there is a Father Time and they can reconsider their actions. It’s not something that would happen frequently anyways. I always need my time during the nights to consider my actions carefully, update logs, analyze voting patterns etc. That time I will especially miss if entire days are skippable twice by Father Time.</p>
<p>If assassin currently attacks reaper, reaper will live, but not give a message to assassin that their target was death immune, effectively outing the target as reaper. Father Time gives away exactly the same information, so I do not see why this has to be a problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 18:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Like when the assassin attacks say <span class="hashtag">#2</span> the Father Time and the night gets reset then they will know that <span class="hashtag">#2</span> is NK. Plus resetting the whole night would get annoying. Like another 40 seconds or how long it is to just click the same button. But I like the idea</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Father Time can also kill the assassin? What are you trying to say?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay but the reaper and possessor can both kill the assassin. The assassin wouldn’t know who it is</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 17:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly, how is that any different than reaper being attacked by assassin and assassin now knowing it’s reaper? It isn’t. If you think it’s imbalanced, you’d want a buff in certain areas? Assassin is invested to keep NK alive for the early stages of the game as well and later on Skip to the Good Part could be used to avoid day trials.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 16:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with this. You’d need to change the first passive or else Assassin just outs him in Logs/Deathnote</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 16:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wouldn’t the first passive ability reveal who the Father Time is? say I’m an assassin and I attacked Father Time and the day resets. Then I know that the person I attacked is Father Time</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 16:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Father Time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Father Time - (Neutral Killer)</strong> This NK manipulates the aspect of time in ToL in interesting ways.</p>
<p><strong>Win Condition:</strong> Same as reaper/possessor.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 1:</strong><br>
Groundhog Night - Father Time will upon being attacked, reset the night timer back to full, having every player choose their action again. They will obtain their original night results, but their actions will reset. Whoever attempted to attack Father Time cannot attack Father Time again that night. Father Time’s original action will not reset and he can attack again after the reset.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2:</strong><br>
All the Time in the World - Father Time is immune to occupation, retargeting and conversion.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability:</strong><br>
Skip to the Good Part - The day timer will lose 80 seconds. If it is 80 seconds or less night time will immediately begin. (2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1:</strong><br>
Your Time is Now - Attack targeted player and rapidly age him towards his death. (Unlimited uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2:</strong><br>
Chronic Corruption - Corrupt past selves of targeted player, attacking every player the target has visited in the game so far, including the player the targeted player visits tonight, bypasses night immunity. (2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Lore:</strong> Pending</p>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong> Father Time’s most unique trait is Skip to the Good Part that ensures BD must act soon if Father Time is found out. Father Time can however easily frame someone by using this too. Skip the day when someone is found out as neutral and that person shall surely be executed. Groundhog Night gives him the needed night immunity in an unique form that does give him away entirely to his attacker, much like reaper’s night immunity. These both have great synergy with Chronic Corruption. There will be more nightly visits if days are skipped and the abilities used prior to a Groundhog Night activation still count as a visit. This makes targeting players who have visited many alive players the most important deduction step for Father Time. Father Time shouldn’t target players like knights or physicians that generally visit the same key player with this ability. The mere existence of Chronic Corruption also makes having a log full of dead people less suspicious, giving scum an easier time to fake-claim in a Father Time’s game. Conversely this also makes BD players amazingly less credible. “This drunk log only contains dead people and he didn’t step up for royal blood, exe!”. Lastly he has the standard attack targeted player this night ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 12:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-37720-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-father-time/37720.rss">[Class Suggestion] Father Time</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
