<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431</link>
    <description>I&#39;m not sure how people feel about this, but I always feel something immensely satisfying about winning as a scorned or fool, but I also find it far more easier to do than winning as a Reaper or Possessor. However, I often feel as if there&#39;s something lacking in my experience AFTER winning as scorned or fool, and while I don&#39;t know how this could possibly be fixed for the foo, I think the implementation of secondary objectives/winning conditions could do wonders to amplify a scorn&#39;s post-victory interactivity. 

The point of additional victory conditions would allow certain neutrals to maintain a stronger connection to the game after they&#39;ve already won the game, and would give them stronger incentives to stay involved. For example, I think it might be interesting for a scorned to gain an additional target or two, REGARDLESS of the factions of those targets, after he or she has executed his or her primary target. The trollbox would, of course, stay active during this time and would not be disabled, and accomplishing these objective(s) would just give the player more gold. Additional victory conditions would not determine a player&#39;s victory status at the end of the game in any way.

I think this sort of change would also benefit NKers or other &#39;difficult to win&#39; classes, like reapers, possessors, and alchemists. It&#39;s more difficult to win as an alchemist or NK than other classes, in my opinion at least, and I think that, instead of having post-victory conditions like such as could be added for the scorned, these &#39;more difficult&#39; classes could have certain &#39;easier&#39; objectives that might somehow be representative of how close they came to winning a game. I&#39;m obviously not talking about &#39;participation&#39; prizes, and I&#39;m not entirely sure how such a thing could be done for alchs/NKs, but I think it would be interesting to experiment with.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 02:07:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intuition]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi guys,</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hippolytus" data-post="8" data-topic="11431">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hippolytus/40/34066_2.png" class="avatar"> Hippolytus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think adding an extra win-condition just for Scorned is confusing however, and not that necessary in the grand scheme of things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I guess I should have been more clear, but by extra winning conditions, I didn’t mean that the scorned actually needs them in order to "win’ the game, I just meant that after he has already <em>achieved</em> his victory condition, he gets another condition that he can refocus on. That way, he can still use his trollbox to continually do just that, troll people while trying to earn more gold. It makes the scorned more dynamic rather than, say, having most scorned players out themselves as scorned afterwards, without anymore cares. Also, this would probably prevent scorned players from just arbitrarily siding with BD or unseen/cult after their victory conditions.</p>
<p>The reason why I thought there might be some interesting ways of adding this for alchs or NKs is a different reason entirely. Usually when BD/evil players die, they can still achieve a full victory condition even though some of them have been dead from night 1 or night 2. On the other hand, a neutral killer or alch who lives until the final day actually ends up being awarded even less than a BD/evil player who has died at n1. I have no idea how this would be altered, so I’m not going to comment on that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 02:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There clearly is a point to it, to make Scorned more fun after already winning. I think adding an extra win-condition just for Scorned is confusing however, and not that necessary in the grand scheme of things.</p>
<p>I’d like Scorned to keep his Troll Box again though, it really is boring to win as Scorned and then literally just sit there. I normally try get myself hung once I have won as Scorned so I can at least talk with the dead people and bet on who is going to die.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 22:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No need to be aggressive.</p>
<p>Scorned is boring after winning, so they want chance for more gold to be won from it after winning, for some thing to do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="4" data-topic="11431" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if you read the OP you would understand</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>if you don’t have anything helpful to say, don’t say anything</p>
<p>I’ve read the OP and I don’t understand the point, I was asking for the thread creator to enlighten me as to why this should be a thing for only one specific class</p>
<p>“read the OP” isn’t helpful at all, it’s just annoying, why the fuck would I ask a question before reading the OP anyway</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 21:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Rope, he said that</p>
<p>And intuition, maybe make the secondary win conditions give scorned more gold at the end of the game, but not be required to win?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if you read the OP you would understand</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 21:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t see the point of putting multiple win conditions for a single class</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 21:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>only works for the scorned</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Secondary and Primary Objectives</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intuition]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure how people feel about this, but I always feel something immensely satisfying about winning as a scorned or fool, but I also find it far more easier to do than winning as a Reaper or Possessor. However, I often feel as if there’s something lacking in my experience AFTER winning as scorned or fool, and while I don’t know how this could possibly be fixed for the foo, I think the implementation of secondary objectives/winning conditions could do wonders to amplify a scorn’s post-victory interactivity.</p>
<p>The point of additional victory conditions would allow certain neutrals to maintain a stronger connection to the game after they’ve already won the game, and would give them stronger incentives to stay involved. For example, I think it might be interesting for a scorned to gain an additional target or two, REGARDLESS of the factions of those targets, after he or she has executed his or her primary target. The trollbox would, of course, stay active during this time and would not be disabled, and accomplishing these objective(s) would just give the player more gold. Additional victory conditions would not determine a player’s victory status at the end of the game in any way.</p>
<p>I think this sort of change would also benefit NKers or other ‘difficult to win’ classes, like reapers, possessors, and alchemists. It’s more difficult to win as an alchemist or NK than other classes, in my opinion at least, and I think that, instead of having post-victory conditions like such as could be added for the scorned, these ‘more difficult’ classes could have certain ‘easier’ objectives that might somehow be representative of how close they came to winning a game. I’m obviously not talking about ‘participation’ prizes, and I’m not entirely sure how such a thing could be done for alchs/NKs, but I think it would be interesting to experiment with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 21:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11431-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/secondary-and-primary-objectives/11431.rss">Secondary and Primary Objectives</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
