<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345</link>
    <description>The monk is a unique BD social class, he turns into the False Monk (Unseen) and the Apostle (Cult).

**Passive ability**
Martyr: If you are executed on trial, illuminate the target who first accused you, revealing their class and faction (doesn&#39;t work on the king, if the king is the first person to accuse him, then the next person will be illuminated instead).

**Passive ability 2**
Vow of Silence: You are unable to whisper and your messages are hidden from the public. You are also unable to write a log.

**Day ability 1**
Mute: Target one player, for the rest of the day he can read your messages but his messages will be hidden from anyone but yourself, and he will be unable to whisper. The other player will not know who is sending the messages. You cannot target the king. Infinite uses.
Note: No one will get notified when you use this ability, so it is easy to fake being muted and hard to prove it.

**Day ability 2**
Focused senses: Hear all whispers for the rest of the day. Infinite uses.

**Night ability 1**
Third eye: Read a player&#39;s log. Infinite uses.

**Night ability 2**
Nirvana: You cannot die or be converted tonight. If someone tries to attack or convert you, everyone will receive a message saying &quot;(Player) tried to attack/convert the monk last night!&quot; 3 uses.


**The False monk (Converted monk, unseen social)**

**Passive ability**
Martyr: If you are executed on trial your class will appear as a BD monk (they will not know you were converted unless you are killed at night) and darken the target who first accused you, &quot;revealing&quot; them as their opposite class, BD classes will appear as a random unseen class, and Unseen classes will appear as a random BD class. Neutral roles will appear as their actual classes. (doesn&#39;t work on the king, if the king is the first person to accuse him, then the next person will be darkened instead).

**Passive ability 2**
Fake Vow: You are unable to whisper and your messages are hidden from the public. You can write a &quot;fake&quot; log that will NOT be shown when you die (check his night ability 1 for more info about this). You can talk normally at night with the unseen.

**Day ability 1**
Mute: Target one player, for the rest of the day he can read your messages but his messages will be hidden from anyone but yourself, and he will be unable to whisper. The other player will not know who is sending the messages. You cannot target the king. Infinite uses.

**Night ability 1**
If your target dies tonight, your fake log will appear instead of theirs. 1 use.

**Night ability 2**
Fake Nirvana: Select a player, send everyone a message saying that &quot;(Player) tried to attack/convert the monk last night!&quot;. 1 use.

**Description**
The monk is a really powerful class that can gather a lot of information by reading whispers and logs, but this is countered by the fact that the monk can only talk to one person every day and there is no way to know who the monk talked to, which can make people wary of people claiming &quot;the monk told me that X player is suspicious&quot;. Also, it is easy for evil roles to pretend they are the monk by not talking all game and also to stay silent one day and claim the next day they were talking to the monk and give false info. However, pretending to be the monk can be risky since it will be sometimes useful for BD to hang the monk in order to use the &quot;Martyr&quot; ability. The monk&#39;s most reliable ability to accuse someone is to use &quot;Nirvana&quot;, however if the monk was converted this can be used to accuse an innocent person. 

Overall, the Monk is a very powerful class with access to important information but its main weakness is the fact that it is hard to trust him and his information. The false monk can easily manipulate information to deceive the bd and help the unseen win, but it is risky to try and convert the monk since &quot;Nirvana&quot; can reveal the Mastermind.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:38:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Forgot to write, but no one gets notified about someone being silenced, only the person being silenced will know, you could pretend monk silenced you by not talking for a day and it could be a risky move but an evil role could pretend to be monk by not talking all game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19345-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>how could he fake it? The person is silenced, an ability unique to monk</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19345-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll try and remember to do that later</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 20:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19345-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My reasoning was that he could use some overpowered abilities to counter the fact that he can’t talk or whisper, and even if he manages to tell someone important info the BD can’t simply blindly trust the person you told it too, since they could be faking it. Even if you told a confirmed BD like the prince, they can’t simply blindly believe you either since you can be converted. But I might be wrong, so would you care to elaborate about which of the abilities you think are overpowered and why? Also, thanks for the feedback!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 20:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19345-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some interesting abilities, but so many of them are overpowered</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 20:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19345-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The monk is a unique BD social class, he turns into the False Monk (Unseen) and the Apostle (Cult).</p>
<p><strong>Passive ability</strong><br>
Martyr: If you are executed on trial, illuminate the target who first accused you, revealing their class and faction (doesn’t work on the king, if the king is the first person to accuse him, then the next person will be illuminated instead).</p>
<p><strong>Passive ability 2</strong><br>
Vow of Silence: You are unable to whisper and your messages are hidden from the public. You are also unable to write a log.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability 1</strong><br>
Mute: Target one player, for the rest of the day he can read your messages but his messages will be hidden from anyone but yourself, and he will be unable to whisper. The other player will not know who is sending the messages. You cannot target the king. Infinite uses.<br>
Note: No one will get notified when you use this ability, so it is easy to fake being muted and hard to prove it.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability 2</strong><br>
Focused senses: Hear all whispers for the rest of the day. Infinite uses.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong><br>
Third eye: Read a player’s log. Infinite uses.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong><br>
Nirvana: You cannot die or be converted tonight. If someone tries to attack or convert you, everyone will receive a message saying “(Player) tried to attack/convert the monk last night!” 3 uses.</p>
<p><strong>The False monk (Converted monk, unseen social)</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive ability</strong><br>
Martyr: If you are executed on trial your class will appear as a BD monk (they will not know you were converted unless you are killed at night) and darken the target who first accused you, “revealing” them as their opposite class, BD classes will appear as a random unseen class, and Unseen classes will appear as a random BD class. Neutral roles will appear as their actual classes. (doesn’t work on the king, if the king is the first person to accuse him, then the next person will be darkened instead).</p>
<p><strong>Passive ability 2</strong><br>
Fake Vow: You are unable to whisper and your messages are hidden from the public. You can write a “fake” log that will NOT be shown when you die (check his night ability 1 for more info about this). You can talk normally at night with the unseen.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability 1</strong><br>
Mute: Target one player, for the rest of the day he can read your messages but his messages will be hidden from anyone but yourself, and he will be unable to whisper. The other player will not know who is sending the messages. You cannot target the king. Infinite uses.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong><br>
If your target dies tonight, your fake log will appear instead of theirs. 1 use.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong><br>
Fake Nirvana: Select a player, send everyone a message saying that “(Player) tried to attack/convert the monk last night!”. 1 use.</p>
<p><strong>Description</strong><br>
The monk is a really powerful class that can gather a lot of information by reading whispers and logs, but this is countered by the fact that the monk can only talk to one person every day and there is no way to know who the monk talked to, which can make people wary of people claiming “the monk told me that X player is suspicious”. Also, it is easy for evil roles to pretend they are the monk by not talking all game and also to stay silent one day and claim the next day they were talking to the monk and give false info. However, pretending to be the monk can be risky since it will be sometimes useful for BD to hang the monk in order to use the “Martyr” ability. The monk’s most reliable ability to accuse someone is to use “Nirvana”, however if the monk was converted this can be used to accuse an innocent person.</p>
<p>Overall, the Monk is a very powerful class with access to important information but its main weakness is the fact that it is hard to trust him and his information. The false monk can easily manipulate information to deceive the bd and help the unseen win, but it is risky to try and convert the monk since “Nirvana” can reveal the Mastermind.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 20:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19345-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-monk-unique-bd-social-and-false-monk-converted-monk/19345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Monk (Unique BD social) and False monk (Converted monk)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
