<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My death note appeared when it wasn&#39;t supposed to</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-death-note-appeared-when-it-wasnt-supposed-to/53795</link>
    <description>**What happened:** I was Hunter and my death note appeared when it was not supposed to.
Patch: 1.1.0, game played around 4:10 PM EST on March 22nd, 2018.

**Steps to reproduce:**
N1 I beared and killed the reaper, but they didn&#39;t die (since they had souls)
N2 I made a cute bear death note (didn&#39;t bear or anything)
N3 I beared, no attackers visited me
N4 I did nothing - didn&#39;t bear, didn&#39;t wolf. But the reaper died and they had my death note. Not sure how they died... maybe prince exed them, cult killed them or something else?

The issue is that he had my death note when he shouldn&#39;t have, since I did nothing that night. I&#39;m guessing my dn was saved from when he ran into me N1, and maybe whoever killed him didn&#39;t have a death note so it used mine?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 20:57:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-death-note-appeared-when-it-wasnt-supposed-to/53795.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My death note appeared when it wasn&#39;t supposed to</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lyssa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>What happened:</strong> I was Hunter and my death note appeared when it was not supposed to.<br>
Patch: 1.1.0, game played around 4:10 PM EST on March 22nd, 2018.</p>
<p><strong>Steps to reproduce:</strong><br>
N1 I beared and killed the reaper, but they didn’t die (since they had souls)<br>
N2 I made a cute bear death note (didn’t bear or anything)<br>
N3 I beared, no attackers visited me<br>
N4 I did nothing - didn’t bear, didn’t wolf. But the reaper died and they had my death note. Not sure how they died… maybe prince exed them, cult killed them or something else?</p>
<p>The issue is that he had my death note when he shouldn’t have, since I did nothing that night. I’m guessing my dn was saved from when he ran into me N1, and maybe whoever killed him didn’t have a death note so it used mine?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-death-note-appeared-when-it-wasnt-supposed-to/53795/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-death-note-appeared-when-it-wasnt-supposed-to/53795/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 20:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53795-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-death-note-appeared-when-it-wasnt-supposed-to/53795.rss">My death note appeared when it wasn&#39;t supposed to</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
