<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Mastermind&#39;s grand scheme</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-masterminds-grand-scheme/71180</link>
    <description>Starting as the right hand for the leader of rebellion, she was always eager to help out the cause with whatever it is needed to be done. Armed with her skills, zeal and loyalty to the rebel leader, the mastermind never fails to accomplished what is asked for her. Tasks ranging from feeding villagers to gain their trust and to assassination, there is nothing that she would not do for the rebellion. 

One fateful day, there is word that her sister will be married off to a noble (not the noble we know). When she heard about this she knew that she would be forced to do something that she would never do. Back in the rebellion&#39;s hideout, the leader grinned at the mastermind, signalling that he has something to be done and that they are one step closer to their goals in overthrowing the kingdom. To her despair, what she had feared had come. She was tasked to kill the noble&#39;s family. Looking straight at her leader with her fingers trembling, she rejected the leader&#39;s order for the first time. 

The leaders grin turned into a frown. Feeling dissapointed and confused, he looked at his other lackeys and ordered them to do the deed instead. As he looked back at the mastermind, he can feel a cold steel slicing through his neck before the warmth of the blood gushing out of it. The others around them were shocked and appalled by this and charged at the assaulter who managed to retaliate and dispatch them at ease.

It wasn&#39;t long before all the members of the rebellion lay lifeless on the floor. She then walked out of the hideout and went to the leader&#39;s home. There, she took out every thing that can relate her with the rebellion and burned them. Little did she know, the leader&#39;s daughter was spying on her. As she was about to take the daggers out to silence the little girl, she immediately sheathed them away and hugged her and took her under her wing. They then moved to another kingdom, Adiart, with the mastermind&#39;s plan to take over the kingdom in mind, not before she sent her farewell to her dear sister.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 17:37:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-masterminds-grand-scheme/71180.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Mastermind&#39;s grand scheme</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[overthebin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Starting as the right hand for the leader of rebellion, she was always eager to help out the cause with whatever it is needed to be done. Armed with her skills, zeal and loyalty to the rebel leader, the mastermind never fails to accomplished what is asked for her. Tasks ranging from feeding villagers to gain their trust and to assassination, there is nothing that she would not do for the rebellion.</p>
<p>One fateful day, there is word that her sister will be married off to a noble (not the noble we know). When she heard about this she knew that she would be forced to do something that she would never do. Back in the rebellion’s hideout, the leader grinned at the mastermind, signalling that he has something to be done and that they are one step closer to their goals in overthrowing the kingdom. To her despair, what she had feared had come. She was tasked to kill the noble’s family. Looking straight at her leader with her fingers trembling, she rejected the leader’s order for the first time.</p>
<p>The leaders grin turned into a frown. Feeling dissapointed and confused, he looked at his other lackeys and ordered them to do the deed instead. As he looked back at the mastermind, he can feel a cold steel slicing through his neck before the warmth of the blood gushing out of it. The others around them were shocked and appalled by this and charged at the assaulter who managed to retaliate and dispatch them at ease.</p>
<p>It wasn’t long before all the members of the rebellion lay lifeless on the floor. She then walked out of the hideout and went to the leader’s home. There, she took out every thing that can relate her with the rebellion and burned them. Little did she know, the leader’s daughter was spying on her. As she was about to take the daggers out to silence the little girl, she immediately sheathed them away and hugged her and took her under her wing. They then moved to another kingdom, Adiart, with the mastermind’s plan to take over the kingdom in mind, not before she sent her farewell to her dear sister.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-masterminds-grand-scheme/71180/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-masterminds-grand-scheme/71180/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 17:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71180-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-masterminds-grand-scheme/71180.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Mastermind&#39;s grand scheme</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
