<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alternate classes</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084</link>
    <description>One thought that kind of went through my head reading in on the should chrono replace phys discussion, what if we had an alternative to &quot;replacing&quot; certain classes. Rather had a few &quot;linked&quot; concepts... Chrono could be the first one.


Linked meaning, a new class is added, in practicality though it is tied with the class it is mixing. IE in short when the game normally would roll a phys, it then flips a coin for the alternative. It still effects the weighing the same, IE 2 phys&#39;s makes 1 chrono impossible, but 1 phys 1 chrono is possible.

The general concept could allow a bit of varying of classes, and allow more classes to be added, even ones that would normally be avoided due to the tendency to &quot;step on the toes&quot; of existing classes. Giving a bit more variety.

Admitted where it gets the roughest to try and figure out would be with cult... as that puts more abilities than one can reasonably give a cultist to try to maintain, not sure how to address it from there. Maybe that would involve one choosable or automatic ability or set of abilities upon conversion/start of the game.

(if automatic it would be random for the starting, chosen automatically based on what convert type if converted).

Having more classes/alternate versions of classes, could also help lessen the &quot;boredom&quot; of classes, as to my knowledge a good portion of the &quot;this class is boring and sucks&quot; is often linked with &quot;I&#39;ve been it 5 games in a row&quot;.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 12:35:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>and besides, even then all you’d have to do is give Timesnatcher some sort of strongman-esque abiliity and then BAM the huge amount of protectives is negated</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 12:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Having a lot of protectives leaves you very offensively weak</p>
<p>Plus the chances of that are super slim</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 12:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s true, not necesserally an auto win or auto lose game for the same reasons with a slew of protectors. but the general point is they probably don’t want too many of the same style of classes in the same game, and quite a few classes have had variants of themselves that were on the drawing board, different enough to almost be their own class, that were scrapped (and that’s just counting the ones we actually know of, who knows what’s on the cutting room floor at imperium). I’d imagine there’s dozens of good classes that would be cool, but would completely step on the toes of the classes we already have enough taht you wouldn’t want 2 of both in the same game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly the BD will prob hang thenselves since they aren’t confirmable.</p>
<p>I wish I was joking tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 03:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>well there could really be a problem coming from say having too many death preventers</p>
<p>2 knights<br>
2 phys<br>
2 chrono<br>
King<br>
2 alc<br>
merc.</p>
<p>in the same game… at least I’m assuming that’s part of the logic in the replacement concept. I can see the logic in possibly needing one to come out before another starts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 03:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah but we are tying to help evils not forcefully add in classes.</p>
<p>Just add the class in and leave it at that. Don’t need to mess with the spawn stuff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 03:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It leaves it exactly where it would be if only one of the classes existed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 03:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay tell me if I’m reading this straight.</p>
<p>There can be 2 physicians but not 2 physicians and a chromancer.</p>
<p>Doesn’t that just limit claim space even more?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 02:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alternate classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One thought that kind of went through my head reading in on the should chrono replace phys discussion, what if we had an alternative to “replacing” certain classes. Rather had a few “linked” concepts… Chrono could be the first one.</p>
<p>Linked meaning, a new class is added, in practicality though it is tied with the class it is mixing. IE in short when the game normally would roll a phys, it then flips a coin for the alternative. It still effects the weighing the same, IE 2 phys’s makes 1 chrono impossible, but 1 phys 1 chrono is possible.</p>
<p>The general concept could allow a bit of varying of classes, and allow more classes to be added, even ones that would normally be avoided due to the tendency to “step on the toes” of existing classes. Giving a bit more variety.</p>
<p>Admitted where it gets the roughest to try and figure out would be with cult… as that puts more abilities than one can reasonably give a cultist to try to maintain, not sure how to address it from there. Maybe that would involve one choosable or automatic ability or set of abilities upon conversion/start of the game.</p>
<p>(if automatic it would be random for the starting, chosen automatically based on what convert type if converted).</p>
<p>Having more classes/alternate versions of classes, could also help lessen the “boredom” of classes, as to my knowledge a good portion of the “this class is boring and sucks” is often linked with “I’ve been it 5 games in a row”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 02:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71084-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/alternate-classes/71084.rss">Alternate classes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
