<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher , Blue dragon (Support)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92</link>
    <description>Name: The Punisher
Affliction: Blue Dragon
Role: Support

Lore: an old prison warden who got insane with the thought of justice.

Day Abilities:

Torture &lt;span style=&quot;color:red;&quot;&gt;[Edited by Xblade ^_^]&lt;/span&gt;: Anyday that a confirmed Blue Dragon member killed (not voted), that night you can torcher someone revealing their &quot;visits&quot; at last 2 nights. Your target will be occupied and you can chat with him anonymously.
ON/Notification: -you saw another innocent fall, you could feel your anger at your hands. they were shaking..... for justice.

Night Abilities:

Relentless Attack: If there was no &quot;evil&quot; role that died in the last 2 days, you can attack someone brutally, both of you resulting dead. Your target will die even if theyy are &quot;night immune&quot;
ON/Notification: -You were covered with the thoughts of revenge and murder.
OFF/Notification: -You saw another murderer fall, you started thinking clearly again.

Interractions:
you will be detected as an enemy if a princess uses &quot;flirt&quot; on you.

during the &quot;day&quot; if a prince chooses to jail the punisher, he will be notified as &quot;your target had a key to get out of the jail&quot; prince will spend the night with no one jailed and the prince wont have the option to jail the punisher afterwards.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 17:07:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher , Blue dragon (Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No role should have "reveal yourself as ". Otherwise no evil role can claim it.</p>
<p>Pls</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 17:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-92-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher , Blue dragon (Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher , Blue dragon (Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am liking the direction that you are going with but I have a few things I would like, to sum up</p>
<p>1st I don’t think he really suits the role of the support seeing how he has the ability to kill. it would make more sense for him to be an Offensive or a killer with this set of ability’s</p>
<p>2nd by confirmed blue dragon I am guessing it is determined by effects such as sheriff (Reveal Mustache [1x] Reveal yourself as The Sheriff) and if this is the case that ability won’t see much play sadly</p>
<p>and finally please change the spelling of Torcher to Torture it took me a while to figure out what you meant,</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 11:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-92-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher , Blue dragon (Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher , Blue dragon (Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ozdeger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Name: The Punisher<br>
Affliction: Blue Dragon<br>
Role: Support</p>
<p>Lore: an old prison warden who got insane with the thought of justice.</p>
<p>Day Abilities:</p>
<p>Torture <span>[Edited by Xblade ^_^]</span>: Anyday that a confirmed Blue Dragon member killed (not voted), that night you can torcher someone revealing their “visits” at last 2 nights. Your target will be occupied and you can chat with him anonymously.<br>
ON/Notification: -you saw another innocent fall, you could feel your anger at your hands. they were shaking… for justice.</p>
<p>Night Abilities:</p>
<p>Relentless Attack: If there was no “evil” role that died in the last 2 days, you can attack someone brutally, both of you resulting dead. Your target will die even if theyy are “night immune”<br>
ON/Notification: -You were covered with the thoughts of revenge and murder.<br>
OFF/Notification: -You saw another murderer fall, you started thinking clearly again.</p>
<p>Interractions:<br>
you will be detected as an enemy if a princess uses “flirt” on you.</p>
<p>during the “day” if a prince chooses to jail the punisher, he will be notified as “your target had a key to get out of the jail” prince will spend the night with no one jailed and the prince wont have the option to jail the punisher afterwards.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-92-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-blue-dragon-support/92.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher , Blue dragon (Support)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
