<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Lore Idea: Maid</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-lore-idea-maid/73673</link>
    <description>      
(Sorry for the formatting wierdness... This is my first forum post.)

   As Priscilla entered the kitchen the nearly deafening noise only bothered her a smidge. Today, she had some really juicy gossip!
        &quot;You wouldn&#39;t believe...&quot; 
        &quot;No! She _didn&#39;t_!&quot;
        The snippets of conversation reached Priscilla&#39;s ears but today she had to remain focused. Quickly spotting Emily Priscilla made a beeline for her. 
        &quot;As I was saying, Elizabeth, the royal prince is clearly the best choice, not that good for nothing drunk that the King calls...&quot; Emily had seen Priscilla and her dazzling sea blue eyes shone with excitement.
        &quot;Well Prissy? Did you get it?&quot; Emily whispered so audibly that she might as well have talked out loud.
        &quot;_Be Quiet_!&quot; Priscilla admonished. &quot;The last thing we need is for some little bird to warn someone.&quot;
         &quot;And what do I care?&quot; Emily stated indignantly, &quot;I&#39;m not afraid! Those assassination stories are only to scare the young children.&quot;
        Priscilla sighed deeply but held her tongue. She had something much more important to discuss.
        &quot;Just come with me will you?&quot;
        Priscilla dragged Emily away from the work rooms and down numerous flights of stairs. She stopped, leaving Emily gulping for air and knocked softly a door. Priscilla pushed the door open and rushed to a small box sitting on a dusty table. Emily nearly lost her breath again.
        &quot;You did get it!&quot; she exclaimed running over beside Prisilla. Her face was shocked when Priscilla held out the nine inch long, bloody knife.
         &quot;What is that thing?&quot; Emily, clearly startled questioned.&quot;I thought you were only going to get proof that Lady Alice and the Prince are in love.&quot;
        &quot;That&#39;s what I was going to do, until I found the knife in Lady Alice&#39;s wardrobe.&quot; Priscilla was talking so high she was almost squealing.
        &quot;But why grab, this?&quot;
         &quot;Don&#39;t you see Emily?&quot; Priscilla grabbed Emily by the shoulders and shook her. &quot;Don&#39;t you see? We have the proof that Lady Alice murdered Sir Derek!&quot;
         Emily was still hesitant. &quot;How is that Proof? What if the killer put the knife there to frame her.
        Priscilla only looked more pleased. &quot;I was also talking to her. She visited Sir Derek the night he died!&quot;
        Emily, who up until this point had barely believed in the assassination rumors, began to feel afraid. &quot;We have to get this information to the King right away. I don&#39;t fancy sticking around here much longer.
        Ignoring her friends panicked state Priscilla grinned. &quot;You know what Em? We just might be promoted to Head Housekeeper for this. Emily smiled back but still felt uneasy. She just prayed that nobody had overheard them.



  Elizabeth the Handmaiden had heard it all. After their abrupt and rude departure, she had made a point of following them. Indeed she was glad she did. The only thing left was to report the foolish girls to her superiors and wait.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 21:54:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-lore-idea-maid/73673.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Lore Idea: Maid</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joyt87]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(Sorry for the formatting wierdness… This is my first forum post.)</p>
<p>As Priscilla entered the kitchen the nearly deafening noise only bothered her a smidge. Today, she had some really juicy gossip!<br>
“You wouldn’t believe…”<br>
“No! She <em>didn’t</em>!”<br>
The snippets of conversation reached Priscilla’s ears but today she had to remain focused. Quickly spotting Emily Priscilla made a beeline for her.<br>
“As I was saying, Elizabeth, the royal prince is clearly the best choice, not that good for nothing drunk that the King calls…” Emily had seen Priscilla and her dazzling sea blue eyes shone with excitement.<br>
“Well Prissy? Did you get it?” Emily whispered so audibly that she might as well have talked out loud.<br>
“<em>Be Quiet</em>!” Priscilla admonished. “The last thing we need is for some little bird to warn someone.”<br>
“And what do I care?” Emily stated indignantly, “I’m not afraid! Those assassination stories are only to scare the young children.”<br>
Priscilla sighed deeply but held her tongue. She had something much more important to discuss.<br>
“Just come with me will you?”<br>
Priscilla dragged Emily away from the work rooms and down numerous flights of stairs. She stopped, leaving Emily gulping for air and knocked softly a door. Priscilla pushed the door open and rushed to a small box sitting on a dusty table. Emily nearly lost her breath again.<br>
“You did get it!” she exclaimed running over beside Prisilla. Her face was shocked when Priscilla held out the nine inch long, bloody knife.<br>
“What is that thing?” Emily, clearly startled questioned.“I thought you were only going to get proof that Lady Alice and the Prince are in love.”<br>
“That’s what I was going to do, until I found the knife in Lady Alice’s wardrobe.” Priscilla was talking so high she was almost squealing.<br>
“But why grab, this?”<br>
“Don’t you see Emily?” Priscilla grabbed Emily by the shoulders and shook her. “Don’t you see? We have the proof that Lady Alice murdered Sir Derek!”<br>
Emily was still hesitant. "How is that Proof? What if the killer put the knife there to frame her.<br>
Priscilla only looked more pleased. “I was also talking to her. She visited Sir Derek the night he died!”<br>
Emily, who up until this point had barely believed in the assassination rumors, began to feel afraid. "We have to get this information to the King right away. I don’t fancy sticking around here much longer.<br>
Ignoring her friends panicked state Priscilla grinned. "You know what Em? We just might be promoted to Head Housekeeper for this. Emily smiled back but still felt uneasy. She just prayed that nobody had overheard them.</p>
<p>Elizabeth the Handmaiden had heard it all. After their abrupt and rude departure, she had made a point of following them. Indeed she was glad she did. The only thing left was to report the foolish girls to her superiors and wait.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-lore-idea-maid/73673/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-lore-idea-maid/73673/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73673-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-lore-idea-maid/73673.rss">New Lore Idea: Maid</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
