<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508</link>
    <description>**Lore:** Gifted with the ability to see the future, the prophets used to be strong allies of the Blue Dragon, however, their power and reputation tainted them, and made them corrupt and unreliable by tricking the people with fake prophecies. The king executed most of them, but a few of them hid in the shadows. Now, they formed a faction destined to use their powers to destroy the Blue Dragon, and rise to power once again.

**Description:** The prophets are a faction with great conversion power but they can be easy to predict since they announce their targets. Their killing power is situational, but most of their roles have killing abilities. As the name suggests, Prophet games would involve a lot of prediction, both from the Prophets themselves and from the BD, since they can trick players by making false prophecies. Prophets are specially vulnerable to observers, and the BD investigative on Scholar games is more similar to an observer than a sheriff. The prophets always start with two roles, &quot;The Oracle&quot; and another random prophet.

Note: Every single &quot;Prophecy&quot; ability will make the prophet that used it visit its target at night (when the prophecy becomes true) even though they are day abilities, unless it is fake.

&gt;**The Oracle:**
&gt;Unique Special, Prophet
&gt;**Passive ability 1**
When you die, other roles will still be able to target you. All of your prophets can use their night ability &quot;Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle.&quot;
&gt;**- Day ability 1: Advent**
At the end of the next night, you will visit your target and convert it to the False Prophets. When you use this ability, a message will be shown to the public telling them who will be converted. There can be a max of 3 other prophets at the same time. If you convert someone while you have the max number of prophets the oldest non-oracle prophet will die. No cool-down, infinite uses.
&gt;**- Day ability 2: Fake advent**
Select a player and send a public message telling the chat that said player will be converted this night. You will not visit said player and they will not be converted. Infinite uses.
&gt;**- Night ability 1:**
&gt;Convert someone who visits you tonight. 3 uses. If several people visit you only the first convertible player will be converted. If you convert someone while you have the max number of prophets the oldest non-oracle prophet will die. If you are dead, you can still use this ability but only once.

The Oracle has great conversion power with advent but can be predicted easily if you are not careful, since it announces who you will be visiting to convert. Fake advent can be used to trick players into wasting their abilities in someone else, or to think someone has been converted when they weren&#39;t. You can also use fake advent on yourself and then use your night ability to trick investigative roles into visiting you and then convert them. The Oracle is not immune to death at night and if he dies the prophets can easily replace him, but an observer can easily find who visited the Oracle. To counter this, the oracle can use his night ability once after he dies, so he will have to try and predict if any investigative roles will try and check his corpse.

&gt;**Prophet of death**
&gt;Killer, prophet. Converts from killing roles.
&gt;**Day ability 1: Prophecy of death**
Select two targets. Announce to the public that one of them will die tonight. You will visit only the first target and kill it. 2 uses.
&gt;**Day ability 2: Fake prophecy**
&gt;Select two targets. Announce to the public that one of them will die tonight. You will not visit any of them tonight. 3 uses.
&gt;**Night ability 1: Deadly countdown**
&gt;After three days, your target will die. This effect goes through night immunity and cannot be healed. 1 use.
&gt;**Night ability 2: Gather power**
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.

&gt;**Prophet of war**
&gt;Offensive, prophet. Converts from offensive roles.
&gt;**Day ability 1: Prophecy of war**
Announce to the public that one player will die if they leave their room tonight. They will die if they visit anyone. 2 uses.
&gt;**Day ability 2: Fake prophecy**
&gt; Announce to the public that one player will die if they leave their room tonight. They will not die even if they leave their room. 3 uses.
&gt;**Night ability 1: Treason**
&gt;The first player that visits your target will attack them. 2 uses.
&gt;**Night ability 2: Gather power**
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.

&gt;**Prophet of plague**
&gt;Support, prophet. Converts from support roles.
&gt;**Day ability 1: Prophecy of plague**
Poison a target. They will die in two nights. 2 uses.
&gt;**Day ability 2: Fake prophecy**
&gt;Make a target think they are poisoned. The poison will disappear automatically the next night, and the target will believe they were healed. 3 uses.
&gt;**Night ability 1: Faulty medicine**
&gt;Your target will be immune to attacks tonight, but if they are healed they will die. 1 use.
&gt;**Night ability 2: Gather power**
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.

&gt;**Prophet of light**
&gt;Investigative, prophet. Converts from investigative roles.
&gt;**Day ability 1: Prophecy of light**
Announce to the public that a player will have their class revealed to the prophets tonight. At the end of the night visit your target to reveal the exact class and faction of the player to the prophets. 2 uses.
&gt;**Day ability 2: Fake prophecy**
&gt;Select two targets. Announce to the public that a player will have their class revealed to the prophets tonight. The target will not be revealed to the prophets. 3 uses.
&gt;**Night ability 1: Curse of the firstborn**
&gt;Select a class from the list of classes (similar to defile). Any targets of said class that visit the prophets tonight will die. 1 use.
&gt;**Night ability 2: Gather power**
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.

&gt;**Prophet of death**
&gt;Social, prophet. Converts from social roles.
&gt;**Day ability 1: Prophecy of silence**
Select a target. Announce to the public that if said target sends more than 3 chat messages or whispers for the rest of the day they will be unable to talk the next day. 2 uses.
&gt;**Day ability 2: Fake prophecy**
Select a target. Announce to the public that if said target sends more than 3 chat messages or whispers today they will be unable to talk the next day. They will still be able to talk the next day. 3 uses.
&gt;**Night ability 1: Dysphonia**
&gt;Target a player. If your target is put on trial tomorrow, anyone who votes execute will be unable to accuse anyone of treason the following day. 1 use.
&gt;**Night ability 2: Gather power**
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.

&gt;**The Scholar**
&gt;Social, prophet. Converts from social roles.
&gt;**Day ability 1: Skepticism**
You will become immune to conversions tonight. Infinite uses, but 2-day cooldown.
&gt;**Day ability 2: Scientific Method**
Find out how many prophecies made today will become true. 1 use.
&gt;**Night ability 1: Field Research**
If a player is visited by a member of the Prophets tonight, you will be notified and you will get a list of everyone who visited your target. If you used skepticism, the player you visit tonight will also be immune to conversions. Infinite uses.

The scholar is different than investigative classes like the sheriff and the paladin, instead of finding if a target is part of the Prophets directly, he can find them by checking their targets. Since prophets usually announce their targets the scholar can easily find the prophets, however, since other BD roles will probably try to visit said target as well, you will have to figure out who is a prophet from your list of suspects. Skepticism is a powerful ability that can help you survive conversions if the Oracle tries to bait you into visiting him and to prevent conversions on someone else, but you will be vulnerable for 2 whole days after you use it. Scientific method can also help you find out if a prophecy will become true to help you avoid baits, but you can only use it once and it becomes less useful if there are many prophecies being made at the same time, since you will only know how many will become true, but not which of them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 01:38:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That is the point of the skill, you can kill a player you “fake poisoned” if they are healed said night, to counter this, healers could wait until the second night before healing. I know this can be a powerful skill, which is why it only has one charge. Besides a target claiming poisoned would be a good target for the scholar to visit since there is a chance of a prophet using Faulty Medicine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21508-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would probably work anyway. A phys or alch is likely to heal them if they claim to be bleeding.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21508-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I worded the skill wrong, what I meant is that the message saying that you were healed will show up, it doesn’t really heal the player. Gonna reword it for clarity, thanks!<br>
Also something I might have no worded right, but every single prophecy (except fake ones) causes you to visit your target at night, even if they are day abilities.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 01:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21508-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Reads Prophet of plague ability’s</em></p>
<p>Use False prophecy</p>
<p>Use Faulty Medicine on the same person</p>
<p>Target dies because of the auto heal</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21508-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Lore:</strong> Gifted with the ability to see the future, the prophets used to be strong allies of the Blue Dragon, however, their power and reputation tainted them, and made them corrupt and unreliable by tricking the people with fake prophecies. The king executed most of them, but a few of them hid in the shadows. Now, they formed a faction destined to use their powers to destroy the Blue Dragon, and rise to power once again.</p>
<p><strong>Description:</strong> The prophets are a faction with great conversion power but they can be easy to predict since they announce their targets. Their killing power is situational, but most of their roles have killing abilities. As the name suggests, Prophet games would involve a lot of prediction, both from the Prophets themselves and from the BD, since they can trick players by making false prophecies. Prophets are specially vulnerable to observers, and the BD investigative on Scholar games is more similar to an observer than a sheriff. The prophets always start with two roles, “The Oracle” and another random prophet.</p>
<p>Note: Every single “Prophecy” ability will make the prophet that used it visit its target at night (when the prophecy becomes true) even though they are day abilities, unless it is fake.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The Oracle:</strong><br>
Unique Special, Prophet<br>
<strong>Passive ability 1</strong><br>
When you die, other roles will still be able to target you. All of your prophets can use their night ability “Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle.”<br>
<strong>- Day ability 1: Advent</strong><br>
At the end of the next night, you will visit your target and convert it to the False Prophets. When you use this ability, a message will be shown to the public telling them who will be converted. There can be a max of 3 other prophets at the same time. If you convert someone while you have the max number of prophets the oldest non-oracle prophet will die. No cool-down, infinite uses.<br>
<strong>- Day ability 2: Fake advent</strong><br>
Select a player and send a public message telling the chat that said player will be converted this night. You will not visit said player and they will not be converted. Infinite uses.<br>
<strong>- Night ability 1:</strong><br>
Convert someone who visits you tonight. 3 uses. If several people visit you only the first convertible player will be converted. If you convert someone while you have the max number of prophets the oldest non-oracle prophet will die. If you are dead, you can still use this ability but only once.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Oracle has great conversion power with advent but can be predicted easily if you are not careful, since it announces who you will be visiting to convert. Fake advent can be used to trick players into wasting their abilities in someone else, or to think someone has been converted when they weren’t. You can also use fake advent on yourself and then use your night ability to trick investigative roles into visiting you and then convert them. The Oracle is not immune to death at night and if he dies the prophets can easily replace him, but an observer can easily find who visited the Oracle. To counter this, the oracle can use his night ability once after he dies, so he will have to try and predict if any investigative roles will try and check his corpse.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Prophet of death</strong><br>
Killer, prophet. Converts from killing roles.<br>
<strong>Day ability 1: Prophecy of death</strong><br>
Select two targets. Announce to the public that one of them will die tonight. You will visit only the first target and kill it. 2 uses.<br>
<strong>Day ability 2: Fake prophecy</strong><br>
Select two targets. Announce to the public that one of them will die tonight. You will not visit any of them tonight. 3 uses.<br>
<strong>Night ability 1: Deadly countdown</strong><br>
After three days, your target will die. This effect goes through night immunity and cannot be healed. 1 use.<br>
<strong>Night ability 2: Gather power</strong><br>
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Prophet of war</strong><br>
Offensive, prophet. Converts from offensive roles.<br>
<strong>Day ability 1: Prophecy of war</strong><br>
Announce to the public that one player will die if they leave their room tonight. They will die if they visit anyone. 2 uses.<br>
<strong>Day ability 2: Fake prophecy</strong><br>
Announce to the public that one player will die if they leave their room tonight. They will not die even if they leave their room. 3 uses.<br>
<strong>Night ability 1: Treason</strong><br>
The first player that visits your target will attack them. 2 uses.<br>
<strong>Night ability 2: Gather power</strong><br>
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Prophet of plague</strong><br>
Support, prophet. Converts from support roles.<br>
<strong>Day ability 1: Prophecy of plague</strong><br>
Poison a target. They will die in two nights. 2 uses.<br>
<strong>Day ability 2: Fake prophecy</strong><br>
Make a target think they are poisoned. The poison will disappear automatically the next night, and the target will believe they were healed. 3 uses.<br>
<strong>Night ability 1: Faulty medicine</strong><br>
Your target will be immune to attacks tonight, but if they are healed they will die. 1 use.<br>
<strong>Night ability 2: Gather power</strong><br>
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Prophet of light</strong><br>
Investigative, prophet. Converts from investigative roles.<br>
<strong>Day ability 1: Prophecy of light</strong><br>
Announce to the public that a player will have their class revealed to the prophets tonight. At the end of the night visit your target to reveal the exact class and faction of the player to the prophets. 2 uses.<br>
<strong>Day ability 2: Fake prophecy</strong><br>
Select two targets. Announce to the public that a player will have their class revealed to the prophets tonight. The target will not be revealed to the prophets. 3 uses.<br>
<strong>Night ability 1: Curse of the firstborn</strong><br>
Select a class from the list of classes (similar to defile). Any targets of said class that visit the prophets tonight will die. 1 use.<br>
<strong>Night ability 2: Gather power</strong><br>
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Prophet of death</strong><br>
Social, prophet. Converts from social roles.<br>
<strong>Day ability 1: Prophecy of silence</strong><br>
Select a target. Announce to the public that if said target sends more than 3 chat messages or whispers for the rest of the day they will be unable to talk the next day. 2 uses.<br>
<strong>Day ability 2: Fake prophecy</strong><br>
Select a target. Announce to the public that if said target sends more than 3 chat messages or whispers today they will be unable to talk the next day. They will still be able to talk the next day. 3 uses.<br>
<strong>Night ability 1: Dysphonia</strong><br>
Target a player. If your target is put on trial tomorrow, anyone who votes execute will be unable to accuse anyone of treason the following day. 1 use.<br>
<strong>Night ability 2: Gather power</strong><br>
Gather power: Visit the Oracle tonight to gather his powers, turning you into the new Oracle. If more than one prophet uses this ability the same day only the first to use it will visit the Oracle. Can only be used if the Oracle is dead.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The Scholar</strong><br>
Social, prophet. Converts from social roles.<br>
<strong>Day ability 1: Skepticism</strong><br>
You will become immune to conversions tonight. Infinite uses, but 2-day cooldown.<br>
<strong>Day ability 2: Scientific Method</strong><br>
Find out how many prophecies made today will become true. 1 use.<br>
<strong>Night ability 1: Field Research</strong><br>
If a player is visited by a member of the Prophets tonight, you will be notified and you will get a list of everyone who visited your target. If you used skepticism, the player you visit tonight will also be immune to conversions. Infinite uses.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The scholar is different than investigative classes like the sheriff and the paladin, instead of finding if a target is part of the Prophets directly, he can find them by checking their targets. Since prophets usually announce their targets the scholar can easily find the prophets, however, since other BD roles will probably try to visit said target as well, you will have to figure out who is a prophet from your list of suspects. Skepticism is a powerful ability that can help you survive conversions if the Oracle tries to bait you into visiting him and to prevent conversions on someone else, but you will be vulnerable for 2 whole days after you use it. Scientific method can also help you find out if a prophecy will become true to help you avoid baits, but you can only use it once and it becomes less useful if there are many prophecies being made at the same time, since you will only know how many will become true, but not which of them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 17:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21508-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-false-prophets/21508.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The False Prophets</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
