<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Neutral social] The Magnate</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242</link>
    <description>_Lore: &quot;There is no good and evil, only order and chaos. The blue dragon has slowly yet steadily undermined the power of the ruling class, calling for the king&#39;s execution in the most extreme cases, giving votes to even the lowliest members of parliament. These impudent fools want to bring about DEMOCRACY, a system one step away from anarchy. The unseen, on the other hand, understand the concept of ruling with an iron fist, to bring about peace, stability, and abundance. I think where my allegiances lay is obvious&quot;_ -The magnate, responding to his mercenary when she asked who he was siding with

&gt;**The Magnate**
Neutral social
**Night ability: Bribery**
_(3 uses)_ Your target will be your puppet the following day. Except through your abilities, they will be unable to speak or vote, and will be unable to use their day abilities. In addition, they will gain a use of each of their abilities
**Night ability: Kidnap**
_(infinite uses)_ Your target will not show up to court the following day, preventing their speaking and voting. This is not announced to the court, but their body will be missing and nothing will happen if they get enough accusations to go onto trial. This counts as an attack for the purposes of knights and healing.
**Day ability: Pawn**
_(usable only if you have a puppet from bribery, can be used multiple times in a day)_ force your puppet to accuse someone of treason. In addition, their vote of execute/pardon will be the same as yours in the next trial
**Day ability: Vehicle of propaganda**
_(usable only if you have a puppet from bribery, can be used multiple times in a day)_ Your next message will be from the mouth of your puppet instead of yours.

goal: live to see the blue dragon fall
Cannot spawn if sorcerer spawned? Maybe?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 13:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Neutral social] The Magnate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It counts as an attack for the purposes of knights and healing, It wasn’t clear on the thing so I shall edit</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 13:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25242-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242.rss">[Neutral social] The Magnate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Neutral social] The Magnate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the idea, but I think “Kidnap” should have a limit, since he can basically remove a player from the court permanently if he wants to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 08:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25242-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242.rss">[Neutral social] The Magnate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Neutral social] The Magnate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sorry, forgot, adding it now, thought it would have been obvious with the lore though?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 02:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25242-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242.rss">[Neutral social] The Magnate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Neutral social] The Magnate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cleanfear]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Very interesting and creative ideas, however I wonder what is the Magnate’s win condintion? I seem to be unable to find it in your suggestion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 02:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25242-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242.rss">[Neutral social] The Magnate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Neutral social] The Magnate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Lore: “There is no good and evil, only order and chaos. The blue dragon has slowly yet steadily undermined the power of the ruling class, calling for the king’s execution in the most extreme cases, giving votes to even the lowliest members of parliament. These impudent fools want to bring about DEMOCRACY, a system one step away from anarchy. The unseen, on the other hand, understand the concept of ruling with an iron fist, to bring about peace, stability, and abundance. I think where my allegiances lay is obvious”</em> -The magnate, responding to his mercenary when she asked who he was siding with</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The Magnate</strong><br>
Neutral social<br>
<strong>Night ability: Bribery</strong><br>
<em>(3 uses)</em> Your target will be your puppet the following day. Except through your abilities, they will be unable to speak or vote, and will be unable to use their day abilities. In addition, they will gain a use of each of their abilities<br>
<strong>Night ability: Kidnap</strong><br>
<em>(infinite uses)</em> Your target will not show up to court the following day, preventing their speaking and voting. This is not announced to the court, but their body will be missing and nothing will happen if they get enough accusations to go onto trial. This counts as an attack for the purposes of knights and healing.<br>
<strong>Day ability: Pawn</strong><br>
<em>(usable only if you have a puppet from bribery, can be used multiple times in a day)</em> force your puppet to accuse someone of treason. In addition, their vote of execute/pardon will be the same as yours in the next trial<br>
<strong>Day ability: Vehicle of propaganda</strong><br>
<em>(usable only if you have a puppet from bribery, can be used multiple times in a day)</em> Your next message will be from the mouth of your puppet instead of yours.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>goal: live to see the blue dragon fall<br>
Cannot spawn if sorcerer spawned? Maybe?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 01:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25242-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-social-the-magnate/25242.rss">[Neutral social] The Magnate</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
