<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875</link>
    <description>(Note:If this is in the wrong category, do change it Mods)

# The &quot;No Info=Evil King&quot; Meta
I personally love the Allies ability. You can find people of your own faction if you are BD/Evil king. Get alignments from people with Neutral king (Another reason to let them live if you like to lynch them) The one problem I have with it is a meta the came with it &quot;No Info=Evil King&quot; This is just plain stupid. 

# Storytime, Starring &quot;Noz the Reaper&quot; and &quot;Random Good King&quot;, Featuring &quot;No Info=Evil King&quot; Meta
I was once in a game as reaper with a King that was about to reveal info, so I chilled him. They said &quot;They aren&#39;t providing any info, Must be Evil King&quot;  I said &quot;Well they may not have info&quot; This sated them for the day and said they would lynch him tomorrow if he provided no info then. I reaped him that night, as to waste a day. As he was reaped he couldn&#39;t provide info, so he was lynched and couldn&#39;t defend because he was well, reaped. He flipped Good King, people said &quot;Report king for Game throwing&quot; I was pissed, he couldn&#39;t defend, he couldn&#39;t provide info, so apparently he is Evil King? So what is the moral of this story? DON&#39;T FUCKING JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS ABOUT THE KING&#39;S ALIGNMENT

# Explaining This Meta
I can see where this meta came from as Evil King sees &quot;Not an ally&quot; for BD and neutral. The problem is the over application for it. If a King refuses to give info willingly, I would be slightly sus of that. If he says he hasn&#39;t used the ability yet, and he said he will use it tonight, we have no problem, Except that people could see this as a way to deflect attention and keep an Evil King on the throne. Ask yourself, which one is the simpler explanation. I guarantee you it is the first one 

# Idea for Fixing This
The solution is simple, if you have doubts about an King alignment. Ask him! He could lie, then you could ask for an Allies result tomorrow. If he provides one well, you have a Good/Neutral King. If he provides a terrible rushed one, he could be evil. 

# Moral of this Thread?
&quot;No Info=Evil King&quot; meta, is dumb if you over apply it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 23:29:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m basically saying that the meta is stupid when people use it when they have nothing else to do</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 23:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4875-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss">Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zarlath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Literally after reading this topic I had a game as the Evil King.<br>
I found none friends 4 nights in a row and yet no-one asked my for leads, nor sent any whisper whatsoever.<br>
BD kept killing each other until Day 4, when it was already too late for them to turn the game around.</p>
<p>If you get unlucky with finding allies and have no role confirmations, then yes, giving no leads is suspicious, but I agree that accusing a king of being evil every time he gives no leads is kinda dumb.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 21:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4875-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss">Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bumping this so people actually see this and stop being idiots about the meta</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 19:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4875-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss">Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the King giving info should be nerfed to like 2 or 3 uses tbh. Having 4 means that the first half of the game is “hey king what info” instead of everyone trying to scumread or rely on hidden BD investigatives. It makes it stale as every game is the same, which it wasn’t before King got the invest ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4875-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss">Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I used the scenario  as an over application of the meta. I was also slightly laughing my ass off at the end of that game. I was jailed by Prince and let let me slide with saying 'If you let me become King, you’ll have an NK off your hands" He let me go, I had to kill a second king due to royal blood</p>
<p>EDIT: I won that game as King when I became it, the MM used Dirty Work ASAP. It was hilarious</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 16:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4875-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss">Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think a King not giving information is a <strong>slight</strong> scum read. A Good BD King has no reason not to help.</p>
<p>Although a King giving information is a <strong>Null</strong> read by itself since it could easily be a Neutral or Evil King trying to lead others astray.</p>
<p>In your specific scenario, you just made an excellent play as a Reaper which confused BD. Those people can report all they want, but that case will go unpunished.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 16:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4875-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss">Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(Note:If this is in the wrong category, do change it Mods)</p>
<h1>The “No Info=Evil King” Meta</h1>
<p>I personally love the Allies ability. You can find people of your own faction if you are BD/Evil king. Get alignments from people with Neutral king (Another reason to let them live if you like to lynch them) The one problem I have with it is a meta the came with it “No Info=Evil King” This is just plain stupid.</p>
<h1>Storytime, Starring “Noz the Reaper” and “Random Good King”, Featuring “No Info=Evil King” Meta</h1>
<p>I was once in a game as reaper with a King that was about to reveal info, so I chilled him. They said “They aren’t providing any info, Must be Evil King”  I said “Well they may not have info” This sated them for the day and said they would lynch him tomorrow if he provided no info then. I reaped him that night, as to waste a day. As he was reaped he couldn’t provide info, so he was lynched and couldn’t defend because he was well, reaped. He flipped Good King, people said “Report king for Game throwing” I was pissed, he couldn’t defend, he couldn’t provide info, so apparently he is Evil King? So what is the moral of this story? DON’T FUCKING JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS ABOUT THE KING’S ALIGNMENT</p>
<h1>Explaining This Meta</h1>
<p>I can see where this meta came from as Evil King sees “Not an ally” for BD and neutral. The problem is the over application for it. If a King refuses to give info willingly, I would be slightly sus of that. If he says he hasn’t used the ability yet, and he said he will use it tonight, we have no problem, Except that people could see this as a way to deflect attention and keep an Evil King on the throne. Ask yourself, which one is the simpler explanation. I guarantee you it is the first one</p>
<h1>Idea for Fixing This</h1>
<p>The solution is simple, if you have doubts about an King alignment. Ask him! He could lie, then you could ask for an Allies result tomorrow. If he provides one well, you have a Good/Neutral King. If he provides a terrible rushed one, he could be evil.</p>
<h1>Moral of this Thread?</h1>
<p>“No Info=Evil King” meta, is dumb if you over apply it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 14:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4875-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/addressing-the-no-info-evil-king-meta/4875.rss">Addressing the &quot;No Info=Evil KIng&quot; Meta</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
