<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Chilling during king selection</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421</link>
    <description>Its safe to say that drunk hard counters reaper. If ur reaper and ur debauched by a drunk, you&#39;re guaranteed to lose even if he dies because of log. At least chilling delays ur loss. However, you arent given the option to chill if the king dies and people (namely the drunk) step up to prove royal blood and subsequently out you. I think you should be allowed to chill during king selection so you have a chance to not instantly get executed the day after u get debauched.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 13:19:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Chilling during king selection</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You will still lose anyways as you can’t empower reap/chill at the same time so the drunk can keep debbing/happy hour you until you run out of souls. The only alternative scenario is that drunk gets killed through the court or the unseen/cult, but that seems unlikely and the logs would still out you. If they’d be converted, they’d likely still deb/occupy you too.</p>
<p>Regardless I do support this change, because it makes chill uesable for framing royals, which is especially good versus drunks, which can completely destroy your game as mentioned before. I just didn’t agree with the scenario you postulated that highlights why this change should be made.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 13:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45421-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421.rss">Chilling during king selection</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chilling during king selection</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have nothing against this. It would be nice for the Reaper to be able to that.</p>
<p>Question: Would they still be able to step up?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45421-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421.rss">Chilling during king selection</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chilling during king selection</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brockvond]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Its safe to say that drunk hard counters reaper. If ur reaper and ur debauched by a drunk, you’re guaranteed to lose even if he dies because of log. At least chilling delays ur loss. However, you arent given the option to chill if the king dies and people (namely the drunk) step up to prove royal blood and subsequently out you. I think you should be allowed to chill during king selection so you have a chance to not instantly get executed the day after u get debauched.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 02:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45421-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/chilling-during-king-selection/45421.rss">Chilling during king selection</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
