<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467</link>
    <description>Lore Link: 
https://tol.wikia.com/The_Reaper

Lore Subject: The Reapers of Corax

Lore:
Although actual Reapers have long been considered a myth we have found evidence of their influence throughout Adiart&#39;s history. There have been three tales of debatable relevance.

Firstly:An urban legend passed around: a section of cultists supposedly dedicated themselves to what they call &quot;The Reaper&#39;s Penance&quot; where they would kidnap a serving maid or child and force them into crypts or mausoleums with little explanation. One child documented his experience and of a paladin who came to his rescue noting the presence of something that created a crushing sensation in his chest and the ravings of lunatics. Of course the tales of children can never be completely believed and no paladin alive has attested to saving a child in need at the time. The child in question however went on to become an assassin of the black rose faction. None can tell why his path led him to evil. The Reaper&#39;s penance carries on to this day every 4 years but one can only wonder that should the reapers be denied their sacrifice whether they shall rise to take it. As a legend we cannot take this as fact but as it turns out most legend is based in fact so perhaps this has legitimate merit.

Secondly:A report from a knight of the realm. A man condemned to die for his assassination of a nobles son accused his jailer of being quite close to a description of these creatures..He begged his wife and son to remain safe while the town sheriff took him away.He yelled out pleading for the guards to skewer him there and then. 2 days later he was due to be hung. The executioner brought out his body on his shoulders. Onlookers attest to his inability to move or speak. His body and face were rigid yet they hung him anyway. It was unclear what happened that day but all law enforcers attest to his good health at time of death. The knight also attests that the man was perfectly fine and the sheriff was not under the influence of dark magic. All we know for sure to guarantee foul play was that the mark of corax appeared on the hand of the accused as soon as he was hanged,

Thirdly: This tale was taken from a Black rose members diary. A bard in a tavern sung jolly songs every night at a local tavern for 7 years always managing to entertain the patrons and making a well earned living at the time till one night he was accosted outside before his show. He entered the tavern and began to sing but his words they warped to form a soliloquy of despair. The lyrics were &quot;And in the dark those muggers see their fateful eyes shall rest. For with my words and my last breath I&#39;ll put them too the test. With woeful sorrow and fated faith I shall bid you all farewell, As now I sing Corax&#39;s song and now i ring his bell&quot;. At that moment the Tavern was engulfed in the dark cloth of a reaper the size of the tavern and the building was erased from this world. The ground scarred with the lyrics where the tavern once was and 37 limp bodies lay there. Shivering in the corner was a singular maiden clawing at her arms and shivering from head to toe. An illegitimate princess of the realm as it were. Naturally the black rose claim this was reserved as knowledge only for kings before a copy was stolen by the black rose from the royal library. It would appear even they fear the reaper.






Comments/Explanations:
The idea behind these tales is to cement that the reapers are feared throughout whatever world this takes place in. The Reapers in my view should be an outside force feared by all the factions. I believe the Blue dragons would be oblivious mostly to them thanks to their loose ties with Corax. The Black rose would wish to avoid them and would have the most information on them and the Cultists would try to appease them.

This entry is to display the relationships that all 3 factions share with the reapers and gives them a nice history as to why perhaps a reaper may show up at the gathering e.g Story two shows they can take human form if needed without giving the lore characters too much information.

Something I wish to add into the lore is that after 2 days the reason people see that a reaper target is dead is that the mark of Corax will appear on their hand. This would give credence to why a shell of a person would be understood to be a reaper victim while at the same time directly attaching the Reapers to Corax in some manner that in the future I would like to manifest as a dead black rose assassin who looks into Corax&#39;s eyes. 

Another thing I wanted to setup was this idea of a giant reaper being summoned by a bard. While not actually a class yet this opens the door to future ideas and teases that we aren&#39;t just thinking of the now. We may not actually make the bard but we&#39;ll also show we aren&#39;t closed minded :) finaly the addition of an illegitimate princess was to introduce the idea that perhaps Royal blood has power over Beings infused with Corax&#39;s power giving the blue dragon a little flavour as a faction.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 04:34:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/reaper">@Reaper</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 04:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-467-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/9/95aa0b238840055fa18c2fb8c99335444fe16b70.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="llZsuQOi3AwHoCOwXztZ8kaQZz2" width="580" height="500"></p>
<p>Revoked</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 04:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-467-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cheers guys!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 12:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-467-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Congrats, new Loremaster</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 07:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-467-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[robflop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This has officially been selected as accepted lore as of the 21th April.<br>
Check it out here: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Reaper" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Reaper</a></p>
<p>Congrats!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 07:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-467-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore Link:<br>
<a href="https://tol.wikia.com/The_Reaper" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://tol.wikia.com/The_Reaper</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: The Reapers of Corax</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
Although actual Reapers have long been considered a myth we have found evidence of their influence throughout Adiart’s history. There have been three tales of debatable relevance.</p>
<p>Firstly:An urban legend passed around: a section of cultists supposedly dedicated themselves to what they call “The Reaper’s Penance” where they would kidnap a serving maid or child and force them into crypts or mausoleums with little explanation. One child documented his experience and of a paladin who came to his rescue noting the presence of something that created a crushing sensation in his chest and the ravings of lunatics. Of course the tales of children can never be completely believed and no paladin alive has attested to saving a child in need at the time. The child in question however went on to become an assassin of the black rose faction. None can tell why his path led him to evil. The Reaper’s penance carries on to this day every 4 years but one can only wonder that should the reapers be denied their sacrifice whether they shall rise to take it. As a legend we cannot take this as fact but as it turns out most legend is based in fact so perhaps this has legitimate merit.</p>
<p>Secondly:A report from a knight of the realm. A man condemned to die for his assassination of a nobles son accused his jailer of being quite close to a description of these creatures…He begged his wife and son to remain safe while the town sheriff took him away.He yelled out pleading for the guards to skewer him there and then. 2 days later he was due to be hung. The executioner brought out his body on his shoulders. Onlookers attest to his inability to move or speak. His body and face were rigid yet they hung him anyway. It was unclear what happened that day but all law enforcers attest to his good health at time of death. The knight also attests that the man was perfectly fine and the sheriff was not under the influence of dark magic. All we know for sure to guarantee foul play was that the mark of corax appeared on the hand of the accused as soon as he was hanged,</p>
<p>Thirdly: This tale was taken from a Black rose members diary. A bard in a tavern sung jolly songs every night at a local tavern for 7 years always managing to entertain the patrons and making a well earned living at the time till one night he was accosted outside before his show. He entered the tavern and began to sing but his words they warped to form a soliloquy of despair. The lyrics were “And in the dark those muggers see their fateful eyes shall rest. For with my words and my last breath I’ll put them too the test. With woeful sorrow and fated faith I shall bid you all farewell, As now I sing Corax’s song and now i ring his bell”. At that moment the Tavern was engulfed in the dark cloth of a reaper the size of the tavern and the building was erased from this world. The ground scarred with the lyrics where the tavern once was and 37 limp bodies lay there. Shivering in the corner was a singular maiden clawing at her arms and shivering from head to toe. An illegitimate princess of the realm as it were. Naturally the black rose claim this was reserved as knowledge only for kings before a copy was stolen by the black rose from the royal library. It would appear even they fear the reaper.</p>
<p>Comments/Explanations:<br>
The idea behind these tales is to cement that the reapers are feared throughout whatever world this takes place in. The Reapers in my view should be an outside force feared by all the factions. I believe the Blue dragons would be oblivious mostly to them thanks to their loose ties with Corax. The Black rose would wish to avoid them and would have the most information on them and the Cultists would try to appease them.</p>
<p>This entry is to display the relationships that all 3 factions share with the reapers and gives them a nice history as to why perhaps a reaper may show up at the gathering e.g Story two shows they can take human form if needed without giving the lore characters too much information.</p>
<p>Something I wish to add into the lore is that after 2 days the reason people see that a reaper target is dead is that the mark of Corax will appear on their hand. This would give credence to why a shell of a person would be understood to be a reaper victim while at the same time directly attaching the Reapers to Corax in some manner that in the future I would like to manifest as a dead black rose assassin who looks into Corax’s eyes.</p>
<p>Another thing I wanted to setup was this idea of a giant reaper being summoned by a bard. While not actually a class yet this opens the door to future ideas and teases that we aren’t just thinking of the now. We may not actually make the bard but we’ll also show we aren’t closed minded <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> finaly the addition of an illegitimate princess was to introduce the idea that perhaps Royal blood has power over Beings infused with Corax’s power giving the blue dragon a little flavour as a faction.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 01:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-467-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-reaper/467.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Reaper</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
