<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum Matches - Forum of Lies</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/c/forum-matches/11</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Forum Matches&#39; category Forum Mafia/Werewolf. Organize @ &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.gg/tol&quot;&gt;https://discord.gg/tol&lt;/a&gt; &lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Looking for &lt;a class=&quot;hashtag&quot; href=&quot;/c/forum-matches/forum-of-lies/14&quot;&gt;#&lt;span&gt;forum-matches:forum-of-lies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ?&lt;/font&gt;</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 17:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/c/forum-matches/11.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>[FM] Please Don&#39;t Hate Me FM: Mad17 Edition [14/17]</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[clonedcheese]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="please-dont-hate-me-fm-mad17-edition-1" class="anchor" href="#please-dont-hate-me-fm-mad17-edition-1"></a>Please Don’t Hate Me FM: Mad17 Edition</h1>
<p>Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/clonedcheese">@clonedcheese</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/atlas">@Atlas</a></p>
<p>Reviewed by <a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a></p>
<p>Alt-modded by <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a></p>
<p>Looking for co-hosts and/or VC bots</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/7/6/7681007a8c62d974d209166f83a495a29612b481.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/7681007a8c62d974d209166f83a495a29612b481" title="article-0-088661BC000005DC-552_308x185"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/6/7681007a8c62d974d209166f83a495a29612b481_2_690x414.jpeg" alt="article-0-088661BC000005DC-552_308x185" data-base62-sha1="gUkJ3BBh4LyRxVULKBd8evfruX7" width="690" height="414" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/6/7681007a8c62d974d209166f83a495a29612b481_2_690x414.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/6/7681007a8c62d974d209166f83a495a29612b481_2_1035x621.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/6/7681007a8c62d974d209166f83a495a29612b481_2_1380x828.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/6/7681007a8c62d974d209166f83a495a29612b481_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">article-0-088661BC000005DC-552_308x185</span><span class="informations">1908×1146 94.5 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><em>Why do people hate me?</em></p>
<p>Flavor will be things a lot of people hate, scum flavor based on my very own unpopular opinions! (Don’t worry they’ll get fakeclaims <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=10" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">)</p>
<h2>
<a name="audience-participation-2" class="anchor" href="#audience-participation-2"></a>Audience participation</h2>
<p>While signups are underway, people may freely suggest a flavor for the game by privately messaging the host through either discord or forum message - something that makes you uncomfortable, something that you really don’t like!</p>
<h2>
<a name="rules-3" class="anchor" href="#rules-3"></a>Rules:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow the <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">global forum rules</a> and the <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-game-rules/78926">Forum Game rules</a>
</li>
<li>Don’t discuss this game outside of host-sanctioned threads/private messages.</li>
<li>Please be respectful to all players.</li>
<li>Don’t weaponise the host.</li>
<li>Please do not use big text, it is reserved for the host.</li>
<li>Do not edit or delete posts. Quickedits for grammar, typos, and/or readability will be allowed, but any edit of content will be modkilled.</li>
<li>Do not quote host private messages.</li>
<li>Do not gamethrow. This includes anything that goes against your stated win condition.</li>
<li>If you do not post for 36 gameplay hours, you will be prodded for inactivity. If you do not respond within the next 12 hours, you will be forced to replace out or modkilled.</li>
<li>Any activity tells will receive newspaper to head <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/angry.png?v=10" title=":angry:" class="emoji" alt=":angry:">
</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="gameplay-4" class="anchor" href="#gameplay-4"></a>Gameplay:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Days will last 48 hours, and nights will last 24 hours.</li>
<li>This is a Mad17 Setup.</li>
</ul>
<details>
<summary>
Setup Description</summary>
<p><font color="green"><strong>13x Town</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>4x Mafia</strong></font></p>
<p>Of the following 18 roles, 1 will randomly be discarded and the other 17 will be assigned at random to one player in the game without regard for the player’s alignment. Each role is restricted to using its action only on the nights listed on the chart. The Mafia will be told which role is not present in the game.</p>
<div class="md-table">
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th><strong>Role</strong></th>
<th><strong>Acts On These Nights</strong></th>
<th><strong>Modifier</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Watcher</td>
<td>n1 Only</td>
<td>Macho</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Watcher</td>
<td>n2 Only</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Alignment Cop</td>
<td>n2 Only</td>
<td>1x Ninja</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Alignment Cop</td>
<td>n3 Only</td>
<td>1x Ninja</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Vigilante</td>
<td>n2 Only</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Vigilante</td>
<td>n3 Only</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Doctor</td>
<td>n1, n3</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Doctor</td>
<td>n2, n4</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Tracker</td>
<td>n1, n3</td>
<td>1x Strongman</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Tracker</td>
<td>n2, n4</td>
<td>1x Strongman</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Jailkeeper</td>
<td>n1, n3</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Jailkeeper</td>
<td>n2, n4</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Roleblocker</td>
<td>n1, n3</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Roleblocker</td>
<td>n2, n4</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Role Cop</td>
<td>n1, n2, n3</td>
<td>1x Strongman</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Jack of All Trades</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>(Role Cop, Tracker, Roleblocker)</td>
<td>n1, n2, n3</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Jack of All Trades</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>(Doctor, Jailkeeper, Voyeur)</td>
<td>n1, n2, n3</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Voyeur</td>
<td>n1, n2, n3, n4</td>
<td>1x Strongman</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<details>
<summary>
Role Cards</summary>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Watcher</strong></h2>
<p>You may watch a player each night. If that player is visited, you learn the names of all the players that used a night action on that player that same night.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Alignment Cop</strong></h2>
<p>You may target one player and learn whether they are town or mafia.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Vigilante</strong></h2>
<p>You may choose one player to kill.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Doctor</strong></h2>
<p>Each night you may protect one player from death.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Tracker</strong></h2>
<p>Each night you may follow one person. If they visit somebody, you will know who.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Jailkeeper</strong></h2>
<p>Each night you may lock somebody up, preventing them from using any night actions but also protecting them from death.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Roleblocker</strong></h2>
<p>Each night you may block a player from successfully performing their night action.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Role Cop</strong></h2>
<p>Each night you have the ability to investigate one player to see what they can do at night. You will be told their role, but not their alignment.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Jack of All Trades</strong></h2>
<p>Every night you may use any one of your three actions, but you may only use each one once per game.</p>
<p>Your three actions are either Role Cop, Tracker, and Roleblocker <em>or</em> Doctor, Jailkeeper, and Voyeur</p>
<p>See the other role cards to learn what these actions do.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Voyeur</strong></h2>
<p>Each night you may target a player and learn what night actions, if any, they were targeted by.</p>
</blockquote>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Role Modifiers</summary>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Macho</strong></h2>
<p>You cannot be protected from nightkills in any way.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Ninja</strong></h2>
<p>You are able to perform night actions without being detected as having targeted anyone by Trackers, Watchers, etc.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><strong>Strongman</strong></h2>
<p>If you perform a kill, you have immunity against this action being manipulated with or protected against.</p>
</blockquote>
</details>
</details>
<p>Dead players may choose to become a VC bot.</p>
<h2>
<a name="executions-5" class="anchor" href="#executions-5"></a>Executions:</h2>
<ul>
<li>To accuse a player, bold your message and type <strong>/vote [player]</strong> or <strong>/accuse [player]</strong> , and ping the hosts. <strong>Any vote that do not ping the hosts will be void.</strong>
</li>
<li>Should majority be reached on a player, they will be executed and the day finishes early.</li>
<li>Should no majority be reached, plurality will take effect and the player with the most votes at the end of the day will be executed. In the case of a tie, no executions will occur.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="logs-6" class="anchor" href="#logs-6"></a>Logs:</h2>
<ul>
<li>There are no logs in this game, although players may be allowed to post cat pictures when they flip at the discretion of the host.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="alts-7" class="anchor" href="#alts-7"></a>Alts:</h2>
<p>Go wild lmao</p>
<p>Contact <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a> and myself in a private message</p>
<h2>
<a name="other-notes-8" class="anchor" href="#other-notes-8"></a>Other Notes:</h2>
<p>If every player wishes the skip the night, the night will be skipped. Type /skip night or something in your rolecard.</p>
<h2>
<a name="player-list-9" class="anchor" href="#player-list-9"></a>Player List:</h2>
<ol>
<li>EliThePsycho</li>
<li>Nanook</li>
<li>Illwei</li>
<li>Ari_2412</li>
<li>Rue</li>
<li>Luxy</li>
<li>Squirrel2412</li>
<li>Ruri</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>Wisp</li>
<li>Kaif</li>
<li>Tilgarial</li>
<li>Kanave</li>
<li>SirDerpsAlot</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="graveyard-10" class="anchor" href="#graveyard-10"></a>Graveyard:</h1>
<h2>
<a name="backups-11" class="anchor" href="#backups-11"></a>Backups:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Zone_Q11</li>
<li>Gghana</li>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
<li>Emilia</li>
<li>Chloe</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="specs-12" class="anchor" href="#specs-12"></a>Specs:</h2>
<ol>
<li>DatBird (informed)</li>
<li>Katze</li>
<li>TrustworthyLiberal</li>
<li>Silviu (uninformed)</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="useful-links-13" class="anchor" href="#useful-links-13"></a>Useful links:</h2>
            <p><small>296 posts - 37 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-please-dont-hate-me-fm-mad17-edition-14-17/89191">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-please-dont-hate-me-fm-mad17-edition-14-17/89191</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 17:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89191</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-please-dont-hate-me-fm-mad17-edition-14-17/89191.rss">[FM] Please Don&#39;t Hate Me FM: Mad17 Edition [14/17]</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Dungeon Master - 5/16 - Misc</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aelin]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>
<a name="dungeon-master-1" class="anchor" href="#dungeon-master-1"></a>Dungeon Master</h2>
<p>Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/aelin">@Aelin</a>, and looking for a co-host!</p>
<hr>
<p><em><strong>Dungeon Master is a turn-based proxy fighter royale… or something.</strong></em></p>
<h2>
<a name="the-map-starts-out-as-a-4x4-grid-which-will-be-turned-into-a-3x3-grid-at-9-players-then-a-2x2-grid-at-4-players-each-player-will-spawn-in-a-different-grid-with-a-preset-loot-pool-2" class="anchor" href="#the-map-starts-out-as-a-4x4-grid-which-will-be-turned-into-a-3x3-grid-at-9-players-then-a-2x2-grid-at-4-players-each-player-will-spawn-in-a-different-grid-with-a-preset-loot-pool-2"></a>The Map starts out as a 4x4 grid, which will be turned into a 3x3 grid at 9 players, then a 2x2 grid at 4 players. Each player will spawn in a different grid with a preset loot pool.</h2>
<p><img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/ifetA15OYPjtZJeAUyCmUATTE3BWH60N6FGq1bdArP3rAjerLFawHjLlmvaZL7LZGGuMEVt2eHwpsp9GNTFuoNsblaAy2fX-Se9XZFnrG8zNiDxcDgtuD_3KGKNqObv83EMtZAg=s0" alt="" width="406" height="406"></p>
<h2>
<a name="rounds-are-split-into-four-phases-each-lasting-12-hours-movement-looting-equipment-and-battle-3" class="anchor" href="#rounds-are-split-into-four-phases-each-lasting-12-hours-movement-looting-equipment-and-battle-3"></a>Rounds are split into four phases, each lasting 12 hours: Movement, Looting, Equipment, and Battle.</h2>
<h2>
<a name="movement-4" class="anchor" href="#movement-4"></a>Movement</h2>
<p>Each round, you may choose to move 1 tile in any direction, including diagonally. You may also choose to stay in your current grid for another go at your loot pool. Every round, player locations will be shown on the map.</p>
<p><strong>ALL ACTIONS CAN BE LOCKED AND WOULD BE MASSIVELY APPRECIATED BY THE HOST IN ORDER TO IMPROVE PROCESSING SPEED.</strong></p>
<h2>
<a name="looting-5" class="anchor" href="#looting-5"></a>Looting</h2>
<p>After you move to your tile, you will have a chance to loot your tile. There are four different types of items; Physical, Magical, Defensive, and Support, as well as four different tiers; Common, Uncommon, Rare, and Legendary. You will be able to submit three looting actions by default.</p>
<p>The center squares of the 4x4 and 3x3 maps will have higher tiered loot than the outskirts on average, while the corners will have the lowest tiered loot.</p>
<p>Rooms will be made if there is more than a single player on a tile in order for the tile to chat. There will also be a main thread active at all times.</p>
<h2>
<a name="equipment-6" class="anchor" href="#equipment-6"></a>Equipment</h2>
<p>Each player will start out with 4 Champions; A Gladiator, a Rogue, a Healer, and a Mage. You will be told which items you have looted from your square, and at this point, you can now equip your items to your Champions. Gladiators and Rogues have an affinity for Physical items, Mages and Healers have an affinity for Magical items, and Rogues and Healers have an affinity for Support items.</p>
<p>Defensive items are broken up into Light Armor, Medium Armor, and Heavy Armor. Only Gladiators can equip Heavy Armor. Healers can not equip Medium Armor.</p>
<p>Each character can equip 2 of any combination of Physical, Magical, and Support items, and 1 Defensive Item.</p>
<h2>
<a name="battling-7" class="anchor" href="#battling-7"></a>Battling</h2>
<p>Gladiators are strong against Mages, Mages are strong against Rogues, and Rogues are strong against Gladiators. All 3 are strong against Healers, but if a Healer is in the fight, their partner becomes strong against both other types of fighters. If two Healers are in the fight, their effect cancels out. Players will get told who is on their tile, their living Champions, as well as the Champions’ health. They will then fight in 2v2 fights with their Champions.*</p>
<p>Gladiators start with 100 health, Mages and Rogues start with 85 health, and Healers start with 80 health. Champions who are strong against another Champion will deal 1.25x damage to that Champion type, and will take 0.8x damage from that Champion type. The Healer passive will negate any opposing teams’ strengths against their partner.</p>
<p>Players will then submit 4 rounds of actions, or a ‘set’, for each character they pick. Character affinities will multiply their respective items’ effects by 1.25x. This stacks additively with strengths rather than multiplicatively.**</p>
<p>If there is only a single player on a tile, instead of a battle phase, they will instead be able to loot a single extra item.</p>
<p>*If there are 3 players on a tile, then they will engage in two separate 2v2 battles. If there are 4 players on a tile, they will be split randomly into single 2v2 battles. This pattern will continue for all odd/even pairings.</p>
<p>**This means that a Gladiator with a Physical weapon would do 1.5x damage to a Mage rather than 1.5625x damage, for example.</p>
<h2>
<a name="actions-8" class="anchor" href="#actions-8"></a>Actions</h2>
<p>There are four types of actions; Attack, Heal, Support, and Evade. Only Healers can Heal. Gladiators can not choose to Support. For each type of Attack action, you must also submit a preference list of what type of character you would like to attack. Evasion will halve the damage you receive from a turn.</p>
<p>For example, a set from a Gladiator could look like:</p>
<p>Attack [Healer, Mage, Gladiator, Rogue]<br>
Attack [Healer, Mage, Gladiator, Rogue]<br>
Evade<br>
Attack [Gladiator, Healer, Mage, Rogue]</p>
<h2>
<a name="calculations-9" class="anchor" href="#calculations-9"></a>Calculations</h2>
<p>Attacks will be calculated starting with a 2d10 for Gladiators, a 3d8 for Rogues, a 4d5 for Mages, and a 1d10 for Healers, and then weapon bonuses will be added (and listed with the item when you pick it up.) After that, Defensive bonuses will be calculated based on the Defensive stat of the item, and then finally, Strength modifiers will be added to get the final damage.</p>
<p>Critical Hits are achieved when you roll the highest number for your base attack (10 for Gladiators, 8 for Rogues, 5 for Mages, and 10 for Healers), and do double the damage.</p>
<p>For example, a Mage attack against a Rogue could look like:</p>
<p>Attack [4, 2, 1, 10] = 17<br>
+1d8 Item [5] = 22<br>
+1d8 Item [3] = 25<br>
Opponent Defense 1d10 [9] = 16<br>
Strength Boost [16x1.25] = 20</p>
<p>This would do 20 damage against a Rogue.<br>
Numbers will be rounded to the nearest whole number.</p>
<p>Only Healers have access to the Heal move. This Healing will be done based on a 1d20, and can go above the original health cap up to 150%, and then item bonuses will be accounted for. Healers can heal either themselves or their partner.</p>
<p>Health stats will be updated at the end of a turn based on the cumulative health total. So, if a Rogue with 10 health takes 15 damage, but is then healed for 20, they will survive with 15 health.</p>
<p>It is up to the players whether they want to have this be hosted on Forums or on Discord. Both options have pros and cons for me, but will probably not effect gameplay.</p>
<h2>
<a name="deathslosing-10" class="anchor" href="#deathslosing-10"></a>Deaths/Losing</h2>
<p>Whenever a Champion ends a turn with less than 1 Health, they will die. A player loses and is out of the game when all 4 of their Champions die.</p>
<p>In the event that no players die within, like, a reasonable amount of turns due to intentional avoidance, the host reserves the right to just fucking nuke people lol</p>
<h2>
<a name="players-11" class="anchor" href="#players-11"></a>Players</h2>
<ol>
<li>Atlas</li>
<li>Whysper</li>
<li>Zone</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>Squirrel</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="backups-12" class="anchor" href="#backups-12"></a>Backups</h2>
<ol>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="spectators-13" class="anchor" href="#spectators-13"></a>Spectators</h2>
<ol>
<li>Silviu</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>87 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/dungeon-master-5-16-misc/89177">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/dungeon-master-5-16-misc/89177</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 20:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89177</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/dungeon-master-5-16-misc/89177.rss">Dungeon Master - 5/16 - Misc</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>TBT Cop 9er game</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[b100ming]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am hosting a mafia game on another site called the bell tree forums.</p>
<p>Requirements:<br>
A tbt account<br>
The ability to tell people when you can’t be active.</p>
<p>Players<br>
1<br>
2<br>
3<br>
4<br>
5<br>
6<br>
7<br>
8<br>
9</p>
<p>Observers:<br>
1<br>
2<br>
3</p>
<p>Replacements<br>
1<br>
2<br>
3</p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tbt-cop-9er-game/89153">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tbt-cop-9er-game/89153</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89153</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tbt-cop-9er-game/89153.rss">TBT Cop 9er game</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Misc] BotF X - New World Chaos - Game Thread (Evil Wins)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Going to the police was a mistake. A shifty figure has been following you for blocks, and you swear people on the street are taking notes as you pass by. You hide around a corner waiting for an ambush, only to see that shifty figure speeding off in an Aston Martin. An old war buddy calls in a favor to look up the license, and… no. No no no no no, how high does this go? The Reds don’t have this kind of influence, not yet, who’s behind this? That’s when you hear the knock.</em><br>
<small>credit to besjbo for the above flavor</small></p>
<h1>
<a name="welcome-to-new-world-chaos-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-crichard564-1" class="anchor" href="#welcome-to-new-world-chaos-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-crichard564-1"></a>Welcome to New World Chaos! Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a>
</h1>
<h1>
<a name="this-script-is-not-my-own-made-by-besjbo-i-do-not-claim-to-have-made-this-script-2" class="anchor" href="#this-script-is-not-my-own-made-by-besjbo-i-do-not-claim-to-have-made-this-script-2"></a>THIS SCRIPT IS NOT MY OWN (made by Besjbo). I DO NOT CLAIM TO HAVE MADE THIS SCRIPT.</h1>
<h1>
<a name="this-script-is-also-a-homebrew-script-meaning-it-is-not-made-using-official-clocktower-characters-3" class="anchor" href="#this-script-is-also-a-homebrew-script-meaning-it-is-not-made-using-official-clocktower-characters-3"></a>THIS SCRIPT IS ALSO A HOMEBREW SCRIPT, MEANING IT IS NOT MADE USING OFFICIAL CLOCKTOWER CHARACTERS.</h1>
<h1>
<a name="please-read-the-below-spoilers-for-information-on-how-to-play-the-game-4" class="anchor" href="#please-read-the-below-spoilers-for-information-on-how-to-play-the-game-4"></a>Please read the below spoilers for information on how to play the game!</h1>
<details>
<summary>
Character List</summary>
<p>Character just means role; the character types are Townsfolk, Outsider, Minion, and Demon.<br>
Townsfolk and Outsiders are good-aligned to start, Minions and the Demon are evil-aligned to start.  There are no neutral parties in Ravenswood Bluff.<br>
[Brackets] denote abilities upon setup; for example, if it says [+1 Outsider], then I replace 1 Townsfolk with 1 Outsider.</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorstebluetownsfolkcolor-5" class="anchor" href="#colorstebluetownsfolkcolor-5"></a><font color="steblue">Townsfolk</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Wiretap</strong></font> - You are 1 of 2 wiretap characters, but do not know which.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Domestic Wiretap</strong> - You start knowing two allied players. When they both die, you learn their characters tonight.</li>
<li>
<strong>Foreign Wiretap</strong> - You start knowing two opposing players. When you die, you learn the Evil character tonight.</li>
</ul>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Double Agent</strong></font> - The Demon sees you instead of a Minion. That Minion recieves no starting information.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Sleeper</strong></font> - You think you are an in-play Minion, and neither of you recieve starting information. If you are “mad” about being the Sleeper, you learn the in-play Demon tonight.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Jurist</strong></font> - Each night, choose a player and learn their character. Good living players register falsely to you.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Freelancer</strong></font> - Each night, choose a Good character. You learn that it is 1 of 2 players, if in play. If not in play, you recieve arbitrary info tonight.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Blacklister</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), choose a character (not yours, not a Traveller). You learn its nearest Evil character, if in play. If not in play, you recieve arbitrary info tonight.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Black Ops</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), you learn if you whispered the Demon today.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Populist</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), you learn a character who was “mad” about being the Populist today.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Diplomat</strong></font> - Each day, you may whisper the storyteller with two other players (not Travellers, different from yesterday) &amp; broker a deal between them. If either player breaks the deal, they malfunction until dawn.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Eavesdropper</strong></font> - Each day, you may visit the Storyteller to learn something about each player you whispered today, in no particular order.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Symbologist</strong></font> - You have 3 Townsfolk abilities, but 1 malfunctions. You also register as the functioning Townsfolk.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Truther</strong></font> - If you die at night, choose a character and learn all players with that character.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Ambassador</strong></font> - You are immune to all abilities and do not count towards the number of living players. One Good player starts knowing the Ambassador is in play.</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorsteblueoutsiderscolor-6" class="anchor" href="#colorsteblueoutsiderscolor-6"></a><font color="steblue">Outsiders</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Libertine</strong></font> - You start holding a Drunk character token. Each night (but not the first), it moves to a player the holder whispered today. You think you are a Townsfolk until the Drunk token moves.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Drunk character is an Outsider with the ability “You do not know you are the Drunk. You<br>
think you are a Townsfolk, but your ability malfunctions.” It cannot start in play. Note that the Demon is still the Demon, even if they are holding this token.</li>
</ul>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Activist</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), a player dies unless a living player was “mad” about being the Activist today (even if you are dead.)<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>MAD-Man</strong></font> - Each night, choose another living player (not a Traveler) to hold the football. If the holder is executed, you drop The Bomb and lose (even if dead).<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Sympathizer</strong></font> - A Townsfolk is Evil and registers as a Defector, but does not know. You have their ability, and the Demon knows them.</p>
<ul>
<li>“Defector” is a character. (Ex: Jurist can see somebody as a Defector). It doesn’t actually have any ability, because you can only register as one, and it cannot be in-play.</li>
</ul>
<h1>
<a name="colorredminionscolor-7" class="anchor" href="#colorredminionscolor-7"></a><font color="red">Minions</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="red"><strong>Agitprop</strong></font> - - Each night, choose a player and a statement. Tomorrow, if that player is “mad” about denying that statement, they might be executed.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Templar</strong></font> - If you nominate a Good player you did not whisper today and they are executed, Evil wins.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Chairman</strong></font> - Once per game at night (but not the first), choose an Outsider player: they swap characters and alignments with the Demon. [+1 Outsider]<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Brainwasher</strong></font> - Townsfolk might recieve the incorrect character in setup (their abilities work normally).</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorreddemonscolor-8" class="anchor" href="#colorreddemonscolor-8"></a><font color="red">Demons</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="red"><strong>Comitern</strong></font> -  Each Comintern knows one other Comintern. Each night (but not the first), a Comintern might die. Evil wins only when all Good players are dead. You register as a Minion too. [Most players are Comintern]<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Draconis</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), choose a character: if in play, that player dies and an Evil player becomes their character. If not in play, a player dies.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Seclorum</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), you learn the character of everyone you whispered today, then choose a player: they die.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Kabal</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), choose a player: they die. If you win, if an Outsider was most responsible for their team losing, they switch teams and win with you. [+1 Outsider]</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Travellers</summary>
<p>Travelers are special and powerful characters with different rules than normal citizens.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Traveler characters are publicly known.</strong> If a player joins the game as the United Nations, for example, everyone knows that they are the United Nations.</li>
<li>
<strong>Traveler alignments are unknown.</strong> Because Traveler characters are known, the question regarding them becomes which side they’re playing for. Travelers are more likely to be good than evil; general practice is that one in three Travelers is evil, but it is possible for there to be only one Traveler in a game and that Traveler to be evil. Evil Travelers will be told who the Demon is when they enter play; Good Travelers will be told nothing. The Demon and Minions will not be told if a Traveler is good or evil.<br>
Note that if the Comitern is in play, Evil Travellers will only be told so, and will not be told any Comitern.</li>
<li>
<strong>Traveler players may join or leave the game at any time.</strong> This game is designed for live play, and the Travelers are designed to accommodate players who arrive late or must leave early. If you would like to play, but cannot join at game start or do not think that you can stay around for the end of the game, then you may consider playing as a Traveler character instead of a normal citizen. However, I will not allow Traveler players to sub out (since the nature of their character is designed for them to simply leave if they cannot play), and if a Traveler player has left the game, they may not rejoin later. I will additionally ask that players who would consider joining as Travelers after the game has started notify me of this before the start of the game; I will compile a list of these potential Travelers and people not on this list by the start of the game will not be allowed to join as a Traveler. If a player wishes to join an in-progress game as a Traveler, I may bar them from choosing certain characters.</li>
<li>
<strong>Travelers with a night ability act before any citizens.</strong> Their abilities will be resolved absolutely first.</li>
<li>
<strong>Travelers are not executed; they are exiled.</strong> An exile is different from an execution in a few key ways.<br>
-An exile is not considered an execution, meaning that a game can see the exile of a Traveler and an execution in the same day.<br>
-An exile is not affected by any abilities affecting nomination, voting or execution.<br>
-An exile may be called for at any time, by anyone, even if that player is presently unable to nominate, and a player who calls for the exile of a Traveler may still nominate if they have not already.<br>
-Dead players may vote on the exile of a Traveler, and they do not spend their ghost vote to do so.<br>
-And finally, a simple majority vote is all that is required to exile a Traveler. However, I will houserule that no more than one exile may occur per day.</li>
</ol>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Traveller Characters</summary>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Presi</font><font color="red">dent</font></strong> - You may privately veto your exile unless the majority of 3 different character types voted for your exile.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">Celeb</font><font color="red">rity</font></strong> - Each night (but not the first), until dusk, a player who was “mad” about everything you said today acts twice.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">Inter</font><font color="red">pol</font></strong> - If the player you nominate is executed, everyone you whispered today may visit the Storyteller tommorow to learn something about that player.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">United</font> <font color="red">Nations</font></strong> - If all living players vote to ratify you, you run nominations from now on, and you may change the nomination and voting rules, excepte on yourself.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">Spym</font><font color="red">aster</font></strong> - Each day, choose a player: if they agree, you learn their character tonight, then their character changes.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Town Composition</summary>
<p>This game is designed for a variable number of players, and thus the composition of the game is able to change depending on how many players join. The following list denotes the composition of the game at each possible player count.</p>
<p>Total Players: Townsfolk/Outsiders/Minions/Demons</p>
<p>5: 3/0/1/1<br>
6: 3/1/1/1<br>
7: 5/0/1/1<br>
8: 5/1/1/1<br>
9: 5/2/1/1<br>
10: 7/0/2/1<br>
11: 7/1/2/1<br>
12: 7/2/2/1</p>
<p>Every character in-game is unique in that more than one of the same character will never appear at the start of the game (there can never be two Wiretaps at the start, for example).</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Phase Length</summary>
<p>Each day phase will last for no longer than 48 hours.</p>
<p>12 hours: Discussion phase. Nominations may not be cast at this time.<br>
24 hours: Nomination phase. Players who wish to nominate may do so at this time, <strong>and votes may begun to be cast during this time as well.</strong><br>
12 hours: Vote finalization. During this time, votes may be cast freely on any existing nomination, but no new nominations may be made. Once this time ends or all votes have been locked in, the day will resolve.</p>
<p>The night phase will last for 24 hours, or until all abilities have been performed and resolved.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
The Storyteller</summary>
<p>Storyteller</p>
<p>The Storyteller is the key moderator for the game; All ability uses at night must be sent to the Storyteller via private message, and Storyteller will have the final say on any open-ended ability behaviors. Storyteller’s goal is to keep the game both fun and balanced, and they’ll often be trying to make it last as long as possible; however, the Storyteller may not alter any existing rules to accomplish this.<br>
Also, the thing the Storyteller uses to keep track of things is called the Grimoire. It’s basically the spreadsheet.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
The Fabled</summary>
<p>The Fabled aren’t really characters so much as special modifiers that the Storyteller can put in play to tweak the game. For example, the Angel can be put into play to help keep newer players from being targeted, or the Buddhist can be put into play to keep the more experienced players from dominating the discussion. Fabled will always be announced when they are in play, along with their effect upon gamestate. A breakdown of Fabled characters we may be using can be found below.</p>
<p><font color="gold"><strong>Angel</strong></font> : Something bad might happen to whomever is most responsible for the death of a new player.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Buddhist</strong></font> : Veteran players may not speak for the first six hours of the day phase.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Hell’s Librarian</strong></font> : Something bad might happen to whomever speaks when the Storyteller calls for silence.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Fiddler</strong></font>: Once per game, at night, the Demon secretly chooses a player of an opposing alignment; All players then choose which of these two wins the game.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Deus Ex Fiasco</strong></font>: Once per game, the storyteller will make a mistake, correct it and publicly admit to it.</p>
<p>If you want any of these added, ping me in signup thread (before game) or in classcard (during game).</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
The Bomb (IMPORTANT, PLEASE READ)</summary>
<p><font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> is a fabled character that is always in play this game. It reads:</p>
<p><strong>If two players (dead or alive) agree to drop the bomb, and at least one is Good, Evil wins. If Comintern is in play, Good wins instead. If both are Evil, Good wins.</strong><br>
(Note that Kabal cannot make an outsider switch teams via dropping the Bomb.)</p>
<p>The only reason to ever drop <strong><font color="maroon">The Bomb</font></strong> as Good is if you believe Comitern is in play.<br>
<strong>I will prevent any attempts to drop <font color="maroon">The Bomb</font> out of intent to gamethrow.</strong><br>
Also, if necessary, I will timegate <strong><font color="maroon">The Bomb</font></strong> to a certain day, depending on playercount.</p>
<p>If you want to drop <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font>, do it like this:</p>
<p><strong>I would like to drop <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> with @[name] <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a></strong><br>
then both of you will either say<br>
<strong>I turn the key <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a></strong> (if both players do this, <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> will be dropped)<br>
or<br>
<strong>I do not turn the key <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a></strong> (if at least one player does this, <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> will not be dropped)</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Scum Info</summary>
<p>On the first night of the game, when relatively few characters act, the evil characters will all be woken to learn who one another are. Evil players will not be allowed to communicate at night. The Demon will be told who all of their Minions are, and the Minions will know who the Demon is and who all of the other Minions are. However, the Minions and the Demon will not learn which specific characters any of their fellow evils are. The Demon will additionally be told three characters that are not in play, to serve as safe claims. They may claim any of these, none of these, or simply hand the claims off to Minions; however they think they will be best served.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Malfunctioning &amp; Registration</summary>
<p>The primary source of interference with abilities in this game is the malfunction. A class that is malfunctioning is not told that they are malfunctioning; if the class is one that gathers information, then the information they receive that night is arbitrary (open-ended, Storyteller may resolve at their discretion), otherwise, the malfunctioning class’ ability simply does not have any effect.</p>
<p>You may also see experienced players refer to malfunctioning as “drunkness”, “poisoning”, or “droison”.</p>
<p>Registration causes a player to “appear” a certain way (for most purposes). For example, if the Jurist picks a good living player, then they learn something they are not. If you pick a character that the Symbologist has a functioning ability of, then you can learn the Symbologist, etc etc etc.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Madness</summary>
<p>Certain character abilities in this script reference a status known as “madness”. What madness means, in the simplest terms, is that when a player is “mad” about something, they are trying to convince the other players that it is true, even if it is not (especially if it is not). Ultimately, the Storyteller is the one who judges whether the “mad” player’s efforts are sufficient to avoid punishment (or to obtain a reward!), but this allows the Storyteller to be more lenient toward players who are unfamiliar with the concept, and by the same token, to expect more from an experienced player.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Nominations and Voting</summary>
<p>Voting in this game works a little differently. After the formal discussion phase has ended, the Storyteller will declare that nominations are opened. A player must be nominated before they can be voted on. Each player may only be nominated once per day, and each player may only nominate once per day. When a nomination is opened, the storyteller will begin to count votes. Votes may be precast, and may be altered so long as they are considered not to be locked in. A vote is locked in when everyone between the accused and the voter (going down the list from the accused) has locked in their vote, or once the day ends, assuming that not all votes on the nomination have been cast. Any votes that are not counted at EoD will be considered votes to pardon. If the count of votes to execute is more than half of the number of living players, and is the highest count of votes against any player that day, the accused will be considered “about to die”. At the end of the day or when all votes on all nominations have been cast, the player who is “about to die” will be executed. There isn’t such a thing as a quickhammer around here; we’re a little more careful with what we do.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Whispers (DIFFERENT THAN NORMAL, PLEASE READ)</summary>
<p>Players may whisper each other in-game through private messages. Whispers must, however, be publicly announced, typically by requesting permission to whisper (a standard format is /whisper [Player]). Once a whisper has been declared and accepted, the two players may whisper via private message until one of them speaks publicly in the game chat, at which point the whisper is considered over and the players must declare whispers again if they wish to whisper publicly.</p>
<p>Additionally, you may send up to 15 words to your neighbors without having to announce a whisper. <strong>These do not count as a whisper for the purposes of abilities.</strong></p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Death</summary>
<p>When a player dies, nothing is revealed about their character and they are allowed to stay in the game and speak. They may not nominate and they will have only one vote token (this will allow them to cast a vote to execute) for the entire game. Evil players who die may thus continue to help their allies by keeping up their claim and spreading misinformation, and good players may similarly help their allies by retaining relevant info that others may have forgotten in the heat of things. Once a player dies, their ability stops working, which means that a player killed before they would perform their ability will not perform their ability, and any ability with a persistent effect will end upon the player’s death.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Victory</summary>
<p>Good wins by eliminating all Demons (you don’t need to kill Minions to win). Evil wins by reducing the game to two living players (even if both players are good). The Storyteller may also declare a victory for Evil if Good may no longer possibly win (for example, if only evil players are left alive and thus no one would nominate the Demon). Certain character abilities may present alternate routes to victory; these classes, if able to appear, will be made known on the character list. In the event of a tie (both teams would win at the same time), Good wins.</p>
</details>
<h1>
<a name="i-am-capping-this-game-at-12-players-not-including-travellers-additionally-i-will-not-be-accepting-travellers-unless-there-is-9-residents-9" class="anchor" href="#i-am-capping-this-game-at-12-players-not-including-travellers-additionally-i-will-not-be-accepting-travellers-unless-there-is-9-residents-9"></a>I am capping this game at 12 players, not including Travellers. Additionally, I will not be accepting travellers unless there is 9 residents.</h1>
<h1>
<a name="playerlist-just-ping-me-and-my-cohost-with-in-and-the-seat-you-want-yes-we-let-you-choose-10" class="anchor" href="#playerlist-just-ping-me-and-my-cohost-with-in-and-the-seat-you-want-yes-we-let-you-choose-10"></a>Playerlist; just ping me and my cohost with /in and the seat you want (yes, we let you choose).</h1>
<ol>
<li>Intensify (<strong><font color="steblue">Presi<font color="red">dent</font></font></strong>)</li>
<li>Magnus</li>
<li>Firekitten</li>
<li>clonedcheese</li>
<li>Icibalus (<strong><font color="steblue">Celeb</font><font color="red">rity</font></strong>)</li>
<li>Nightingale</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>PKR</li>
<li>Atlas</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="backups-11" class="anchor" href="#backups-11"></a>Backups</h1>
<ol>
<li>Blitz</li>
<li>Amelia</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="spectators-informed-12" class="anchor" href="#spectators-informed-12"></a>Spectators (informed)</h1>
<ol>
<li>DatBird</li>
<li>Silviu</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="if-you-have-any-questions-feel-free-to-ask-in-your-card-we-are-here-to-help-13" class="anchor" href="#if-you-have-any-questions-feel-free-to-ask-in-your-card-we-are-here-to-help-13"></a>If you have <em>any</em> questions, feel free to ask in your card. We are here to help.</h1>
            <p><small>2080 posts - 20 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-botf-x-new-world-chaos-game-thread-evil-wins/89139">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-botf-x-new-world-chaos-game-thread-evil-wins/89139</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 23:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89139</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-botf-x-new-world-chaos-game-thread-evil-wins/89139.rss">[Misc] BotF X - New World Chaos - Game Thread (Evil Wins)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[FM] Sussy Jungle Oligarchy - CANNED</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <div align="center">
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bnyAej_u15A/maxresdefault.jpg" width="690" height="388"></p>
<h1>
<a name="jungle-oligarchy-run-by-geyde-1" class="anchor" href="#jungle-oligarchy-run-by-geyde-1"></a>Jungle Oligarchy run by <a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a>
</h1>
</div>
<h3>
<a name="rules-2" class="anchor" href="#rules-2"></a>Rules</h3>
<ul>
<li>Global Forum Rules</li>
<li><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Forum™ Mafia™ Rules™ by™ Luxy™ the™ <small>former</small> Moderator™</a></li>
</ul>
<p>Rulebreaks will be handled in a case-by-case basis, prioritizing precedence.</p>
<p>Hosts are Geyde and Dat</p>
<h3>
<a name="mechanics-3" class="anchor" href="#mechanics-3"></a>Mechanics</h3>
<p>Rolelist:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><font color="green"><strong>Vanilla Crewmate</strong></font> x8<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Fortnite</strong></font> x3<br>
<font color="brown"><strong>Impostor</strong></font> x2</p>
</blockquote>
<details>
<summary>
Example Rolecards</summary>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="green">Vanilla Crewmate</font></h1>
<p>You have no special abilities of your own, but can vote and talk freely.</p>
<p><em>You win when all threats to the crewmates have been eliminated and there is at least one crewmate player alive.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="red">Fortnite</font></h1>
<p>Your partners are [x] and [y]. You may talk to them during the day and night.<br>
During the day, you must submit a list of 3 players, which can change throughout the day. At the start of night, the list is made public in-thread; if the Impostors choose to nightkill, the target must be one from the list.</p>
<p><em>You win when at least half of the living players are fortnite, or when nothing can prevent this from happening.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="brown">Impostor</font></h1>
<p>Your partner is [x]. You may talk to them during the day and night. You also have a factional kill which must target a non-Impostor player. However, the target must be one from the list posted in-thread (if there is no list, then you may choose freely). If a day ends in No Execution, then this factional kill becomes mandatory.</p>
<p><em>You win when at least half of the living players are impostors and at least crewmate role remains, or if you obtain full majority, or when nothing can prevent this from happening.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</details>
<ul>
<li>48/24 phases</li>
<li>Banning system is Majority and Plurality. To vote for a ban, type <strong>/vote [put player’s name here]</strong> and ping the host in the same post.</li>
<li>Post per phase cap of 200, which is lifted 2 hours before EoD and in MyLo/LyLo.</li>
<li>Minimum post requirement of 15 posts per phase</li>
<li>WotM in effect…but not really. Not going to be harsh about this.</li>
<li>VCs will be added to the OP after the day ends.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Endgame Mech:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Fortnite or Impostors win if they obtain a full majority of living players, or if they make up half <em>and</em> at least one Crewmate role is still alive.</li>
<li>If Fortnite and Impostors ever make up equal numbers, with no Crewmate roles left alive, then Fortnite wins. Fortnite also wins if a day phase begins with one Fortnite, one Impostor, and one Crewmate.</li>
</ul>
<h3>
<a name="lads-join-4" class="anchor" href="#lads-join-4"></a>Lads (/join)</h3>
<ol>
<li>clonedcheese</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>Whysper</li>
<li>Tilgarial</li>
<li>Blitz</li>
<li>Ruri</li>
<li>iaafr</li>
<li>Zone_Q11</li>
<li>PokemonKidRyan</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h3>
<a name="backup-backup-5" class="anchor" href="#backup-backup-5"></a>Backup (/backup)</h3>
<ol>
<li>Wisp</li>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
<li>GGhana</li>
<li>Intensify</li>
</ol>
<h3>
<a name="spectator-spec-6" class="anchor" href="#spectator-spec-6"></a>Spectator (/spec)</h3>
<ol>
<li>chloe - uninformed</li>
<li>eli- informed</li>
<li>min -uninformed</li>
<li>kyo- something who knows</li>
<li>silviu - uninformed</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>154 posts - 39 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-sussy-jungle-oligarchy-canned/89129">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-sussy-jungle-oligarchy-canned/89129</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 20:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89129</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-sussy-jungle-oligarchy-canned/89129.rss">[FM] Sussy Jungle Oligarchy - CANNED</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Special, MU] Didney Worl Mafia [19/19]</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="didney-worl-mafia-1" class="anchor" href="#didney-worl-mafia-1"></a>Didney Worl Mafia</h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/6/b/6b74e8bcc882d958305113909b130da390097e0c.jpeg" alt="didneyworl" data-base62-sha1="fkBz5GuYgHAoSoIzst5GfbOxyW0" width="500" height="274"></p>
<h1>
<a name="hosted-by-gghana-and-katze-2" class="anchor" href="#hosted-by-gghana-and-katze-2"></a>Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/gghana">@GGhana</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/katze">@Katze</a>
</h1>
<h2>
<a name="rules-3" class="anchor" href="#rules-3"></a><code>Rules</code>
</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow the <a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Forum/Discord/Game/Meta Rules - Please Read First</a>, the <a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Official Forum Mafia and Forum of Lies Rules</a>, <a href="https://www.mafiauniverse.com/forums/threads/27-Forum-Rules?p=2009&amp;viewfull=1#post2009" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Forum Rules</a>, and <a href="https://www.mafiauniverse.com/forums/threads/29704-Partner-Community-Guidelines" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Partner Community Guidelines </a>. Please make sure you have enough time for this game before you sign up.</li>
<li>Alts are allowed, you may make one on Mafia Universe, if you are making an alt you must inform the hosts, you cannot make an alt to join this game if you are banned/signup blacklisted from Forum of Lies or Mafia Universe.</li>
<li><em><strong>You are not allowed to blame Katze for bad flavor. Blame GGhana instead</strong></em></li>
<li>Signups will be held in this thread and on Mafia Universe, the game itself will be on <a href="https://www.mafiauniverse.com/forums/" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Mafia Universe </a>. It is REQUIRED to have an MU account to signup for this game.</li>
<li>Discord is required to sign up for this game.</li>
<li><strong>Breaking any MU rules in this subforum will be considered a rulebreak on FoL.</strong></li>
<li><strong>People who are sign-up blacklisted on FoL may not join games in this subforum.</strong></li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="gameplay-4" class="anchor" href="#gameplay-4"></a><code>Gameplay</code>
</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>SOD/EOD:</strong> Noon EST</li>
<li>
<strong>Phase Lengths:</strong> 48/24</li>
<li>
<strong>Minimum Posting Requirement (per phase):</strong> 15</li>
<li>
<strong>Execution:</strong> Majority (starting D2) + Plurality. No vote is a valid vote, however the execution cannot be skipped twice in a row. Tied executions will be decided randomly.</li>
<li>
<strong>Factional:</strong> Factional kills are optional. The factional kill cannot be skipped twice in a row. The factional kill is assigned.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="setup-5" class="anchor" href="#setup-5"></a><code>Setup</code>
</h2>
<ul>
<li>Closed</li>
<li>There are guaranteed to be two factions. The uninformed majority called <font color="green"> Town </font> and an informed minority called <font color="red"> Disney </font>. Other factions and third parties may exist. Lost wolves may exist. Your rolecard will not lie about your alignment, flips cannot be altered. However flips may be janitored.</li>
<li>This is a role madness setup. There are no ITAs.</li>
<li>Flavour is not alignment indicative, and any flavour outside of Role pms is not alignment or role indicative, try to flavour solve at your own risk.</li>
</ul>
<p>Action Order:</p>
<p>Passives/Triggered Effects (as appropriate)<br>
Commuting<br>
Hiding<br>
Strongman Killing<br>
Absorbing actions<br>
Copying actions<br>
Bus Driving<br>
Roleblocking<br>
Stylized Roleblocking (e.g. Jailkeeping)<br>
Redirecting<br>
Doctors<br>
Stylized Doctors (e.g. Bodyguard)<br>
Misc<br>
Killing<br>
Player Investigative<br>
Action Investigative</p>
<p>If two roleblockers target each other then both will fail their night actions.</p>
<h2>
<a name="signups-6" class="anchor" href="#signups-6"></a><code>Signups</code>
</h2>
<ol>
<li>Mistyx</li>
<li>Twice Shrunk</li>
<li>NANOOKTHECONQUEROR</li>
<li>mpatching</li>
<li>Phraze</li>
<li>Marluxion</li>
<li>zoisite</li>
<li>Butterscotch Sundae</li>
<li>Arete</li>
<li>Chandelure</li>
<li>~b100ming~</li>
<li>PsychoKang</li>
<li>Mewtini</li>
<li>God_Emperor</li>
<li>iaafr</li>
<li>Rokon</li>
<li>marry</li>
<li>Boquise</li>
<li>neopest</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="backups-7" class="anchor" href="#backups-7"></a><code>Backups</code>
</h2>
<p>Windwardaway<br>
Luxy</p>
<h2>
<a name="spectators-8" class="anchor" href="#spectators-8"></a><code>Spectators</code>
</h2>
<p>Appelsiini</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Wisdom of the mod will be used in this game, if deemed necessary. We wish to ensure that the game is healthy, while also introducing multiple players to Forum of Lies. All decisions are final.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
            <p><small>66 posts - 22 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/special-mu-didney-worl-mafia-19-19/89121">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/special-mu-didney-worl-mafia-19-19/89121</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 15:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89121</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/special-mu-didney-worl-mafia-19-19/89121.rss">[Special, MU] Didney Worl Mafia [19/19]</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Misc] BotF X - New World Chaos - Signups (8/13)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Going to the police was a mistake. A shifty figure has been following you for blocks, and you swear people on the street are taking notes as you pass by. You hide around a corner waiting for an ambush, only to see that shifty figure speeding off in an Aston Martin. An old war buddy calls in a favor to look up the license, and… no. No no no no no, how high does this go? The Reds don’t have this kind of influence, not yet, who’s behind this? That’s when you hear the knock.</em><br>
<small>credit to besjbo for the above flavor</small></p>
<h1>
<a name="welcome-to-new-world-chaos-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-crichard564-1" class="anchor" href="#welcome-to-new-world-chaos-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-crichard564-1"></a>Welcome to New World Chaos! Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a>
</h1>
<h1>
<a name="this-script-is-not-my-own-made-by-besjbo-i-do-not-claim-to-have-made-this-script-2" class="anchor" href="#this-script-is-not-my-own-made-by-besjbo-i-do-not-claim-to-have-made-this-script-2"></a>THIS SCRIPT IS NOT MY OWN (made by Besjbo). I DO NOT CLAIM TO HAVE MADE THIS SCRIPT.</h1>
<h1>
<a name="this-script-is-also-a-homebrew-script-meaning-it-is-not-made-using-official-clocktower-characters-3" class="anchor" href="#this-script-is-also-a-homebrew-script-meaning-it-is-not-made-using-official-clocktower-characters-3"></a>THIS SCRIPT IS ALSO A HOMEBREW SCRIPT, MEANING IT IS NOT MADE USING OFFICIAL CLOCKTOWER CHARACTERS.</h1>
<h1>
<a name="please-read-the-below-spoilers-for-information-on-how-to-play-the-game-4" class="anchor" href="#please-read-the-below-spoilers-for-information-on-how-to-play-the-game-4"></a>Please read the below spoilers for information on how to play the game!</h1>
<details>
<summary>
Character List</summary>
<p>Character just means role; the character types are Townsfolk, Outsider, Minion, and Demon.<br>
Townsfolk and Outsiders are good-aligned to start, Minions and the Demon are evil-aligned to start.  There are no neutral parties in Ravenswood Bluff.<br>
[Brackets] denote abilities upon setup; for example, if it says [+1 Outsider], then I replace 1 Townsfolk with 1 Outsider.</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorstebluetownsfolkcolor-5" class="anchor" href="#colorstebluetownsfolkcolor-5"></a><font color="steblue">Townsfolk</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Wiretap</strong></font> - You are 1 of 2 wiretap characters, but do not know which.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Domestic Wiretap</strong> - You start knowing two allied players. When they both die, you learn their characters tonight.</li>
<li>
<strong>Foreign Wiretap</strong> - You start knowing two opposing players. When you die, you learn the Evil character tonight.</li>
</ul>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Double Agent</strong></font> - The Demon sees you instead of a Minion. That Minion recieves no starting information.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Sleeper</strong></font> - You think you are an in-play Minion, and neither of you recieve starting information. If you are “mad” about being the Sleeper, you learn the in-play Demon tonight.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Jurist</strong></font> - Each night, choose a player and learn their character. Good living players register falsely to you.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Freelancer</strong></font> - Each night, choose a Good character. You learn that it is 1 of 2 players, if in play. If not in play, you recieve arbitrary info tonight.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Blacklister</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), choose a character (not yours, not a Traveller). You learn its nearest Evil character, if in play. If not in play, you recieve arbitrary info tonight.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Black Ops</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), you learn if you whispered the Demon today.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Populist</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), you learn a character who was “mad” about being the Populist today.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Diplomat</strong></font> - Each day, you may whisper the storyteller with two other players (not Travellers, different from yesterday) &amp; broker a deal between them. If either player breaks the deal, they malfunction until dawn.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Eavesdropper</strong></font> - Each day, you may visit the Storyteller to learn something about each player you whispered today, in no particular order.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Symbologist</strong></font> - You have 3 Townsfolk abilities, but 1 malfunctions. You also register as the functioning Townsfolk.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Truther</strong></font> - If you die at night, choose a character and learn all players with that character.<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Ambassador</strong></font> - You are immune to all abilities and do not count towards the number of living players. One Good player starts knowing the Ambassador is in play.</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorsteblueoutsiderscolor-6" class="anchor" href="#colorsteblueoutsiderscolor-6"></a><font color="steblue">Outsiders</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Libertine</strong></font> - You start holding a Drunk character token. Each night (but not the first), it moves to a player the holder whispered today. You think you are a Townsfolk until the Drunk token moves.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Drunk character is an Outsider with the ability “You do not know you are the Drunk. You<br>
think you are a Townsfolk, but your ability malfunctions.” It cannot start in play. Note that the Demon is still the Demon, even if they are holding this token.</li>
</ul>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Activist</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), a player dies unless a living player was “mad” about being the Activist today (even if you are dead.)<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>MAD-Man</strong></font> - Each night, choose another living player (not a Traveler) to hold the football. If the holder is executed, you drop The Bomb and lose (even if dead).<br>
<font color="steblue"><strong>Sympathizer</strong></font> - A Townsfolk is Evil and registers as a Defector, but does not know. You have their ability, and the Demon knows them.</p>
<ul>
<li>“Defector” is a character. (Ex: Jurist can see somebody as a Defector). It doesn’t actually have any ability, because you can only register as one, and it cannot be in-play.</li>
</ul>
<h1>
<a name="colorredminionscolor-7" class="anchor" href="#colorredminionscolor-7"></a><font color="red">Minions</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="red"><strong>Agitprop</strong></font> - - Each night, choose a player and a statement. Tomorrow, if that player is “mad” about denying that statement, they might be executed.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Templar</strong></font> - If you nominate a Good player you did not whisper today and they are executed, Evil wins.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Chairman</strong></font> - Once per game at night (but not the first), choose an Outsider player: they swap characters and alignments with the Demon. [+1 Outsider]<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Brainwasher</strong></font> - Townsfolk might recieve the incorrect character in setup (their abilities work normally).</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorreddemonscolor-8" class="anchor" href="#colorreddemonscolor-8"></a><font color="red">Demons</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="red"><strong>Comitern</strong></font> -  Each Comintern knows one other Comintern. Each night (but not the first), a Comintern might die. Evil wins only when all Good players are dead. You register as a Minion too. [Most players are Comintern]<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Draconis</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), choose a character: if in play, that player dies and an Evil player becomes their character. If not in play, a player dies.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Seclorum</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), you learn the character of everyone you whispered today, then choose a player: they die.<br>
<font color="red"><strong>Kabal</strong></font> - Each night (but not the first), choose a player: they die. If you win, if an Outsider was most responsible for their team losing, they switch teams and win with you. [+1 Outsider]</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Travellers</summary>
<p>Travelers are special and powerful characters with different rules than normal citizens.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Traveler characters are publicly known.</strong> If a player joins the game as the United Nations, for example, everyone knows that they are the United Nations.</li>
<li>
<strong>Traveler alignments are unknown.</strong> Because Traveler characters are known, the question regarding them becomes which side they’re playing for. Travelers are more likely to be good than evil; general practice is that one in three Travelers is evil, but it is possible for there to be only one Traveler in a game and that Traveler to be evil. Evil Travelers will be told who the Demon is when they enter play; Good Travelers will be told nothing. The Demon and Minions will not be told if a Traveler is good or evil.<br>
Note that if the Comitern is in play, Evil Travellers will only be told so, and will not be told any Comitern.</li>
<li>
<strong>Traveler players may join or leave the game at any time.</strong> This game is designed for live play, and the Travelers are designed to accommodate players who arrive late or must leave early. If you would like to play, but cannot join at game start or do not think that you can stay around for the end of the game, then you may consider playing as a Traveler character instead of a normal citizen. However, I will not allow Traveler players to sub out (since the nature of their character is designed for them to simply leave if they cannot play), and if a Traveler player has left the game, they may not rejoin later. I will additionally ask that players who would consider joining as Travelers after the game has started notify me of this before the start of the game; I will compile a list of these potential Travelers and people not on this list by the start of the game will not be allowed to join as a Traveler. If a player wishes to join an in-progress game as a Traveler, I may bar them from choosing certain characters.</li>
<li>
<strong>Travelers with a night ability act before any citizens.</strong> Their abilities will be resolved absolutely first.</li>
<li>
<strong>Travelers are not executed; they are exiled.</strong> An exile is different from an execution in a few key ways.<br>
-An exile is not considered an execution, meaning that a game can see the exile of a Traveler and an execution in the same day.<br>
-An exile is not affected by any abilities affecting nomination, voting or execution.<br>
-An exile may be called for at any time, by anyone, even if that player is presently unable to nominate, and a player who calls for the exile of a Traveler may still nominate if they have not already.<br>
-Dead players may vote on the exile of a Traveler, and they do not spend their ghost vote to do so.<br>
-And finally, a simple majority vote is all that is required to exile a Traveler. However, I will houserule that no more than one exile may occur per day.</li>
</ol>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Traveller Characters</summary>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Presi</font><font color="red">dent</font></strong> - You may privately veto your exile unless the majority of 3 different character types voted for your exile.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">Celeb</font><font color="red">rity</font></strong> - Each night (but not the first), until dusk, a player who was “mad” about everything you said today acts twice.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">Inter</font><font color="red">pol</font></strong> - If the player you nominate is executed, everyone you whispered today may visit the Storyteller tommorow to learn something about that player.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">United</font> <font color="red">Nations</font></strong> - If all living players vote to ratify you, you run nominations from now on, and you may change the nomination and voting rules, excepte on yourself.<br>
<strong><font color="steblue">Spym</font><font color="red">aster</font></strong> - Each day, choose a player: if they agree, you learn their character tonight, then their character changes.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Town Composition</summary>
<p>This game is designed for a variable number of players, and thus the composition of the game is able to change depending on how many players join. The following list denotes the composition of the game at each possible player count.</p>
<p>Total Players: Townsfolk/Outsiders/Minions/Demons</p>
<p>5: 3/0/1/1<br>
6: 3/1/1/1<br>
7: 5/0/1/1<br>
8: 5/1/1/1<br>
9: 5/2/1/1<br>
10: 7/0/2/1<br>
11: 7/1/2/1<br>
12: 7/2/2/1</p>
<p>Every character in-game is unique in that more than one of the same character will never appear at the start of the game (there can never be two Wiretaps at the start, for example).</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Phase Length</summary>
<p>Each day phase will last for no longer than 48 hours.</p>
<p>12 hours: Discussion phase. Nominations may not be cast at this time.<br>
24 hours: Nomination phase. Players who wish to nominate may do so at this time, <strong>and votes may begun to be cast during this time as well.</strong><br>
12 hours: Vote finalization. During this time, votes may be cast freely on any existing nomination, but no new nominations may be made. Once this time ends or all votes have been locked in, the day will resolve.</p>
<p>The night phase will last for 24 hours, or until all abilities have been performed and resolved.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
The Storyteller</summary>
<p>Storyteller</p>
<p>The Storyteller is the key moderator for the game; All ability uses at night must be sent to the Storyteller via private message, and Storyteller will have the final say on any open-ended ability behaviors. Storyteller’s goal is to keep the game both fun and balanced, and they’ll often be trying to make it last as long as possible; however, the Storyteller may not alter any existing rules to accomplish this.<br>
Also, the thing the Storyteller uses to keep track of things is called the Grimoire. It’s basically the spreadsheet.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
The Fabled</summary>
<p>The Fabled aren’t really characters so much as special modifiers that the Storyteller can put in play to tweak the game. For example, the Angel can be put into play to help keep newer players from being targeted, or the Buddhist can be put into play to keep the more experienced players from dominating the discussion. Fabled will always be announced when they are in play, along with their effect upon gamestate. A breakdown of Fabled characters we may be using can be found below.</p>
<p><font color="gold"><strong>Angel</strong></font> : Something bad might happen to whomever is most responsible for the death of a new player.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Buddhist</strong></font> : Veteran players may not speak for the first six hours of the day phase.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Hell’s Librarian</strong></font> : Something bad might happen to whomever speaks when the Storyteller calls for silence.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Fiddler</strong></font>: Once per game, at night, the Demon secretly chooses a player of an opposing alignment; All players then choose which of these two wins the game.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>Deus Ex Fiasco</strong></font>: Once per game, the storyteller will make a mistake, correct it and publicly admit to it.</p>
<p>If you want any of these added, ping me in signup thread (before game) or in classcard (during game).</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
The Bomb (IMPORTANT, PLEASE READ)</summary>
<p><font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> is a fabled character that is always in play this game. It reads:</p>
<p><strong>If two players (dead or alive) agree to drop the bomb, and at least one is Good, Evil wins. If Comintern is in play, Good wins instead. If both are Evil, Good wins.</strong><br>
(Note that Kabal cannot make an outsider switch teams via dropping the Bomb.)</p>
<p>The only reason to ever drop <strong><font color="maroon">The Bomb</font></strong> as Good is if you believe Comitern is in play.<br>
<strong>I will prevent any attempts to drop <font color="maroon">The Bomb</font> out of intent to gamethrow.</strong><br>
Also, if necessary, I will timegate <strong><font color="maroon">The Bomb</font></strong> to a certain day, depending on playercount.</p>
<p>If you want to drop <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font>, do it like this:</p>
<p><strong>I would like to drop <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> with @[name] <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a></strong><br>
then both of you will either say<br>
<strong>I turn the key <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a></strong> (if both players do this, <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> will be dropped)<br>
or<br>
<strong>I do not turn the key <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/crichard564">@CRichard564</a></strong> (if at least one player does this, <font color="maroon"><strong>The Bomb</strong></font> will not be dropped)</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Scum Info</summary>
<p>On the first night of the game, when relatively few characters act, the evil characters will all be woken to learn who one another are. Evil players will not be allowed to communicate at night. The Demon will be told who all of their Minions are, and the Minions will know who the Demon is and who all of the other Minions are. However, the Minions and the Demon will not learn which specific characters any of their fellow evils are. The Demon will additionally be told three characters that are not in play, to serve as safe claims. They may claim any of these, none of these, or simply hand the claims off to Minions; however they think they will be best served.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Malfunctioning &amp; Registration</summary>
<p>The primary source of interference with abilities in this game is the malfunction. A class that is malfunctioning is not told that they are malfunctioning; if the class is one that gathers information, then the information they receive that night is arbitrary (open-ended, Storyteller may resolve at their discretion), otherwise, the malfunctioning class’ ability simply does not have any effect.</p>
<p>You may also see experienced players refer to malfunctioning as “drunkness”, “poisoning”, or “droison”.</p>
<p>Registration causes a player to “appear” a certain way (for most purposes). For example, if the Jurist picks a good living player, then they learn something they are not. If you pick a character that the Symbologist has a functioning ability of, then you can learn the Symbologist, etc etc etc.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Madness</summary>
<p>Certain character abilities in this script reference a status known as “madness”. What madness means, in the simplest terms, is that when a player is “mad” about something, they are trying to convince the other players that it is true, even if it is not (especially if it is not). Ultimately, the Storyteller is the one who judges whether the “mad” player’s efforts are sufficient to avoid punishment (or to obtain a reward!), but this allows the Storyteller to be more lenient toward players who are unfamiliar with the concept, and by the same token, to expect more from an experienced player.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Nominations and Voting</summary>
<p>Voting in this game works a little differently. After the formal discussion phase has ended, the Storyteller will declare that nominations are opened. A player must be nominated before they can be voted on. Each player may only be nominated once per day, and each player may only nominate once per day. When a nomination is opened, the storyteller will begin to count votes. Votes may be precast, and may be altered so long as they are considered not to be locked in. A vote is locked in when everyone between the accused and the voter (going down the list from the accused) has locked in their vote, or once the day ends, assuming that not all votes on the nomination have been cast. Any votes that are not counted at EoD will be considered votes to pardon. If the count of votes to execute is more than half of the number of living players, and is the highest count of votes against any player that day, the accused will be considered “about to die”. At the end of the day or when all votes on all nominations have been cast, the player who is “about to die” will be executed. There isn’t such a thing as a quickhammer around here; we’re a little more careful with what we do.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Whispers (DIFFERENT THAN NORMAL, PLEASE READ)</summary>
<p>Players may whisper each other in-game through private messages. Whispers must, however, be publicly announced, typically by requesting permission to whisper (a standard format is /whisper [Player]). Once a whisper has been declared and accepted, the two players may whisper via private message until one of them speaks publicly in the game chat, at which point the whisper is considered over and the players must declare whispers again if they wish to whisper publicly.</p>
<p>Additionally, you may send up to 15 words to your neighbors without having to announce a whisper. <strong>These do not count as a whisper for the purposes of abilities.</strong></p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Death</summary>
<p>When a player dies, nothing is revealed about their character and they are allowed to stay in the game and speak. They may not nominate and they will have only one vote token (this will allow them to cast a vote to execute) for the entire game. Evil players who die may thus continue to help their allies by keeping up their claim and spreading misinformation, and good players may similarly help their allies by retaining relevant info that others may have forgotten in the heat of things. Once a player dies, their ability stops working, which means that a player killed before they would perform their ability will not perform their ability, and any ability with a persistent effect will end upon the player’s death.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Victory</summary>
<p>Good wins by eliminating all Demons (you don’t need to kill Minions to win). Evil wins by reducing the game to two living players (even if both players are good). The Storyteller may also declare a victory for Evil if Good may no longer possibly win (for example, if only evil players are left alive and thus no one would nominate the Demon). Certain character abilities may present alternate routes to victory; these classes, if able to appear, will be made known on the character list. In the event of a tie (both teams would win at the same time), Good wins.</p>
</details>
<h1>
<a name="i-am-capping-this-game-at-12-players-not-including-travellers-additionally-i-will-not-be-accepting-travellers-unless-there-is-9-residents-9" class="anchor" href="#i-am-capping-this-game-at-12-players-not-including-travellers-additionally-i-will-not-be-accepting-travellers-unless-there-is-9-residents-9"></a>I am capping this game at 12 players, not including Travellers. Additionally, I will not be accepting travellers unless there is 9 residents.</h1>
<h1>
<a name="playerlist-just-ping-me-and-my-cohost-with-in-and-the-seat-you-want-yes-we-let-you-choose-10" class="anchor" href="#playerlist-just-ping-me-and-my-cohost-with-in-and-the-seat-you-want-yes-we-let-you-choose-10"></a>Playerlist; just ping me and my cohost with /in and the seat you want (yes, we let you choose).</h1>
<ol>
<li>
</li>
<li>Magnus</li>
<li>Firekitten</li>
<li>clonedcheese</li>
<li>Icibalus (<strong><font color="steblue">Celeb</font><font color="red">rity</font></strong>)</li>
<li>Nightingale</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>PKR</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>Atlas</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="backups-11" class="anchor" href="#backups-11"></a>Backups</h1>
<ol>
<li>Blitz</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="spectators-informed-12" class="anchor" href="#spectators-informed-12"></a>Spectators (informed)</h1>
<ol>
<li>DatBird</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="if-you-have-any-questions-feel-free-to-ask-in-your-card-we-are-here-to-help-13" class="anchor" href="#if-you-have-any-questions-feel-free-to-ask-in-your-card-we-are-here-to-help-13"></a>If you have <em>any</em> questions, feel free to ask in your card. We are here to help.</h1>
            <p><small>522 posts - 26 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-botf-x-new-world-chaos-signups-8-13/89116">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-botf-x-new-world-chaos-signups-8-13/89116</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89116</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-botf-x-new-world-chaos-signups-8-13/89116.rss">[Misc] BotF X - New World Chaos - Signups (8/13)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Your Turn To Survivor [Misc] - canned</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="your-turn-to-survivor-the-main-game-of-your-turn-to-die-but-this-time-with-only-that-14-players-will-build-allies-deduce-liars-and-betray-their-friends-1" class="anchor" href="#your-turn-to-survivor-the-main-game-of-your-turn-to-die-but-this-time-with-only-that-14-players-will-build-allies-deduce-liars-and-betray-their-friends-1"></a>Your turn to Survivor. The main game of Your Turn To Die, but this time with only that. 14 players will build allies, deduce liars, and betray their friends!</h1>
<p>Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/marshal">@Marshal</a>  and <a class="mention" href="/u/clonedcheese">@clonedcheese</a></p>
<hr>
<h1>
<a name="how-the-game-works-2" class="anchor" href="#how-the-game-works-2"></a>How the game works:</h1>
<h2>
<a name="roles-3" class="anchor" href="#roles-3"></a>Roles</h2>
<p>All players will be randomly assigned a card. This card will say your role. These roles are between <font color="CYAN"><strong>Commoner</strong></font>, <font color="RED"><strong>Sacrifice</strong></font>, <font color="LIME"><strong>Sage</strong></font> and <font color="YELLOW"><strong>Keymaster</strong></font>. If you reveal your role (Or fake one in the chat) Please quote it in your classcard as I will leave a list of claims in a post at the start of every trial.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<font color="CYAN"><strong>Commoner</strong></font> is a basic role. If you have this role, you’re just a basic player during that round, and all you do is vote and discuss.</li>
<li>
<font color="RED"><strong>Sacrifice</strong></font> is a special role. If you have this role, you will die at the end of the main game unless you are voted by the majority. If you are voted by the majority, you will escape with a victory while also granting victory a player of your choosing, chosen publicly. You will have an extra vote on yourself for the 2nd stage of the main game.</li>
<li>
<font color="LIME"><strong>Sage</strong></font> is a role where you know who the <font color="YELLOW"><strong>Keymaster</strong></font> is when you get it, due to it’s Clairyovant ability. Using this role could be tactical, however, claiming this role may get you killed due to not being the <font color="RED"><strong>Sacrifice</strong></font>.</li>
<li>
<font color="YELLOW"><strong>Keymaster</strong></font> is a role where if you are voted by the majority. All players who have not won already will lose the game.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="phases-4" class="anchor" href="#phases-4"></a>Phases:</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Alliance phase:</strong> This is 24 hour period before every main game. Every player gets to talk to other players before they recieve their card. They can plan out as much as they want to.</li>
<li>
<strong>Main Game Stage 1:</strong> You will decide the majority -2 of the players to place onto the chopping block vote during <strong>Main Game Stage 2</strong> (so, for example, if there are 12 players alive, Majority is 7. 7-2 is 5, so 5 players would go on the chopping block). This phase lasts 24 hours.</li>
<li>
<strong>Main Game Stage 2:</strong> you will decide based on the players who were elected to die, who you will kill. Be careful of the <font color="red"><strong>Sacrifice</strong></font> however, as if they are voted, they will pick a player to win with them and win the game. Claiming your role during this phase, especially if you aren’t on the stand, is a perfect time to claim.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="winloss-conditions-5" class="anchor" href="#winloss-conditions-5"></a>Win/loss conditions.</h2>
<h3>
<a name="you-will-win-if-6" class="anchor" href="#you-will-win-if-6"></a>You will win if:</h3>
<ul>
<li>You are voted out as the <strong><font color="red">Sacrifice</font></strong>, or chosen by them to win with them.</li>
<li>You are one of the last 4 players alive</li>
</ul>
<h3>
<a name="you-will-lose-if-7" class="anchor" href="#you-will-lose-if-7"></a>You will lose if:</h3>
<ul>
<li>You are voted out as <font color="CYAN"><strong>Commoner</strong></font>, <font color="LIME"><strong>Sage</strong></font> or <font color="YELLOW"><strong>Keymaster</strong></font>
</li>
<li>The <font color="YELLOW"><strong>Keymaster</strong></font> is voted out while you are alive.</li>
<li>You are the <strong><font color="red">Sacrifice</font></strong> and fail to get yourself voted out.</li>
<li>Two <strong><font color="red">Sacrifices</font></strong> are voted out while you are alive, and you are not chosen to win by them.</li>
<li>You vote for the <strong><font color="red">Sacrifice</font></strong> during chapter 5, and are not the sacrifice or chosen by them to win.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>As this game has 14 players, 2 players per chapter die, and the game ends at the final 4 if it has not already ended, there will be a maximum of 5 chapters.</em></p>
<hr>
<h1>
<a name="playerlist-8" class="anchor" href="#playerlist-8"></a>Playerlist.</h1>
<ol>
<li>Blitz</li>
<li>Alice</li>
<li>Jane</li>
<li>Apprentice</li>
<li>Magnus</li>
<li>Squirrel2412</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>Whysper</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="backups-9" class="anchor" href="#backups-9"></a>Backups</h1>
<ol>
<li>Datbird</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="specs-10" class="anchor" href="#specs-10"></a>Specs</h1>
<ol>
<li>Silviu</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>84 posts - 22 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/your-turn-to-survivor-misc-canned/89077">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/your-turn-to-survivor-misc-canned/89077</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 21:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89077</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/your-turn-to-survivor-misc-canned/89077.rss">Your Turn To Survivor [Misc] - canned</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[VFM] Town vs Bandits - Day 5 (4/13) - Bandits Win!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/5/2/524c376ddfc9936fd8e363292f724063ca13df99.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="bK2rDlbHt5p7HqhRUwTcBlXEHfX" width="503" height="273"></p>
<h2>
<a name="town-vs-bandits-hosted-and-designed-by-wazza-and-geyde-reviewed-by-datbird-1" class="anchor" href="#town-vs-bandits-hosted-and-designed-by-wazza-and-geyde-reviewed-by-datbird-1"></a>Town vs Bandits - Hosted and designed by <a class="mention" href="/u/wazza">@Wazza</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a>, Reviewed by <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a>
</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h2>Dagnabbit! Them there bandits have invaded our prestine Town!</h2>
<p>But we can’t figure out who they are, so we’ve recruited all members of the Town to come together in order to find and enact <em>justice</em> upon em! Unfortunately, we entered WIFOM hell and have to out-predict them because our officers are trainees and are terrible at their job. Good luck, we suck.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<h2>
<a name="mechanics-2" class="anchor" href="#mechanics-2"></a>Mechanics:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Open Setup</li>
<li>48/24 Phases - Night can be skipped if all players agree, when the day ends may be changed depending when the night is skipped.</li>
<li>The Bandits will speak in either a private thread or private discord depending on what they desire.</li>
<li>The Bandits have a mandatory Factional Kill (if not performed the kill will be randomized among living town players) and a Factional One-Shot Rolecop.</li>
<li>The Bandit Factional Kill and the Bandit Factional One-Shot Rolecop may not be done alongside each other.</li>
<li>Threadmarks will include Final Vote Counts, day starts, night starts and any other important events</li>
<li>Bandits do not flip as their role, instead they flip as Bandit, because that’s the only thing we’re competent enough to figure out.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="rules-3" class="anchor" href="#rules-3"></a>Rules:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow the <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Forum Rules</a> and <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-game-rules/78926">Forum Game Rules</a>. Failure to do so will result in a warning and consequently a force-replace or modkill if needed.</li>
<li>A minimum of 20 content posts are required per day, if it is impossible for you to reach this amount, please inform me beforehand. If you are prodded twice for this, you will be force-replaced or modkilled if needed. If you post no content in a single day that did not end early, you will be force-replaced immediately unless you can provide a good enough reasoning beforehand.</li>
<li>Excessive AtE is frowned upon, don’t use it.</li>
<li>Each day, you make make a maximum of 200 posts, on content or not, an hour before EoD this will be lifted. Any votes done after you have reached your post limit will not punish you.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="voting-4" class="anchor" href="#voting-4"></a>Voting:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Majority and Plurality are enabled, however on Day 1, Majority is disabled. Which, of course, means there is a Day 1 executed.</li>
<li>If two or more wagons are tied for plurality, a random player between the tied wagons will be executed.</li>
<li>To vote a player, type <strong>/vote [name] <a class="mention" href="/u/chloe">@Chloe</a></strong> otherwise the vote will not count.</li>
<li>MyLo (mis-eliminate and lose) and LyLo (eliminate or lose) will be announced, and votes will be locked. This means that your first vote is final and cannot be changed.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="rolelist-5" class="anchor" href="#rolelist-5"></a>Rolelist:</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font><br>
<font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font><br>
<font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town x8</strong></font><br>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Goon</strong></font><br>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Inheriting Ninja</strong></font><br>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Inheriting Strongwilled</strong></font></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<h2>
<a name="rolecards-6" class="anchor" href="#rolecards-6"></a>Rolecards:</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="GREEN">Vanilla Town</font></h1>
<p>Your only abilities are your voice and your vote.</p>
<p>You are practically completely useless in anything you try to accomplish or do in life, your uselessness holds no bounds whatsoever, but that doesn’t stop you from enacting your <em>right</em> as a citizen to murder people in the name of justice.</p>
<p><em>Defeat the Bandits in the name of justice.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="GREEN">Town Informed Tracker</font></h1>
<p>Each night, you may choose to track a player, you will know who they visit.<br>
Your results will be either ‘Your target visited [player]’, ‘Your target didn’t visit anyone’ or ‘No Result’.<br>
Additionally, You know that [x] is the <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font>.</p>
<p>After being arrested for committing tax fraud, he was released on set circumstances because he’s actually good at not being useless.</p>
<p><em>Defeat the Bandits in the name of justice.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="GREEN">Town Informed Jailkeeper</font></h1>
<p>Each night, you may choose to jail a player. Their action will be roleblocked and they will be protected from nightkills.<br>
You may not target the same player consecutively.<br>
Additionally, You know that [x] is the <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font>.</p>
<p>Extremely delusional, constantly talks about how the bandits are wolves or mafia for some reason, also calls fellow citizens villagers to go along with this, would be in a mental facility, however he’s still one of the only compteent ones.</p>
<p><em>Defeat the Bandits in the name of justice.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="BROWN">Bandit Goon</font></h1>
<p>Your only abilities are your voice and your vote.</p>
<p>You tagged along with your fellow bandits, you’re similar to the person who just mouths the words to a song during a choir, you’re absolutely pointless, but you’re trying your best and that’s all that matters. However, your best clearly isn’t enough, you’re practically useless anyway.</p>
<p><em>Have majority of the Town be Bandits or have equal numbers of both.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="BROWN">Bandit Inheriting Ninja</font></h1>
<p>Your visits are hidden when performing the factional kill.<br>
If the Strongwilled dies, you will become immune to roleblocks when performing the factional kill.</p>
<p>Cannot stop screaming about how it isn’t just a phase.</p>
<p><em>Have majority of the Town be Bandits or have equal numbers of both.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="BROWN">Bandit Inheriting Strongwilled</font></h1>
<p>You are immune to roleblocks when performing the factional kill.<br>
If the Ninja dies, your visits will be hidden when performing the factional kill.</p>
<p>You have no dignity, nothing to lose, so at the end of the day, who cares who you pick and choose.</p>
<p><em>Have majority of the Town be Bandits or have equal numbers of both.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Flavour Written here will not be used, instead the flavour will be tailored to The Princess Bride.</p>
<h2>
<a name="things-changed-from-the-previous-game-that-got-canned-7" class="anchor" href="#things-changed-from-the-previous-game-that-got-canned-7"></a>Things changed from the previous game (that got canned):</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Players will flip as <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font>, <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font>, <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> or <font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Universal Backup Fruit Vendor</strong></font>’s competence got it killed, instead its intelligence spread out to other Citizens…okay nevermind, it only went to the other two Citizens that could actually do things and they became <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font> and <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font>. A new <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> also joined the Town to accommodate this.</li>
<li>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Tracker</strong></font> learned a new skill but unfortunately lost it’s own to gain Bandits a One-Shot Factional Rolecop.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<h2>
<a name="players-8" class="anchor" href="#players-8"></a>Players:</h2>
<ol>
<li>
<s>Alice</s> - <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> - Killed Night 4</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>
<s>willtaylor</s> - <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> - Executed Day 2</li>
<li>
<s>Chloe</s> <s>UwU (Katze)</s> - <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> - Killed Night 1</li>
<li>
<s>Marluxion</s> - <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> - Modkilled Day 4</li>
<li>
<s>staypositivefriend</s> - <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font> - Killed Night 2</li>
<li>
<s>WindwardAway</s> <s>Wisp</s> - <font color="brown"><strong>Bandit</strong></font> - Executed Day 3</li>
<li>
<s>Vulgard</s> - <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> - Executed Day 1</li>
<li>Arctic</li>
<li>GGhana</li>
<li>
<s>EliThePsycho</s> - <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font> - Killed Night 3</li>
<li>Prophylaxis</li>
<li>Emilia</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="backups-9" class="anchor" href="#backups-9"></a>Backups:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Apprentice</li>
<li>Amelia</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="spectators-10" class="anchor" href="#spectators-10"></a>Spectators:</h2>
<ol>
<li>DatBird (Uninformed)</li>
<li>Marshal (Uninformed)</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="threadmarks-11" class="anchor" href="#threadmarks-11"></a>Threadmarks:</h2>
<p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/3">Day 1 Begins</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1639">Day 1 - Postcap Lifted</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1847">Day 1 Ends - Vulgard Executed</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-1-12-13/89035/1851">UwU replaces Chloe</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-1-12-13/89035/1854">Day 2 Begins - UwU Dead</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-2-11-13/89035/2259">Wisp replaces WindwardAway</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2334">sulit replaces GGhana</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2711">Day 2 - Postcap Lifted</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2748">Day 2 Ends - Willtaylor Executed</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-3-9-13/89035/2752">Day 3 Begins - staypositivefriend Dead</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-3-9-13/89035/3458">Day 3 - Postcap Lifted</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-3-8-13/89035/3530">Day 3 Ends - Wisp Executed</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-4-7-13/89035/3532">Day 4 Begins - EliThePsycho Dead</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-4-6-13/89035/3804">Day 4 Ends - Marluxion Modkilled</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-5-5-13/89035/3807">Day 5 Begins - Alice Dead</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-5-4-13-bandits-win/89035/4277">End of Game - Emilia Executed</a></p>
<h2>
<a name="votecounts-12" class="anchor" href="#votecounts-12"></a>Votecounts:</h2>
<div class="md-table">
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Day</th>
<th>Votecounts</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>1</td>
<td>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/8">#8</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/401">#401</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/495">#495</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/598">#598</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1175">#1175</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1180">#1180</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1232">#1232</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1255">#1255</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1321">#1321</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1436">#1436</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1463">#1463</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1505">#1505</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1527">#1527</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1552">#1552</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1564">#1564</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1639">#1639</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1651">#1651</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1665">#1665</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1682">#1682</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1728">#1728</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1756">#1756</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1781">#1781</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1802">#1802</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1812">#1812</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1818">#1818</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1836">#1836</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-1-13-13/89035/1845">#1845</a>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2</td>
<td>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/1857">#1857</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/1905">#1905</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2199">#2199</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2261">#2261</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2277">#2277</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2291">#2291</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2519">#2519</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2523">#2523</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2604">#2604</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2640">#2640</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2659">#2659</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2664">#2664</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2701">#2701</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2711">#2711</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2717">#2717</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2721">#2721</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2728">#2728</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2732">#2732</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2737">#2737</a>, <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-night-2-10-13/89035/2747">#2747</a>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div><hr>
<p>If you have any questions, feel free to dm me in your rolecard and I will answer them.</p>
            <p><small>4543 posts - 28 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-5-4-13-bandits-win/89035">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-5-4-13-bandits-win/89035</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 22:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89035</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-day-5-4-13-bandits-win/89035.rss">[VFM] Town vs Bandits - Day 5 (4/13) - Bandits Win!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[VFM] A Hat in Time Cop13er - Town Wins!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>                    <a href="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/561381759795855370/852987195812347904/a-hat-in-time-switch-hero.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/561381759795855370/852987195812347904/a-hat-in-time-switch-hero.png" width="690" height="388">
          </a>

</p>
<h1>
<a name="welcome-to-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-arctic-1" class="anchor" href="#welcome-to-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-arctic-1"></a>Welcome to A Hat in Time Cop13er! Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/arctic">@Arctic</a>
</h1>
<h1>
<a name="rules-2" class="anchor" href="#rules-2"></a>Rules</h1>
<p>Follow the rules found here:</p><aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="244">
  <div class="title">
    <div class="quote-controls"></div>
    <img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar">
    <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Forum/Discord/Game/Meta Rules - Please Read First</a> <a class="badge-wrapper  bullet" href="/c/announcements/8"><span class="badge-category-bg" style="background-color: #F7941D;"></span><span style="" data-drop-close="true" class="badge-category clear-badge" title="Official staff announcements. Although you can’t post, you can reply.
Chat @ https://discord.gg/tol">Official Announcements</span></a>
  </div>
  <blockquote>
    Looking for just our in-game rules? 




All changes are effective immediately 
This applies to all ToL forum categories, Twitch, Steam forum/communities, Reddit, Discord server, and any other ToL/i42 sites.

This is an extension to both our official <a href="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/legal/terms.html" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Terms of Service</a> and our standard <a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/guidelines">Community Guidelines</a> that should be read first and foremost. 


Also note <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/subscriber_agreement/" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Steam’s Subscriber Agreement</a> as well as <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/online_conduct" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Steam’s Code of Conduct</a> that also stacks with our own. 

TL;DR: Mods+ can ban you for any reason, so…
  </blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="78926">
  <div class="title">
    <div class="quote-controls"></div>
    <img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/luxy/40/18622_2.png" class="avatar">
    <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Official Forum Game Rules</a> <a class="badge-wrapper  bullet" href="/c/forum-matches/fol-discussion/16"><span class="badge-category-parent-bg" style="background-color: #BF1E2E;"></span><span class="badge-category-bg" style="background-color: #BF1E2E;"></span><span style="" data-drop-close="true" class="badge-category clear-badge">Discussion</span></a>
  </div>
  <blockquote>
    The following rules are default and apply to all forum games unless the host explicitly states any changes. 

Do not angleshoot, cheat, or abuse loopholes in the rules. This includes using out-of-game information to your advantage, such as the “last online” function. In addition, saying that you have a read that you cannot say because it would qualify as angleshooting or otherwise violate the rules qualifies as angleshooting and is not allowed.
Do not weaponize hosts/moderators.
Do not discuss r…
  </blockquote>
</aside>
<p>
Additionally, for this game, a minimum requirement of <strong>20 substantive, on-topic, game related posts</strong> per in game day are required. Posts that are explicitly or obviously made solely for the purpose of meeting this requirement do not count towards the minimum, nor do posts containing <em>solely</em> a vote. The first time a player fails to meet this requirement, they will be given a warning; the second time they fail to meet it, they will be replaced out. A player who zero-posts will be subbed out without a warning. This requirement may be reduced or waived if an execution is hammered early by majority.</p>
<h1>
<a name="rolelist-3" class="anchor" href="#rolelist-3"></a>Rolelist</h1>
<p><font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Cop</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia Goon</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia Goon</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia Goon</strong></font></p>
<details>
<summary>
Sample Role PMs (this flavor will not be present)</summary>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="undefined">Hat Kid (Town Vanilla)</font></h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/2/d/2d64570d76fe2aca77f97d7b71f5452b98cf3fc3.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="6tysKAPRJyc9AM0gS2Eaj4AIKRl" width="180" height="185"><br>
<em>“I’m a time traveling explorer! No area is too dangerous for me and my umbrella. My mission is to find all the time pieces so I can go home!”</em><br>
Your weapons are your voice and your vote. Use them wisely.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="undefined">Hat Kid (Town Cop)</font></h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/2/d/2d64570d76fe2aca77f97d7b71f5452b98cf3fc3.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="6tysKAPRJyc9AM0gS2Eaj4AIKRl" width="180" height="185"><br>
<em>“I’m a time traveling explorer! No area is too dangerous for me and my umbrella. My mission is to find all the time pieces so I can go home!”</em><br>
Each night, you may target a player (not yourself). You learn if they are a member of the <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font>.</p>
<p>Additionally, you know that [X] is <font color="undefined"><strong>Town</strong></font>. Their name will be redacted upon your flip.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="red">Hat Kid (Mafia Goon)</font></h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/2/d/2d64570d76fe2aca77f97d7b71f5452b98cf3fc3.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="6tysKAPRJyc9AM0gS2Eaj4AIKRl" width="180" height="185"><br>
<em>“I’m a time traveling explorer! No area is too dangerous for me and my umbrella. My mission is to find all the time pieces so I can go home!”</em><br>
You share a 24/7 private chat with your fellow members of the Mafia. Each night, the Mafia must kill a player outside your faction.</p>
</blockquote>
</details>
<h1>
<a name="gameplay-4" class="anchor" href="#gameplay-4"></a>Gameplay</h1>
<ul>
<li>This setup is a cop13er with A Hat in Time flavor. Flavor solve at your own risk, for flavor is NAI.</li>
<li>Days are 48 hours long, Nights are 24. At all points during the night, if all alive players vote to skip the night, the game will immediatley progress into the next day.</li>
<li>The wincon for the <font color="undefined"><strong>Town</strong></font> is <em>Kill all <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> members.</em> The wincon for the <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> is to <em>Reach parity with the  <font color="undefined"><strong>Town</strong></font></em>
</li>
<li>The <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> will communicate through a special Discord/Forum PM</li>
<li>No-execute is a valid vote, and may be hammered to end the day early. In cases where no-execute and another vote are tied at the end of the day, no-execute will have priority in the rand.</li>
<li>In cases where the votes are tied, the result will be randed in spec chat.</li>
<li>Self votes are <strong>not</strong> valid votes.</li>
<li>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> have a factional kill. It is mandatory, and must be performed every night. If they do not submit a kill, it will be randomized outside of the <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font>.</li>
<li>All votes must be in the form <strong>/vote [name of player]</strong> (and ping the hosts/vc bots) to be considered valid, and all unvotes must be in the form <strong>/unvote</strong> (and ping the hosts/vc bots) This is to enable the smooth processing of votes.</li>
<li>Executions are both majority and plurality</li>
</ul>
<h3>
<a name="alts-are-not-allowed-5" class="anchor" href="#alts-are-not-allowed-5"></a>Alts are not allowed.</h3>
<h1>
<a name="playerlist-6" class="anchor" href="#playerlist-6"></a>Playerlist</h1>
<ol>
<li>Alice</li>
<li>
<s>thepigeonnyc</s> - <strong>Executed D1 -</strong> <font color="undefined"><strong>DJ Grooves (Vanilla Town)</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>Silviu</s> - <strong>Died N2</strong> - <strong><font color="undefined">Mafia Boss (Town Cop)</font></strong>
</li>
<li>
<s>Chloe</s> → Mistyx</li>
<li>Centuries</li>
<li>
<s>Zone_Q11</s> → <s>Wazza</s> → clonedcheese</li>
<li>Ruri</li>
<li>
<s>Vulgard</s> → <s>Emilia</s> - <strong>Executed D3</strong> - <strong><font color="red">Queen Vannessa (Mafia Goon)</font></strong>
</li>
<li>Marl</li>
<li>
<s>Cream</s> - <strong>Died N1 -</strong> <font color="undefined"><strong>Bow Kid (Vanilla Town)</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>LiL</s> - <strong>Died N3 -</strong> <strong><font color="undefined">Giant Goat (Vanilla Town)</font></strong>
</li>
<li>Psyx</li>
<li>
<s>Appelsiini</s> - <strong>Executed D2</strong> - <strong><font color="red">Moon Jumper (Mafia Goon)</font></strong>
</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="backups-7" class="anchor" href="#backups-7"></a>Backups</h1>
<ol>
<li>Wazza</li>
<li>Katze</li>
<li>GGhana</li>
<li>Mistyx</li>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="spectators-8" class="anchor" href="#spectators-8"></a>Spectators</h1>
<ol>
<li>Marshal (uninformed)</li>
<li>DatBird (uninformed)</li>
<li>Min(formed)</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>5427 posts - 34 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-town-wins/89005">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-town-wins/89005</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 01:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-89005</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-town-wins/89005.rss">[VFM] A Hat in Time Cop13er - Town Wins!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[VFM] Town vs Bandits - Randing (13/13)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/5/2/524c376ddfc9936fd8e363292f724063ca13df99.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="bK2rDlbHt5p7HqhRUwTcBlXEHfX" width="503" height="273"></p>
<h2>
<a name="town-vs-bandits-hosted-and-designed-by-wazza-and-geyde-reviewed-by-datbird-1" class="anchor" href="#town-vs-bandits-hosted-and-designed-by-wazza-and-geyde-reviewed-by-datbird-1"></a>Town vs Bandits - Hosted and designed by <a class="mention" href="/u/wazza">@Wazza</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a>, Reviewed by <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a>
</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h2>Dagnabbit! Them there bandits have invaded our prestine Town!</h2>
<p>But we can’t figure out who they are, so we’ve recruited all members of the Town to come together in order to find and enact <em>justice</em> upon em! Unfortunately, we entered WIFOM hell and have to out-predict them because our officers are trainees and are terrible at their job. Good luck, we suck.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<h2>
<a name="mechanics-2" class="anchor" href="#mechanics-2"></a>Mechanics:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Open Setup</li>
<li>48/24 Phases - Night can be skipped if all players agree, when the day ends may be changed depending when the night is skipped.</li>
<li>The Bandits will speak in either a private thread or private discord depending on what they desire.</li>
<li>The Bandits have a mandatory Factional Kill (if not performed the kill will be randomized among living town players) and a Factional One-Shot Rolecop.</li>
<li>The Bandit Factional Kill and the Bandit Factional One-Shot Rolecop may not be done alongside each other.</li>
<li>Threadmarks will include Final Vote Counts, day starts, night starts and any other important events</li>
<li>Bandits do not flip as their role, instead they flip as Bandit, because that’s the only thing we’re competent enough to figure out.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="rules-3" class="anchor" href="#rules-3"></a>Rules:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow the <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Forum Rules</a> and <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-game-rules/78926">Forum Game Rules</a>. Failure to do so will result in a warning and consequently a force-replace or modkill if needed.</li>
<li>A minimum of 20 content posts are required per day, if it is impossible for you to reach this amount, please inform me beforehand. If you are prodded twice for this, you will be force-replaced or modkilled if needed. If you post no content in a single day that did not end early, you will be force-replaced immediately unless you can provide a good enough reasoning beforehand.</li>
<li>Excessive AtE is frowned upon, don’t use it.</li>
<li>Each day, you make make a maximum of 200 posts, on content or not, an hour before EoD this will be lifted. Any posts done after you have reached your post limit will not punish you.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="voting-4" class="anchor" href="#voting-4"></a>Voting:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Majority and Plurality are enabled, however on Day 1, Majority is disabled. Which, of course, means there is a Day 1 executed.</li>
<li>If two or more wagons are tied for plurality, a random player between the tied wagons will be executed.</li>
<li>To vote a player, type <strong>/vote [name] <a class="mention" href="/u/wazza">@Wazza</a></strong> otherwise the vote will not count.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="rolelist-5" class="anchor" href="#rolelist-5"></a>Rolelist:</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font><br>
<font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font><br>
<font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town x8</strong></font><br>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Goon</strong></font><br>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Inheriting Ninja</strong></font><br>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Inheriting Strongwilled</strong></font></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<h2>
<a name="rolecards-6" class="anchor" href="#rolecards-6"></a>Rolecards:</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="GREEN">Vanilla Town</font></h1>
<p>Your only abilities are your voice and your vote.</p>
<p>You are practically completely useless in anything you try to accomplish or do in life, your uselessness holds no bounds whatsoever, but that doesn’t stop you from enacting your <em>right</em> as a citizen to murder people in the name of justice.</p>
<p><em>Defeat the Bandits in the name of justice.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="GREEN">Town Informed Tracker</font></h1>
<p>Each night, you may choose to track a player, you will know who they visit.<br>
Your results will be either ‘Your target visited [player]’, ‘Your target didn’t visit anyone’ or ‘No Result’.<br>
Additionally, You know that [x] is the <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font>.</p>
<p>After being arrested for committing tax fraud, he was released on set circumstances because he’s actually good at not being useless.</p>
<p><em>Defeat the Bandits in the name of justice.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="GREEN">Town Informed Jailkeeper</font></h1>
<p>Each night, you may choose to jail a player. Their action will be roleblocked and they will be protected from nightkills.<br>
You may not target the same player consecutively.<br>
Additionally, You know that [x] is the <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font>.</p>
<p>Extremely delusional, constantly talks about how the bandits are wolves or mafia for some reason, also calls fellow citizens villagers to go along with this, would be in a mental facility, however he’s still one of the only compteent ones.</p>
<p><em>Defeat the Bandits in the name of justice.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="BROWN">Bandit Goon</font></h1>
<p>Your only abilities are your voice and your vote.</p>
<p>You tagged along with your fellow bandits, you’re similar to the person who just mouths the words to a song during a choir, you’re absolutely pointless, but you’re trying your best and that’s all that matters. However, your best clearly isn’t enough, you’re practically useless anyway.</p>
<p><em>Have majority of the Town be Bandits or have equal numbers of both.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="BROWN">Bandit Inheriting Ninja</font></h1>
<p>Your visits are hidden when performing the factional kill.<br>
If the Strongwilled dies, you will become immune to roleblocks when performing the factional kill.</p>
<p>Cannot stop screaming about how it isn’t just a phase.</p>
<p><em>Have majority of the Town be Bandits or have equal numbers of both.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="BROWN">Bandit Inheriting Strongwilled</font></h1>
<p>You are immune to roleblocks when performing the factional kill.<br>
If the Ninja dies, your visits will be hidden when performing the factional kill.</p>
<p>You have no dignity, nothing to lose, so at the end of the day, who cares who you pick and choose.</p>
<p><em>Have majority of the Town be Bandits or have equal numbers of both.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Flavour Written here will not be used, instead the flavour will be tailored to The Princess Bride.</p>
<h2>
<a name="things-changed-from-the-previous-game-that-got-canned-7" class="anchor" href="#things-changed-from-the-previous-game-that-got-canned-7"></a>Things changed from the previous game (that got canned):</h2>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Players will flip as <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font>, <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font>, <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> or <font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Universal Backup Fruit Vendor</strong></font>’s competence got it killed, instead its intelligence spread out to other Citizens…okay nevermind, it only went to the other two Citizens that could actually do things and they became <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Jailkeeper</strong></font> and <font color="GREEN"><strong>Town Informed Tracker</strong></font>. A new <font color="GREEN"><strong>Vanilla Town</strong></font> also joined the Town to accommodate this.</li>
<li>
<font color="BROWN"><strong>Bandit Tracker</strong></font> learned a new skill but unfortunately lost it’s own to gain Bandits a One-Shot Factional Rolecop.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<h2>
<a name="players-8" class="anchor" href="#players-8"></a>Players:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Alice</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>willtaylor</li>
<li>Chloe</li>
<li>Marluxion</li>
<li>staypositivefriend</li>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
<li>Vulgard</li>
<li>Arctic</li>
<li>GGhana</li>
<li>EliThePsycho</li>
<li>Prophylaxis</li>
<li>Emilia</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="backups-9" class="anchor" href="#backups-9"></a>Backups:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Katze</li>
<li>Sulit</li>
<li>Amelia</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="spectators-10" class="anchor" href="#spectators-10"></a>Spectators:</h2>
<ol>
<li>DatBird (Uninformed)</li>
<li>Marshal (Uninformed)</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="threadmarks-11" class="anchor" href="#threadmarks-11"></a>Threadmarks:</h2>
<hr>
<p>If you have any questions, feel free to ping me and I will answer them.</p>
            <p><small>247 posts - 27 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-randing-13-13/88979">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-randing-13-13/88979</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88979</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-town-vs-bandits-randing-13-13/88979.rss">[VFM] Town vs Bandits - Randing (13/13)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Minority Rule Royale 2: Teams Edition- Eli and Intensify Wins!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[DatBird]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>
<a name="colorlightbluewelcome-to-minority-rule-royale-2-teams-editioncolor-1" class="anchor" href="#colorlightbluewelcome-to-minority-rule-royale-2-teams-editioncolor-1"></a><font color="lightblue">Welcome to Minority Rule Royale 2: Teams Edition!</font>
</h2>
<p>Hosted by DatBird and potential Cohost <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/flushed.png?v=10" title=":flushed:" class="emoji" alt=":flushed:"><br>
<em>credit to Marl for original Minority Rule Royale</em></p>
<p><em>Welcome to Minority Rule Royale  2: Teams Edition!  The rules are pretty simple. I will present you a choice of several rooms—just choose one to enter.  If you pick the room with the most people, you will all meet a horrible demise</em>.</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorlightblue-how-to-play-color-2" class="anchor" href="#colorlightblue-how-to-play-color-2"></a><font color="lightblue"> How to play? </font>
</h1>
<p>Every round, you will be given a list of rooms to choose from. PM me your pick privately. if you pick the room a majority of the players pick, you will be eliminated. If there is a tie, then both rooms are considered a majority and players who picked both are eliminated. The game will end once there are two or fewer players left. .</p>
<p>Since its team edition, you will have to find a partner and signup with both of you claiming to be each other partners. Team size is limited to 2. Do <strong>/Join with <span class="mention">@PLAYER</span> as my partner</strong> to join. Feel free to PM or DM each other as long as you include me. I will need separate dms for submissions tho, so don’t just submit in your team chat.</p>
<h2>
<a name="colorlightblueroomscolor-3" class="anchor" href="#colorlightblueroomscolor-3"></a><font color="lightblue">Rooms</font>
</h2>
<p><strong><font color="skyblue">Air </font></strong> - A random picker becomes light.<br>
<strong><font color="#801080">Betrayal </font></strong>- If this room is tied for the minority, it gains infinite picks and becomes the majority.<br>
<strong><font color="black">Death </font></strong>- Everyone who picks this dies, even if it is not the majority.<br>
<strong><font color="#DFDFDF">Dice </font></strong>- Everyone who picks this is given a random status.<br>
<strong><font color="#BFBF00">Divide </font></strong>- Everyone who picks this counts as half.<br>
<strong><font color="lightbrown">Earth </font></strong>- A random picker becomes heavy.<br>
<strong><font color="#800000">Evil </font></strong>- All pickers become cursed.<br>
<strong><font color="#FF00FF">False </font></strong>- This room does nothing, but it takes the name of another random room.<br>
<strong><font color="#8000FF">Force </font></strong>- A random person who did pick this will change to a random room in the current pool.<br>
<strong><font color="#BF0080">Gravity </font></strong>- A random person who did not pick this will change to this room.<br>
<strong><font color="Cornflowerblue">Holy </font></strong>- A random picker becomes a saint. All other pickers become cursed.<br>
<strong><font color="#800080">Illusion </font></strong>- This room takes the effect of another secret room before the start of the round.<br>
<strong><font color="#808080">Insanity </font></strong>- A random picker becomes insane.<br>
<strong><font color="#00BFFF">Life </font></strong>- If nobody picks this, everybody dies.<br>
<strong><font color="green">Luck </font></strong>- If this room is the majority, then one random picker will survive. If this is not the majority, then one random picker will die.<br>
<strong><font color="#000080">Majority</font></strong> - If this room is the majority, the rooms with the second most votes will be the majority.<br>
<strong><font color="#FFBF40">Multiply </font></strong>- Everyone who picks this counts as two.<br>
<strong><font color="sienna">Mundane </font></strong>- This room literally does nothing.<br>
<strong><font color="dark">Murder </font></strong>- One random picker becomes a Serial Killer<br>
<strong><font color="darkred">Mystery </font></strong>- Everyone who picks this is given a random status. They are not informed which status they received.<br>
<strong><font color="#505050">Permanency </font></strong>- If picked by anyone, this room will also be in the pool for the next round. Once this room is the majority, it is removed from the pool for all future rounds.<br>
<strong><font color="#509090">Protection </font></strong>- All pickers are immune to death this round for any reason other than the majority. A random picker becomes a bodyguard.<br>
<strong><font color="#0080FF">Purity </font></strong>- Everyone who picks this loses all statuses.<br>
<strong><font color="#FF0000">Rejuvinate </font></strong>- Everyone who picks this becomes healthy.<br>
<strong><font color="#00EF00">Spite </font></strong>- A random picker will becomes cursed.<br>
<strong><font color="Steelblue">Secrecy</font></strong> - All pickers become cultists.<br>
<strong><font color="blue">Unity </font></strong> - If all players pick this, nobody will die due to the majority.<br>
<strong><font color="#006030">Ritual </font></strong> - All pickers get the soulbound status.<br>
<strong><font color="#282828">Graveyard </font></strong> - If nobody picks this room, three random dead players are revived.<br>
<strong><font color="#ffafa0">Duplicate </font></strong> - Takes the effect of the room with the most pickers (at the time this room activates).<br>
<strong><font color="orange">Friendship</font></strong> -  If this room isn’t the majority, all players in this room will move to the room of their teammate and receive the effects of that room. Unless you are both in this room in which case nothing happens to yall.</p>
<h2>
<a name="colorlightbluestatusescolor-4" class="anchor" href="#colorlightbluestatusescolor-4"></a><font color="lightblue">Statuses</font>
</h2>
<p><font color="#408000">Bodyguard </font>- Nobody who picks the same room as you can die for any reason other than the majority. If anyone who would die without your intervention is saved, you will die instead.<br>
<font color="Steelblue">Cultist</font> - If there are any cultists, then there will be a room that only its members may pick. It will be denoted in [brackets].<br>
<font color="#804080">Cursed</font>- You will die next round unless your status is removed or your death is prevented. This status is removed afterwards.<br>
<font color="#FF0000">Healthy</font> - You cannot die for any reason except for the majority. Once your death is prevented by this status, this status will be removed.<br>
<font color="#808080">Insane</font> - You must pick the majority or you will die.<br>
<font color="skyblue">Light</font> - You do not count as a picker for the next round. This status is removed afterwards.<br>
<font color="lightbrown">Heavy</font> - Your pick counts as two picks for the next round. This status is removed afterwards.<br>
<font color="Cornflowerblue">Saint</font>- You are immune to death. Once your death is prevented by this status, this status will be removed.<br>
<font color="#0000BF">Serial Killer</font> - A random person who picks the same room as you will die.<br>
<font color="#006030">Soulbound </font> - If you lose this status you will die.</p>
<p><strong>Order of application goes:</strong></p>
<p>Effects of the Room<br>
Existing Statuses<br>
Majority calculated (Death from majority happens here.)<br>
New Statuses</p>
<h1>
<a name="colorlightbluespecial-rulescolor-5" class="anchor" href="#colorlightbluespecial-rulescolor-5"></a><font color="lightblue">Special Rules</font>
</h1>
<ol>
<li>
<font color="red"><strong>Care Package:</strong></font> Every round, a random room will be chosen to contain a care package. Picking this room awards you with a single tangerine! <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/tangerine.png?v=10" title=":tangerine:" class="emoji" alt=":tangerine:"> Tangerines <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/tangerine.png?v=10" title=":tangerine:" class="emoji" alt=":tangerine:">  are useless, but will be used to break ties at the end of the game. In the case of a tie, the player with the most tangerines <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/tangerine.png?v=10" title=":tangerine:" class="emoji" alt=":tangerine:">  will win!</li>
<li>
<font color="lightblue"><strong>Shrinking Circle:</strong></font> The formula for determining the amount of rooms has been scrapped. The game will start with 8 rooms. Every round, the pool will shrink by one until there are only two rooms remaining. (This does not count rooms that exist due to special circumstances such as cultist.)</li>
<li>
<strong><font color="orange">Teams</font></strong>: If teammates end up in the same room by the end of the New Statuses phase they will receive a <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/tangerine.png?v=10" title=":tangerine:" class="emoji" alt=":tangerine:">  Tangerine <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/tangerine.png?v=10" title=":tangerine:" class="emoji" alt=":tangerine:"> each! That means more chances of winning ties. Also if one of you wins the game, both of you do. <s>Prepare to get carried</s>. There is also the new Friendship room to work with teammates’ mechanics.</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="colorlightblueliving-participantscolor-6" class="anchor" href="#colorlightblueliving-participantscolor-6"></a><font color="lightblue">Living Participants</font>
</h1>
<ol>
<li><s>Team Number 1: Wazza and Min</s></li>
<li>Team Number 2:<s>Eli</s> and Intensify</li>
<li>Team Number 3: <s>Marluxion</s> and WindwardAway</li>
<li>Paper Mario Birds: thepigeonnyc and Silviu</li>
<li><s>Frens: clonedcheese and Jane</s></li>
<li><s>UntrustworthyLiberal: Aelin and TrustworthyLiberal</s></li>
<li><s>Team Somewhat Polish:Orangeandblack5 and Arete</s></li>
<li>Bread and Butter: <s>Chloe</s> and Sulit</li>
<li>Team Marshal: <s>Marshal</s> and GGhana</li>
<li><s>Team Number 5: Luxy and Nerbins</s></li>
<li>Team Number 6: Squirrel and <s>Italy</s>
</li>
<li>Team Number 7: Emilia and <s>KyoDaz</s>
</li>
<li><s>Team Number 8: Appel and willtaylor</s></li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="colorlightblue-linkscolor-7" class="anchor" href="#colorlightblue-linkscolor-7"></a><font color="lightblue"> Links</font>
</h1>
<p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-signups-13-infinite/88952/165">Phase 1 Begins: Rooms are…</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-phase-2-11-teams-13-teams-19-alive/88952/397">Phase 1 Ends and Phase 2 Begins…</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-phase-3-10-teams-13-teams-17-alive/88952/572">Phase 2 Ends and Phase 3 begins…</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-phase-3-10-teams-13-teams-17-alive/88952/691">Phase 3 Ends and Phase 4 Begins</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-phase-5-6-teams-13-teams-8-alive/88952/779">Phase 4 Ends and Phase 5 Begins…</a></p>
<h1>
<a name="colorlightblue-phases-are-24-hours-this-game-will-start-when-it-seems-like-everyone-has-a-team-and-no-one-else-is-joining-color-8" class="anchor" href="#colorlightblue-phases-are-24-hours-this-game-will-start-when-it-seems-like-everyone-has-a-team-and-no-one-else-is-joining-color-8"></a><font color="lightblue"> PHASES ARE 24 HOURS. This game will start when it seems like everyone has a team and no one else is joining. </font>
</h1>
            <p><small>1154 posts - 39 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-eli-and-intensify-wins/88952">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-eli-and-intensify-wins/88952</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 02:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88952</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/minority-rule-royale-2-teams-edition-eli-and-intensify-wins/88952.rss">Minority Rule Royale 2: Teams Edition- Eli and Intensify Wins!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[VFM] A Hat in Time Cop13er - Signups (FULL)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>                    <a href="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/561381759795855370/852987195812347904/a-hat-in-time-switch-hero.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/561381759795855370/852987195812347904/a-hat-in-time-switch-hero.png" width="690" height="388">
          </a>

</p>
<h1>
<a name="welcome-to-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-arctic-1" class="anchor" href="#welcome-to-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-hosted-by-elithepsycho-and-arctic-1"></a>Welcome to A Hat in Time Cop13er! Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/arctic">@Arctic</a>
</h1>
<h1>
<a name="rules-2" class="anchor" href="#rules-2"></a>Rules</h1>
<p>Follow the rules found here:</p><aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="244">
  <div class="title">
    <div class="quote-controls"></div>
    <img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar">
    <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Forum/Discord/Game/Meta Rules - Please Read First</a> <a class="badge-wrapper  bullet" href="/c/announcements/8"><span class="badge-category-bg" style="background-color: #F7941D;"></span><span style="" data-drop-close="true" class="badge-category clear-badge" title="Official staff announcements. Although you can’t post, you can reply.
Chat @ https://discord.gg/tol">Official Announcements</span></a>
  </div>
  <blockquote>
    Looking for just our in-game rules? 




All changes are effective immediately 
This applies to all ToL forum categories, Twitch, Steam forum/communities, Reddit, Discord server, and any other ToL/i42 sites.

This is an extension to both our official <a href="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/legal/terms.html" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Terms of Service</a> and our standard <a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/guidelines">Community Guidelines</a> that should be read first and foremost. 


Also note <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/subscriber_agreement/" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Steam’s Subscriber Agreement</a> as well as <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/online_conduct" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Steam’s Code of Conduct</a> that also stacks with our own. 

TL;DR: Mods+ can ban you for any reason, so…
  </blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="78926">
  <div class="title">
    <div class="quote-controls"></div>
    <img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/luxy/40/18622_2.png" class="avatar">
    <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Official Forum Game Rules</a> <a class="badge-wrapper  bullet" href="/c/forum-matches/fol-discussion/16"><span class="badge-category-parent-bg" style="background-color: #BF1E2E;"></span><span class="badge-category-bg" style="background-color: #BF1E2E;"></span><span style="" data-drop-close="true" class="badge-category clear-badge">Discussion</span></a>
  </div>
  <blockquote>
    The following rules are default and apply to all forum games unless the host explicitly states any changes. 

Do not angleshoot, cheat, or abuse loopholes in the rules. This includes using out-of-game information to your advantage, such as the “last online” function. In addition, saying that you have a read that you cannot say because it would qualify as angleshooting or otherwise violate the rules qualifies as angleshooting and is not allowed.
Do not weaponize hosts/moderators.
Do not discuss r…
  </blockquote>
</aside>
<p>
Additionally, for this game, a minimum requirement of <strong>20 substantive, on-topic, game related posts</strong> per in game day are required. Posts that are explicitly or obviously made solely for the purpose of meeting this requirement do not count towards the minimum, nor do posts containing <em>solely</em> a vote. The first time a player fails to meet this requirement, they will be given a warning; the second time they fail to meet it, they will be replaced out. A player who zero-posts will be subbed out without a warning. This requirement may be reduced or waived if an execution is hammered early by majority.</p>
<h1>
<a name="rolelist-3" class="anchor" href="#rolelist-3"></a>Rolelist</h1>
<p><font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Vanilla</strong> </font><br>
<font color="undefined"><strong>Town Cop</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia Goon</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia Goon</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia Goon</strong></font></p>
<details>
<summary>
Sample Role PMs (this flavor will not be present)</summary>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="undefined">Hat Kid (Town Vanilla)</font></h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/2/d/2d64570d76fe2aca77f97d7b71f5452b98cf3fc3.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="6tysKAPRJyc9AM0gS2Eaj4AIKRl" width="180" height="185"><br>
<em>“I’m a time traveling explorer! No area is too dangerous for me and my umbrella. My mission is to find all the time pieces so I can go home!”</em><br>
Your weapons are your voice and your vote. Use them wisely.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="undefined">Hat Kid (Town Cop)</font></h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/2/d/2d64570d76fe2aca77f97d7b71f5452b98cf3fc3.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="6tysKAPRJyc9AM0gS2Eaj4AIKRl" width="180" height="185"><br>
<em>“I’m a time traveling explorer! No area is too dangerous for me and my umbrella. My mission is to find all the time pieces so I can go home!”</em><br>
Each night, you may target a player (not yourself). You learn if they are a member of the <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font>.</p>
<p>Additionally, you know that [X] is <font color="undefined"><strong>Town</strong></font>. Their name will be redacted upon your flip.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="red">Hat Kid (Mafia Goon)</font></h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/2/d/2d64570d76fe2aca77f97d7b71f5452b98cf3fc3.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="6tysKAPRJyc9AM0gS2Eaj4AIKRl" width="180" height="185"><br>
<em>“I’m a time traveling explorer! No area is too dangerous for me and my umbrella. My mission is to find all the time pieces so I can go home!”</em><br>
You share a 24/7 private chat with your fellow members of the Mafia. Each night, the Mafia must kill a player outside your faction.</p>
</blockquote>
</details>
<h1>
<a name="gameplay-4" class="anchor" href="#gameplay-4"></a>Gameplay</h1>
<ul>
<li>This setup is a cop13er with A Hat in Time flavor. Flavor solve at your own risk, for flavor is NAI.</li>
<li>Days are 48 hours long, Nights are 24. At all points during the night, if all alive players vote to skip the night, the game will immediatley progress into the next day.</li>
<li>The wincon for the <font color="undefined"><strong>Town</strong></font> is <em>Kill all <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> members.</em> The wincon for the <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> is to <em>Reach parity with the  <font color="undefined"><strong>Town</strong></font></em>
</li>
<li>The <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> will communicate through a special Discord/Forum PM</li>
<li>No-execute is a valid vote, and may be hammered to end the day early. In cases where no-execute and another vote are tied at the end of the day, no-execute will have priority in the rand.</li>
<li>In cases where the votes are tied, the result will be randed in spec chat.</li>
<li>Self votes are <strong>not</strong> valid votes.</li>
<li>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font> have a factional kill. It is mandatory, and must be performed every night. If they do not submit a kill, it will be randomized outside of the <font color="red"><strong>Mafia</strong></font>.</li>
<li>All votes must be in the form <strong>/vote [name of player]</strong> (and ping the hosts/vc bots) to be considered valid, and all unvotes must be in the form <strong>/unvote</strong> (and ping the hosts/vc bots) This is to enable the smooth processing of votes.</li>
<li>Executions are both majority and plurality</li>
</ul>
<h3>
<a name="alts-are-not-allowed-5" class="anchor" href="#alts-are-not-allowed-5"></a>Alts are not allowed.</h3>
<h1>
<a name="playerlist-6" class="anchor" href="#playerlist-6"></a>Playerlist</h1>
<ol>
<li>Alice</li>
<li>thepigeonnyc</li>
<li>Silviu</li>
<li>Chloe</li>
<li>Centuries</li>
<li>Zone_Q11</li>
<li>Ruri</li>
<li>Vulgard</li>
<li>Marl</li>
<li>Cream</li>
<li>LiL</li>
<li>Psyx</li>
<li>Appelsiini</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="backups-7" class="anchor" href="#backups-7"></a>Backups</h1>
<ol>
<li>Wazza</li>
<li>Katze</li>
<li>GGhana</li>
<li>Mistyx</li>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
</ol>
<h1>
<a name="spectators-8" class="anchor" href="#spectators-8"></a>Spectators</h1>
<ol>
<li>Marshal (uninformed)</li>
<li>DatBird (uninformed)</li>
<li>Min(formed)</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>239 posts - 40 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-signups-full/88946">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-signups-full/88946</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 02:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88946</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/vfm-a-hat-in-time-cop13er-signups-full/88946.rss">[VFM] A Hat in Time Cop13er - Signups (FULL)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Ciconia FM - Game Over - Order of the Public Bath Wins</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[astand]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647" title="Ciconia FM"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_517x348.jpeg" alt="Ciconia FM" data-base62-sha1="3cyxMRacLAlBRykMY841LtDASqP" width="517" height="348" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_517x348.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Ciconia FM</span><span class="informations">719×485 145 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<h2>
<a name="ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-designed-and-hosted-by-astand-cohosted-by-kyodaz-1" class="anchor" href="#ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-designed-and-hosted-by-astand-cohosted-by-kyodaz-1"></a>Ciconia FM: When They Cry - designed and hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/astand">@astand</a>, cohosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/kyodaz">@KyoDaz</a>.</h2>
<p>Reviewer is <a class="mention" href="/u/osieorb18">@osieorb18</a>, alt mod is <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a>.</p>
<h2>
<a name="rules-2" class="anchor" href="#rules-2"></a>Rules:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow all <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Rules</a> and <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Official Forum Game Rules.</a>
</li>
<li>Make at least 15 game-related posts each day (unless day ends early). If you fail to meet this requirement, you might get replaced. For 0 posting in full game day I will force replace you without any questions.</li>
<li>Don’t edit posts. This includes quickediting for typos, just don’t do it.</li>
<li>Alt accounts are allowed. Tell me your identity privately and send an application to <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a> if you wish to play on an alt. You are allowed to speculate on identities of alt accounts.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="general-information-3" class="anchor" href="#general-information-3"></a>General information:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Closed setup.</li>
<li>The game will contain bastard and/or experimental mechanics. However, OP will never lie, your rolecard will never lie, and no flips will ever be false.</li>
<li>Days are 48 hours, nights are 24 hours.</li>
<li>Eliminations are majority + plurality. In case of a tie, elimination will be randed.</li>
<li>At EoD, votes made up to :59 mark will be accepted (but not at :00 mark).</li>
<li>It will not be announced if the game reaches MYLO/LYLO.</li>
<li>
<font color="007F46"><strong>Order of the Public Bath</strong></font> is uninformed majority and <font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order</strong></font> is informed minority.</li>
<li>
<font color="007F46"><strong>Order of the Public Bath’s</strong></font> win condition is: <em>Eliminate all members of the Ninth Prime Chivalric Order and all other possible threats to Order of the Public Bath.</em>
</li>
<li>
<font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order’s</strong></font> win condition is: <em>Achieve parity with the Order of the Public Bath and eliminate all other possible threats to Ninth Prime Chivalric Order.</em>
</li>
<li>Other win conditions may or may not exist.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="game-mechanics-4" class="anchor" href="#game-mechanics-4"></a>Game mechanics:</h2>
<ul>
<li>There are no conversions.</li>
<li>There may or may not be lost wolves.</li>
<li>Flavor/role claims are allowed <strong>at your own risk</strong>.</li>
<li>Flavor (character name, in-universe faction and kette) isn’t alignment indicative, but might be role indicative for some roles while being misleading or not role indicative for others.</li>
<li>
<font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order’s</strong></font> factional kill is assigned. Performing it doesn’t prevent using other night actions.</li>
<li>You can’t perform actions on N0 unless specified otherwise.</li>
<li>Deadline for submitting actions is one hour before the end of the phase (whether day or night).</li>
<li>If you have several different night (day) abilities, then you can use all of them during a single night (day), unless specified otherwise.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="example-rolecard-5" class="anchor" href="#example-rolecard-5"></a>Example rolecard:</h2>
<details>
<summary>
VT</summary>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb" title="Example Town"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_542x500.jpeg" alt="Example Town" data-base62-sha1="uHyLJtVz7IB36iLqG4A7faDiIKn" width="542" height="500" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_542x500.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_813x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Example Town</span><span class="informations">1018×939 268 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
</details>
<h2>
<a name="backups-6" class="anchor" href="#backups-6"></a>Backups:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Arctic</li>
<li>Prophylaxis</li>
<li>Whysper</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="theatergoers-7" class="anchor" href="#theatergoers-7"></a>Theatergoers:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Alice (uninformed)</li>
<li>Appelsiini (uninformed)</li>
<li>Arete (informed)</li>
<li>DatBird (uninformed)</li>
<li>Intensify (informed)</li>
<li>Jane (uninformed)</li>
<li>katze (informed)</li>
<li>Silviu200530 (uninformed)</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>5941 posts - 43 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-game-over-order-of-the-public-bath-wins/88909">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-game-over-order-of-the-public-bath-wins/88909</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 21:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88909</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-game-over-order-of-the-public-bath-wins/88909.rss">Ciconia FM - Game Over - Order of the Public Bath Wins</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Ciconia FM - Dead Chat</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[astand]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="there-is-dead-interaction-in-this-game-1" class="anchor" href="#there-is-dead-interaction-in-this-game-1"></a>There is dead interaction in this game.</h1>
<h1>
<a name="however-if-you-wish-you-can-leave-this-chat-and-join-spec-chat-tell-me-in-your-rolecard-2" class="anchor" href="#however-if-you-wish-you-can-leave-this-chat-and-join-spec-chat-tell-me-in-your-rolecard-2"></a>However, if you wish, you can leave this chat and join spec chat (tell me in your rolecard).</h1>
            <p><small>1367 posts - 20 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-dead-chat/88907">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-dead-chat/88907</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 21:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88907</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-dead-chat/88907.rss">Ciconia FM - Dead Chat</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TrustworthyLiberal]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="colorgreenvldr-3-experimentscolor-1" class="anchor" href="#colorgreenvldr-3-experimentscolor-1"></a><font color="Green">VLDR 3: Experiments</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="(color)">   </font></p>
<p>Hosted by TrustworthyLiberal<br>
Co-Host(s): Kyo, Solic</p>
<h1>
<a name="important-notes-2" class="anchor" href="#important-notes-2"></a>Important Notes</h1>
<p><strong>As a notice this game will run Wed through Saturday and be on pause sunday through Tusday.</strong><br>
<strong>The hosts may or may not utilize WOTM to prohibit players from joining.</strong><br>
In addition i am looking for 1/2 co-hosts to make action processing as smooth as possible</p>
<p>Hope to start on Wednesday Augest 18th maw allow disscusion to start slightly before this time.<br>
Likely close this thread sometime before that to rand roles and allow any questions to form.</p>
<h3>
<a name="how-to-play-3" class="anchor" href="#how-to-play-3"></a>How to Play</h3>
<p>The game will shift through three cycles, Discussion, Roaming, and Ambidex, until it is over. Note that this game is complex and has many elements and factors. Please read all of the below before signing up.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Discussion</summary>
<p>During Discussion all players can speak in the main thread. All players will be in the same room, so actions can be performed on other players during this time. You can also choose to end Discussion early by leaving the room. After you have left you can no longer talk in the main thread, and players can no longer perform actions on you.</p>
<p>Discussion will last for 24 hours, or until 3/4 of the total players have left the room.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Roaming</summary>
<p>During roaming all players can move about and perform actions, search for items, attack other players, and explore in a pre-made map via PMs. If two or more people are in the same place they will be added to a PM in which they can talk privately.</p>
<p>There will likely be different puzzles you can solve to get better and upgraded gear and to unlock other areas of the map.</p>
<p>Roaming lasts 48 hours or until all players say in their PM that they would like Roaming to end.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Ambidex</summary>
<p>During Ambidex all players will return to the room Discussion takes place. However, no actions can be performed at this time. Players will publicly vote on 1 of 3 lists that say which players will be paired with whom during the Ambidex Games.</p>
<p>After pairings have been voted on, the main thread will be closed and all players must decide whether to ally or betray their partner in their PM. If a player doesn’t cast a vote they will ally by default. If both partners don’t cast a vote they will both betray by default.</p>
<p><strong>Ally vs. Ally:</strong> Both players gain 2 Ambidex Points.<br>
<strong>Ally vs. Betray:</strong> The person who allied will lose 3 points, and the betrayer will gain 4.<br>
<strong>Betray vs. Betray:</strong> Both players will earn zero Amdidex Points.</p>
<p>Ambidex Phase will last 48 hours, 24 for voting, 24 to submit Ally or Betray.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Stats</summary>
<p>If an action a player performs has a chance to fail, a 1d20 will be rolled with discobot. Depending on the action, the player will have one or more of their stats added to the roll. This will determine how successful it is. There are five different stats that can be applied to actions.</p>
<p><strong>Strength (STR):</strong> Lifting or pushing heavy things, pulling things, attacking with melee-based weapons, etc.<br>
<strong>Precision (PRC):</strong> Throwing items, attacking with ranged weapons, doing actions with items that are hard to maneuver, etc.<br>
<strong>Endurance (END):</strong> How much hits you can, how much you can withstand harmful effects, etc.<br>
<strong>Intelligence (INT):</strong> Searching rooms, gaining information, healing, building things, etc.<br>
<strong>Agility (AGI):</strong> Dodging hits, running, attacking with melee weapons, etc.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Inventory and Items</summary>
<p>During the game, players may find useful items they want to keep with them, or take them from other players.</p>
<p>Players have a limited inventory space. They have 5 public inventory slots that can be seen by anyone looking into their inventory, and 1 private slot that no one can see unless the player is unconscious or specifically shows it to someone.</p>
<p>In addition, some players may start with an addition private role slot, in which a role item can be stored.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Roles</summary>
<p>Before the game starts, players will be assigned a role via PM. Roles will dictate unique abilities, stats, your alignment, and your win condition. Roles are custom.</p>
<p>Claiming anything on your rolecard is allowed. Players can make fake rolecards, abilities, stats, alignments or wincons. Speculating on the above is also allowed.</p>
<p>The four alignments are Good, Evil, Wildcard and Neutral.</p>
<p><strong>Good</strong> players need to help others, and help as many people escape as possible.<br>
<strong>Neutral</strong> players need to escape at all costs, and may have other side goals.<br>
<strong>Wildcard</strong> players have a more flexible win condition and can end up being any of the other three alignments.<br>
<strong>Evil</strong> players are there to sabotage others, cause chaos, and cause conflict and potentially death.<br>
There is no role list.</p>
<p><strong>Roles and alignments will not be flipped upon death.</strong></p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Actions</summary>
<p>Players submit actions to the moderator in order to interact with other players and the map. These can be anything; picking up an item, punching another player, doing a backflip, investigate a part of the room.</p>
<p>To perform an action, type <strong>/action,</strong> for example <strong>/Investigate the Couches.</strong> Actions can be submitted in your PM, in chats with other players, or in the main thread during discussion. You can submit actions anytime except during the Ambidex phase.</p>
<p>Players can set automatic actions for when they are AFK in case something happens to them while they are gone. If they have nothing set I will generally do something for them. <em>I’m not just going to let someone get stabbed because they were AFK</em>.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Combat</summary>
<p>All weapons will have a certain damage amount. When a player attacks another, I will take the weapons damage amount and add it to the attacks strength. For example, if a player with a strength stat of 4 attacks a player with a weapon that does four damage, they will do eight damage.</p>
<p>If a player attempts to dodge an attack I will roll a 1d20 and choose a number depending on how the player is attacked. If the number rolled is more than that number the player will successfully dodge.</p>
<p>I am flexible processing combat actions and might award more damage points for creativity.</p>
<p>Health is calculated by 20+(5*END stat). If a player takes more damage than this they will be knocked out. If a player is hit after that they will die.</p>
<p>Medical items will have a flat healing amount, and extra healing will be added on by the INT stat*2.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Ambidex Points and Winning</summary>
<p>Every player will start with 4 Ambidex Points. Ambidex Point totals will be visible at all times in the OP. If a player ever has less than one Ambidex Point they will immediately die.</p>
<p>If a player has more than or equal to 11 Ambidex Points, they can access the Door Number 11 that is located in the map. When the door is opened, it will remain open for 11 seconds, then it will close forever and the game will end. Only players with 11 points or more can exit the door.</p>
<p><strong>The Ambidex Game is the only way to earn Ambidex Points, and the Door Number 11 is the only way to escape.</strong></p>
</details>
<h3>
<a name="game-maps-and-room-descriptions-4" class="anchor" href="#game-maps-and-room-descriptions-4"></a>Game Maps And Room Descriptions</h3>
<h2>
<a name="colorcyanfacility-map-color-5" class="anchor" href="#colorcyanfacility-map-color-5"></a><font color="Cyan">Facility Map </font>
</h2>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/7/c/7c822e381b8af84495663f517af2c12b1786a5f8.png" alt="Facilitiy Map" data-base62-sha1="hLs7fdZ9KkfcVhtTn1mtdSCUvVe" width="370" height="324"></p>
<details>
<summary>
Door Bay</summary>
<p>This is the main room where the doors await the ambidex game and everyone wakes up in.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Lobby</summary>
<p>Comfy looking lobby with a pair of couchs and a few tables with chairs setup with a carpet.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Cabin</summary>
<p>A simple navy style cabin that holds a thin layer of dust over it.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Kitchen</summary>
<p>Stocked kitchen with some nice food to pair with it mostly stainless steel.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Laundry Room</summary>
<p>Beat down room with old machinery and table to bat has a weird clicking sound.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Art Room</summary>
<p>Narrow room with some nice art to go to it though seems almost more like a hallway then a room though.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
???</summary>
<p>Wouldn’t you like to know.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Stroage Room</summary>
<p>Boxs scattered around the flooring with no real set order a tower of which has formed in the back corner</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Elevator Room</summary>
<p>Room with a pair of elevators</p>
</details>
<h3>
<a name="rules-6" class="anchor" href="#rules-6"></a>Rules</h3>
<p>Breaking any of the below will first give you a warning, and breaking them again will result in a force replacement or a modkill.</p>
<ol>
<li>Follow all Global Forum Rules</li>
<li>Do not discuss the game outside this thread or in your PM(s)</li>
<li>Do not copy and paste, directly quote, or screenshot anything sent by me.</li>
<li>Do not game throw, or go directly against your win condition.</li>
<li>Do not angleshoot.</li>
<li>Do not edit or delete any posts in the main thread or in any PMs.</li>
<li>Do your best to be active, doing actions and posting every phase, getting Ambidex actions in.</li>
<li>Mod has the right to add, change, or remove rules.</li>
</ol>
<h3>
<a name="signing-up-7" class="anchor" href="#signing-up-7"></a>Signing Up</h3>
<p>To sign up, do /in, /join, just express interest in joining in the thread.<br>
<strong>The hosts may or may not utilize WOTM to prohibit players from joining.</strong></p>
<p>1: EliThePsycho: 8<br>
2: DatBird: 8<br>
3: Amelia: 1<br>
4: Icibalus: 10<br>
5: Geyde: 1<br>
6: Aelin: 8<br>
7: Atlas: 1<br>
8: Apprentice: 10<br>
9: Wazza: 8<br>
10: Jane: 3<br>
11: Marluxion: 6<br>
12: <s>Silviu200530</s> Whysper: 8</p>
<p><strong>Back-Up</strong><br>
1: Whysper<br>
2: Nightingale<br>
3: thepigeonnyc<br>
4: WindwardAway</p>
<p><strong>Spec</strong><br>
1: Sulit<br>
2: Min</p>
            <p><small>2972 posts - 19 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 05:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88882</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>🔥 Cat Battle Royale ARCHIE WIN</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/7/4/744c43cf502f6abdda66f35d482d4c7d8956d8a7.png" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/744c43cf502f6abdda66f35d482d4c7d8956d8a7" title="image"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/4/744c43cf502f6abdda66f35d482d4c7d8956d8a7_2_690x82.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="gAOMz75LFKKNK8wB1jRoFjBtzwj" width="690" height="82" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/4/744c43cf502f6abdda66f35d482d4c7d8956d8a7_2_690x82.png, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/7/4/744c43cf502f6abdda66f35d482d4c7d8956d8a7.png 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/7/4/744c43cf502f6abdda66f35d482d4c7d8956d8a7.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/4/744c43cf502f6abdda66f35d482d4c7d8956d8a7_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">878×105 86.4 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<h2>
<a name="colororange-fire-rules-fire-color-1" class="anchor" href="#colororange-fire-rules-fire-color-1"></a><font color="orange"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> Rules <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> </font>
</h2>
<p>Follow Global Forum Rules</p>
<details>
<summary>
</summary>
<p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926" class="inline-onebox">Official Forum Game Rules</a></p>
<p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244" class="inline-onebox">Global Forum/Discord/Game/Meta Rules - Please Read First</a></p>
</details>
<h2>
<a name="colororange-fire-how-to-enter-fire-color-2" class="anchor" href="#colororange-fire-how-to-enter-fire-color-2"></a><font color="orange"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> How To Enter <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> </font>
</h2>
<p>Send katze and I a private message via the forums or discord containing a picture of your cat, your cat’s name, and a brief description of your cat.</p>
<h2>
<a name="colororange-fire-how-to-play-fire-color-3" class="anchor" href="#colororange-fire-how-to-play-fire-color-3"></a><font color="orange"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> How To Play <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> </font>
</h2>
<p>1: Send me cat.<br>
2: Get placed in cat bracket.<br>
3: Compete against other kitties in cat bracket.<br>
4: Profit (free cat pics).</p>
<p>Each “phase” will last 24 hours, in which anyone can vote on which cats advance in the bracket. After each 24 hours, the bracket will be updated based on votes, cats will be YEETED from the competition, and another phase will begin until there is A SINGLE CAT STANDING. (the best cat)</p>
<p>YOU DON’T HAVE TO BE IN THE GAME TO VOTE.</p>
<h2>
<a name="colororange-fire-faq-fire-color-4" class="anchor" href="#colororange-fire-faq-fire-color-4"></a><font color="orange"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> FAQ <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> </font>
</h2>
<p>Q: Can I submit a cat I don’t actually own?<br>
A: As long as it has a name and you have a picture of it (and you are willing to sacrifice it to the battle royale.) (Must have met cat in person)</p>
<p>Q: Can I vote even if I’m not in the game?<br>
A: Yes</p>
<p>Q: What kind of picture should I send?<br>
A: Any works</p>
<p>Q: Can I vote for my own cat?<br>
A: Sure.</p>
<p>Q: Can people in the competition vote and people who have been eliminated vote?<br>
A: Sure.</p>
<p>Q: This isn’t dangerous right?<br>
A: <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/butter.png?v=10" title=":butter:" class="emoji" alt=":butter:"></p>
<p>Q: Can I submit more than 1 cat?<br>
A: You may submit a maximum of 2 cats.</p>
<p>Q: Can I submit my cat that’s totally not my dog?<br>
A: Hm. Sure. (May the bracket be in your favor)</p>
<p>Q: if i drive down to florida and get a picture of katze can i submit it<br>
A: Yes</p>
<p>Q: can it be 2 pics of same cat<br>
A: if they have different names</p>
<h2>
<a name="colororange-fire-prize-fire-color-5" class="anchor" href="#colororange-fire-prize-fire-color-5"></a><font color="orange"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> Prize <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> </font>
</h2>
<p>Cat Champion Forum Title (1 Month)</p>
<h2>
<a name="colororange-fire-current-bracket-fire-color-6" class="anchor" href="#colororange-fire-current-bracket-fire-color-6"></a><font color="orange"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> Current Bracket <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=10" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> </font>
</h2>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/0/5/052b4c28ae4e33ad11a183d7b2806bdbc443bfbe.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/052b4c28ae4e33ad11a183d7b2806bdbc443bfbe" title="image"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/0/5/052b4c28ae4e33ad11a183d7b2806bdbc443bfbe_2_639x500.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="JJ9pylswGN9Zmd69rPaDdcPz7U" width="639" height="500" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/0/5/052b4c28ae4e33ad11a183d7b2806bdbc443bfbe_2_639x500.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/0/5/052b4c28ae4e33ad11a183d7b2806bdbc443bfbe_2_958x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/0/5/052b4c28ae4e33ad11a183d7b2806bdbc443bfbe_2_1278x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/0/5/052b4c28ae4e33ad11a183d7b2806bdbc443bfbe_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1317×1029 78 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<h1>
<a name="submissions-must-be-sent-by-date2021-08-17-time220000-timezoneamericaindianapolis-7" class="anchor" href="#submissions-must-be-sent-by-date2021-08-17-time220000-timezoneamericaindianapolis-7"></a>Submissions must be sent by <span data-date="2021-08-17" data-time="22:00:00" class="discourse-local-date" data-timezone="America/Indianapolis" data-email-preview="2021-08-18T02:00:00Z UTC">2021-08-18T02:00:00Z</span>
</h1>
            <p><small>378 posts - 30 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cat-battle-royale-archie-win/88856">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cat-battle-royale-archie-win/88856</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 01:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88856</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cat-battle-royale-archie-win/88856.rss">🔥 Cat Battle Royale ARCHIE WIN</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Ciconia FM: Thread 1 - Day 1</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[astand]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647" title="Ciconia FM"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_517x348.jpeg" alt="Ciconia FM" data-base62-sha1="3cyxMRacLAlBRykMY841LtDASqP" width="517" height="348" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_517x348.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Ciconia FM</span><span class="informations">719×485 145 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<h2>
<a name="ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-designed-and-hosted-by-astand-cohosted-by-kyodaz-1" class="anchor" href="#ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-designed-and-hosted-by-astand-cohosted-by-kyodaz-1"></a>Ciconia FM: When They Cry - designed and hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/astand">@astand</a>, cohosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/kyodaz">@KyoDaz</a>.</h2>
<p>Reviewer is <a class="mention" href="/u/osieorb18">@osieorb18</a>, alt mod is <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a>.</p>
<h2>
<a name="rules-2" class="anchor" href="#rules-2"></a>Rules:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow all <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Rules</a> and <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Official Forum Game Rules.</a>
</li>
<li>Make at least 15 game-related posts each day (unless day ends early). If you fail to meet this requirement, you might get replaced. For 0 posting in full game day I will force replace you without any questions.</li>
<li>Don’t edit posts. This includes quickediting for typos, just don’t do it.</li>
<li>Alt accounts are allowed. Tell me your identity privately and send an application to <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a> if you wish to play on an alt. You are allowed to speculate on identities of alt accounts.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="general-information-3" class="anchor" href="#general-information-3"></a>General information:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Closed setup.</li>
<li>The game will contain bastard and/or experimental mechanics. However, OP will never lie, your rolecard will never lie, and no flips will ever be false.</li>
<li>Days are 48 hours, nights are 24 hours.</li>
<li>Eliminations are majority + plurality. In case of a tie, elimination will be randed.</li>
<li>At EoD, votes made up to :59 mark will be accepted (but not at :00 mark).</li>
<li>It will not be announced if the game reaches MYLO/LYLO.</li>
<li>
<font color="007F46"><strong>Order of the Public Bath</strong></font> is uninformed majority and <font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order</strong></font> is informed minority.</li>
<li>
<font color="007F46"><strong>Order of the Public Bath’s</strong></font> win condition is: <em>Eliminate all members of the Ninth Prime Chivalric Order and all other possible threats to Order of the Public Bath.</em>
</li>
<li>
<font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order’s</strong></font> win condition is: <em>Achieve parity with the Order of the Public Bath and eliminate all other possible threats to Ninth Prime Chivalric Order.</em>
</li>
<li>Other win conditions may or may not exist.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="game-mechanics-4" class="anchor" href="#game-mechanics-4"></a>Game mechanics:</h2>
<ul>
<li>There are no conversions.</li>
<li>There may or may not be lost wolves.</li>
<li>Flavor/role claims are allowed <strong>at your own risk</strong>.</li>
<li>Flavor (character name, in-universe faction and kette) isn’t alignment indicative, but might be role indicative for some roles while being misleading or not role indicative for others.</li>
<li>
<font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order’s</strong></font> factional kill is assigned. Performing it doesn’t prevent using other night actions.</li>
<li>You can’t perform actions on N0 unless specified otherwise.</li>
<li>Deadline for submitting actions is one hour before the end of the phase (whether day or night).</li>
<li>If you have several different night (day) abilities, then you can use all of them during a single night (day), unless specified otherwise.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="example-rolecard-5" class="anchor" href="#example-rolecard-5"></a>Example rolecard:</h2>
<details>
<summary>
VT</summary>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb" title="Example Town"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_542x500.jpeg" alt="Example Town" data-base62-sha1="uHyLJtVz7IB36iLqG4A7faDiIKn" width="542" height="500" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_542x500.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_813x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Example Town</span><span class="informations">1018×939 268 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
</details>
<h2>
<a name="backups-6" class="anchor" href="#backups-6"></a>Backups:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Arctic</li>
<li>Prophylaxis</li>
<li>Whysper</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="theatergoers-7" class="anchor" href="#theatergoers-7"></a>Theatergoers:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Alice (uninformed)</li>
<li>Appelsiini (uninformed)</li>
<li>Arete (informed)</li>
<li>DatBird (uninformed)</li>
<li>Intensify (informed)</li>
<li>Jane (uninformed)</li>
<li>katze (informed)</li>
<li>Silviu200530 (uninformed)</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>6553 posts - 31 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-thread-1-day-1/88821">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-thread-1-day-1/88821</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88821</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-thread-1-day-1/88821.rss">Ciconia FM: Thread 1 - Day 1</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The lost setup - the remains of umineko fm iii</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightingale]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Forum Matches</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>some of you guys might remember that i put a lot of work into an umineko fm iii setup back in march-april before completely scrapping it and starting again</p>
<p>anyways, i think i have definitively moved on from it because frankly, the setup had a lot of flaws (tbh i think there were a lot of good ideas in there too! it just wouldnt meet my modern standards at all), so i have decided to c/p it from my notepad into this thread so you guys can look at it and see if theres like, any fundamental problems with my design style back then, whether ive already identified them or not</p>
<p>also some of you might find it cool</p>
<p><strong>disclaimer:</strong> i havent looked at this all in 4 months, im just copy-pasting it from my notepad, so the views on balance (or p much anything) contained in the following posts might not represent my current views<br>
nya</p>
<p>also yeah my art has gotten better lol</p>
<p>posts soon:tm:</p>
            <p><small>22 posts - 7 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-lost-setup-the-remains-of-umineko-fm-iii/88784">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-lost-setup-the-remains-of-umineko-fm-iii/88784</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 20:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88784</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-lost-setup-the-remains-of-umineko-fm-iii/88784.rss">The lost setup - the remains of umineko fm iii</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Ciconia FM: When They Cry - Signups (25/25) - Full</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[astand]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647" title="Ciconia FM"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_517x348.jpeg" alt="Ciconia FM" data-base62-sha1="3cyxMRacLAlBRykMY841LtDASqP" width="517" height="348" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_517x348.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/1/6/1671e7b6aee48e79ec524002f7385a1dd1d97647_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Ciconia FM</span><span class="informations">719×485 145 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<h2>
<a name="ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-designed-and-hosted-by-astand-cohosted-by-kyodaz-1" class="anchor" href="#ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-designed-and-hosted-by-astand-cohosted-by-kyodaz-1"></a>Ciconia FM: When They Cry - designed and hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/astand">@astand</a>, cohosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/kyodaz">@KyoDaz</a>.</h2>
<p>Reviewer is <a class="mention" href="/u/osieorb18">@osieorb18</a>, alt mod is <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a>.</p>
<h2>
<a name="rules-2" class="anchor" href="#rules-2"></a>Rules:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow all <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244">Global Rules</a> and <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Official Forum Game Rules.</a>
</li>
<li>Make at least 15 game-related posts each day (unless day ends early). If you fail to meet this requirement, you might get replaced. For 0 posting in full game day I will force replace you without any questions.</li>
<li>Don’t edit posts. This includes quickediting for typos, just don’t do it.</li>
<li>Alt accounts are allowed. Tell me your identity privately and send an application to <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a> if you wish to play on an alt. You are allowed to speculate on identities of alt accounts.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="general-information-3" class="anchor" href="#general-information-3"></a>General information:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Closed setup.</li>
<li>The game will contain bastard and/or experimental mechanics. However, OP will never lie, your rolecard will never lie, and no flips will ever be false.</li>
<li>Days are 48 hours, nights are 24 hours.</li>
<li>Eliminations are majority + plurality. In case of a tie, elimination will be randed.</li>
<li>At EoD, votes made up to :59 mark will be accepted (but not at :00 mark).</li>
<li>It will not be announced if the game reaches MYLO/LYLO.</li>
<li>
<font color="007F46"><strong>Order of the Public Bath</strong></font> is uninformed majority and <font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order</strong></font> is informed minority.</li>
<li>
<font color="007F46"><strong>Order of the Public Bath’s</strong></font> win condition is: <em>Eliminate all members of the Ninth Prime Chivalric Order and all other possible threats to Order of the Public Bath.</em>
</li>
<li>
<font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order’s</strong></font> win condition is: <em>Achieve parity with the Order of the Public Bath and eliminate all other possible threats to Ninth Prime Chivalric Order.</em>
</li>
<li>Other win conditions may or may not exist.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="game-mechanics-4" class="anchor" href="#game-mechanics-4"></a>Game mechanics:</h2>
<ul>
<li>There are no conversions.</li>
<li>There may or may not be lost wolves.</li>
<li>Flavor/role claims are allowed <strong>at your own risk</strong>.</li>
<li>Flavor (character name, in-universe faction and kette) isn’t alignment indicative, but might be role indicative for some roles while being misleading or not role indicative for others.</li>
<li>
<font color="CC000D"><strong>Ninth Prime Chivalric Order’s</strong></font> factional kill is assigned. Performing it doesn’t prevent using other night actions.</li>
<li>You can’t perform actions on N0 unless specified otherwise.</li>
<li>Deadline for submitting actions is one hour before the end of the phase (whether day or night).</li>
<li>If you have several different night (day) abilities, then you can use all of them during a single night (day), unless specified otherwise.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="example-rolecard-5" class="anchor" href="#example-rolecard-5"></a>Example rolecard:</h2>
<details>
<summary>
VT</summary>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb" title="Example Town"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_542x500.jpeg" alt="Example Town" data-base62-sha1="uHyLJtVz7IB36iLqG4A7faDiIKn" width="542" height="500" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_542x500.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_813x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/7/d72dcb54a3df448c0d964baeda780440116a0acb_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Example Town</span><span class="informations">1018×939 268 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
</details>
<h2>
<a name="sign-ups-6" class="anchor" href="#sign-ups-6"></a>Sign-ups:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Aelin</li>
<li>Alkali</li>
<li>Atlas</li>
<li>clonedcheese</li>
<li>EliThePsycho</li>
<li>Galena</li>
<li>Hippolytus</li>
<li>Icibalus</li>
<li>Liattac</li>
<li>Luxy</li>
<li>Marluxion</li>
<li>Marshal</li>
<li>min</li>
<li>Nightingale</li>
<li>PokemonKidRyan</li>
<li>Rue</li>
<li>Shurian</li>
<li>sulit</li>
<li>thepigeonnyc</li>
<li>Triplethree</li>
<li>Vulgard</li>
<li>Wazza</li>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
<li>YunoGasai</li>
<li>Zerokito</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="backups-7" class="anchor" href="#backups-7"></a>Backups:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Arctic</li>
<li>Prophylaxis</li>
<li>Whysper</li>
</ol>
<h2>
<a name="theatergoers-8" class="anchor" href="#theatergoers-8"></a>Theatergoers:</h2>
<ol>
<li>Alice (uninformed)</li>
<li>Appelsiini (uninformed)</li>
<li>Arete (informed)</li>
<li>DatBird (uninformed)</li>
<li>Intensify (informed)</li>
<li>Jane (uninformed)</li>
<li>katze (informed)</li>
<li>Silviu200530 (uninformed)</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>750 posts - 49 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-signups-25-25-full/88777">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-signups-25-25-full/88777</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 19:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88777</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ciconia-fm-when-they-cry-signups-25-25-full/88777.rss">Ciconia FM: When They Cry - Signups (25/25) - Full</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[MISC] [Signups] VLDR 3: Experiments at Work 12/12</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TrustworthyLiberal]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Signups</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="colorgreenvldr-3-experimentscolor-1" class="anchor" href="#colorgreenvldr-3-experimentscolor-1"></a><font color="Green">VLDR 3: Experiments</font>
</h1>
<p><font color="(color)">   </font></p>
<p>Hosted by TrustworthyLiberal<br>
Co-Host(s): Kyo, Solic</p>
<h1>
<a name="important-notes-2" class="anchor" href="#important-notes-2"></a>Important Notes</h1>
<p><strong>As a notice this game will run Wed through Saturday and be on pause sunday through Tusday.</strong><br>
<strong>The hosts may or may not utilize WOTM to prohibit players from joining.</strong><br>
In addition i am looking for 1/2 co-hosts to make action processing as smooth as possible</p>
<p>Hope to start on Wednesday Augest 18th maw allow disscusion to start slightly before this time.<br>
Likely close this thread sometime before that to rand roles and allow any questions to form.</p>
<h3>
<a name="how-to-play-3" class="anchor" href="#how-to-play-3"></a>How to Play</h3>
<p>The game will shift through three cycles, Discussion, Roaming, and Ambidex, until it is over. Note that this game is complex and has many elements and factors. Please read all of the below before signing up.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Discussion</summary>
<p>During Discussion all players can speak in the main thread. All players will be in the same room, so actions can be performed on other players during this time. You can also choose to end Discussion early by leaving the room. After you have left you can no longer talk in the main thread, and players can no longer perform actions on you.</p>
<p>Discussion will last for 24 hours, or until 3/4 of the total players have left the room.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Roaming</summary>
<p>During roaming all players can move about and perform actions, search for items, attack other players, and explore in a pre-made map via PMs. If two or more people are in the same place they will be added to a PM in which they can talk privately.</p>
<p>There will likely be different puzzles you can solve to get better and upgraded gear and to unlock other areas of the map.</p>
<p>Roaming lasts 48 hours or until all players say in their PM that they would like Roaming to end.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Ambidex</summary>
<p>During Ambidex all players will return to the room Discussion takes place. However, no actions can be performed at this time. Players will publicly vote on 1 of 3 lists that say which players will be paired with whom during the Ambidex Games.</p>
<p>After pairings have been voted on, the main thread will be closed and all players must decide whether to ally or betray their partner in their PM. If a player doesn’t cast a vote they will ally by default. If both partners don’t cast a vote they will both betray by default.</p>
<p><strong>Ally vs. Ally:</strong> Both players gain 2 Ambidex Points.<br>
<strong>Ally vs. Betray:</strong> The person who allied will lose 3 points, and the betrayer will gain 4.<br>
<strong>Betray vs. Betray:</strong> Both players will earn zero Amdidex Points.</p>
<p>Ambidex Phase will last 48 hours, 24 for voting, 24 to submit Ally or Betray.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Stats</summary>
<p>If an action a player performs has a chance to fail, a 1d20 will be rolled with discobot. Depending on the action, the player will have one or more of their stats added to the roll. This will determine how successful it is. There are five different stats that can be applied to actions.</p>
<p><strong>Strength (STR):</strong> Lifting or pushing heavy things, pulling things, attacking with melee-based weapons, etc.<br>
<strong>Precision (PRC):</strong> Throwing items, attacking with ranged weapons, doing actions with items that are hard to maneuver, etc.<br>
<strong>Endurance (END):</strong> How much hits you can, how much you can withstand harmful effects, etc.<br>
<strong>Intelligence (INT):</strong> Searching rooms, gaining information, healing, building things, etc.<br>
<strong>Agility (AGI):</strong> Dodging hits, running, attacking with melee weapons, etc.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Inventory and Items</summary>
<p>During the game, players may find useful items they want to keep with them, or take them from other players.</p>
<p>Players have a limited inventory space. They have 5 public inventory slots that can be seen by anyone looking into their inventory, and 1 private slot that no one can see unless the player is unconscious or specifically shows it to someone.</p>
<p>In addition, some players may start with an addition private role slot, in which a role item can be stored.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Roles</summary>
<p>Before the game starts, players will be assigned a role via PM. Roles will dictate unique abilities, stats, your alignment, and your win condition. Roles are custom.</p>
<p>Claiming anything on your rolecard is allowed. Players can make fake rolecards, abilities, stats, alignments or wincons. Speculating on the above is also allowed.</p>
<p>The four alignments are Good, Evil, Wildcard and Neutral.</p>
<p><strong>Good</strong> players need to help others, and help as many people escape as possible.<br>
<strong>Neutral</strong> players need to escape at all costs, and may have other side goals.<br>
<strong>Wildcard</strong> players have a more flexible win condition and can end up being any of the other three alignments.<br>
<strong>Evil</strong> players are there to sabotage others, cause chaos, and cause conflict and potentially death.<br>
There is no role list.</p>
<p><strong>Roles and alignments will not be flipped upon death.</strong></p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Actions</summary>
<p>Players submit actions to the moderator in order to interact with other players and the map. These can be anything; picking up an item, punching another player, doing a backflip, investigate a part of the room.</p>
<p>To perform an action, type <strong>/action,</strong> for example <strong>/Investigate the Couches.</strong> Actions can be submitted in your PM, in chats with other players, or in the main thread during discussion. You can submit actions anytime except during the Ambidex phase.</p>
<p>Players can set automatic actions for when they are AFK in case something happens to them while they are gone. If they have nothing set I will generally do something for them. <em>I’m not just going to let someone get stabbed because they were AFK</em>.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Combat</summary>
<p>All weapons will have a certain damage amount. When a player attacks another, I will take the weapons damage amount and add it to the attacks strength. For example, if a player with a strength stat of 4 attacks a player with a weapon that does four damage, they will do eight damage.</p>
<p>If a player attempts to dodge an attack I will roll a 1d20 and choose a number depending on how the player is attacked. If the number rolled is more than that number the player will successfully dodge.</p>
<p>I am flexible processing combat actions and might award more damage points for creativity.</p>
<p>Health is calculated by 20+(5*END stat). If a player takes more damage than this they will be knocked out. If a player is hit after that they will die.</p>
<p>Medical items will have a flat healing amount, and extra healing will be added on by the INT stat*2.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Ambidex Points and Winning</summary>
<p>Every player will start with 4 Ambidex Points. Ambidex Point totals will be visible at all times in the OP. If a player ever has less than one Ambidex Point they will immediately die.</p>
<p>If a player has more than or equal to 11 Ambidex Points, they can access the Door Number 11 that is located in the map. When the door is opened, it will remain open for 11 seconds, then it will close forever and the game will end. Only players with 11 points or more can exit the door.</p>
<p><strong>The Ambidex Game is the only way to earn Ambidex Points, and the Door Number 11 is the only way to escape.</strong></p>
</details>
<h3>
<a name="game-maps-and-room-descriptions-4" class="anchor" href="#game-maps-and-room-descriptions-4"></a>Game Maps And Room Descriptions</h3>
<h2>
<a name="colorcyanfacility-map-color-5" class="anchor" href="#colorcyanfacility-map-color-5"></a><font color="Cyan">Facility Map </font>
</h2>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/7/c/7c822e381b8af84495663f517af2c12b1786a5f8.png" alt="Facilitiy Map" data-base62-sha1="hLs7fdZ9KkfcVhtTn1mtdSCUvVe" width="370" height="324"></p>
<p>Room Descriptions will be added here on game start as well as updates as more areas become open.</p>
<h3>
<a name="rules-6" class="anchor" href="#rules-6"></a>Rules</h3>
<p>Breaking any of the below will first give you a warning, and breaking them again will result in a force replacement or a modkill.</p>
<ol>
<li>Follow all Global Forum Rules</li>
<li>Do not discuss the game outside this thread or in your PM(s)</li>
<li>Do not copy and paste, directly quote, or screenshot anything sent by me.</li>
<li>Do not game throw, or go directly against your win condition.</li>
<li>Do not angleshoot.</li>
<li>Do not edit or delete any posts in the main thread or in any PMs.</li>
<li>Do your best to be active, doing actions and posting every phase, getting Ambidex actions in.</li>
<li>Mod has the right to add, change, or remove rules.</li>
</ol>
<h3>
<a name="signing-up-7" class="anchor" href="#signing-up-7"></a>Signing Up</h3>
<p>To sign up, do /in, /join, just express interest in joining in the thread.<br>
<strong>The hosts may or may not utilize WOTM to prohibit players from joining.</strong></p>
<p>1: <a class="mention" href="/u/elithepsycho">@EliThePsycho</a><br>
2: <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a><br>
3: <a class="mention" href="/u/amelia">@Amelia</a><br>
4: <a class="mention" href="/u/icibalus">@Icibalus</a><br>
5: <a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a><br>
6: <a class="mention" href="/u/aelin">@Aelin</a><br>
7: <a class="mention" href="/u/atlas">@Atlas</a><br>
8: <a class="mention" href="/u/apprentice">@Apprentice</a><br>
9: <a class="mention" href="/u/wazza">@Wazza</a><br>
10: Jane<br>
11: Marluxion<br>
12: Silviu200530</p>
<p><strong>Back-Up</strong><br>
1: Whysper<br>
2: Nightingale<br>
3: thepigeonnyc<br>
4: WindwardAway</p>
<p><strong>Spec</strong><br>
1: Sulit<br>
2: Min</p>
            <p><small>247 posts - 34 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-signups-vldr-3-experiments-at-work-12-12/88763">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-signups-vldr-3-experiments-at-work-12-12/88763</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 20:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88763</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-signups-vldr-3-experiments-at-work-12-12/88763.rss">[MISC] [Signups] VLDR 3: Experiments at Work 12/12</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>BotC / BotF Discussion</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>  </p>
            <p><small>178 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botc-botf-discussion/88754">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botc-botf-discussion/88754</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88754</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botc-botf-discussion/88754.rss">BotC / BotF Discussion</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Interest Check: Life of the Party</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would people join a misc with 3d inspection mechanics and like actual distance consideration for things like throwing and also hopefully lighting mechanics additionally on the inspection mechanics so when the lights are off the actual image is dimmed too<br>
I’ve designed two rooms so far and just want to see what people think before I actually commit to making a mansion in 3d<br>
They’re definitely not pretty and the main hall is subject to change but meh w/e it’s just a preview<br>
Current plan is to have “heretics” run around the mansion with secret passages and other players (the partygoers) to try and find a way out or otherwise defeat the heretics in some way</p>
<p>                    <a href="https://i.imgur.com/ZRQZXNv.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://i.imgur.com/ZRQZXNv.png" width="690" height="381">
          </a>

</p>
<p>If the player closer inspects the bookshelves:</p>
<p>                    <a href="https://i.imgur.com/ovTfPsP.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://i.imgur.com/ovTfPsP.png" width="690" height="381">
          </a>

</p>
            <p><small>37 posts - 16 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-life-of-the-party/88737">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-life-of-the-party/88737</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 18:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88737</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-life-of-the-party/88737.rss">Interest Check: Life of the Party</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>PJO FM - 3/13 - Demigods (Town) Wins!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aelin]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>
<a name="percy-jackson-fm-1" class="anchor" href="#percy-jackson-fm-1"></a>Percy Jackson FM</h2>
<p>Hosted by <a class="mention" href="/u/aelin">@Aelin</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/mistyx">@Mistyx</a> and reviewed by <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a></p>
<h2>
<a name="image396x500upload9xtgacfqxkir8qbb0ricqmfvf3gjpeg-game-info-2" class="anchor" href="#image396x500upload9xtgacfqxkir8qbb0ricqmfvf3gjpeg-game-info-2"></a><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/4/2/42dc3098ec56bfdcb14fcb2cdbefb1851998d106.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/42dc3098ec56bfdcb14fcb2cdbefb1851998d106" title="image"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/4/2/42dc3098ec56bfdcb14fcb2cdbefb1851998d106_2_396x500.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="9xtgACFQXkIr8QBB0rICQMFvF3g" width="396" height="500" srcset="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/4/2/42dc3098ec56bfdcb14fcb2cdbefb1851998d106_2_396x500.jpeg, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/4/2/42dc3098ec56bfdcb14fcb2cdbefb1851998d106.jpeg 1.5x, https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/4/2/42dc3098ec56bfdcb14fcb2cdbefb1851998d106.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/4/2/42dc3098ec56bfdcb14fcb2cdbefb1851998d106_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">558×704 137 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div>
<br>
Game Info</h2>
<ul>
<li>Game Size: 13</li>
<li>Game Speed: Days: 48/24</li>
<li>Game Type: Special - Rolemadness</li>
<li>This game has bastard mechanics. However, the OP and your rolecard will not lie to you.</li>
<li>There may or may not be anti-claim mechanics in place.</li>
<li>There is a D1 Start and a D1 Execute. Executions are both Plurality and Majority.</li>
<li>Days are 48 hours and Nights are 24 hours. Actions will lock one hour before EoN. Night may be skipped if all living players with applicable abilities vote to skip the night.</li>
<li>MyLo/LyLo will be announced.</li>
<li>The Titans have a 24/7 scumchat, and the nightkill is mandatory and assignable.</li>
<li>This is a closed game. However, you are aware of the fact that there are ten town members and three scum members.</li>
<li>Scum do get fakeclaims.</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<a name="game-rules-3" class="anchor" href="#game-rules-3"></a>Game Rules</h2>
<ul>
<li>Follow the General Forum Rules, linked here - <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/global-forum-discord-game-meta-rules-please-read-first/244" class="inline-onebox">Global Forum/Discord/Game/Meta Rules - Please Read First</a>, as well as the Forum Mafia Rules, linked here - <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926" class="inline-onebox">Official Forum Game Rules</a>
</li>
<li>Alts are not allowed in this game.</li>
<li>Actions are done by messaging in your rolecard. Questions may be asked in your rolecard.</li>
<li>Last wills/logs are not present in the game.</li>
<li>Votes must be done in the format of <strong>/vote [PLAYER NAME]</strong> <a class="mention" href="/u/aelin">@Aelin</a> and any applicable cohosts or vc-bots, and unvotes must be done in the format of <strong>/unvote</strong> <a class="mention" href="/u/aelin">@Aelin</a>. If this is not followed, your vote will not be considered valid. This is to make it easier on me, thank you for understanding.</li>
<li>No-elimination is not a valid vote.</li>
<li>Players should post at least 20 on-topic posts per day. If a player fails to meet this, they will first be prodded, and then either force-replaced or modkilled.</li>
<li>Excessive AtE is heavily frowned upon.</li>
</ul>
<p>Limited Rolelist:</p>
<p><font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Titan</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Titan</strong></font><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Titan</strong></font></p>
<details>
<summary>
Example Rolecards (These flavors are not in the game)</summary>
<blockquote>
<p><strong><font color="gree">Travis Stoll</font></strong><br>
<em>Son of Hermes</em></p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/0/a/0ab7ba2c01f70d3a438074647e1e86abd172a956.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="1wOpke6OS04FWzDfLIWI6YUokya" width="200" height="200"></p>
<p><em><font color="gree"><strong>Demigod</strong></font> - Offensive</em></p>
<p><strong>Night: Up To No Good</strong> - Pick a player and… <em>watch over them</em> for the night. See who visits them and who they visit. (2 Uses)</p>
<p><font color="gree"><em><strong>Defeat the Titans.</strong></em></font></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong><font color="red">Oceanus</font></strong></p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/a/5/a5814302224c61c37bac15a7f599b85be6e3a54a.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="nC7IVy9E6wJlI7b4jEjuKkyCBUS" width="201" height="251"></p>
<p><em><font color="red"><strong>Titan</strong></font> - Support</em></p>
<p><strong>Day: Mist</strong> - Cover all titans in a thin layer of mist, causing all alignment checks on them tonight to return as ‘Demigod’ for the night. (2 Uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night: Fraternizing</strong> - Choose a player and add them to a neighborhood. (2 Uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night: High Tide</strong> -  Prevent all visits to you tonight. Abilities used on you will still take up a Use. (3 Uses)</p>
<p><font color="red"><em><strong>Reach parity with the Demigods.</strong></em></font></p>
</blockquote>
</details>
<p>Win Conditions:</p>
<p>Demigods: <font color="gree"><em><strong>Defeat the Titans.</strong></em></font><br>
Titans: <font color="red"><em><strong>Reach parity with the Demigods.</strong></em></font></p>
<p>Players:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<s>EliThePsycho</s> - <strong>Executed D2</strong> - <strong><font color="gree">Katie Gardner</font></strong>
</li>
<li>
<s>clonedcheese</s> - <strong>Died N1</strong> - <font color="gree"><strong>Annabeth Chase</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>Emilia</s> → WindwardAway</li>
<li>
<s>Wazza</s> - <strong>Died N2</strong> - <font color="gree"><strong>Percy Jackson</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>Silviu</s> - <strong>Died N4</strong> - <font color="gree"><strong>Jason Grace</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>Zone</s> - <strong>Died N2</strong> - <font color="red"><strong>Kronos</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>Luxy</s> - <strong>Executed D3</strong> - <font color="gree"><strong>Reyna Ramirez-Arellano</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>thepigeonnyc</s> - <strong>Executed D1</strong> - <font color="gree"><strong>Hazel Levesque</strong></font>
</li>
<li>
<s>Nightingale</s> - <strong>Executed D4</strong> - <font color="red"><strong>Koios</strong></font>
</li>
<li>Jane</li>
<li>
<s>min</s> - <strong>Died Night 3</strong> - <font color="gree"><strong>Will Solace</strong></font>
</li>
<li>gorta</li>
<li>Marluxion</li>
</ol>
<p>Backups:</p>
<ol>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
<li>Wazza</li>
</ol>
<p>Spectators:</p>
<ol>
<li>Marshal (Uninformed)</li>
<li>Chloe (Uninformed)</li>
<li>sulit (Uninformed)</li>
<li>astand (Informed)</li>
<li>katze (Uninformed)</li>
<li>Intensify (Informed)</li>
<li>DatBird (Informed)</li>
<li>KyoDaz (Uninformed)</li>
<li>Arete (Informed)</li>
<li>Whysper (Uninformed)</li>
<li>Arctic (Uninformed)</li>
<li>A very cute girl (Informed)</li>
</ol>
<p>Threadlinks:<br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pjo-fm-day-2-11-13/88703/1582" class="inline-onebox">PJO FM - 3/13 - Demigods (Town) Wins! - #1582 by Aelin</a> - EoD1/EoN1<br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pjo-fm-night-2-10-13/88703/2661" class="inline-onebox">PJO FM - 3/13 - Demigods (Town) Wins! - #2661 by Aelin</a> - EoD2<br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pjo-fm-day-3-8-13/88703/3104" class="inline-onebox">PJO FM - 3/13 - Demigods (Town) Wins! - #3104 by Aelin</a> - EoD3<br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pjo-fm-night-4-5-13/88703/3305" class="inline-onebox">PJO FM - 3/13 - Demigods (Town) Wins! - #3305 by Aelin</a> - EoD4</p>
            <p><small>3900 posts - 31 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pjo-fm-3-13-demigods-town-wins/88703">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pjo-fm-3-13-demigods-town-wins/88703</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 12:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88703</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pjo-fm-3-13-demigods-town-wins/88703.rss">PJO FM - 3/13 - Demigods (Town) Wins!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Completed</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="88559">
  <div class="title">
    <div class="quote-controls"></div>
    <img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/amelia/40/41779_2.png" class="avatar">
    <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-signups-15-15-game-will-start-soon/88559">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Signups (15/15) - Game will start soon</a> <a class="badge-wrapper  bullet" href="/c/forum-matches/fol-signups/17"><span class="badge-category-parent-bg" style="background-color: #BF1E2E;"></span><span class="badge-category-bg" style="background-color: #BF1E2E;"></span><span style="" data-drop-close="true" class="badge-category clear-badge" title="Signups to the Forum Games.">Signups</span></a>
  </div>
  <blockquote>
    Well now, welcome to the ninth game of Blood on the Forums, hosted by me, myself and I, Amelia. This time, we seem to be invaded by a peculiar sort of foe, infiltration from inside the Town itself! Also we seem to be harboring a princess from another realm as well. 
<details><summary>Character List</summary>This game will be running an entirely custom script, this time with a few new characters, some of whom may strike fear into a player’s heart, while others bring a saving grace to the ailed Damsel or dying out town. Old …</details>
  </blockquote>
</aside>

<h2>
<a name="threadmarks-1" class="anchor" href="#threadmarks-1"></a>Threadmarks</h2>
<p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-night-1-15-15/88620/2">Night One Begins  - 15/15 Alive</a></p>
<p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/1883">Day One ends with Gorta being executed and dies</a></p>
<p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/1886">Night Two has ended with Leafia found dead in the night</a></p>
<h2>
<a name="nomination-history-2" class="anchor" href="#nomination-history-2"></a>Nomination History</h2>
<details>
<summary>
Day One</summary>
<ol>
<li>Zone_Q11 nominates thepigeonnyc</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>
<details>
<summary>
Zone_Q11's Accusation</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zone_Q11" data-post="261" data-topic="88620">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/zone_q11/40/36658_2.png" class="avatar"> Zone_Q11:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Down with the slankers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
thepigeonnyc's Defence</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="thepigeonnyc" data-post="330" data-topic="88620" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/thepigeonnyc/40/41028_2.png" class="avatar"> thepigeonnyc:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have literally no reason not to open claim.</p>
<p>King here!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</details>
</blockquote>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>Cloned Cheese has nominated Zone_Q11<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/351" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #351 by clonedcheese</a><br>
Defence: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/363" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #363 by Zone_Q11</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Intensify has nominated SkyRed/Jane.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/442" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #442 by Intensify</a><br>
Defence: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/451" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #451 by SkyRED</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Nuclear_Rehab has nominated An_Gorta_Pratai.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/638" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #638 by Nuclear_Rehab</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/642" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #642 by Nuclear_Rehab</a><br>
Defence: Not applicable.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Atlas has nominated Nuclear_Rehab,<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/662" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #662 by Atlas</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/663" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #663 by Atlas</a><br>
Defence: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/673" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #673 by Nuclear_Rehab</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Leafia nominates Nightingale.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/554" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #554 by Leafia</a><br>
Defence: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/580" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #580 by Nightingale</a><br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/581" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #581 by Nightingale</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Day Two</summary>
<ol>
<li>thepigeonnyc has nominated Zone_Q11.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/2452" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #2452 by thepigeonnyc</a><br>
Defence:</li>
</ol>
<p>2, Nightingale has nominated ElithePsycho.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/2464" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #2464 by Nightingale</a><br>
Defence:</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<p>Wazza has nominated Intensify.<br>
Accusation:<br>
Defence:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Leafia has nominated Nightingale.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/2477" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #2477 by Leafia</a><br>
Defence:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Zone_Q11 has nominated Jane.<br>
Accusation:  <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/2753" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #2753 by Zone_Q11</a><br>
Defence:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Atlas has nominated Nightingale.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/2770" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #2770 by Atlas</a><br>
Defence:</p>
</li>
</ol>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Day Three</summary>
</details>
<h2>
<a name="exile-history-3" class="anchor" href="#exile-history-3"></a>Exile History</h2>
<details>
<summary>
Day One</summary>
<ol>
<li>ElithePsycho has called for the exile of Apprentice.<br>
Accusation: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/852" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #852 by EliThePsycho</a><br>
Defence: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/854" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #854 by Apprentice</a>
</li>
</ol>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Day Two</summary>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Eli has called for the exile of Wazza.<br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/2619" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #2619 by EliThePsycho</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>PokemonKidRyan has called for the exile of Apprentice.<br>
<a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-day-2-15-17/88620/3065" class="inline-onebox">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins - #3065 by PokemonKidRyan</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Day Three</summary>
</details>
<h2>
<a name="voting-history-4" class="anchor" href="#voting-history-4"></a>Voting History</h2>
<details>
<summary>
Day One</summary>
<p>an_Gorta_pratai - 11 execute votes and executed.<br>
Nuclear_Rehab - 1 execute vote and 6 pardon votes.<br>
SkyRed - 0 execute votes and 7 pardon votes.<br>
thepigeonnyc - 0 execute votes and 7 pardon votes.<br>
Zone_Q11 - 2 execute votes and 6 pardon votes.<br>
Nightingale - 3 execute votes and 3 pardon votes.<br>
Apprentice - 0 votes for exile.</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Day Two</summary>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Day Three</summary>
</details>
<h2>
<a name="seating-order-5" class="anchor" href="#seating-order-5"></a>Seating Order</h2>
<ol>
<li>Silviu200530</li>
<li>Nuclear_Rehab</li>
<li>clonedcheese</li>
<li>
<s>SkyRED</s> Jane</li>
<li>an_gorta_pratai</li>
<li>thepigeonnyc</li>
<li>Atlas</li>
<li>EliThePsycho</li>
<li>YoubutWorse</li>
<li>
<s>Tangeld</s> Whysper</li>
<li>Zone_Q11</li>
<li>Leafia</li>
<li>PokemonKidRyan</li>
<li>Nightingale</li>
<li>Intensify</li>
<li>
<font color="steblue">Appre</font><font color="red">ntice</font> (Beggar) (Traveled Away d3)</li>
<li>
<font color="steblue">Waz</font><font color="red">za</font> (Scapegoat)</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>5830 posts - 30 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-evil-wins/88620">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-evil-wins/88620</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 16:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88620</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botf-ix-call-for-distress-evil-wins/88620.rss">BotF IX - Call for Distress - Evil wins</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
