<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Suggestion] CW Buff, Give Call the Dead Passive</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316</link>
    <description>It&#39;s always been my opinion that Court Wizard is a week class, and needs a bit more something to really be able to make their mark on the game. My idea for how to do this is to give them the same passive as the Psychic, Call the Dead (only perhaps renamed to be more about magic, but that&#39;s really neither here nor there).

This is especially relevant now that Death Knight is going to be removed from the game in the latest patch. A big risk of this is that as a result, if there&#39;s no Psychic in the game, nobody has any real reason to stick around in dead chat and might as well leave as soon as they&#39;re killed if there&#39;s no Psychic.

Giving the CW the same passive completely changes things in that regard. If CW can also see and interact with dead chat at night, that makes it that much more likely that there&#39;s at least 1 BD class that can talk with chat (as neither Psychic or CW are guaranteed spawns, but if both have it, that increases the chances that there&#39;s at least 1 BD by just that much), giving people that much more reason to stick around even though DK&#39;s not a thing anymore. 

In addition, even with CW having the same passive, CW and Psychic will still very much be distinct classes. Psychic will still have Link Minds/Private Matters/Telepathy whereas CW wouldn&#39;t and likewise CW has Tornado and Barrier, so they still play completely differently outside of that and would thus use the passive itself in similar but distinct ways (with Psychic confirming given info to others w/Telepathy and CW combining the info they get with Tornado/Barrier to help more effectively protect players they believe are at risk). The main point is just to have one more BD chat that talk with chat even if Psychic doesn&#39;t spawn/is dead, giving people reason to stick around.

That and the other purpose of course being to give CW a much needed buff, one of the very few classes that needs one IMO. This seems to be a good, balanced way of accomplishing all of those goals. That&#39;s my take anyway.

Thank you to anyone and everyone who takes the time to read this and have a great day! ^__^</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 03:00:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] CW Buff, Give Call the Dead Passive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually I’d give CW reanimate as a day ability. Talking to the dead makes him, other CW’s and the Psychic auto confirmed to each other.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40316-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316.rss">[Suggestion] CW Buff, Give Call the Dead Passive</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] CW Buff, Give Call the Dead Passive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then with up to 2 CW and 1 Psychic, this means you can have the dead confirm you both, which is not how it should be done frankly, but I will agree that CW should get a nice day ability for a buff</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40316-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316.rss">[Suggestion] CW Buff, Give Call the Dead Passive</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] CW Buff, Give Call the Dead Passive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShironRS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s always been my opinion that Court Wizard is a week class, and needs a bit more something to really be able to make their mark on the game. My idea for how to do this is to give them the same passive as the Psychic, Call the Dead (only perhaps renamed to be more about magic, but that’s really neither here nor there).</p>
<p>This is especially relevant now that Death Knight is going to be removed from the game in the latest patch. A big risk of this is that as a result, if there’s no Psychic in the game, nobody has any real reason to stick around in dead chat and might as well leave as soon as they’re killed if there’s no Psychic.</p>
<p>Giving the CW the same passive completely changes things in that regard. If CW can also see and interact with dead chat at night, that makes it that much more likely that there’s at least 1 BD class that can talk with chat (as neither Psychic or CW are guaranteed spawns, but if both have it, that increases the chances that there’s at least 1 BD by just that much), giving people that much more reason to stick around even though DK’s not a thing anymore.</p>
<p>In addition, even with CW having the same passive, CW and Psychic will still very much be distinct classes. Psychic will still have Link Minds/Private Matters/Telepathy whereas CW wouldn’t and likewise CW has Tornado and Barrier, so they still play completely differently outside of that and would thus use the passive itself in similar but distinct ways (with Psychic confirming given info to others w/Telepathy and CW combining the info they get with Tornado/Barrier to help more effectively protect players they believe are at risk). The main point is just to have one more BD chat that talk with chat even if Psychic doesn’t spawn/is dead, giving people reason to stick around.</p>
<p>That and the other purpose of course being to give CW a much needed buff, one of the very few classes that needs one IMO. This seems to be a good, balanced way of accomplishing all of those goals. That’s my take anyway.</p>
<p>Thank you to anyone and everyone who takes the time to read this and have a great day! <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 02:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40316-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-cw-buff-give-call-the-dead-passive/40316.rss">[Suggestion] CW Buff, Give Call the Dead Passive</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
