<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Allow Veterans to play with New Player Class Restrictions</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-veterans-to-play-with-new-player-class-restrictions/49897</link>
    <description>Further explanation in case the title wasn&#39;t clear - We all know that new players are restricted from getting some of the more important roles (King, Prince, MM, and CL). I think it would be nice if there was a toggle button in the options menu that allowed you to turn these restrictions on, even once you are no longer considered a new player. There are times where I really want to play TOL, but don&#39;t feel like playing a super important role, so this would definitely get me to play the game more.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 05:03:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-veterans-to-play-with-new-player-class-restrictions/49897.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Allow Veterans to play with New Player Class Restrictions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mojojojo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Further explanation in case the title wasn’t clear - We all know that new players are restricted from getting some of the more important roles (King, Prince, MM, and CL). I think it would be nice if there was a toggle button in the options menu that allowed you to turn these restrictions on, even once you are no longer considered a new player. There are times where I really want to play TOL, but don’t feel like playing a super important role, so this would definitely get me to play the game more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-veterans-to-play-with-new-player-class-restrictions/49897/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-veterans-to-play-with-new-player-class-restrictions/49897/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 05:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-49897-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-veterans-to-play-with-new-player-class-restrictions/49897.rss">Allow Veterans to play with New Player Class Restrictions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
