<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>improving MVP system</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603</link>
    <description>i have some ideas to replace the mvp system, make it so your actions in the game and performance give u points and the persons with the highest amount of point will get the mvp. u should get points for winning obviously, points for surviving the game while winning, points for succesfully performing ur night ability: like healing a as phys bonus when player is bd retracted if player is nk/cult/unseen, aiding as CW, occuping evil as butler/drunk, jailing evil as prince, protecting BD/killing evil as knight, finding unseen/cult as sheriff warp an invest class as apostle  ect. also points should be given to people who accuse and vote exe on players whom are members from the opposite party. points should be retracted when: u accuse and execute people from ur own party, u kill BD as knight/prince, butler. aiding evil as unseen, pardon members of the opposite party. instead of voting the 3 best people each player should be able to give someone +1 and -1 point. u get the point. this is by no means worked out and need to be designed for each class individually. but this way people get rated based on there actions in game and not by popularity or bc he&#39;s prince/mystic/alch and survived the game. if this system get implemented and works properly u could also implement a ladder system so u play again evenly skilled players. but this is just a thought and would probably be to hard to implement and take to much time and resources from the devs.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 17:07:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>improving MVP system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bit too complicated</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 17:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72603-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603.rss">improving MVP system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>improving MVP system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="4" data-topic="72603">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually you can just use win/loss, and you <em>should</em> just use win/loss.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well I am talking about for a ranked system… which while I agree, it’s impossible to do right and ranked probably should never be done. It’s impossible to do fairly in social deduction games in general, and conversion makes the impossible, well ridiculously impossible.</p>
<p>but if it is eventually going to be done no matter what, and the goal is to do the best possible job at an impossible task. it will need as many factors as possible on top of win loss. so I would say it would have to try and use both actions and mvp votes to some degree. All the metrics obviously have something hugely broken with them.</p>
<p>MVP - Corruption, players intentionally conspiring to boost eachother regardless of the game outcome. Also of course no one is able to fully realize the intricacies of everyone’s plays, the game winning move may have been something so subtle nobody noticed it except the person doing it.</p>
<p>Win-Loss - Conversion means you often play yourself (You make BD win, then get sent to the side you doomed), or the opposite - you suck, oh but you happened to have joined the other side and can crush the team that you completely let down the whole game. and of course no matter what, 9/10 times you are only a small part of the impact no matter what. Generally speaking in social deduction games, the higher the skill level the more often the majority faction wins, because people improve at lie detection at a faster rate than convincingly lying, unfortunately that also means, the higher you are ranked, the more you will win with the majority faction, the lower ranked you are the more often you will lose with the majority faction.</p>
<p>Action based - Actions are 80% luck, who you check, who you block etc… is more or less somewhere between a wild guess and a solid hunch, if you were fully certain from the scumread that made you do something, you’d have executed him in the day.</p>
<p>So yes if you were trying to make a working ranking system (something I still believe is impossible), you’d need to use all flawed methods and try and make them counteract eachother</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 15:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72603-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603.rss">improving MVP system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>improving MVP system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually you can just use win/loss, and you <em>should</em> just use win/loss.</p>
<p>In this case, it doesn’t work because you can’t rank a social deduction game in a truly meaningful manner.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 14:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72603-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603.rss">improving MVP system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>improving MVP system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s pro’s and cons to both systems. The biggets flaw IMO is that the game is won and lost in day chat. You can be an amazing sheriff, and hit unseen 3 nights in a row… But if you can’t convince the BD to actually execute you are nothing.</p>
<p>Likewise you can be a brilliant CW and figure everything out by reading people’s logs, and convey that information out, basically carrying the game for BD without having a single meaningful use of your night actions.</p>
<p>I do however think a system similar to what you propose would be necessary for ranking if a ranked mode ever came out. you can’t trust humans to judge things for ranking, yet you also can’t use a win/loss ratio by itself without creating unfair elo hell scenerios.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 12:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72603-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603.rss">improving MVP system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>improving MVP system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NAOtheRitualist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Too complicated but</p>
<p><strong>/s</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72603-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603.rss">improving MVP system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>improving MVP system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BBgunners]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i have some ideas to replace the mvp system, make it so your actions in the game and performance give u points and the persons with the highest amount of point will get the mvp. u should get points for winning obviously, points for surviving the game while winning, points for succesfully performing ur night ability: like healing a as phys bonus when player is bd retracted if player is nk/cult/unseen, aiding as CW, occuping evil as butler/drunk, jailing evil as prince, protecting BD/killing evil as knight, finding unseen/cult as sheriff warp an invest class as apostle  ect. also points should be given to people who accuse and vote exe on players whom are members from the opposite party. points should be retracted when: u accuse and execute people from ur own party, u kill BD as knight/prince, butler. aiding evil as unseen, pardon members of the opposite party. instead of voting the 3 best people each player should be able to give someone +1 and -1 point. u get the point. this is by no means worked out and need to be designed for each class individually. but this way people get rated based on there actions in game and not by popularity or bc he’s prince/mystic/alch and survived the game. if this system get implemented and works properly u could also implement a ladder system so u play again evenly skilled players. but this is just a thought and would probably be to hard to implement and take to much time and resources from the devs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 08:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72603-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/improving-mvp-system/72603.rss">improving MVP system</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
