<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Does Magic Barrier not count as a visit?</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/does-magic-barrier-not-count-as-a-visit/34293</link>
    <description>#### What happened?
I was a Court Wizard in a Cult game (latest patch). I was accused and executed because the Observer saw me not visit anyone the night I claimed to have Magic Barrier&#39;ed (which I did).
The Observer was not converted and in the post-game he confirmed me he saw me not visiting. Incidentally, I was barrier&#39;ing him that night, so no weird shenanigans should have been possible (the new Apostle can&#39;t Mind Warp anyway).

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?
The Observer should have seen me visit him.

#### Steps to reproduce:
Use Magic Barrier as a Court Wizard and have an Observer follow you.

#### Comments:
I&#39;m assuming this is a bug, since nowhere does it says that Magic Barrier doesn&#39;t count as a visit.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 17:48:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/does-magic-barrier-not-count-as-a-visit/34293.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Does Magic Barrier not count as a visit?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Loudo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>I was a Court Wizard in a Cult game (latest patch). I was accused and executed because the Observer saw me not visit anyone the night I claimed to have Magic Barrier’ed (which I did).<br>
The Observer was not converted and in the post-game he confirmed me he saw me not visiting. Incidentally, I was barrier’ing him that night, so no weird shenanigans should have been possible (the new Apostle can’t Mind Warp anyway).</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>The Observer should have seen me visit him.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<p>Use Magic Barrier as a Court Wizard and have an Observer follow you.</p>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>I’m assuming this is a bug, since nowhere does it says that Magic Barrier doesn’t count as a visit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/does-magic-barrier-not-count-as-a-visit/34293/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/does-magic-barrier-not-count-as-a-visit/34293/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 17:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34293-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/does-magic-barrier-not-count-as-a-visit/34293.rss">Does Magic Barrier not count as a visit?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
