<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My neutral classes reworked</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607</link>
    <description> 6 of my neutral classes. Take a look and tell me what you think about them 


[details=&quot;Inspirer&quot;] 

Name - Inspirer

Faction - neutral

Win condition - survive to see the BD fall

Passive 1 - My bright side - inspire anyone who visits you, healing them the night they visit you_

Day Ability 1 - Hideout - have your followers meet you in a meeting tonight(simialar to cult\unseen meetings){2 uses}_

Night Ability 1 - Convincing argument - Make a player realize that everyone should live together in harmony.(Convert a player into a neutral of their class, with one goal to protect the inspirer){2 uses}_

Ex. If a Noble is converted Neutral then the Noble will keep all of his day and night ability but his win condition will change. He will also appear Neutral from there on out.

Night ability 2 - Pep talk - Convince your followers that they are unstoppable. Make your concerted followers death immune and occupy immune for the night. {2 uses}
[/details]


[details=“Peace Keeper]
**Name - Peace Keeper** 
**_Faction - Neutral_**
**_Class - offensive_**  

Lore: As this silly war grew, the peace keeper felt sick. After losing his son because of the war he decides to only trust them who are Neutral in the war. Maybe they could help end this... or if all else fails the NK could get rid of them all. 

**Passive 1:** 
_**Little hope**_ - on days where no one die, you gain death immunity that night. 

**Passive 2:**
**_Failure_** - if all neutrals die then you will die the next day. If every Neutral is dead except the NK, then you will know who the NK is 

**Day Ability 1:**
**_Special connections_** - send your personal mercenary to guard someone. You can guard yourself. They will be alerted that they were guarded by a mercenary. (Unlimited uses)(2 day cool down)

**Day Ability 2:**
**_Hidden dungeon -_** chat with a player of your choice tonight. Separate tab. ( does not work on prince target and can be interrupted by mystic link (unlimited uses)

**Night ability 1:**
**_Showing your true colors_** - pick 3 people and you will know how many are neutral out of the 3. If there is not enough people then you can&#39;t use this ability. (unlimited uses)

_Ex. You pick 4,6,9_
_Message says_
_(&quot;2 out of 3 of your targets are neutral&quot;) or_
_(&quot;No targets are neutral)_

**Night ability 2:**
_Peace treaty -_ declare no trials the next day 
(2 uses)

**Win condition** - you win if there is another Neutral alive with you at the end of the game(includes NK, if NK is last Neutral alive)

Notes: this is a class that can really help both sides. BD might want to keep him alive for protection but also might need to kill him if he is defending the NK
[/details]

[details=“Builder”]
                  •Builder 

            **_Work in progress_** 

&gt;Description: this is a class built heavily around different constructions and when to make them. Each construction has different attributes and is dangerous to visit.  

&gt;Mechanics - only one builder per game, the builder will only spawn in 16 man games. If the builder dies with a construction still up then the building will still remain.  
&gt;
&gt;All constructions cab be built in anyone&#39;s room. Everyone can visit that player as normal but depending on the building something else could happen 

&gt;**Type - special** 
&gt;**Faction - Neutral** 

&gt;•The Builder will know what faction he is working for. 

&gt;**Passive 1:**
**_Hard worker -_** can use both day abilities on the same day
&gt;
&gt;**Passive 2:**
**_Long hours_** - When you are attacked your first time, you will be immune because you spent extra hours at work. If you are brought to jail then the construction will be stalled for a day. 

&gt;**Day Ability 1:**
**_Construction_** - select a building to start working on, it will be finished the night you select it. Then select a player to build the room in. (Unlimited uses)(1 day cool down) 
&gt;
&gt;_Church_ ❤️ - If any BD member visits the room where the church is then they will be healed of any poison/bleeding. If any unseen/cult visit then everyone else who visits the church will die that night 
&gt;
&gt;_Blacksmith_ ⚔️ - anyone who visits the blacksmith will regain all uses of their limited abilities and occu immunity for the next night. 
&gt;
&gt;_Stable_ 🐴 - if the builder selects the stables at night then the time will be increased for an extra 10 secs during the day and is able to have an extra trail during the next day. 2 time use per construction. If a player selects this then they will hide in the stable preventing anyone from visiting them. 
&gt;
&gt;_Dungeon_ 🗝 - If king sends a guard to the dungeon then the prince will be night immune. If any unseen/cult visit the dungeon then the prince can&#39;t exe his target that night. If a neutral or BD visit the dungeon then they can hear the prison chat for the following night.(they will hear prince and captive when they chat)
&gt;
&gt;_Library_ 📚 - If anyone visits the player with the library then they will gain a passive based off of the room where the library is. 
- if the library is in a room where the player has an occu immune passive then anyone who visits will be occu immune for the next night. 
- if the library is in a room where the player has a death immune passive then they will be death immune the next night
if the library is in a room where the player has both death and occ immune passive then they will gain both the next night. 
-  If they have two passives then their next limited ability will take no uses.
- (Can only be built day 3 and beyond)

&gt;
&gt;**Day Ability 2:**
_**Destruction**_ - destroy your current building(unlimited uses)

&gt;**Night ability 1:**
_**Secret door**_ - select yourself, anyone who visits you will be redirected to where you built your building if you have one. If you don&#39;t then you may not use this ability(2 uses)
&gt;
&gt;**Night ability 2:**
**_Loose nails_** - undo the nails collapsing the building on any players who decided to visit the current building, making them all bleed. The current construction will be destroyed. (Unlimited uses)

&gt;**Win condition** - have the starting king and his faction lose to win. 

Lore: The King decided to cut your pay for his own benefits. Now the builder is out for revenge.  

Thanks for the help @Firelitten,  @Htm, @NuclearBurrito and others I didn&#39;t mention
[/details]

[details=“Punisher”]
Backstory - the Punisher is sick of these silly faction wars and decides to take action 

Win condition - survive with any other Neutral player till the end of the game(includes NK&#39;s also)

Passive 1 - little hope - when no one has died when you wake up during the morning then you will be death and occu immune that night. 

Day Ability 1 - knock out - Instintly murder a player. {1 uses}. Everyone will be alerted

Day Ability 2 - Deep cut - make a player bleed, they are given the normal message &quot;you are bleeding, you have 2 days to live.&quot; But really the have 1 day to live until death.(can only be used during the first half of the day) {3 uses}

Night ability 1 - Punish - click on two people making on of them bleed and you will attack the other one
{2 uses}

Night ability 2 - special surprise - click on a player and any one that wants to do something to that player(attack,heal,occu) will be redirected to the Punisher that night. If any one was planning on killing that player but the Punisher redirected it to him then, the person attacking will die{3 uses}

Ex. 
The Punisher is #2. 
The assassin is #3. 
The alch is #4. 

The Punisher uses &quot;special surprise&quot; on #4. The same night #3(the assassin)wanted to kill #4(the alch)The assassin will be redirected to the Punisher and die. 

If you remember back when the drunk had his first night ability, it&#39;s similar to that

Notes: This can only spawn when it&#39;s a 16 player game. 

• Ability was removed. I thought this would make it too one sided towards helping BD. 
Day Ability 2 - lie detector - know secretly what a player did last night{3 uses}. 

• this works well with my inspirer class 

Tell me what you think
[/details]


[details=“Boogeyman”]
This class is designed to mess with people so enjoy

&gt;***_Name - boogeyman_**. still trying to find name that fits in the game. 
**_Faction - neutral_**
**_Type - support_** 

&gt;**Passive 1**: **_just a myth_** - if anyone visits you then you will know who it was 
&gt;
&gt;**Passive 2**: **the legend lives**_ - if the boogeyman dies then the person who killed him, dies the next day.[this is to punish the evil doers for attacking him, meaning that people should try to kill him during the day]

&gt;**Day ability 1**: _**Going insane**_ - make someone crazy having them hear people talk but they wont know who is talking, everyone will appear as anonymous, this includes whispers. (4 uses)
&gt;
&gt;**Day ability 2**: _**in your head**_ - select two players. The first player will send the message and the second player will receive it. After selecting two players then a box will show up where you can type a whisper and it will appear as the first player is whispering to the second. (Unlimited uses)

&gt;**Night ability 1**: _**crawling my way inside**_ - select a player and then select one of the false info you want to place in their mind (unlimited uses)
- you were attacked and healed
- you were occupied 
- a hunter has attacked you
- a mercanary has stood guard at your door
- anyother messages during the night that I did not mention 

&gt;
&gt;
&gt;**Night ability 2**: _**I&#39;m not real**_ - select a player, any night action that will be performed on you will be switched to selected player. The player will also be framed that night making them appear as unseen/cult or killer/offense depending on who investages them(4 uses)

&gt;**Win condition** - survive To see the BD fall


&gt;Changes:
&gt;
&gt;- **Night ability 1** - Crawling my way inside - get in someone’s head, allowing you to use the day ability 1 on them (unlimited uses)
^ this allowed you to pretty much do an unlimited troll box on someone which would be too overpowered
&gt;
&gt;- **Night ability 2** - kidnapped - steal a person and bring them to the woods. They will not be able to hear,vote, or talk the following day(4 uses)
^ I do agree that this would be boring for the player 
&gt;
&gt;- Win condition was also changed to more suitable gameplay 
&gt;

Tell me what you think
[/details]



[details=“Apprentice”]
**Name - apprentice
**_Faction - Neutral_**
**_Class Type - Investigative_**


**Passive 1 - slowly dying** - The first time you are attacked, he will not die but the next day and night you will not be able to use any abilities, also you will not be able to talk in any form of chat (includes prince or psychic chat for that night)

**Passive 2 - known allies** - if anyone evil decides to visit you (NK, cult/unseen) then you will know the name of the player who visited you and what they did to you that night. 

**Day Ability 1 - soul snatcher** - take a players night ability and use it tonight. (unlimited uses)

- This will always take the unlimited ability unless they don’t have a unlimited ability.
- If you take someone’s night ability that has unlimited then they won’t know you took one, but if there is a limit then you will be alerted that some of your soul has been taken.
- If you take someone’s soul for the third time, who has royal blood then you would gain royal blood. 

**Night Ability 1 - full body swap** - become a class of your choice(except any Unique classes) you will become that class for the next day and night. When you become a class you are allowed to use their day and night abilities (2 uses)

Notes:
- if you become a BD member and are checked that night by an invest Ability then you will show up as BD for that night.
- if you become a fool and get killed during the day that morning then you will win still.

**Win condition**- survive to see the BD fall. 

**My thoughts -** this is a class to help counter BD while also having a lot of claiming space.
[/details]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 19:00:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My neutral classes reworked</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t know. Probably from the builder suggestion</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 19:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60607-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607.rss">My neutral classes reworked</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My neutral classes reworked</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good catch. I’ll change that</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 19:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60607-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607.rss">My neutral classes reworked</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My neutral classes reworked</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>dunno</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60607-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607.rss">My neutral classes reworked</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My neutral classes reworked</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why did I get pinged?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 18:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60607-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607.rss">My neutral classes reworked</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My neutral classes reworked</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="60607">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Win condition - survive to see the BD fall</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="60607">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Day Ability 1- True to your Kingdom - make a player conversion immune{1}_</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><strong>Uhhhh</strong>…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 18:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60607-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607.rss">My neutral classes reworked</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My neutral classes reworked</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>6 of my neutral classes. Take a look and tell me what you think about them</p>
<details>
<summary>
Inspirer</summary>
<p>Name - Inspirer</p>
<p>Faction - neutral</p>
<p>Win condition - survive to see the BD fall</p>
<p>Passive 1 - My bright side - inspire anyone who visits you, healing them the night they visit you_</p>
<p>Day Ability 1 - Hideout - have your followers meet you in a meeting tonight(simialar to cult\unseen meetings){2 uses}_</p>
<p>Night Ability 1 - Convincing argument - Make a player realize that everyone should live together in harmony.(Convert a player into a neutral of their class, with one goal to protect the inspirer){2 uses}_</p>
<p>Ex. If a Noble is converted Neutral then the Noble will keep all of his day and night ability but his win condition will change. He will also appear Neutral from there on out.</p>
<p>Night ability 2 - Pep talk - Convince your followers that they are unstoppable. Make your concerted followers death immune and occupy immune for the night. {2 uses}</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
“Peace Keeper</summary>
<p><strong>Name - Peace Keeper</strong><br>
<strong><em>Faction - Neutral</em></strong><br>
<strong><em>Class - offensive</em></strong></p>
<p>Lore: As this silly war grew, the peace keeper felt sick. After losing his son because of the war he decides to only trust them who are Neutral in the war. Maybe they could help end this… or if all else fails the NK could get rid of them all.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 1:</strong><br>
<em><strong>Little hope</strong></em> - on days where no one die, you gain death immunity that night.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Failure</em></strong> - if all neutrals die then you will die the next day. If every Neutral is dead except the NK, then you will know who the NK is</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Special connections</em></strong> - send your personal mercenary to guard someone. You can guard yourself. They will be alerted that they were guarded by a mercenary. (Unlimited uses)(2 day cool down)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Hidden dungeon -</em></strong> chat with a player of your choice tonight. Separate tab. ( does not work on prince target and can be interrupted by mystic link (unlimited uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Showing your true colors</em></strong> - pick 3 people and you will know how many are neutral out of the 3. If there is not enough people then you can’t use this ability. (unlimited uses)</p>
<p><em>Ex. You pick 4,6,9</em><br>
<em>Message says</em><br>
<em>(“2 out of 3 of your targets are neutral”) or</em><br>
<em>("No targets are neutral)</em></p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2:</strong><br>
<em>Peace treaty -</em> declare no trials the next day<br>
(2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - you win if there is another Neutral alive with you at the end of the game(includes NK, if NK is last Neutral alive)</p>
<p>Notes: this is a class that can really help both sides. BD might want to keep him alive for protection but also might need to kill him if he is defending the NK</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Builder</summary>
<pre><code>              •Builder 

        **_Work in progress_** 
</code></pre>
<blockquote>
<p>Description: this is a class built heavily around different constructions and when to make them. Each construction has different attributes and is dangerous to visit.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Mechanics - only one builder per game, the builder will only spawn in 16 man games. If the builder dies with a construction still up then the building will still remain.</p>
<p>All constructions cab be built in anyone’s room. Everyone can visit that player as normal but depending on the building something else could happen</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Type - special</strong><br>
<strong>Faction - Neutral</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>•The Builder will know what faction he is working for.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Passive 1:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Hard worker -</em></strong> can use both day abilities on the same day</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Long hours</em></strong> - When you are attacked your first time, you will be immune because you spent extra hours at work. If you are brought to jail then the construction will be stalled for a day.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Construction</em></strong> - select a building to start working on, it will be finished the night you select it. Then select a player to build the room in. (Unlimited uses)(1 day cool down)</p>
<p><em>Church</em> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/heart.png?v=9" title=":heart:" class="emoji" alt=":heart:"> - If any BD member visits the room where the church is then they will be healed of any poison/bleeding. If any unseen/cult visit then everyone else who visits the church will die that night</p>
<p><em>Blacksmith</em> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crossed_swords.png?v=9" title=":crossed_swords:" class="emoji" alt=":crossed_swords:"> - anyone who visits the blacksmith will regain all uses of their limited abilities and occu immunity for the next night.</p>
<p><em>Stable</em> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/horse.png?v=9" title=":horse:" class="emoji" alt=":horse:"> - if the builder selects the stables at night then the time will be increased for an extra 10 secs during the day and is able to have an extra trail during the next day. 2 time use per construction. If a player selects this then they will hide in the stable preventing anyone from visiting them.</p>
<p><em>Dungeon</em> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/old_key.png?v=9" title=":old_key:" class="emoji" alt=":old_key:"> - If king sends a guard to the dungeon then the prince will be night immune. If any unseen/cult visit the dungeon then the prince can’t exe his target that night. If a neutral or BD visit the dungeon then they can hear the prison chat for the following night.(they will hear prince and captive when they chat)</p>
<p><em>Library</em> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/books.png?v=9" title=":books:" class="emoji" alt=":books:"> - If anyone visits the player with the library then they will gain a passive based off of the room where the library is.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>if the library is in a room where the player has an occu immune passive then anyone who visits will be occu immune for the next night.</li>
<li>if the library is in a room where the player has a death immune passive then they will be death immune the next night<br>
if the library is in a room where the player has both death and occ immune passive then they will gain both the next night.</li>
<li>If they have two passives then their next limited ability will take no uses.</li>
<li>(Can only be built day 3 and beyond)</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong><br>
<em><strong>Destruction</strong></em> - destroy your current building(unlimited uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night ability 1:</strong><br>
<em><strong>Secret door</strong></em> - select yourself, anyone who visits you will be redirected to where you built your building if you have one. If you don’t then you may not use this ability(2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2:</strong><br>
<strong><em>Loose nails</em></strong> - undo the nails collapsing the building on any players who decided to visit the current building, making them all bleed. The current construction will be destroyed. (Unlimited uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - have the starting king and his faction lose to win.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Lore: The King decided to cut your pay for his own benefits. Now the builder is out for revenge.</p>
<p>Thanks for the help <span class="mention">@Firelitten</span>,  <a class="mention" href="/u/htm">@Htm</a>, <a class="mention" href="/u/nuclearburrito">@NuclearBurrito</a> and others I didn’t mention</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Punisher</summary>
<p>Backstory - the Punisher is sick of these silly faction wars and decides to take action</p>
<p>Win condition - survive with any other Neutral player till the end of the game(includes NK’s also)</p>
<p>Passive 1 - little hope - when no one has died when you wake up during the morning then you will be death and occu immune that night.</p>
<p>Day Ability 1 - knock out - Instintly murder a player. {1 uses}. Everyone will be alerted</p>
<p>Day Ability 2 - Deep cut - make a player bleed, they are given the normal message “you are bleeding, you have 2 days to live.” But really the have 1 day to live until death.(can only be used during the first half of the day) {3 uses}</p>
<p>Night ability 1 - Punish - click on two people making on of them bleed and you will attack the other one<br>
{2 uses}</p>
<p>Night ability 2 - special surprise - click on a player and any one that wants to do something to that player(attack,heal,occu) will be redirected to the Punisher that night. If any one was planning on killing that player but the Punisher redirected it to him then, the person attacking will die{3 uses}</p>
<p>Ex.<br>
The Punisher is <span class="hashtag">#2</span>.<br>
The assassin is <span class="hashtag">#3</span>.<br>
The alch is <span class="hashtag">#4</span>.</p>
<p>The Punisher uses “special surprise” on <span class="hashtag">#4</span>. The same night <span class="hashtag">#3</span>(the assassin)wanted to kill <span class="hashtag">#4</span>(the alch)The assassin will be redirected to the Punisher and die.</p>
<p>If you remember back when the drunk had his first night ability, it’s similar to that</p>
<p>Notes: This can only spawn when it’s a 16 player game.</p>
<p>• Ability was removed. I thought this would make it too one sided towards helping BD.<br>
Day Ability 2 - lie detector - know secretly what a player did last night{3 uses}.</p>
<p>• this works well with my inspirer class</p>
<p>Tell me what you think</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Boogeyman</summary>
<p>This class is designed to mess with people so enjoy</p>
<blockquote>
<p>*<strong><em>Name - boogeyman</em></strong>. still trying to find name that fits in the game.<br>
<strong><em>Faction - neutral</em></strong><br>
<strong><em>Type - support</em></strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong>: <strong><em>just a myth</em></strong> - if anyone visits you then you will know who it was</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2</strong>: <strong>the legend lives</strong>_ - if the boogeyman dies then the person who killed him, dies the next day.[this is to punish the evil doers for attacking him, meaning that people should try to kill him during the day]</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Day ability 1</strong>: <em><strong>Going insane</strong></em> - make someone crazy having them hear people talk but they wont know who is talking, everyone will appear as anonymous, this includes whispers. (4 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Day ability 2</strong>: <em><strong>in your head</strong></em> - select two players. The first player will send the message and the second player will receive it. After selecting two players then a box will show up where you can type a whisper and it will appear as the first player is whispering to the second. (Unlimited uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong>: <em><strong>crawling my way inside</strong></em> - select a player and then select one of the false info you want to place in their mind (unlimited uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>you were attacked and healed</li>
<li>you were occupied</li>
<li>a hunter has attacked you</li>
<li>a mercanary has stood guard at your door</li>
<li>anyother messages during the night that I did not mention</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong>: <em><strong>I’m not real</strong></em> - select a player, any night action that will be performed on you will be switched to selected player. The player will also be framed that night making them appear as unseen/cult or killer/offense depending on who investages them(4 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - survive To see the BD fall</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong> - Crawling my way inside - get in someone’s head, allowing you to use the day ability 1 on them (unlimited uses)<br>
^ this allowed you to pretty much do an unlimited troll box on someone which would be too overpowered</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong> - kidnapped - steal a person and bring them to the woods. They will not be able to hear,vote, or talk the following day(4 uses)<br>
^ I do agree that this would be boring for the player</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Win condition was also changed to more suitable gameplay</p>
</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
<p>Tell me what you think</p>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Apprentice</summary>
<p>**Name - apprentice<br>
<strong><em>Faction - Neutral</em></strong><br>
<strong><em>Class Type - Investigative</em></strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive 1 - slowly dying</strong> - The first time you are attacked, he will not die but the next day and night you will not be able to use any abilities, also you will not be able to talk in any form of chat (includes prince or psychic chat for that night)</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2 - known allies</strong> - if anyone evil decides to visit you (NK, cult/unseen) then you will know the name of the player who visited you and what they did to you that night.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1 - soul snatcher</strong> - take a players night ability and use it tonight. (unlimited uses)</p>
<ul>
<li>This will always take the unlimited ability unless they don’t have a unlimited ability.</li>
<li>If you take someone’s night ability that has unlimited then they won’t know you took one, but if there is a limit then you will be alerted that some of your soul has been taken.</li>
<li>If you take someone’s soul for the third time, who has royal blood then you would gain royal blood.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1 - full body swap</strong> - become a class of your choice(except any Unique classes) you will become that class for the next day and night. When you become a class you are allowed to use their day and night abilities (2 uses)</p>
<p>Notes:</p>
<ul>
<li>if you become a BD member and are checked that night by an invest Ability then you will show up as BD for that night.</li>
<li>if you become a fool and get killed during the day that morning then you will win still.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong>- survive to see the BD fall.</p>
<p><strong>My thoughts -</strong> this is a class to help counter BD while also having a lot of claiming space.</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 18:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60607-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-neutral-classes-reworked/60607.rss">My neutral classes reworked</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
