<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Dragon Calls Out</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-dragon-calls-out/9710</link>
    <description>For as long as anyone can remember, religious worship of the Dragon that gave the Blue Dragon their name was conducted on a daily basis. For about 15 years, a specific individual who goes by the name the Priest has conducted daily sermons. The Blue Dragon has always been able to rely on the Priest to do so, never once missing one. However, on one fateful day, as the Blue Dragon congregated in the church, the Priest was not there waiting for them. 

Many had already realised that something was off. This had never happened before, so something had to have gone wrong. A desperate search for the Priest began throughout the castle, with everyone looking in all of the rooms, for a sign of a struggle, or perhaps something more sinister. Eventually, a member called out to the others nearby. They had found something, but it wasn&#39;t what any of them were expecting to find. It was a handwritten note, left atop the Priest&#39;s desk. It read as follows:
&gt; Fellow Blue Dragon,
By now you have probably been looking all over for me, since I won&#39;t have shown up for the sermon. Do not fear. The Dragon itself has called out to me, seeking for me to join it. Unfortunately, for me to do so, I have had to let go of my mortal self. While this may come as a shock, there is nothing to worry about. I will be watching out for you, as always, but better than I ever could before. Thank you all for believing in the power of the Dragon. You all will be rewarded in your own way, given time.
Sincerely, The Priest

The Blue Dragon were surprised at what they had learned, yet understanding. As the Priest had said before, the Priest and everyone else would eventually reach a time where they would come to serve the Dragon, and it had finally happened for the Priest. While they no longer would participate in daily sermons to further their connection with the Dragon, each of them found a way to perfect their craft, ensuring that they would have a place in the Dragon&#39;s Kingdom.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 16:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-dragon-calls-out/9710.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Dragon Calls Out</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For as long as anyone can remember, religious worship of the Dragon that gave the Blue Dragon their name was conducted on a daily basis. For about 15 years, a specific individual who goes by the name the Priest has conducted daily sermons. The Blue Dragon has always been able to rely on the Priest to do so, never once missing one. However, on one fateful day, as the Blue Dragon congregated in the church, the Priest was not there waiting for them.</p>
<p>Many had already realised that something was off. This had never happened before, so something had to have gone wrong. A desperate search for the Priest began throughout the castle, with everyone looking in all of the rooms, for a sign of a struggle, or perhaps something more sinister. Eventually, a member called out to the others nearby. They had found something, but it wasn’t what any of them were expecting to find. It was a handwritten note, left atop the Priest’s desk. It read as follows:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Fellow Blue Dragon,<br>
By now you have probably been looking all over for me, since I won’t have shown up for the sermon. Do not fear. The Dragon itself has called out to me, seeking for me to join it. Unfortunately, for me to do so, I have had to let go of my mortal self. While this may come as a shock, there is nothing to worry about. I will be watching out for you, as always, but better than I ever could before. Thank you all for believing in the power of the Dragon. You all will be rewarded in your own way, given time.<br>
Sincerely, The Priest</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Blue Dragon were surprised at what they had learned, yet understanding. As the Priest had said before, the Priest and everyone else would eventually reach a time where they would come to serve the Dragon, and it had finally happened for the Priest. While they no longer would participate in daily sermons to further their connection with the Dragon, each of them found a way to perfect their craft, ensuring that they would have a place in the Dragon’s Kingdom.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-dragon-calls-out/9710/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-dragon-calls-out/9710/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9710-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-dragon-calls-out/9710.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Dragon Calls Out</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
