<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179</link>
    <description>[quote]
# [color=#a698aa]The Gatecrasher[/color] 
**`Unique Neutral Social`**
`ɢᴏᴀʟ: Become King.`
[/quote] 
Passives:
[quote]
**Trickery:** Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing.
**Determination:** Immune to death at night once, this will be lost when you get Royal Blood or achieve your objective. 
[/quote]

Day Abilities:
[quote]
**Persuasive:** Target a player. That player will be unable to step to become King today. _1 use._
**Trollbox:** Choose a target player and whisper a short phrase into the troll box. It will appear as if that player said it. The target will not see the message. _∞ uses._
[/quote]
Night Abilities:
[quote]
**Blackmail:** Nullifies the King&#39;s Guard for the night. _2 uses._
**Wile:** Target a player. If he has Royal Blood you will temporarily remove it and get it youself for the next 2 following days. Can&#39;t target same player twice. _3 uses._
[/quote]

**Interactions:**
* People would not be aware their Royal Blood passive was gone ~~until they can&#39;t step, of course~~. It will come back once the two days have passed as well, it&#39;s a temporary measure taken from Gatecrasher. 
* King&#39;s Guards nullified by _Blackmail_ will work just like an empowered Reap or Assassin attack after Frenzy targeting the original Guard&#39;s target.
* The player targeted by _Persuasive_ will receive a message saying he was convinced to not step as King. It works for both Royals and non-Royals.
* Once Gatecrasher becomes King, he will have no guards. 
* The passive _Determination_ won&#39;t be back if the GC loses his Royal Blood.

I had in mind a not-so-uncommon idea of a Neutral whose objective is to be King. To achieve his goal he has access to disruptive tools, both to convince the court the King must be executed and to prevent other players to step up. I put him up as Social even though _Blackmail_ is more of a Offensive ability because everything else fits this role better. 

How this would effect the current game: First of all, it would be one more Neutral class, so Fool, Alchemist and Mercenary would have lower chances of spawning as double. As it is unique, double Gatecrashers obviously would not be a thing. However, nothing stops you from claiming Gatecrasher and hope there is none in the match; it&#39;s a class that can&#39;t be confirmed to the court until someone needs to step. You can say you used trollbox on a fellow neut or ask him to say he can&#39;t step, who knows. 

As far as claiming space go, it obviously won&#39;t stop at being able to claim Gatecrasher. Princess, Nobles and Drunk will lose their easy confirmability and it gives MM space to claim Princess that lost their Royal Blood. However, as this is temporary, there are chances that someone will face a situation where they need to step again to confirm they were indeed Royals once. They are niche, but they surely will exist. The reason for that is, as always, put more strategical thought for both BD and evils, as they must correctly time King&#39;s deaths in order to fake claim better. This is also a potential claim to Inquisitor to hide himself from Sorcerer. ~~Yeah, Inq does not need any more chances to win atm, but I am counting on the future balances.~~

The decision behind no Guards is once GC becomes King his objective is already accomplished and he does not need to survive like other Neutral Kings. He still has his Day Abilities, but if any evil wants to attack him they are free to do so. 

The reason why, even being an option, claiming Gatecrasher is bad (just like you don&#39;t want to claim Fool or Scorned ~~sometimes~~) is because once King is confirmed Good you are a threat to BD. They will likely execute you or abuse your Night Immunity to confirms Knights or even your class. 

Well, feedback is appreciated!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 18:16:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After last patch this suggestion isnt needed anymore xD</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 18:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Htm" data-post="5" data-topic="71179" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/htm/40/20871_2.png" class="avatar"> Htm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is nullifying the king’s guard meaning that the use is gone or would it be like an occupy?</p>
<p>Other than that great work on this.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The use would be gone and the guard would have no effect. It is tricky, though, yet powerful; how to know the nights the King will guard? It only has 2 uses, so you don’t want to spam. You can gamble a first night attack-guard (happens pretty often) and keep the second use to questions like “why King did not guard Prince?!” when they actually did.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 04:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well yeah, probably a slight change to how step days begin, giving a 5 seconds space for day abilities. Not only for that class, btw! I always found strange we have no way to use DA on step day until King is chosen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 04:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is nullifying the king’s guard meaning that the use is gone or would it be like an occupy?</p>
<p>Other than that great work on this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 03:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Silent_Ace1778]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lot of work was done here and I liked it, we could always use more Troll boxes :^). I really love the fact it gives room for Mm to claim Princess that lost RB. However their ability to convince a Royal not to step would be hard to time down and may get clicked on too late. Really good job though!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 03:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yup, the idea is basically that I would say; a “King Scorned”. The difference is that this does not equal to execute the King or wait for him to die, but more efficiently to become the King.  The King’s alignment will once matter if King can confirm himself as Good and people ask your claim, out of this situation you can wait for poison, empowers, executions and other measures killing him without any real impact of his alignment. It’s not that hard to get a King killed, really, even less hard with the tools at GC’s reach.</p>
<p>The problem with a redirection Neut (and I HEAVILY agree with that, we need both more neuts and more redirections) is to establish an objective. Probably someone who needs to survive and redirects abilities targeting them to someone else, I had something like that in mind for a while. Well, back to the subject:</p>
<p>The class relies on luck as much as any other class. Luck is a factor important to basically any action in the first days, but so is strategy. This class would require no more luck than any other neutral, I think. May be hard to convince people to vote you up if there is another Royal, but their night and day abilities make it so a skilled GC can shut down two steps for that day and become King without the need for the court to vote.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 17:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Enchiladas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This class seems like a scorned for king, in that it will try to mess with it at anytime. I appreciate the idea of adding another neutral, but since king could be good or evil, I would heavily suggest not implementing it, as it there is more need for a redirecting neutral, than another social neutral. Also, I feel like this class would rely on luck quite a bit, like it’s scorned counter part</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="#a698aa">The Gatecrasher</font></h1>
<p><strong><code>Unique Neutral Social</code></strong><br>
<code>ɢᴏᴀʟ: Become King.</code></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Passives:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Trickery:</strong> Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing.<br>
<strong>Determination:</strong> Immune to death at night once, this will be lost when you get Royal Blood or achieve your objective.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Day Abilities:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Persuasive:</strong> Target a player. That player will be unable to step to become King today. <em>1 use.</em><br>
<strong>Trollbox:</strong> Choose a target player and whisper a short phrase into the troll box. It will appear as if that player said it. The target will not see the message. <em>∞ uses.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Night Abilities:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Blackmail:</strong> Nullifies the King’s Guard for the night. <em>2 uses.</em><br>
<strong>Wile:</strong> Target a player. If he has Royal Blood you will temporarily remove it and get it youself for the next 2 following days. Can’t target same player twice. <em>3 uses.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><strong>Interactions:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>People would not be aware their Royal Blood passive was gone <s>until they can’t step, of course</s>. It will come back once the two days have passed as well, it’s a temporary measure taken from Gatecrasher.</li>
<li>King’s Guards nullified by <em>Blackmail</em> will work just like an empowered Reap or Assassin attack after Frenzy targeting the original Guard’s target.</li>
<li>The player targeted by <em>Persuasive</em> will receive a message saying he was convinced to not step as King. It works for both Royals and non-Royals.</li>
<li>Once Gatecrasher becomes King, he will have no guards.</li>
<li>The passive <em>Determination</em> won’t be back if the GC loses his Royal Blood.</li>
</ul>
<p>I had in mind a not-so-uncommon idea of a Neutral whose objective is to be King. To achieve his goal he has access to disruptive tools, both to convince the court the King must be executed and to prevent other players to step up. I put him up as Social even though <em>Blackmail</em> is more of a Offensive ability because everything else fits this role better.</p>
<p>How this would effect the current game: First of all, it would be one more Neutral class, so Fool, Alchemist and Mercenary would have lower chances of spawning as double. As it is unique, double Gatecrashers obviously would not be a thing. However, nothing stops you from claiming Gatecrasher and hope there is none in the match; it’s a class that can’t be confirmed to the court until someone needs to step. You can say you used trollbox on a fellow neut or ask him to say he can’t step, who knows.</p>
<p>As far as claiming space go, it obviously won’t stop at being able to claim Gatecrasher. Princess, Nobles and Drunk will lose their easy confirmability and it gives MM space to claim Princess that lost their Royal Blood. However, as this is temporary, there are chances that someone will face a situation where they need to step again to confirm they were indeed Royals once. They are niche, but they surely will exist. The reason for that is, as always, put more strategical thought for both BD and evils, as they must correctly time King’s deaths in order to fake claim better. This is also a potential claim to Inquisitor to hide himself from Sorcerer. <s>Yeah, Inq does not need any more chances to win atm, but I am counting on the future balances.</s></p>
<p>The decision behind no Guards is once GC becomes King his objective is already accomplished and he does not need to survive like other Neutral Kings. He still has his Day Abilities, but if any evil wants to attack him they are free to do so.</p>
<p>The reason why, even being an option, claiming Gatecrasher is bad (just like you don’t want to claim Fool or Scorned <s>sometimes</s>) is because once King is confirmed Good you are a threat to BD. They will likely execute you or abuse your Night Immunity to confirms Knights or even your class.</p>
<p>Well, feedback is appreciated!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 16:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71179-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-gatecrasher-neutral-social/71179.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Gatecrasher [Neutral Social]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
