<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540</link>
    <description>Once a man dedicated to the life of helping others the herbalist or Physician continued to help others whether It be curing them of poison or helping them recover from a fatal injury, or even others attacking them. The Physician/Herbalist was very skilled in these tasks and that is what made him get a name for him self in the kingdom. He was so well known that everyone that he saved, began to praise him. He boasted in this praise and was overwhelmed by it.

One day in the kingdom, he was so into the fame that he usually got that he was surprised when no one ended up caring.
This destroyed his ego, and he went into the night depressed and saddened who went to sleep thinking of the worst, until he heard a knock on his door. He could only think that It was a knight executing him for suspicion of being evil. He thought of the worst and opened the door, accepting his fate.
..........
Nothing Happened.
He opened his eyes slowing to see a man in a hood. The man came into the room, and closed the door behind him. The man then said, &quot;You seem like you can be useful and powerful, the Blue Dragon doesn&#39;t Realize your potential and neither do they praise you for it.&quot; The Herbalist/Physician Opened his mouth to say something but then closed it shut. The man in the hood then stated &quot;If you want others to treat you with respect, I would recommend you joining our group, the unseen.&quot; The Herbalist/Physician Gladly accepted this invitation for he will finally be treated with more respect then he ever was. For he was no longer a measly Physician, but a King of A Herbalist.
-----------------------------------------
Comments/ Explanations
I feel as though the Physician/Herbalist should have a giant ego seeing as though he saves peoples lives, and is not honor driven. This will lead toward his hate-trod toward the Blue Dragon, and will end up with him joining the unseen.    
This makes sense do to the fact that Blue Dragon that are converted to unseen in my mind have to have a grudge toward Blue Dragon, and this is why Sheriff and Prince are unconvertable. In all the Physician to herbalist is well-explained in this lore suggestion in my opinion but share your opinion by replying, thanks :3</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 23:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>he should have a hero complex</p>
<p>also, because you put in the line without a space above it, it made everything look big</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 23:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2540-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Once a man dedicated to the life of helping others the herbalist or Physician continued to help others whether It be curing them of poison or helping them recover from a fatal injury, or even others attacking them. The Physician/Herbalist was very skilled in these tasks and that is what made him get a name for him self in the kingdom. He was so well known that everyone that he saved, began to praise him. He boasted in this praise and was overwhelmed by it.</p>
<h2>One day in the kingdom, he was so into the fame that he usually got that he was surprised when no one ended up caring.<br>
This destroyed his ego, and he went into the night depressed and saddened who went to sleep thinking of the worst, until he heard a knock on his door. He could only think that It was a knight executing him for suspicion of being evil. He thought of the worst and opened the door, accepting his fate.<br>
…<br>
Nothing Happened.<br>
He opened his eyes slowing to see a man in a hood. The man came into the room, and closed the door behind him. The man then said, “You seem like you can be useful and powerful, the Blue Dragon doesn’t Realize your potential and neither do they praise you for it.” The Herbalist/Physician Opened his mouth to say something but then closed it shut. The man in the hood then stated “If you want others to treat you with respect, I would recommend you joining our group, the unseen.” The Herbalist/Physician Gladly accepted this invitation for he will finally be treated with more respect then he ever was. For he was no longer a measly Physician, but a King of A Herbalist.</h2>
<p>Comments/ Explanations<br>
I feel as though the Physician/Herbalist should have a giant ego seeing as though he saves peoples lives, and is not honor driven. This will lead toward his hate-trod toward the Blue Dragon, and will end up with him joining the unseen.<br>
This makes sense do to the fact that Blue Dragon that are converted to unseen in my mind have to have a grudge toward Blue Dragon, and this is why Sheriff and Prince are unconvertable. In all the Physician to herbalist is well-explained in this lore suggestion in my opinion but share your opinion by replying, thanks :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2540-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist/2540.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
