<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328</link>
    <description>Ever had a crazy game you just **had** to tell people about? Post it in this thread, I at least am curious as to other people&#39;s thought process&#39; going through a game.

I have my own entry below if you&#39;re interested

---------------

Alright I&#39;m going to tell a tale that I had happen to me in a game, which for all intents and purposes was decided in turns 3 and 4 and then eventually spiraled out of control into the mess that was the conclusion. And it&#39;s all _my_ fault.

Now of course, I&#39;m assigned my least favorite role in the game: _Prince_. A role in which is fairly heavy on note taking and situational awareness.
 It&#39;s a key component that can lead to many &quot;checkmate&quot; scenarios in which if the prince plays perfectly, he can carry victory on his back.
 
 So night 3 I jail a claimed Observer[14]. In his log, he says that during night2, he followed [3] and [3] visited the King.
 
 Well wouldn&#39;t you know it, the next day, king is dead day 4.
 
 Looking at his diary - he didn&#39;t write his night 2 results, leading us to believe that the king was reaped. 
 [14] was also lead to believe that the king was reaped and tried to despreately point out that [3] visited the king night2 admists all the accusations of an unseen[16]
 Someone had to question [3], and that someone was going to be me.
 
 night4 comes and I ask [3] for his role and logs.
 He claims the following:
 
 phys (n1- heal king, n2- heal king, n3 - heal randomGuy[10])
 
 It checked out with [14]&#39;s claim but at this point I thought that risking a physician wouldn&#39;t be too big of a deal so I went with it.
 To my surprise, he was actually a physician. Not only that, it turns out the King wasn&#39;t reaped,
but was instead killed by an unseen assassin, and the king just didn&#39;t have any entries from night2&#39;s results onwards.

This of course means that if the physician[3] healed the king night3, 
I wouldn&#39;t have been questioning [3] in the first place and his[3&#39;s] death would have been prevented.

Because the physician[3] died by my hands, there was a need for healing poison in which our Reaper[5] was so happily willing to claim alchemist to do.
This unintentionally(as this was his first time as reaper) gave 5 a sort of shield to freely &quot;heal&quot; the many who claimed to be poisoned without question.


Eventually, the game fell apart with the mastermind avoiding execution, the unseen got voting majority and executed the reaper along with the last Blue Dragon member for the win.


Lessons Learned:

So with the latest patch (1.07b) giving 4 uses of poison and bleeding has caused physicians to be more valuable, and was a lesson I hadn&#39;t learned yet.

Having access to executions as prince is sometimes more valuable than using them, 
especially when it&#39;s down to 2 members left as having an execute can determine BD to be a winner over a draw. Using my execute recklessly like this to test [14&#39;s] claim as observer was a huge mistake on my part that ended up costing Blue Dragon the game. As only being able to jail people wasn&#39;t enough, and gave the rest of the Blue Dragon enough reason to let the reaper live.

I hope that was at least an entertaining read. I often wonder if other people have crazy games they want to share, so I thought I&#39;d share mine to see if that&#39;s the case.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 19:21:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>only on a case by case basis <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 19:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am glad they are so tough on toxicity but banning for bussing and generally well-known techniques in mafia games is bullshit tbh.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 19:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/roll_eyes.png?v=9" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/roll_eyes.png?v=9" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/roll_eyes.png?v=9" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/roll_eyes.png?v=9" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/roll_eyes.png?v=9" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/roll_eyes.png?v=9" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 19:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="2" data-topic="8328">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I find out that 13 is my ally. Unseen, yay! I know that I have to get him hanged to net myself some nice BD cred, so the next day I call him out, get him hanged</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Technically gamethrowing under the current rule set, just a heads up <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/roll_eyes.png?v=9" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 19:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just had a fun game . I start as Cult King</p>
<p>Turn 1 i guard cos i am superstitious like that  and sure enough the possessor comes for me .<br>
during the day I get an alchemist message me saying he will heal me as long as I vouch for him etc .</p>
<p>Over the next few turns i start investigating and the possessor keeps coming for me , but i am being healed</p>
<p>turn 3 i get a cult member and throw him under the bus to get creds</p>
<p>next turn a princess whispers me to share info . she is suspicious of my alch ,so i let her know hes my pet alch .</p>
<p>a few turns later an observer gives the old neut out and wants to hang my alch .</p>
<p>i convince them to let him live because the possessor keeps coming for me and he is being helpful .</p>
<p>After a few more turns, a couple of cult and most oft the rest have died , the  possessor jumps and my princess that been whispering me starts to aim at me , but i quickly spin it back by asking her what she had whispered to me the day before , princess is stumped and we hang as possessor .</p>
<p>That   leaves me , the alchemist and a paladin claim left at the table . "gasp EVIL KING " and “paladin converted” shouts come from the paladin and me .</p>
<p>The alchemist calmly points out that he has won either way ! So we both start pleading with the Alchemist .<br>
He points his finger at me .<br>
The paldin reassures him hes made the right choice .<br>
On the stand I plead with the alchemist " dude , they all wanted to kill you turn 5 , i talked them down" as the paladin continued to  congratulate the alchemist on his choice to support the BD .</p>
<p>The votes come in and the Alchemist has flipped !</p>
<p>We quickly vote up the paladin, that fumes,as we execute him.</p>
<p>The alchemist just said " the king saved me when you lot where all shouting neuts out !"</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 17:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PandaKing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had a game where the Reaper stepped up as the new King and actually was pretty honest in chat that he was the reaper but wants to help BD win because he doesn’t like the reaper odds.  Surpringsly we all voted for the Reaper to be king and he did actually help the BD win the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 16:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Evil King. Oh boy.</p>
<p>So on Night 2, I find out that 13 is my ally. Unseen, yay! I know that I have to get him hanged to net myself some nice BD cred, so the next day I call him out, get him hanged (Assassin, thank goodness), and look like a Good King to your average citizen. Nice.</p>
<p>That night, thr Prince dies. People start asking the Priest to revive Prince, and I know that I cannot let that happen. I use my newfound credibility to lead the town in randomly voting up 4 for a claim. He makes it, and it’s kinda sketchy, but player 9 is pushing him pretty hard. He must be pretty good at the game, and confident in himself, so I encourage pardoning 4 and move to vote up 9 after he is the only one to vote execute.</p>
<p>9 hits the stand real quick, and immediately claims Priest. <em>Nailed it.</em> The pardon votes start rolling in, but it’s too late; I’m in charge now. I decide to execute the Priest and watch the shock on people’s faces as they realized I played them for fools. And though I may have been executed the next day, I’d say it was more than a fair trade.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 14:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markio16]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ever had a crazy game you just <strong>had</strong> to tell people about? Post it in this thread, I at least am curious as to other people’s thought process’ going through a game.</p>
<p>I have my own entry below if you’re interested</p>
<hr>
<p>Alright I’m going to tell a tale that I had happen to me in a game, which for all intents and purposes was decided in turns 3 and 4 and then eventually spiraled out of control into the mess that was the conclusion. And it’s all <em>my</em> fault.</p>
<p>Now of course, I’m assigned my least favorite role in the game: <em>Prince</em>. A role in which is fairly heavy on note taking and situational awareness.<br>
It’s a key component that can lead to many “checkmate” scenarios in which if the prince plays perfectly, he can carry victory on his back.</p>
<p>So night 3 I jail a claimed Observer[14]. In his log, he says that during night2, he followed [3] and [3] visited the King.</p>
<p>Well wouldn’t you know it, the next day, king is dead day 4.</p>
<p>Looking at his diary - he didn’t write his night 2 results, leading us to believe that the king was reaped.<br>
[14] was also lead to believe that the king was reaped and tried to despreately point out that [3] visited the king night2 admists all the accusations of an unseen[16]<br>
Someone had to question [3], and that someone was going to be me.</p>
<p>night4 comes and I ask [3] for his role and logs.<br>
He claims the following:</p>
<p>phys (n1- heal king, n2- heal king, n3 - heal randomGuy[10])</p>
<p>It checked out with [14]'s claim but at this point I thought that risking a physician wouldn’t be too big of a deal so I went with it.<br>
To my surprise, he was actually a physician. Not only that, it turns out the King wasn’t reaped,<br>
but was instead killed by an unseen assassin, and the king just didn’t have any entries from night2’s results onwards.</p>
<p>This of course means that if the physician[3] healed the king night3,<br>
I wouldn’t have been questioning [3] in the first place and his[3’s] death would have been prevented.</p>
<p>Because the physician[3] died by my hands, there was a need for healing poison in which our Reaper[5] was so happily willing to claim alchemist to do.<br>
This unintentionally(as this was his first time as reaper) gave 5 a sort of shield to freely “heal” the many who claimed to be poisoned without question.</p>
<p>Eventually, the game fell apart with the mastermind avoiding execution, the unseen got voting majority and executed the reaper along with the last Blue Dragon member for the win.</p>
<p>Lessons Learned:</p>
<p>So with the latest patch (1.07b) giving 4 uses of poison and bleeding has caused physicians to be more valuable, and was a lesson I hadn’t learned yet.</p>
<p>Having access to executions as prince is sometimes more valuable than using them,<br>
especially when it’s down to 2 members left as having an execute can determine BD to be a winner over a draw. Using my execute recklessly like this to test [14’s] claim as observer was a huge mistake on my part that ended up costing Blue Dragon the game. As only being able to jail people wasn’t enough, and gave the rest of the Blue Dragon enough reason to let the reaper live.</p>
<p>I hope that was at least an entertaining read. I often wonder if other people have crazy games they want to share, so I thought I’d share mine to see if that’s the case.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 02:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8328-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lying-thrones-for-the-soul-a-thread-where-we-share-tales-of-crazy-games/8328.rss">Lying Thrones for the Soul - a thread where we share tales of crazy games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
