<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help me learn the game: example skill feedback</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293</link>
    <description>Creating good fake logs is an important skill for many roles (basically all non-bd and even some bd). Identifying fake logs is important for everyone. Part of this is experience, and that&#39;s a good thing. You should get better at a game when you spend more time playing it.

But I want some more help. It would be great to see more examples of what skill interactions look like to each player. I&#39;m thinking something in the class cards. Maybe I click an ability, get a popup to choose a target class, and get some info like &quot;you see: ...&quot; / &quot;they see...&quot;.

For a particularly complicated example, the interaction I was curious about is Sorc magic cloak + magic missile into princess will o&#39; wisp. Does the wow target see the visit?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 23:56:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help me learn the game: example skill feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Magic Cloak hides your visits, so combined with an attack on the Wisping Princess, both the dead Princess and the target of the Wisp will not see the Sorcerer, but they will see other visitors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 23:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-46293-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293.rss">Help me learn the game: example skill feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help me learn the game: example skill feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tialyss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Creating good fake logs is an important skill for many roles (basically all non-bd and even some bd). Identifying fake logs is important for everyone. Part of this is experience, and that’s a good thing. You should get better at a game when you spend more time playing it.</p>
<p>But I want some more help. It would be great to see more examples of what skill interactions look like to each player. I’m thinking something in the class cards. Maybe I click an ability, get a popup to choose a target class, and get some info like “you see: …” / “they see…”.</p>
<p>For a particularly complicated example, the interaction I was curious about is Sorc magic cloak + magic missile into princess will o’ wisp. Does the wow target see the visit?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 23:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-46293-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/help-me-learn-the-game-example-skill-feedback/46293.rss">Help me learn the game: example skill feedback</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
