<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955</link>
    <description>Another one of my neuts. I&#39;ve been experimenting around with two ideas as of late, one which pertains to neutrals. I&#39;ve been trying to move away from overdone neutral goals such as surviving, winning with faction _N_, or dumb puzzle-based neuts that have zero interactivity and just encourage d1 claiming and then being left alone for the rest of the match. So my first attempt at a unique Neutral goal is to create a pseudo-faction where the Strigoi must work to survive in order to infect others while at the same time preventing the current infected players from dying.

To add more interactivity and prevent d1 claiming, I added a scum factor which is the second idea I&#39;ve been experimenting, which is a ToS Arso-like perma frame. While the Strigoi can win with BD, their goals are essentially conflicting as the Strigoi needs to bite, ergo frame, as many players as possible. 

&gt; # [color = &quot;Firebrick&quot;] The Strigoi [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Offensive [/color]** 
**Blood Sucker (Passive)** - If the Strigoi is using Vampiric Bite then he will heal himself if he would be nightkilled. The Strigoi will always be under the effect of Vampirism.
**No Pulse (Passive)** - Grants the Strigoi immunity to redirection and occupation.
**Mist Form (Day)** - All visits to the Strigoi will be prevented this coming night - 2 uses 
**Blood Frenzy (Day)** - All players under the effect of Vampirism will receive the benefits of No Pulse and the healing from Blood Sucker if the Vampire successfully uses Vampiric Bite. - 2 uses 
**Vampiric Bite (Night)** - Bites a player, infecting them with Vampirism, preventing healing, and occupying them. Players infected with Vampirism will be shown as a Strigoi(Neutral/Offensive) for investigative abilities and will have their visits hidden. - Infinite uses 
*Make sure at least half of the living remainder of the Court is infected with Vampirism by the end of the game.* 

* Blood Sucker is here as a form of protection against random night kills.
* No Pulse is required as offensive classes need to be immune against occupations and redirection.
* Blood Frenzy is done to help protect the Strigoi&#39;s infected targets.
* Mist Form and the bite&#39;s occupation helps the user fakeclaim Butler.
* The bite is self-explanatory. Negative effects are basically mandatory here as otherwise people will be open claiming just to be left alone for the rest of the match.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 01:42:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Funny thing you should mention this, but originally Vampirism would also block healing on the target barring Blood Frenzy. Though I agree with this as this creates claimspace for fake Phys and Alch claims.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 01:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68955-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Idea! Make the bite also prevent the next heal on the target (not counting blood frenzy of course)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 01:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68955-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>10/10</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 19:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68955-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another one of my neuts. I’ve been experimenting around with two ideas as of late, one which pertains to neutrals. I’ve been trying to move away from overdone neutral goals such as surviving, winning with faction <em>N</em>, or dumb puzzle-based neuts that have zero interactivity and just encourage d1 claiming and then being left alone for the rest of the match. So my first attempt at a unique Neutral goal is to create a pseudo-faction where the Strigoi must work to survive in order to infect others while at the same time preventing the current infected players from dying.</p>
<p>To add more interactivity and prevent d1 claiming, I added a scum factor which is the second idea I’ve been experimenting, which is a ToS Arso-like perma frame. While the Strigoi can win with BD, their goals are essentially conflicting as the Strigoi needs to bite, ergo frame, as many players as possible.</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="Firebrick"> The Strigoi </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Offensive </font></strong><br>
<strong>Blood Sucker (Passive)</strong> - If the Strigoi is using Vampiric Bite then he will heal himself if he would be nightkilled. The Strigoi will always be under the effect of Vampirism.<br>
<strong>No Pulse (Passive)</strong> - Grants the Strigoi immunity to redirection and occupation.<br>
<strong>Mist Form (Day)</strong> - All visits to the Strigoi will be prevented this coming night - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Blood Frenzy (Day)</strong> - All players under the effect of Vampirism will receive the benefits of No Pulse and the healing from Blood Sucker if the Vampire successfully uses Vampiric Bite. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Vampiric Bite (Night)</strong> - Bites a player, infecting them with Vampirism, preventing healing, and occupying them. Players infected with Vampirism will be shown as a Strigoi(Neutral/Offensive) for investigative abilities and will have their visits hidden. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Make sure at least half of the living remainder of the Court is infected with Vampirism by the end of the game.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Blood Sucker is here as a form of protection against random night kills.</li>
<li>No Pulse is required as offensive classes need to be immune against occupations and redirection.</li>
<li>Blood Frenzy is done to help protect the Strigoi’s infected targets.</li>
<li>Mist Form and the bite’s occupation helps the user fakeclaim Butler.</li>
<li>The bite is self-explanatory. Negative effects are basically mandatory here as otherwise people will be open claiming just to be left alone for the rest of the match.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 19:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68955-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-strigoi/68955.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Strigoi</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
