<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve rolled Merc quite a few times since most recent changes to the class. Here are my thoughts. I would welcome input from others.

Since the inclusion of Sellsword, and with other protective BD classes, Mercenary seems to be considered largely redundant and unnecessary by BD. Often Merc gets exed as a suspicious claim for SS, NK, (I&#39;ve even been exed as a purported MM), or exed just to eliminate a Neut Counter on the list (&quot;no loss&quot; is heard frequently). They are usually targeted by Unseen/Cult/Killers because of their prohibitive abilities, but BD doesn&#39;t have enough interest in keeping Merc alive when that Neut Counter elimination is such valuable deductive information.

Here are some of the issues I keep bumping into in my playtime as Mercenary:
Why trust a Merc claim when you can trust a confirmed Knight?
Anything claimed by a Merc can be doubled or faked by a different class&#39;s abilities. Occupations are easily falsified by other classes, and Guards can be mistaken for Sellsword abilities.
Also, players *want* confirmation.
In a choice between a Merc guard and a Knight guard, Prince usually does and frankly should choose Knight because Knight kills back -- and the death note confirms them. Not so for Merc.
True too of the player behind our hypothetical Knight: they want that confirmation too - it&#39;s their ticket to survival, even in the event of a conversion.
It also makes Merc an ungratifying class to play. There is no material difference that Merc can make to impact the outcome of the game in early game, and if they survive early game, they better hope NK is dead too! Usually other BD members see them as &quot;getting underfoot,&quot; and they aren&#39;t quite Neutral in their win conditions - so they get no support from their &quot;Let&#39;s see which way the wind blows&quot; Neutral faction-mates.

Give Mercenary a way to confirm themselves. This is a standalone suggestion. As far as potential solutions to restoring their viability in play... random ideas:

Re-combining Merc and SS into one &quot;Mercenary&quot; type class that be contracted to both factions
Making Merc and SS &quot;twinned&quot; classes - somehow, making their win conditions supportive of each other, as a converse to Sorc/Inq
Making Merc more supportive of other Neut classes, (e.g. an Alch-specific empowering guard abiltiy or something, an extra TB for fool if guarded by Merc prior night, etc)
Maybe even allowing Merc to support (&quot;borrow&quot;) the win conditions of a fellow Neut as a form of their own win conditions.

Idc if you think my suggests are poo, but the info on Merc play is good, and I hope to see it restored to a fun class. TY</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 14:55:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Are you sure you want to continue this old conversation?<br>
Yes.<br>
I don’t like staying nerfed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-48</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s a fair idea, then. Daytime SS locks your night abilities from usage. Might be worth increasing number of SS to 5, then? Under this paradigm, the more SS uses the Alch has, the less useful they become to BD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-47</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would have to work something akin to SS still being a day ability, but it locks the night abilities when used. ToL’s coding only supports up to two night abilities per class so programming it that way wouldn’t be the optimal method.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/46</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-46</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I still think the best idea to satisfy what the community wants out of Alch is to move their Stoneskin as a night ability and give them 3 uses of healing potion, 3 uses of stoneskin and 3 uses of bombing.</p>
<p>There  was an additional suggestion for letting them recharge uses of a potion by using another, which I wouldn’t be opposed to, but I think that suggestion as a baseline would solve a lot of the problems the community has with the class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/45</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 16:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-45</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes. But more bombs lead to them being more dangerous <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 14:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-44</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/face_with_raised_eyebrow.png?v=9" title=":face_with_raised_eyebrow:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":face_with_raised_eyebrow:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/43</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 14:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-43</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then can we increase bombs instead?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/42</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-42</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Agree with all of this.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ShadowKnight" data-post="23" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shadowknight/40/5439_2.png" class="avatar"> ShadowKnight:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We need more appealing Neutral classes that are hard to confirm but are still tempting to BD keep alive</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s why I like this Merc rework.</p>
<p>Alchemist needs to have their heals reduced to 2 uses. Their current yolo healing strategy not only helps confirm them, but also slows down evil progress a lot. True alchemists need to be put under the gun when BD asks why they can’t heal the poisoned Sheriff when the alchemist replies, “I used all my heals already.” Now BD is faced with a tough decision, similar to that of trusting a Merc claim. Might not always happen that way, but reducing heals from unlimited to 2 is a step in the right direction.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/41</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 14:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-41</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Merc has the highest win rate in the game. He doesn’t need more survivability</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 13:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-40</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Issue is there’s literally never going to be a reason not to convert a Sellsword for the extra member</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 09:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-39</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Helpful” as in “Significantly helpful to the Blue Dragon”.</p>
<p>As FK said, Alch and Merc are “helpful” classes because Alch’s kit and Merc’s wincon and kit encourage them to work with the BD</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 09:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-38</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A potential way to make Mercenary more interesting to play while maintaining the goals I mentioned before is to make Mercenary Unique but convertible into the Sellsword (whether or not we want to make Sellsword unavailable if the game has a Mercenary or we’re okay with a two-Sellsword game is another matter).</p>
<p>Making Mercenary convertible allows for them to be buffed so that they perform a significantly powerful service for BD at the cost of, if converted, become an anti-BD class that doesn’t count against Cult/Unseen numbers (but can’t coordinate with them at night).</p>
<p>Might also want to change the Sellsword’s Intimidate for something less likely to tip off BD? Maybe making it an occupy that makes the target think the action went through? With limited uses, of course.</p>
<p>Now this idea necessitates the new Mercenary to have a truly useful ability that makes it tempting for BD to keep it around.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 03:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-37</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ShadowKnight" data-post="26" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shadowknight/40/5439_2.png" class="avatar"> ShadowKnight:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can do both! And Neutrals can be both, too.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mercenaries are pretty much fully reliant on BD as Possessors and Reapers have extremely low win rates while you absolutely cannot rely on Sorcerers as they also win with the Unseen or Cult. Meanwhile Alchemists suffer from the 3-checks issue and they need to be reworked as the majority of times it’s far better to side with BD rather than evils unless BD is playing horrendously. Right now neither of them are wild cards.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ShadowKnight" data-post="26" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shadowknight/40/5439_2.png" class="avatar"> ShadowKnight:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Having <em>only</em> more BD classes leads to a very “roll of the dice” claimspace for evils, where they might be forced to claim early and later executed on the spot when it’s revealed that 2 of the classes they claimed as were already present in the game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The same 2-class limit applies to neutrals and it’s even worse as there is also a limit of neutrals in the game, so if you’re fakeclaiming Alchemist while a Fool and a Mercenary are dead in a Sorc game, you’re basically a goner. We don’t need more claimable neutral classes while expanding the amount of BD classes would easily remove the 2-class issue.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ShadowKnight" data-post="30" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shadowknight/40/5439_2.png" class="avatar"> ShadowKnight:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Neutral claims should be riskier/less trustworthy than BD claims, but they shouldn’t be altogether invalid.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They aren’t invalid, it’s just that players are going to be far more open to any accusation or suspicion levied towards you. You can’t mud the waters by claiming you got framed as since you can’t be a Scorned target then it’s extremely unlikely that a Mystic or Noble got converted, and you’re less likely to get players on the fence as if a neutral claim ends up executed then it’s no loss to BD.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ShadowKnight" data-post="30" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shadowknight/40/5439_2.png" class="avatar"> ShadowKnight:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not to mention that Neutral classes being viable claimspaces is a slight buff to Neutral Killers against faction-detecting abilities.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In short, claiming Neutral as a chainsaw defense against a 2-use secondary ability from a class that may not even spawn or even survive until the late-game. Genius. You’re far more likely to get stuck in a 3-neut game than being peeked by an Observer. And there’s also the fact that if it’s already mid-late game and a NK is still out loose, BD will start by culling off the neutral claims.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 02:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="w1ngz" data-post="27" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/w1ngz/40/9182_2.png" class="avatar"> w1ngz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d be curious to see a chart of Merc win rates since Sellsword’s inclusion to see if others are having similar experiences as I am.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThroneOfLiesGame/comments/8t0rw9/this_weeks_charts_not_pinned_this_time/" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Here.</a> Mercs don’t need any buffs as their win rate is insanely high at the low sixties.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="w1ngz" data-post="27" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/w1ngz/40/9182_2.png" class="avatar"> w1ngz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But - “helpful” is not a universal definition. No offense intended, but linguistically, this “rule of thumb” needs clarification, especially if being used to determine balancing needs; please define Helpful as it applies here, so that we can reference it for the rest of this thread; it’d be quite…Helpful <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Can block people from visiting and prevent kills/conversion, has one night of night immunity, and basically need to see the Unseen or Cult lose in order to win.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="w1ngz" data-post="27" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/w1ngz/40/9182_2.png" class="avatar"> w1ngz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Helpful in the EYES of BD?.. well, now that’s another matter entirely, and while it seems that there are independently plenty of players who support Merc’s on their BD team, I have yet to see evidence of that in the actual game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It really depends on how you are playing. If you claim early and cooperate with BD, scumread Unseen/Cult members and get them lynch, help BD by properly Shielding and Guarding, and whatnot then you won’t be executed. If you claim d5 without doing anything while expecting BD to carry you, then that’s a surefire way to get executed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 01:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RawkHawk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d argue that neutral claims shouldn’t be viable at all. Simply put, neutrals never have BD’s goal. Yes inquisitor and merc have goals that line up with BD, but at no point are they forced to work with them. Neutrals are risky because of this, and bd should only trust them in times of desperation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-33</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alch is helpful to the BD.</p>
<p>It heals.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[w1ngz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>do you mind including some “Helpful” content? like the reference?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But having more claimable Neutral classes <em>as well as</em> BD classes being less confirmable is the best of both worlds, as it reduces the odds of that scenario happening by providing more options for everyone. Not to mention that Neutral classes being viable claimspaces is a slight buff to Neutral Killers against faction-detecting abilities.</p>
<p>Neutral claims should be riskier/less trustworthy than BD claims, but they shouldn’t be altogether invalid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is one.</p>
<p>Discord there is a image</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RawkHawk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re not exactly wrong here, but that’s true for neutrals as well. 2 alchs or 2 mercs pop up? The other guy claiming it is lying. Heck, if you get one alch, a merc, and then a fool dies, you know any more neutral claims are evil. It’s a lot better to have claim able BD classes than neutrals, as neutrals have a lower hard limit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[w1ngz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d be curious to see a chart of Merc win rates since Sellsword’s inclusion to see if others are having similar experiences as I am.<br>
I’m not a pro, but I do have hundreds of hours in game, so not <em>entirely</em> a noob either <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
The 2/3 rule is great and I’ve seen it each time it’s been posted…<br>
But - “helpful” is not a universal definition. No offense intended, but linguistically, this “rule of thumb” needs clarification, especially if being used to determine balancing needs; please define Helpful as it applies here, so that we can reference it for the rest of this thread; it’d be quite…Helpful <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
Reason it needs defining here is because it’s an opinion-based defintion. Sure, I think Merc is hugely helpful. But how are you asking the Average Moon2sub to weigh that when they load a game with no reference point?<br>
Helpful to BD? Undoubtedly! I believe Merc is one of the strongest BD assets!<br>
Helpful in the EYES of BD?.. well, now that’s another matter entirely, and while it seems that there are independently plenty of players who support Merc’s on their BD team, I have yet to see evidence of that in the actual game.<br>
Forums != Gameplay; so let’s see some statistics! Those stats should really actually tell dev’s all they need to know on this issue, tbh. I’m just making some noise to call attention to it <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Alice" data-post="25" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/alice/40/32176_2.png" class="avatar"> Alice:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Or add more BD-aligned classes that are difficult to confirm. BD-sided neutrals in general are pretty meh as the entire point of neutrals is to serve as wild-cards with their own goal in mind.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can do both! And Neutrals can be both, too.</p>
<p>The Mercenary, Inquisitor and Alchemist’s goals are cleverly designed, in that while there is encouragement to side with BD, it’s not mandatory. If they are fine-tuned/reworked to a satisfactory point, they could become decent wild cards that BD is tempted to keep around and evils can claim as.</p>
<p>Having <em>only</em> more BD classes leads to a very “roll of the dice” claimspace for evils, where they might be forced to claim early and later executed on the spot when it’s revealed that 2 of the classes they claimed as were already present in the game. Sure, the situation is rarer the more overall BD classes there are, but with some classes being guaranteed, others being unique and others being easy to confirm, the pool of viable BD claims needs to expand dramatically for that to be viable. It’s a lot easier to improve the helpful Neutral classes instead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 23:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Old Mercenary meta was basically to let your first contract die and the re-contract the Prince or a confirmed neut that nobody would bother such as an Alchemist or the Inquisitor. It was an interesting concept but in practice the idea was terrible. Plus, it was stupidly easy to confirm so you couldn’t fake it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Anarys" data-post="12" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/invoker-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Anarys:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I strongly think that mercenary should be able to choose which faction to side with like the alchemist but they can only have support/defensive abilities.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They’d by default just side with BD as the current win-rate is roughly split 52/38/10 for BD/Unseen or Cult/NK. It’s far more reliant to just side with BD.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ShadowKnight" data-post="23" data-topic="68348">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shadowknight/40/5439_2.png" class="avatar"> ShadowKnight:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There need to be claimable neutral classes to avoid a dearth of claimspace.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or add more BD-aligned classes that are difficult to confirm. BD-sided neutrals in general are pretty meh as the entire point of neutrals is to serve as wild-cards with their own goal in mind.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 23:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Restoring Merc Viability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He’s both 1 and 2. Helpful essentially means that BD wants to have them around. Since Mercenaries cannot win with the Unseen/Cult and have abilities that favor BD such as Shield, then he falls under 2. If he’s given 3 he’d become too strong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 23:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68348-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/restoring-merc-viability/68348.rss">Restoring Merc Viability</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
