<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757</link>
    <description>**The Conqueror (Neutral Killer) - An exiled Knight hellbent on destroying the Kingdom.**

**Passive Ability 1: Reinforced Armor**
Immune to death at night. 

**Passive Ability 2: Determination**
Immune to most occupation and redirection abilities.

**Day Ability 1: Mark For Death (2 uses)**
Target a player for death, guaranteeing that you will kill them. (Bypasses night immunity, occupying, and healing).

**Day Ability 2 (Optional): Haemmorhage (4 uses)**
Cause a player to bleed. They will die in two nights.

**Night Ability 1: Combat**
Best a player in combat, occupying and killing them.

**Night Ability 2: Outpost (2 uses)**
Removes bleeding and poison, and attacks anyone trying to attack you.

**Lore: Pity the Worthless**
The Knights of the Blue Dragon were known as stalwart, powerful figures, defenders of the kingdom - and proud to serve, to boot! Tales were woven up and down the streets of the training, trials and tribulations each soldier had been put through, each ensuring their place as Castle Adiart&#39;s most revered and respected fighters.

This person was no such Knight. Infamous for being weak and unreliable, they were always present when the Kingdom was at its most defenceless, and while correlation may not equal causation, the council agreed that they must have been actively sabotaging the Blue Dragon from the inside. Surely, nobody as incompetent as them would have been able to join the Knights&#39; ranks! With this decision reached, the pitiful Knight was brought to the King, and ordered to leave Castle Adiart, never to return upon penalty of death.

The now former Knight huffed and stewed as they were escorted towards the gates. In the shadows, the Mastermind shook their head, not even bothering with the figure. What would be the point in converting someone as lowly as them? They would only hinder our operations.

Peering out from under a trapdoor, the Seeker, too, decided against approaching the exiled. While tempting to keep around as a sacrifice for Mithras, the Blood God would almost certainly take it as an insult to have such a worthless being offered up to them, and angering such a powerful force was not on the Cult&#39;s agenda today.

And yet, through all the bodies and movement, the Knight glimpsed both of them, and became angered ever further. How could even the miscreants of society turn their back on them? Were they truly worth nothing to anybody in this sickening place?

The exiled person had seen enough. After being thrown out of the Castle Grounds, they began to wander off into the unknown, searching for days upon days to find a solution to themselves. And as time progressed, their anger turned into determination. _&quot;Sabotage? Worthless? Detrimental? How dare they!  I&#39;ll show them, I&#39;ll show them all! From top to bottom, as long as it takes me, I will prove to everyone - The council of Knights, the veiled Unseen, the bloody Cult, I shall show them all my capabilities, I will make them all regret ever passing me up!&quot;_

An encampment&#39;s light shimmered over the plains&#39; vast horizon. Quickly, the exiled rushed over to find a mysterious gentleman, tending to his wounds. Alongside him lay his armor, the likes of which the former Knight had never seen before - reinforced with a plethora of gemstones and ores to an impenetrable point. The figure tilted his head up to look at his recent guest, and in one swift motion raised up and put his steel up to the neck of the worthless being.

_&quot;I will give you five seconds to explain to me why I shouldn&#39;t slit your throat right now.&quot;_

Hopelessly, the exiled spluttered out what they could out of their own nervous breaths.

_&quot;I&#39;m... gah, I&#39;m... I&#39;m in exile, I haven&#39;t seen anyone in days, I just thought-&quot;_

The mysterious man shoved them to the ground and pointed his sword at the neck of the Knight.

_&quot;...Keep talking.&quot;_

And so the Knight explained their situation, the grievances they had faced, the ignorance of the Blue Dragon, and the sheer refusal of the Cult and the Unseen to even have him amongst their ranks. And all the while the mystery man listened, nodding along - in agreement, perhaps? Or maybe he just enjoyed a good story. In either case, he withdrew his sword from in front of the Knight, and slid across another blade in the direction of the exiled.

_&quot;Pick it up.&quot;_

_&quot;Ex-excuse me?&quot;_

_&quot;I said pick it up. And take these as well, you&#39;ll need them.&quot;_

The man chucked a set of armor towards the Knight - the same type of armor they had laid eyes on upon reaching the camp. Donning the new equipment, they were swivelled round by the mysterious man and lead towards a set of training dummies he had set up as the Knight was getting prepared The exiled stood there, but instead of being bewildered, they began to look focussed, prepared. Almost as if they were expecting this to happen to them at any moment during their travels. The man pointed towards the dummies.

_&quot;That one? That&#39;s the one who said you were a detriment to your unit.&quot;_

_&quot;That one? That&#39;s the one who said you weren&#39;t even worthy as a sacrifice.&quot;_

_&quot;That one? That&#39;s the one who said you would only slow down their meticulous takeover.&quot;_

And as the exiled built their anger, recounting the hurtful memories of their past, the mysterious man pointed to another dummy, larger than the others.

_&quot;That one? That&#39;s the very man who exiled you from Castle Adiart. Now go forth, my trainee. Go forth and deliver unto them sweet justice. Go forth... and conquer them all.&quot;_</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlueStorm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Updated Outpost to only attack any visitors attempting to attack you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71757-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757.rss">The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lightsin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now Traveling to: For Honor</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer) - An exiled Knight hellbent on destroying the Kingdom.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Named after my For Honor Main, so kudos to you, my dude.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 1: Reinforced Armor</strong><br>
Immune to death at night.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t really need to say much here tbh.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 2: Determination</strong><br>
Immune to most occupation and redirection abilities.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Maybe combine with the other passive to create kind of like a Sorcerer?<br>
or not, since possessor didn’t do it…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1: Mark For Death (2 uses)</strong><br>
Target a player for death, guaranteeing that you will kill them. (Bypasses night immunity, occupying, and healing).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>glad there’s a way to bypass death immunity, as thats the only thing i hate about possessor.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2 (Optional): Haemmorhage (4 uses)</strong><br>
Cause a player to bleed. They will die in two nights.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>adds more KPN. you could try making it cured in 2 nights(since it’ll distract the healers)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1: Combat</strong><br>
Best a player in combat, occupying and killing them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Gotta love that Medieval Warfare</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2: Outpost (2 uses)</strong><br>
Removes bleeding and poison, and attacks all visitors.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and TOS Vet. (yet could let you claim hunter, except no wolf)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BlueStorm" data-post="1" data-topic="71757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bluestorm/40/22263_2.png" class="avatar"> BlueStorm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lore: Pity the Worthless</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>honestly, i’m not a lore kinda guy, but it’s good. makes you sympathize with the dude.<br>
(even though I’m fine with being a Reaper of Corax, here to rid the castle of all the Heretics)</p>
<p>but to be honest<br>
the KPN can be very high, which i don’t know if thats good or not.</p>
<p>total KPN:<br>
1 bleed kill + Outpost = 3 KPN, and thats only if you get 2 visitors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 23:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71757-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757.rss">The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlueStorm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Updated Outpost to attack all visitors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 04:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71757-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757.rss">The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Find a way to remove the RNG from Outpost.</p>
<p>For example:<br>
Killing all visitors (kinda like CoD)<br>
Killing one visitor only if there is exactly one<br>
Killing any amount of a spacific kind of visitor (Attackers, Investigatives, ect)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 02:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71757-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757.rss">The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlueStorm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Conqueror (Neutral Killer) - An exiled Knight hellbent on destroying the Kingdom.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 1: Reinforced Armor</strong><br>
Immune to death at night.</p>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 2: Determination</strong><br>
Immune to most occupation and redirection abilities.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1: Mark For Death (2 uses)</strong><br>
Target a player for death, guaranteeing that you will kill them. (Bypasses night immunity, occupying, and healing).</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2 (Optional): Haemmorhage (4 uses)</strong><br>
Cause a player to bleed. They will die in two nights.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1: Combat</strong><br>
Best a player in combat, occupying and killing them.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2: Outpost (2 uses)</strong><br>
Removes bleeding and poison, and attacks anyone trying to attack you.</p>
<p><strong>Lore: Pity the Worthless</strong><br>
The Knights of the Blue Dragon were known as stalwart, powerful figures, defenders of the kingdom - and proud to serve, to boot! Tales were woven up and down the streets of the training, trials and tribulations each soldier had been put through, each ensuring their place as Castle Adiart’s most revered and respected fighters.</p>
<p>This person was no such Knight. Infamous for being weak and unreliable, they were always present when the Kingdom was at its most defenceless, and while correlation may not equal causation, the council agreed that they must have been actively sabotaging the Blue Dragon from the inside. Surely, nobody as incompetent as them would have been able to join the Knights’ ranks! With this decision reached, the pitiful Knight was brought to the King, and ordered to leave Castle Adiart, never to return upon penalty of death.</p>
<p>The now former Knight huffed and stewed as they were escorted towards the gates. In the shadows, the Mastermind shook their head, not even bothering with the figure. What would be the point in converting someone as lowly as them? They would only hinder our operations.</p>
<p>Peering out from under a trapdoor, the Seeker, too, decided against approaching the exiled. While tempting to keep around as a sacrifice for Mithras, the Blood God would almost certainly take it as an insult to have such a worthless being offered up to them, and angering such a powerful force was not on the Cult’s agenda today.</p>
<p>And yet, through all the bodies and movement, the Knight glimpsed both of them, and became angered ever further. How could even the miscreants of society turn their back on them? Were they truly worth nothing to anybody in this sickening place?</p>
<p>The exiled person had seen enough. After being thrown out of the Castle Grounds, they began to wander off into the unknown, searching for days upon days to find a solution to themselves. And as time progressed, their anger turned into determination. <em>“Sabotage? Worthless? Detrimental? How dare they!  I’ll show them, I’ll show them all! From top to bottom, as long as it takes me, I will prove to everyone - The council of Knights, the veiled Unseen, the bloody Cult, I shall show them all my capabilities, I will make them all regret ever passing me up!”</em></p>
<p>An encampment’s light shimmered over the plains’ vast horizon. Quickly, the exiled rushed over to find a mysterious gentleman, tending to his wounds. Alongside him lay his armor, the likes of which the former Knight had never seen before - reinforced with a plethora of gemstones and ores to an impenetrable point. The figure tilted his head up to look at his recent guest, and in one swift motion raised up and put his steel up to the neck of the worthless being.</p>
<p><em>“I will give you five seconds to explain to me why I shouldn’t slit your throat right now.”</em></p>
<p>Hopelessly, the exiled spluttered out what they could out of their own nervous breaths.</p>
<p><em>“I’m… gah, I’m… I’m in exile, I haven’t seen anyone in days, I just thought-”</em></p>
<p>The mysterious man shoved them to the ground and pointed his sword at the neck of the Knight.</p>
<p><em>“…Keep talking.”</em></p>
<p>And so the Knight explained their situation, the grievances they had faced, the ignorance of the Blue Dragon, and the sheer refusal of the Cult and the Unseen to even have him amongst their ranks. And all the while the mystery man listened, nodding along - in agreement, perhaps? Or maybe he just enjoyed a good story. In either case, he withdrew his sword from in front of the Knight, and slid across another blade in the direction of the exiled.</p>
<p><em>“Pick it up.”</em></p>
<p><em>“Ex-excuse me?”</em></p>
<p><em>“I said pick it up. And take these as well, you’ll need them.”</em></p>
<p>The man chucked a set of armor towards the Knight - the same type of armor they had laid eyes on upon reaching the camp. Donning the new equipment, they were swivelled round by the mysterious man and lead towards a set of training dummies he had set up as the Knight was getting prepared The exiled stood there, but instead of being bewildered, they began to look focussed, prepared. Almost as if they were expecting this to happen to them at any moment during their travels. The man pointed towards the dummies.</p>
<p><em>“That one? That’s the one who said you were a detriment to your unit.”</em></p>
<p><em>“That one? That’s the one who said you weren’t even worthy as a sacrifice.”</em></p>
<p><em>“That one? That’s the one who said you would only slow down their meticulous takeover.”</em></p>
<p>And as the exiled built their anger, recounting the hurtful memories of their past, the mysterious man pointed to another dummy, larger than the others.</p>
<p><em>“That one? That’s the very man who exiled you from Castle Adiart. Now go forth, my trainee. Go forth and deliver unto them sweet justice. Go forth… and conquer them all.”</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 01:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71757-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-conqueror-neutral-killer/71757.rss">The Conqueror (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
