<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>{Class Suggestion) The Devil and the Minion. Rework</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-devil-and-the-minion-rework/36357</link>
    <description>Name - The Devil
Class NK

Win condition: The Reaper has failed you. The Devil decides to go up there and murder everyone himself  

Passive 1 - Pure evil - Night immune and occu immune 

Passive 2 - Back from Hell - if you die then you will consume your living minions soul if you have one

Day Ability 1 - Deep cut - make a player bleed. The message sent to the player says that they will die in two days but because The Devil gave you a deep cut you will die in one day{2 uses}

Day Ability 2 - A New Face - Take a body from Hell allowing you to transform into any role for the night coming up and the next morning. Ex. Picks Butler to become. The next morning he will be able to poison king and that night he will be able to occu someone. If you are checked the night you do this then your will appear as the faction you&#39;ve picked that night{1 use}. 

Night Ability 1 - Satins left hand - convert a non unique class into a Neutral Minion. {Unlimited uses} {Max 1 minion at a time} {3 day cool down}

Night Ability 2 - Depths of Hell - catch a player on fire this night burning them alive. The fire is so big that the players next to him can smell the smoke of the fire. (Unlimited use)

Ex. The Devil set 4 on fire. Players 3 and 5 will get a message saying that &quot;you smelled smoke in the air&quot; or &quot;you see a big light coming from the other room&quot;

Name - The Minion
Neutral 
Win condition: Have the Devil win at all cost

Passive 1 - evil runs in the family - You will know who The Devil is and what he does at night

Passive 2 - if you&#39;re the first Minion then you will have 2 &quot;strait to Hell&quot; uses. If not then you will have 1

Day Ability 1 - known tourcher - when he use this Ability then you won&#39;t go to jail tonight even if the prince selected you to {2 uses}(Notes: this will by you a day or two to give The Devil another day to either recharge his abilities or survive a bit longer)

Day Ability 2 - Slow learner - make a player bleed, but it will take 3 days for them to bleed to death instead of 2. (The message to the player will say that tou have 2 days to live){3uses}

Night ability 1 - Strait to Hell - You send the player that The Devil killed tonight strait to Hell. Making it so nobody will know what the players class was and you also steal their log, making it so you can read it when ever you want(Similar to the Nobles snoop Ability)

Night ability 2 - taking the blame - when you use this Ability then you will go and murder the player instead of the Devil.(because you will be killing the player there will be no fire showing the neibors rooms)(The Devil will know when you do this action){2 uses}

Notes: I think this is a new take on the NK. Origannaly I was going to have him be able to have 2 minions and talk in a meeting at night.(similar to the unseen/cult).he was also not going to be able to kill and the minions would just be given a night ability to bleed. But I feel this works better. If you got any questions or comments please tell me below</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 17:08:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-devil-and-the-minion-rework/36357.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>{Class Suggestion) The Devil and the Minion. Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Name - The Devil<br>
Class NK</p>
<p>Win condition: The Reaper has failed you. The Devil decides to go up there and murder everyone himself</p>
<p>Passive 1 - Pure evil - Night immune and occu immune</p>
<p>Passive 2 - Back from Hell - if you die then you will consume your living minions soul if you have one</p>
<p>Day Ability 1 - Deep cut - make a player bleed. The message sent to the player says that they will die in two days but because The Devil gave you a deep cut you will die in one day{2 uses}</p>
<p>Day Ability 2 - A New Face - Take a body from Hell allowing you to transform into any role for the night coming up and the next morning. Ex. Picks Butler to become. The next morning he will be able to poison king and that night he will be able to occu someone. If you are checked the night you do this then your will appear as the faction you’ve picked that night{1 use}.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1 - Satins left hand - convert a non unique class into a Neutral Minion. {Unlimited uses} {Max 1 minion at a time} {3 day cool down}</p>
<p>Night Ability 2 - Depths of Hell - catch a player on fire this night burning them alive. The fire is so big that the players next to him can smell the smoke of the fire. (Unlimited use)</p>
<p>Ex. The Devil set 4 on fire. Players 3 and 5 will get a message saying that “you smelled smoke in the air” or “you see a big light coming from the other room”</p>
<p>Name - The Minion<br>
Neutral<br>
Win condition: Have the Devil win at all cost</p>
<p>Passive 1 - evil runs in the family - You will know who The Devil is and what he does at night</p>
<p>Passive 2 - if you’re the first Minion then you will have 2 “strait to Hell” uses. If not then you will have 1</p>
<p>Day Ability 1 - known tourcher - when he use this Ability then you won’t go to jail tonight even if the prince selected you to {2 uses}(Notes: this will by you a day or two to give The Devil another day to either recharge his abilities or survive a bit longer)</p>
<p>Day Ability 2 - Slow learner - make a player bleed, but it will take 3 days for them to bleed to death instead of 2. (The message to the player will say that tou have 2 days to live){3uses}</p>
<p>Night ability 1 - Strait to Hell - You send the player that The Devil killed tonight strait to Hell. Making it so nobody will know what the players class was and you also steal their log, making it so you can read it when ever you want(Similar to the Nobles snoop Ability)</p>
<p>Night ability 2 - taking the blame - when you use this Ability then you will go and murder the player instead of the Devil.(because you will be killing the player there will be no fire showing the neibors rooms)(The Devil will know when you do this action){2 uses}</p>
<p>Notes: I think this is a new take on the NK. Origannaly I was going to have him be able to have 2 minions and talk in a meeting at night.(similar to the unseen/cult).he was also not going to be able to kill and the minions would just be given a night ability to bleed. But I feel this works better. If you got any questions or comments please tell me below</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-devil-and-the-minion-rework/36357/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-devil-and-the-minion-rework/36357/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 17:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-36357-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-devil-and-the-minion-rework/36357.rss">{Class Suggestion) The Devil and the Minion. Rework</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
