<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Scorned (Class and Lore Suggestion)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156</link>
    <description>**The Scorned**- Wildcard
_To prevent the spawn of demons across the landscape, you have been tasked with orchestrating a public sacrifice of a single Blue-Dragon loyalist to Mithras.  How could you get a respectable group to perform a sacrifice? Dress it up as a public execution. There&#39;s only one person whose death could please both you and the blood God, who whispers in your ears. One person who carried out the death of your beloved sister, a passionate anti-communist and member of the Unseen. This would be a most beneficent deal._

**Goal: Get your target publicly executed, or destroy the Blue Dragon**
Note: If the Blue Dragon loses whether you are dead or alive, you still win.
If your target is lynched while you are alive or dead, you win.

**Passive: Obsessed:** Your target is [TargetName, TargetRole]
Your target cannot have Royal blood, or be a Priest (Given balance changes, any other roles can be added or removed to the list of roles that cannot be targeted)
You are immune to Death and Conversion
You know everything that happens to your target (who visits them, who they visit, and what happens to them **but not who does what action**)


**Passive: Rite of Mithras:** If your target is put on the stand, and the amount of pardon votes is equal to the amount of execution votes, your target will suffer immediate hemorrhagic fever, and the crowds will watch your target bleed to death with awe and confusion.

**Day: Unlimited Use: Point**: Force someone to vote against someone else.
You can only use this once per vote. (ex: You can&#39;t rapidly switch it around, but if someone is voted up, then down, you can use it again)
(This can either be used to help stroke up votes (Risky) 
Or it can be used to be the final vote in the accusal of your target (Safer)) 

**Day: Unlimited: Silence:** Disable someone&#39;s voice for the day. Cooldown of one day.
(This can be used as a last ditch effort to hush your target up or someone who is trying to protect them) 

**Night: Unlimited: Whispers of Mithras:** Link your mind with another&#39;s, allowing you to anonymously talk to them for the rest of the night.

**Night:Unlimited:Stalk** Instead of knowing who your target visits and who visits your target, Stalk a chosen victim, knowing who visits them, who they visit.





 ___________________________________Words, Explanation, Discussion, Opinion_______

This is how the Scorned role should be, to me.

This WildCard is the combination of Investigation and Social power to take down your target. Use them well, and if they don&#39;t suit you, simply talk your way through it. You have great power, but faking a scumread on someone is good as well. 

In regards to strategy, 
1st thing, you should always wait until  someone else dies before you accuse your target at the least.If you accuse someone of being a role that cannot exist in the current game, you&#39;re dead and you have to hope the enemies of the Blue Dragon will drag your disemboweled corpse to victory.

2nd, Have some evidence, and make use of your abilities to make sure that not all of it is false. You have to claim a somewhat believable role to give your target the challenge of defending him/herself instead of just calling you Scorned and hopping off of the stand. You can claim to be an Observer, or you can be risky and claim another role.  (You&#39;ll be able to claim Psychic easily if Visions and Telepathy are removed. They&#39;re very overpowered abilities)

3rd, When using Point early, don&#39;t use it unless you&#39;re absolutely sure they&#39;re either reaped or away from their keyboard. If they know they&#39;ve been used, they&#39;ll either search for a Psychic (if your case is good enough), or you&#39;re dead. However, if you use it as the last vote, even if they do figure it out, they can&#39;t say they were used as a vote unless your target is pardoned, and at that point, it&#39;s best if you lay low. 

____________________________________________________________________________

The Scorned has three targets

**Problems with that**
You&#39;re more dependent on the Unseen and Cult- If you can&#39;t get your target hung, the Unseen will have to take care of it, and sometimes that doesn&#39;t work. If they&#39;re converted by the Unseen or Cult, I&#39;ll assume you need to betray your &quot;team&quot; to vote them out. Essentially, you don&#39;t know what team you have to &quot;ride&quot; with, and this constant switching of behavior will out you as a &quot;Fool&quot;, and you will be executed effective immediately by the nearest Prince (Or as a fake fool which will lead to your intestines painting the walls) 

The skill aspect is less visible- Yes, you can scheme to get someone lynched, but how often will that work? Probably once a game (Assuming most or all targets are Blue Dragon, because otherwise would topple the balance and have your role as a &quot;almost protected&quot; class of neutral (like the Alchemist) in which some don&#39;t trust you but overall you stay as long as you don&#39;t cause trouble (In the Alchemist&#39;s case, killing someone and not being a pet Doctor). Wanting someone dead should always be trouble.  Overall: the strategy is just &quot;get someone lynched, wait&quot;. 

Solution: 

One target that is not an instantly confirmed role, but is always good. 
-Any Blue Dragon role besides King, Psychic, Prince, Noble (Because that&#39;s two), Priest  (As roles are tweaked, and suggestions are made, Roles can be added and removed to the list of roles that shouldn&#39;t be the target) 

A side goal of ensuring the loss of the Blue Dragon
-If this target dies or you just can&#39;t get them executed, you still do this to win
This gets rid of the whole &quot;pet neutral&quot; aspect where someone can just say &quot;my target is this guy, he&#39;s Blue Dragon, don&#39;t hurt me&quot; scheme. That&#39;s pretty much the only strategy that shouldn&#39;t be employed (This strategy would make the BD like you in some cases, and protect the now-confirmed player. At this point, the King, regardless of faction would be forced to bend the knee as this random player is now the God-King. It is too much of a risk to kill him at night, converting him is the only way to get rid of him. Eventually if the Unseen/Cult begin to win, they may or may not lynch the target out of pity.) 

**Question: Should it be conversion immune?**
Tried to think of something where the answer is no, you see how far that went with all of the complications, I figure it should in fact be conversion immune considering it works with potential converters to win anyways. 

**Question: What should it actually, you know, do**
As a class that wants to get other roles killed, it is probably good to have some sort of investigative power to use and claim something.  Otherwise, there could be more disruptive and social abilities to sway the crowds to your whim.

**Question: What happens if the target is converted?**
You&#39;ve got two choices. I don&#39;t personally like this because then you can be a &quot;pet&quot; neutral, but it&#39;s only fair that if you do get him/her hung after your hard work framing him/her, even if he/she happened to get turned overnight, it&#39;s fair. And if you don&#39;t want to anymore, you help the evil side. At least you can&#39;t be a turncoat for the BD in the beginning.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 02:19:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Scorned (Class and Lore Suggestion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bounty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>&lt;3 thanks for putting the demon in</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 02:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2156-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156.rss">The Scorned (Class and Lore Suggestion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Scorned (Class and Lore Suggestion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If I am correct, the public announcement in discord says that they are testing “The Scorned”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 01:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2156-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156.rss">The Scorned (Class and Lore Suggestion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Scorned (Class and Lore Suggestion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Scorned</strong>- Wildcard<br>
<em>To prevent the spawn of demons across the landscape, you have been tasked with orchestrating a public sacrifice of a single Blue-Dragon loyalist to Mithras.  How could you get a respectable group to perform a sacrifice? Dress it up as a public execution. There’s only one person whose death could please both you and the blood God, who whispers in your ears. One person who carried out the death of your beloved sister, a passionate anti-communist and member of the Unseen. This would be a most beneficent deal.</em></p>
<p><strong>Goal: Get your target publicly executed, or destroy the Blue Dragon</strong><br>
Note: If the Blue Dragon loses whether you are dead or alive, you still win.<br>
If your target is lynched while you are alive or dead, you win.</p>
<p><strong>Passive: Obsessed:</strong> Your target is [TargetName, TargetRole]<br>
Your target cannot have Royal blood, or be a Priest (Given balance changes, any other roles can be added or removed to the list of roles that cannot be targeted)<br>
You are immune to Death and Conversion<br>
You know everything that happens to your target (who visits them, who they visit, and what happens to them <strong>but not who does what action</strong>)</p>
<p><strong>Passive: Rite of Mithras:</strong> If your target is put on the stand, and the amount of pardon votes is equal to the amount of execution votes, your target will suffer immediate hemorrhagic fever, and the crowds will watch your target bleed to death with awe and confusion.</p>
<p><strong>Day: Unlimited Use: Point</strong>: Force someone to vote against someone else.<br>
You can only use this once per vote. (ex: You can’t rapidly switch it around, but if someone is voted up, then down, you can use it again)<br>
(This can either be used to help stroke up votes (Risky)<br>
Or it can be used to be the final vote in the accusal of your target (Safer))</p>
<p><strong>Day: Unlimited: Silence:</strong> Disable someone’s voice for the day. Cooldown of one day.<br>
(This can be used as a last ditch effort to hush your target up or someone who is trying to protect them)</p>
<p><strong>Night: Unlimited: Whispers of Mithras:</strong> Link your mind with another’s, allowing you to anonymously talk to them for the rest of the night.</p>
<p><strong>Night:Unlimited:Stalk</strong> Instead of knowing who your target visits and who visits your target, Stalk a chosen victim, knowing who visits them, who they visit.</p>
<p>____________________________<em><strong><strong><strong>Words, Explanation, Discussion, Opinion</strong></strong></strong></em></p>
<p>This is how the Scorned role should be, to me.</p>
<p>This WildCard is the combination of Investigation and Social power to take down your target. Use them well, and if they don’t suit you, simply talk your way through it. You have great power, but faking a scumread on someone is good as well.</p>
<p>In regards to strategy,<br>
1st thing, you should always wait until  someone else dies before you accuse your target at the least.If you accuse someone of being a role that cannot exist in the current game, you’re dead and you have to hope the enemies of the Blue Dragon will drag your disemboweled corpse to victory.</p>
<p>2nd, Have some evidence, and make use of your abilities to make sure that not all of it is false. You have to claim a somewhat believable role to give your target the challenge of defending him/herself instead of just calling you Scorned and hopping off of the stand. You can claim to be an Observer, or you can be risky and claim another role.  (You’ll be able to claim Psychic easily if Visions and Telepathy are removed. They’re very overpowered abilities)</p>
<p>3rd, When using Point early, don’t use it unless you’re absolutely sure they’re either reaped or away from their keyboard. If they know they’ve been used, they’ll either search for a Psychic (if your case is good enough), or you’re dead. However, if you use it as the last vote, even if they do figure it out, they can’t say they were used as a vote unless your target is pardoned, and at that point, it’s best if you lay low.</p>
<hr>
<p>The Scorned has three targets</p>
<p><strong>Problems with that</strong><br>
You’re more dependent on the Unseen and Cult- If you can’t get your target hung, the Unseen will have to take care of it, and sometimes that doesn’t work. If they’re converted by the Unseen or Cult, I’ll assume you need to betray your “team” to vote them out. Essentially, you don’t know what team you have to “ride” with, and this constant switching of behavior will out you as a “Fool”, and you will be executed effective immediately by the nearest Prince (Or as a fake fool which will lead to your intestines painting the walls)</p>
<p>The skill aspect is less visible- Yes, you can scheme to get someone lynched, but how often will that work? Probably once a game (Assuming most or all targets are Blue Dragon, because otherwise would topple the balance and have your role as a “almost protected” class of neutral (like the Alchemist) in which some don’t trust you but overall you stay as long as you don’t cause trouble (In the Alchemist’s case, killing someone and not being a pet Doctor). Wanting someone dead should always be trouble.  Overall: the strategy is just “get someone lynched, wait”.</p>
<p>Solution:</p>
<p>One target that is not an instantly confirmed role, but is always good.<br>
-Any Blue Dragon role besides King, Psychic, Prince, Noble (Because that’s two), Priest  (As roles are tweaked, and suggestions are made, Roles can be added and removed to the list of roles that shouldn’t be the target)</p>
<p>A side goal of ensuring the loss of the Blue Dragon<br>
-If this target dies or you just can’t get them executed, you still do this to win<br>
This gets rid of the whole “pet neutral” aspect where someone can just say “my target is this guy, he’s Blue Dragon, don’t hurt me” scheme. That’s pretty much the only strategy that shouldn’t be employed (This strategy would make the BD like you in some cases, and protect the now-confirmed player. At this point, the King, regardless of faction would be forced to bend the knee as this random player is now the God-King. It is too much of a risk to kill him at night, converting him is the only way to get rid of him. Eventually if the Unseen/Cult begin to win, they may or may not lynch the target out of pity.)</p>
<p><strong>Question: Should it be conversion immune?</strong><br>
Tried to think of something where the answer is no, you see how far that went with all of the complications, I figure it should in fact be conversion immune considering it works with potential converters to win anyways.</p>
<p><strong>Question: What should it actually, you know, do</strong><br>
As a class that wants to get other roles killed, it is probably good to have some sort of investigative power to use and claim something.  Otherwise, there could be more disruptive and social abilities to sway the crowds to your whim.</p>
<p><strong>Question: What happens if the target is converted?</strong><br>
You’ve got two choices. I don’t personally like this because then you can be a “pet” neutral, but it’s only fair that if you do get him/her hung after your hard work framing him/her, even if he/she happened to get turned overnight, it’s fair. And if you don’t want to anymore, you help the evil side. At least you can’t be a turncoat for the BD in the beginning.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 23:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2156-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-scorned-class-and-lore-suggestion/2156.rss">The Scorned (Class and Lore Suggestion)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
