<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361</link>
    <description>While the game is enjoyable to play as of version 1.12, I have some suggestions:

**King**
I know it is in the guide, but putting the 65%-35% in class description as well would be a good idea.

**Alchemist**
Should be able to target the King with both potions. They are neutrals, give them some more freedom to act.

**Mystic**
They are very bland right now. A Prince-light. I know many don’t want back ’talk to dead’ because it was such a hard counter to evils (Possessor mainly). And I think I agree with that. Being able to talk to dead players decreases the impact of dying. But I also see many dedicated players in dead chat wishing they’d have a little extra to do. Games feel a lot less impactful right now. Dead? Onto the next game!
Suggestions:
* Make Mystic unique
* Remove Link Minds
* Give Conduit 5 uses
* Change (or clarify?) Private Matter: … hidden from the public (including from Nobles using Maid Spy).
* Add night-time ability: Séance (3 uses): Select any BD member that died this game. He/she will get a selection of 3 premade ‘deathnotes’ to show the mystic. This selection of 3 will be from a collection of 20+ premade deathnotes. The dead BD member can show one or none of those 3 deathnotes. These notes won’t include numbers or texts, just drawings to interpret. If a dead BD member is targeted more than once, he/she gets a new set of 3 options to pick from each time. Yes, I know this suggestion is a stretch from a programming stance, but it would make communicating with the dead possible but less powerful and completely unique. This suggestion is inspired by the Mysterium board game btw. As a general quality of life measure: Upon dead, a BD member will be informed whether or not there is at least one Mystic active. (So he knows he can safely leave if there is none active)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 07:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[techwolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Heres the thing its not going to be made since the devs are done with dead interaction</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 07:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NosduhYons]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Séance seems very cool and a good change. I think it would be interesting if what the Mystic could do was select  a category such as how they died (This would be of balance, for example there would be no deathnote that could be selected for poss jump, just possibly poss). They would then need to decipher something, I think this may make Séance more useful. I don’t know that it would be easy to program or any of the other categories that  the Mystic could choose from. At the moment I think that the Séance presented is too weak and would ultimately turn Mystic into a simpler class that doesn’t have much use. I do think that Mystic currently needs to have some attention. It would also be interesting to see how Séance would effects classes such as Illusionists and Apostles, if Séance would be included or missing from one or both. I think that, although slightly off-topic, something should be done with Illusionist to make it so that you don’t need to automatically change your claim and get a new will because you were converted.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 02:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ulkesh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First, since Séance is more like an ‘extra’ for the Mystic that isn’t overly powerful, it is not that big a deal.</p>
<p>Second, that’s why I suggested that BD upon death would be informed that a Mystic is active. Surely it won’t convince all to stay, but it may help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>At the same time however, most dead people will be gone</p>
<p>So good luck getting a successful Seance off</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 07:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ah ive been playing mystic wrong</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 04:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes they do. You can always get one of those people to claim by saying. I’ll give you a cookie if you claim. Always works</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 04:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes. But .No .Not .Anymore. Becuase. Nobody. Claims. To. Mystic. <strong>OOF</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 04:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dead. Should. Stay. Dead.</p>
<p>Mystics are great at gathering info.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 04:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[techwolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well like i said they dont plan to <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> which sucks</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 04:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think it’s fine that he voices his need for death interaction in some way. Many of us still hold the same sentiment and if enough people speak up about it, the developers might change their mind about their current stance on it. I do agree that this form is needlessly complicated, but I honestly saw nothing wrong with the old incarnations of death interaction.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 04:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[techwolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually it was also on the psychics old passive cause someone dead who was bd could have been mind warper or something</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ulkesh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for linking the post.</p>
<p>I understand their reasoning and most likely they won’t follow up on my suggestion. But their decision was based on actual talking with living people after death and dead people acting as Death Knights. Both were extremely impactful and rather detrimental if no targets were available. That was indeed more like a hostage situation. What I’m suggesting is far less drastic. It is a very limited interaction with limited use. Séance is not where the strength of the Mystic lies. So not being able to use it, doesn’t impact the power level of the Mystic that much (you can’t outright communicate with dead people). Also, I think this unique way of communication could actually be an incentive for people to stay after they die.</p>
<p>I also wonder whether it is just coincidence that we see more people leaving while alive these days. Leaving once you’re dead makes you less invested in individual games. They tend to be more fast paced and less impactful. So less barrier for some to leave even while they are still alive (and don’t like their class or how things are going).</p>
<p>Lastly, I don’t think Mystic needs Link Minds if he/she already has Conduit. Being able to link 2 players with  potentially gives double the information each night. (as such players could give info to one another). And again, Conduit is far more unique then Link Minds, which is quite similar to jailing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[techwolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>question “Why remove dead people interactions from living abilities?”</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Dead chat/interactions has always been random and unreliable. There’s no fun factor in forcing people to stay after dead to claim your gp. Died night 1? Still get some gp out of it without waiting til the end.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>We now offer a % gp after the match ends if you left while dead, which discourages players to stay even-more if they don’t want to (most players left or afk’d immediately after death, anyway)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>We want dead chat to be more of a spectate/optional thing than being a core part of the game. It’s one of those things that’s “cool at first”, but you realize very fast is both useless and frustrating~ for example, we couldn’t reward a % leaving while dead while these features existed.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>TL;DR: We don’t want to hold your gp hostage by making you stay (if dead). Dead interactions were unreliable and too random (mostly bad-random). Died n1? np - quit, queue back up, get gp later when the old game ends.  What he said</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[techwolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dude xblade littrely said in news its not returning im not saying its bad for a return of it but its littrely not happening and mystic needs link minds to find classes</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ulkesh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Luxx" data-post="12" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/luxx/40/1222_2.png" class="avatar"> Luxx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>B, I didn’t know for sure if they could or couldn’t. OP suggested they couldn’t so I will apologize for that mistake.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I suppose it could be read that way, but my OP meant to say: The Alchemist should be able to arget the King with both potions… <em>as opposed to just the healing potion he is currently able to use on the King.</em></p>
<p>I agree with <a class="mention" href="/u/solic">@Solic</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/nuclearburrito">@NuclearBurrito</a>: The king has plenty of counterplay now he has 6 guards and stepping up as Neutral isn’t all that powerful for reasons mentioned. Also note that ‘guaranteed neutral’ is in some cases an overstatement as well. And finally: Yes, the starting king can use OE on Alchemist, but trying to bomb the King is not the sole way of dealing with that threat. Offering the King assistance since you an win with him regardless of his alignment is also a decent move for an Alchemist.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/techwolves">@techwolves</a>: I know several people did not like the interaction with dead people because of the sheer impact it had on the game. The knowledge from dead people is extremely powerful. Still, there are also people that feel some limited assistance/interaction is a nice way to stay involved and emerged in a game even after you are killed off.</p>
<p>Also, I honestly don’t think my suggestion is that complex once implemented.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[techwolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The current mystic is fine we dont need to lose link minds alch used to do it in beta but people didnt like it and another thing they are done with dead intrraction</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 19:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Luxx" data-post="12" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/luxx/40/1222_2.png" class="avatar"> Luxx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A was in response to an old meta people used. It was a counter measure to it.<br>
Psycho King was the response to the meta where NKs would kill king and elect themselves as guaranteed Neutral king. There’s no reason to remove King’s Alch yolo bomb immunity and reopen the chance for that meta to re-appear.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think that meta would really apply here. Alch has less bombs than king has guards and even if he could kill the king N1 every game it doesn’t make nearly as much sense to actually follow through with that meta.</p>
<p>With the NK meta it was a way to eliminate the NK without having to actually go through the trouble of finding him.</p>
<p>Here the alch is already on your side as much as he would as king. So voting the alch has no benefit compared to voting a royal or other BD. Especially when you consider that Killing someone doesn’t prove crap because all scum can kill.</p>
<p>That and the alch has no reason to do this either because simply working with a king and thus getting 4 guards AND 4 stoneskins while also not painting a target on your back is a good thing.</p>
<p>TLDR: Alch has no more chance of causing this meta any more than Butler does now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 19:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="11" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A is impractical because anyone in their right mind would ignore the possable psycho king in favor of a royal or other BD.</p>
<p>B is false. You can heal king.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A was in response to an old meta people used. It was a counter measure to it.<br>
Psycho King was the response to the meta where NKs would kill king and elect themselves as guaranteed Neutral king. There’s no reason to remove King’s Alch yolo bomb immunity and reopen the chance for that meta to re-appear.</p>
<p>B, I didn’t know for sure if they could or couldn’t. OP suggested they couldn’t so I will apologize for that mistake.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 16:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Luxx" data-post="8" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/luxx/40/1222_2.png" class="avatar"> Luxx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The reason Alchemist is unable to target King at all is due to A) Alchemists killing King and stepping up for guaranteed Neutral King and B) Not being able to heal for consistency (I assume at least lol)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A is impractical because anyone in their right mind would ignore the possable psycho king in favor of a royal or other BD.</p>
<p>B is false. You can heal king.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 16:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>King has plenty of counterplay with his 6 guards. This ruling no longer applies in the allies-less ToL meta. I think he should regain the ability to bomb king.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 15:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>King</p>
<p>I know it is in the guide, but putting the 65%-35% in class description as well would be a good idea.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Support</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Alchemist</p>
<p>Should be able to target the King with both potions. They are neutrals, give them some more freedom to act.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then alch will kill king any chance he can if he is starter. Since king can bypass alch stoneskin.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They are very bland right now. A Prince-light. I know many don’t want back ’talk to dead’ because it was such a hard counter to evils (Possessor mainly). And I think I agree with that. Being able to talk to dead players decreases the impact of dying. But I also see many dedicated players in dead chat wishing they’d have a little extra to do. Games feel a lot less impactful right now. Dead? Onto the next game!</p>
<p>Suggestions:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This rework is a bit complicated</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 15:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Alchemist</p>
<p>Should be able to target the King with both potions. They are neutrals, give them some more freedom to act.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The reason Alchemist is unable to target King at all is due to A) Alchemists killing King and stepping up for guaranteed Neutral King and B) Not being able to heal for consistency (I assume at least lol)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 14:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I know it is in the guide, but putting the 65%-35% in class description as well would be a good idea.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Alchemist</p>
<p>Should be able to target the King with both potions. They are neutrals, give them some more freedom to act.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes.  It doesn’t make sense that the alchemist can’t kill the king.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Mystic</p>
<p>They are very bland right now. A Prince-light. I know many don’t want back ’talk to dead’ because it was such a hard counter to evils (Possessor mainly). And I think I agree with that. Being able to talk to dead players decreases the impact of dying. But I also see many dedicated players in dead chat wishing they’d have a little extra to do. Games feel a lot less impactful right now. Dead? Onto the next game!</p>
<p>Suggestions:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is too complex.  I do agree that mystic needs a rework though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 13:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lily]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ulkesh" data-post="1" data-topic="60361">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Ulkesh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Alchemist</p>
<p>Should be able to target the King with both potions. They are neutrals, give them some more freedom to act.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Murica.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 13:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post 1.12 suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ulkesh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I completely missed that survey, thank you for mentioning it <a class="mention" href="/u/cheesyknives">@CheesyKnives</a> !</p>
<p>And… The options listed there are SO much better than what I suggested here, that I (shamefully) withdrew my CW suggestion from my initial post.</p>
<p>As far as the Noble is concerned, you are right. I removed this suggestion as well. Why change what is so much fun right now <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>On the Mystic:</p>
<ul>
<li>Conduit is kinda nice come to think of it. My suggestion now includes giving it 5 uses and removing Link Minds instead. Link Minds is a jail with no uber-occu and no possibity to exe after all. Conduit is more unique.</li>
<li>About Séance: I think the concept itself s really easy to grasp. But what to make of it is highly subjective and not auto-useful at all. Which is the idea. Also, this requires a different type of skill than the deduction based reasoning that is required for most of the rest of this game, which I like. (in fact, these interpretations are not much dependant on IQ at all)</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60361-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/post-1-12-suggestions/60361.rss">Post 1.12 suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
