<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429</link>
    <description>## The Silencer (Neutral Offensive)

**Lore:**
You&#39;re some crazy bard/singer or something that thinks their own voice is so beautiful that you think you&#39;re the only person in the world that&#39;s allowed to speak. 

**Objective:**
You win when everyone is dead or silenced. (Once everyone has been silenced that is alive you will win, even if you die later.)

**Passive 1: Compulsive singing**
Your voice is so divine, it would be a crime not to use it. Everytime you stay in your room you will sing.
If you do not take any actions at night (and you&#39;re not occupied or jailed) everyone who visits you will know who you are. 

**Day ability 1: The sound of Silence**
Nobody can hear others speak for 10 seconds. But they will hear themselves speak. (they won&#39;t get a notification about this) 2 uses.

**Night ability 1: Silence**
Remove a target&#39;s tongue. They will not be able to speak until they die. infinite uses

**Night ability 2: Silen... oops**
You try to remove a target&#39;s tongue, but you accidently kill them. Oops. 2 uses

## Notes:
Maybe silenced people and silencer should be able to talk with psychic since that&#39;s some mind reading voodoo. Dunno. 
Should probably not spawn with both reaper and possessor in one game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 22:52:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insert_Cancer_Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seems like a very straight forward class in my opinion, but maybe a little hard to win. People can just spam votes like they do with BM’r, confirming that there is a Silencer in the game. Overall, this seems like a very nice neutral, although it is obviously harder to win the more people there are, and if there is a Cult rather then an Unseen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 22:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3429-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grizzfang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Changes:</p>
<p>Can speak now.</p>
<p>New passive is basically there to force you to use your night abilities every night, but not in a way that makes it impossible for you to choose not to do anything. Maybe I could extend this concept with some kind of Bard convertable BD class but I’ll have to think that up first.</p>
<p>Selftargetting Trollbox removed because it serves little purpose now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 16:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3429-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grizzfang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re probably right on the passive not working out, i’ll see if i can work that out.</p>
<p>I don’t think it’s such an overpowered class though, compared to what we already have. People will want you dead because of the nuisance that you are and while the win condition is easier, you don’t have the safety at night like poss/reaper. Lategame you will probably not have a very hard time because there are so few peopl, but getting to lategame is gonna be pretty tough when everyone wants you dead and any killer could kill you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 16:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3429-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Passive should be changed to “You can speak only 3 times per day. You can speak as much as you want at night”</p>
<p>In addition, it shouldn’t be able to kill 3 times; 2 times max, like alchemist</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 12:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3429-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nazle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is going to be fairly awful for those who get the class as they cannot speak for the entire game which I don’t like at all - as there is no deduction, they cannot trick people as easily and I imagine  the winratio for this class would be very low considering the passive, or very high considering he can kill and silence. The concept with a class silencing others etc… can work, having the class not being able to talk… a big no no, the abilities and passives you have chosen would not work out well for ToL in my opinion. Balancing this class would be very hard considering all the super overpowered abilites you have given it, therefore I do not want it in the game.</p>
<p>Pretty much what I am trying to say:<br>
Blackmailing and being able to Kill  Big no<br>
Not being able to talk himself: Big no</p>
<p>Nice of you to take the time and try to brainstorm about what we need, so please keep updating and change your class if you want and I’ll give feedback <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 22:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3429-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grizzfang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>The Silencer (Neutral Offensive)</h2>
<p><strong>Lore:</strong><br>
You’re some crazy bard/singer or something that thinks their own voice is so beautiful that you think you’re the only person in the world that’s allowed to speak.</p>
<p><strong>Objective:</strong><br>
You win when everyone is dead or silenced. (Once everyone has been silenced that is alive you will win, even if you die later.)</p>
<p><strong>Passive 1: Compulsive singing</strong><br>
Your voice is so divine, it would be a crime not to use it. Everytime you stay in your room you will sing.<br>
If you do not take any actions at night (and you’re not occupied or jailed) everyone who visits you will know who you are.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability 1: The sound of Silence</strong><br>
Nobody can hear others speak for 10 seconds. But they will hear themselves speak. (they won’t get a notification about this) 2 uses.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1: Silence</strong><br>
Remove a target’s tongue. They will not be able to speak until they die. infinite uses</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2: Silen… oops</strong><br>
You try to remove a target’s tongue, but you accidently kill them. Oops. 2 uses</p>
<h2>Notes:</h2>
<p>Maybe silenced people and silencer should be able to talk with psychic since that’s some mind reading voodoo. Dunno.<br>
Should probably not spawn with both reaper and possessor in one game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 21:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3429-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-silencer/3429.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Silencer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
