<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Court Wizard contest application</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-contest-application/54587</link>
    <description>Cw

**Passive - Master of Magic** - you can use both of your night and day abilities at the same time.

Day abilities:

**Mirror image** (2 uses) - everything that was meant to target you this night will not work. (just like hide)

**Magical barrier** (3 uses)- choose a player they will be immune to being poisoned/bleeded for the rest of the day.

Night ability: 

**Illusion** (unlimited uses) - Choose a player. You will choose who they target, you can&#39;t target (use this ability on) the same player 2 days in a row.

**Greater Magical Shield** ( 2 uses)- Everyone will be immune to occupation and target changing this night.

My foughts:

I dont know if passive even can be implemented in the game (every class can only use one ablity) but it would be something different to everything we had so far. Day abilities are nothing new but they provide support and self defense that support class should in my opinion have. Night abilities allow Cw to take thing in his own hands. Shield can hurt bd if used at the wrong time but used at the right time can decide about someone&#39;s life (ensure heal for example).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:54:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-contest-application/54587.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard contest application</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Borys_Nosek]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cw</p>
<p><strong>Passive - Master of Magic</strong> - you can use both of your night and day abilities at the same time.</p>
<p>Day abilities:</p>
<p><strong>Mirror image</strong> (2 uses) - everything that was meant to target you this night will not work. (just like hide)</p>
<p><strong>Magical barrier</strong> (3 uses)- choose a player they will be immune to being poisoned/bleeded for the rest of the day.</p>
<p>Night ability:</p>
<p><strong>Illusion</strong> (unlimited uses) - Choose a player. You will choose who they target, you can’t target (use this ability on) the same player 2 days in a row.</p>
<p><strong>Greater Magical Shield</strong> ( 2 uses)- Everyone will be immune to occupation and target changing this night.</p>
<p>My foughts:</p>
<p>I dont know if passive even can be implemented in the game (every class can only use one ablity) but it would be something different to everything we had so far. Day abilities are nothing new but they provide support and self defense that support class should in my opinion have. Night abilities allow Cw to take thing in his own hands. Shield can hurt bd if used at the wrong time but used at the right time can decide about someone’s life (ensure heal for example).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-contest-application/54587/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-contest-application/54587/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54587-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-contest-application/54587.rss">Court Wizard contest application</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
