<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748</link>
    <description>### Make yourself welcome, samurai-domo.
![image|590x359](upload://fpv9a6SPQ8IfyTXKj1j8qjDmQtF.jpeg) 
# Legend of the Five Rings (Rokugan) FM, hosted by @Mercenary, co-hosted by @Geyde.
**The Rules are as Follows.**
- After 24 hours of inactivity, you will be prodded. Failure to answer in the following 24 hours is a replacement. If I do not find a suitable replacement in another 24 hours, the slot is modkilled.
\+ General Forum Rules

**The &quot;Warnings&quot; are as Follows.**
- There *are* anticlaim mechanics.
- There are two main factions in the game: The Empire (Town) and the Shadowlands (Mafia)
- There may be or may not be neutrals.
- There may be or may not be lost wolves.
- There may be or may not be flip-altering mechanics, but none of them will change the alignment of a flipped player, although they may hide it.
- There may be or may not be Godfather, Framer and Miller effects.
- There may be or not be Dead communication.
- There are no vanillas.
- Evil faction has a chat all-times active.
- This game is not bastard.

# **Special Game Mechanics**
- There are 9 clans, based on flavor. Each one of them has 2 to 6 families. Alongside that, there are 4 paths: Courtier, Shugenja, Bushi and Monk.
- Your clan is the general grouping of your family. Each clan is more likely to have families of with a specific set of skills. For an example, if you roll a Phoenix, you have more chances to roll something that support your allies.
- Your family is your class or role, however you like to call it. It is your set of skills. Of course, Kuni Yoriko and Kuni Tohsaka are two different characters in flavor. But as both are from the Kuni family, they both have the same mechanicals.
- Be careful with japanese naming conventions! Your family is, in flavor, the surname (first name) of your flavor. Kitsu Shiro is from the Kitsu family.
- Your path is your class type, defined by flavor. Courtiers dwell in the court, shugenjas are holy spellcasters, bushi are steel-bound warriors and monks are reclusive monastics.
- Flavor is faction, path, clan and family-indicative. You can ask me what would be the faction, clan, family and path of a certain character.
- Your clan and your family will decide your flavor. Your flavor will decide your path. (if you are of the Crab Clan and Kuni Family and I roll a shugenja flavor, you will be a shugenja). 
- Each family lists a path. It does not mean that all characters from a family will be from said path, it is just high likely they will be (out of the 50 members of the Daigotsu family, 45 of them are Bushi).
- For clarifiance, all ninjas and berserkers in the game are considered to be Bushi here. All maho-tsukai are Shugenja. All engineers and alike are Courtier if they aren&#39;t Bushi. Related to flavor.
- If I ever lack flavor for the scum (Shadowlands) members, I&#39;ll take flavor from a normal town (Empire) character and add &quot;Corrupted&quot; to their name.
- I&#39;ll only use people that were at some point alive at the 12nd century in the timeline for flavor. Dead people can&#39;t mafia. 
- One person spawns as Daigotsu. Daigotsu is known to be the leader of the Shadowlands faction.

# **The Great Clans**
Here is the greatest mechanic of the game! The Clan roulette.
Before the game starts (at Day 0, after your know your alignment), send me in a DM the faction you want to roll for. You will be randomly assorted to a Family inside said Clan. Each result has equal chances of rolling. I don&#39;t recommend debating at this because it will be counted as a clan claim when the game starts if you try to exploit this on purpose.
Basically, each Clan is a set of classes. Choose a clan, and I&#39;ll randomly roll inside it your class.

[details=&quot;Crab Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Crab_Clan
The [color=blue]**Crab Clan**[/color]  serve as the Defenders of the Empire. They spend their lives upon the Kaiu Wall, standing vigilant along the southwestern border of Rokugan to defend against the next attack from the Shadowlands. Every day, the Crab warriors give their lives defending the Wall so that the people of the other clans might live in peace and security. The Crab value this duty above everything, even honor. They might be gruff, unkempt and downright rude at times, but no one questions their strength or courage.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that can defend your allies.**

&gt; ## Hida
&gt; **Empire, Crab, Hida, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Hiruma
&gt; **Empire, Crab, Hituma, Bushi**
&gt; Target a player at night. All actions performed by bushi who visit them are redirectioned to you.

&gt; ## Kaiu
&gt; **Empire, Crab, Kaiu, Courtier or Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Kuni
&gt; **Empire, Crab, Kuni, Shugenja or Monk**
&gt; Finds at night if a player is a member of the Shadowlands. Results are always correct.

&gt; ## Yasuki
&gt; **Empire, Crab, Yasuki, Courtier**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Toritaka
&gt; **Empire, Crab, Toritaka, Bushi**
&gt; At night, delay all actions targeting a player by one night (They will take effect the next night).
[/details]
[details=&quot;Crane Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Crane_Clan
The [color=lavender]**Crane Clan**[/color], Left Hand of the Emperor, was known throughout Rokugan for its skilled duelists and artisans. The Crane were also noted courtiers, wielding great power in the courts of the land. They pursued excellence in all things, and the traditions established by Lady Doji were now customary in the Emperor&#39;s Court. The formal dueling system, iaijutsu, was established by Doji&#39;s husband, Kakita. Their preferential status with the Imperial line was renowned and throughout history the clan had had fewer taxes and more gifts heaped upon them. They were the masters of the courts and had the status and wealth commensurate with such a position.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that can mess up with wagonomics.**

&gt; ## Doji
&gt; **Empire, Crane, Doji, Courtier or Bushi**
&gt; Neighbourizer. The chat is closed upon their death. Can remove people from the chat at will. 
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Kakita
&gt; **Empire, Crane, Kakita, Bushi or Courtier**
&gt; If target player&#39;s wagon ever receives more votes than 1/3 (rounded up) of the total alive players tomorrow, Kakita&#39;s vote secretly counts as double. If the target is a courtier, it backfires and instead target&#39;s vote will secretly count as double.

&gt; ## Daidoji
&gt; **Empire, Crane, Daidoji, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Asahina
&gt; **Empire, Crane, Asahina, Shugenja**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
[/details]
[details=&quot;Dragon Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Dragon_Clan
The  [color=lightgreen]**Dragon Clan**[/color]  was founded by Togashi, the most enigmatic of Amaterasu&#39;s children. For over a thousand years it has been their duty to watch and record the history of Rokugan. While the Dragon are seen as reclusive and aloof by most clans, they understand the necessity of acting only when the time is right.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that can investigate other players.**

&gt; ## Togashi
&gt; **Empire, Dragon, Togashi, Monk**
&gt; Hide behind a player, and all actions targeting you will fail, but all actions targeting them will also affect you.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Kitsuki
&gt; **Empire, Dragon, Kitsuki, Courtier or Bushi**
&gt; Target a player each night to learn their flavor name. When you use this ability, you can&#39;t defended by any means on the night it is used.

&gt; ## Mirumoto
&gt; **Empire, Dragon, Mirumoto, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Tamori
&gt; **Empire, Dragon, Tamori, Shugenja or Monk**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
[/details]
[details=&quot;Lion Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Lion_Clan
The **[color=yellow]Lion Clan[/color]** were the Right Hand of the Emperor, recording the military and political interactions between the Clans. They were the epitome of bushido and the very example of valor. Next to the Seppun family they were most likely to serve as the Emperor&#39;s guardsmen. They comprised the greater portion of the Imperial Legions.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that can influence a little your own death.**

&gt; ## Ikoma
&gt; **Empire, Lion, Ikoma, Bushi or Courtier**
&gt; 1-shot day motivator.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Kitsu
&gt; **Empire, Lion, Kitsu, Shugenja**
&gt; Receive a single message from the dead chat at the end of the night.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Matsu
&gt; **Empire, Lion, Matsu, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
[/details]
[details=&quot;Mantis Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Mantis_Clan
The [color=green]**Mantis Clan**[/color] is one of the Great Clans of Rokugan. Specifically, their duties within the Emerald Empire are to guard and patrol all the lands of the Empire which do not belong to any other clan, including the seas of Rokugan. They protect the Empire against threats from the oceans, particulalrly any potential gaijin invaders.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for unusual abilities that require creativity.**

&gt; ## Yoritomo
&gt; **Empire, Mantis, Yoritomo, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
&gt; This ability can only be triggered one time per night, and Daigotsu is immune to its effect.

&gt; ## Moshi
&gt; **Empire, Mantis, Moshi, Shugenja**
&gt; Once per game, select a dead player aligned with the Empire. You will steal one of their abilities, at your choice if they have more than one.

&gt; ## Tsuruchi 
&gt; **Empire, Mantis, Tsuruchi, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
[/details]
[details=&quot;Scorpion Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Scorpion_Clan
The **[color=red]Scorpion Clan[/color]** and its members are widely considered to be villainous and untrustworthy by the rest of Rokugan, though they merely attempt to fulfill the duty given to their family by the First Emperor on the day of his ascension.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that can kill other players.**

&gt; ## Bayushi
&gt; **Empire, Scorpion, Bayushi, Bushi or Courtier**
&gt; Make a player start to bleed. They will die in two nights, unless they are healed.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Shosuro
&gt; **Empire, Scorpion, Shosuro, Courtier or Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Soshi
&gt; **Empire, Scorpion, Soshi, Shugenja or Courtier**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Yogo
&gt; **Empire, Scorpion, Yogo, Shugenja**
&gt; At night, kill a player if they have made less than 20*(numbers of days that have passed) posts.
[/details]
[details=&quot;Phoenix Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Phoenix_Clan
The **[color=orange]Phoenix Clan[/color]** is known throughout Rokugan for their skilled shugenja and mastery of elemental magic. The Phoenix are also noted pacifists, preferring diplomacy to war if at all possible. The Phoenix presence in the courts of the land is not great as their courtiers are relatively few, although they are not isolationists like the Dragon Clan.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that can support your allies.**

&gt; ## Isawa
&gt; **Empire, Phoenix, Isawa, Shugenja**
&gt; Heal target player. It will remove bleeding and prevent normal attacks.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Shiba
&gt; **Empire, Phoenix, Shiba, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Asako
&gt; **Empire, Phoenix, Asako, Shugenja**
&gt; Your target&#39;s next action or effect can&#39;t be stopped by any means. If they have a conditional effect for their action, it will be removed for this night.

&gt; ## Agasha
&gt; **Empire, Phoenix, Agasha, Shugenja**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
[/details]
[details=&quot;Unicorn Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Unicorn_Clan
Once known as the Ki-Rin Clan, the **[color=magenta]Unicorn Clan[/color]** departed Rokugan shortly after the first Day of Thunder. The Kami Shinjo, founder of the clan, hoped to avert other threats to Rokugan by discovering them first. They roamed the world for eight centuries before returning to Rokugan.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that can hinder your foes.**

&gt; ## Shinjo
&gt; **Empire, Unicorn, Shinjo, Bushi**
&gt; Roleblock target player at night.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Utaku
&gt; **Empire, Unicorn, Utaku, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Moto
&gt; **Empire, Unicorn, Moto, Bushi**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
&gt; When you activate this ability, everyone visiting you will be attacked by you.

&gt; ## Ide
&gt; **Empire, Unicorn, Ide, Courtier**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Iuchi
&gt; **Empire, Unicorn, Iuchi, Shugenja**
&gt; Select two players. All players visiting the first target will instead visit the second one. Please note this is one-directional.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
[/details]
[details=&quot;Spider Clan&quot;]
https://l5r.fandom.com/wiki/Samurai_of_the_Spider_Clan
Not much was known about the [color=green]**Spider Clan**[/color] to Rokugan at large. Formed in 1169 by the Lost and other factions that swore fealty to Daigotsu, it was technically not an actual clan, until Empress Iweko I conferred Great Clan status in 1173.
**If you choose this Clan, you will most likely roll for abilities that hinder the members of the Empire.
Only Shadowlands players may roll at this clan, but players on the Shadowlands can roll on any faction.**

&gt; ## Daigotsu 
&gt; **Shadowlands, Spider, Daigotsu, Bushi**
&gt; The first player who rolls this family will be given the flavor of Daigotsu Kanpeki, who is a Monk instead of a Bushi.
&gt; If both Daigotsu Kanpeki and Daigotsu, Dark Lord of Jigoku are alive at Day 5+, the Shadowlands instantly win the game.
(for clarifiance, there is a family named Daigotsu and a character named Daigotsu. They are not the same person and do not have the same abilities)

&gt; ## Goju
&gt; **Shadowlands, Spider, Goju, Courtier or Bushi**
&gt; When using the factional kill, you are immune to tracker and watcher-like effects.
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Ninube
&gt; **Shadowlands, Spider, Ninube, Shugenja or Courtier**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Kokujin
&gt; **Shadowlands, Spider, Kokujin, Shugenja**
&gt; At night, learn the full classcard of a player.

&gt; ## Susumu
&gt; **Shadowlands, Spider, Susumu, Shugenja**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*

&gt; ## Gyushi
&gt; **Shadowlands, Spider, Gyushi, Shugenja**
&gt; *The remaining of this classcard is hidden.*
[/details]

# Players
The setup can run at both 17 and 22 players, but runs better at 22!

1. Hippolytus
1. Marshal
2. Jgoesgaming
3. Vulgard
4. Alice
5. Arete
6. Napoleon
7. ~~Luxy &lt;3~~ N. 1
8. BlueStorm
9. SDaL
10. Gypyx
12. DryBones
13. ~~Possessed~~ Nightfall
14. Emilia
15. Italy
16. Redrover1760
18. Sulit
19. DatBird
20. Zone
21. Fossil
22. WazzaAzza
22. Yuzen &lt;3

# Backups
1. KyoDaz
2. Ami

# People looking at you from above and judging your sins
(spectators)
1. Astand
2. Mist1422</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:37:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Signups</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I unlocked it in case Merc needs to do host things here</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/461">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/461</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-461</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My b, have a good day.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/arete">@Arete</a> lock this thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/460">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/460</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-460</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got DQ’ed due to mod error. So yeah, replaced.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/459">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/459</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-459</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mercenary" data-post="1" data-topic="80748">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/mercenary/40/32041_2.png" class="avatar"> Mercenary:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fossil</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>??? Did you replace out?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/458">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/458</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-458</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not playing, so I’m not going to talk in it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/457">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/457</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-457</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wrong thread bud.</p>
<p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-game-thread-day-1-22-22-need-one-replacement/80957/1611" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-game-thread-day-1-22-22-need-one-replacement/80957/1611</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/456">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/456</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-456</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s open again?!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/455">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/455</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 19:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-455</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/454">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/454</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-454</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Nightfall has replaced Possessed</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/453">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/453</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 16:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-453</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>A replacement is needed.</h1>
<h1>Please message <a class="mention" href="/u/mercenary">@Mercenary</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/luxy">@Luxy</a> if you are interested (not me).</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/452">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/452</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 19:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-452</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Merc says: if anyone needs anything about lore, the L5R Wikia is very complete and solid.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/451">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/451</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 07:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-451</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>I’m closing the thread for now to prevent people from angleshooting pre-game discussion</h1>
<h1>
<a class="mention" href="/u/mercenary">@Mercenary</a> let me know if/when you would like it unlocked</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/450">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/450</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-450</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/449">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/449</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-449</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s fine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/448">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/448</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-448</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gypyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh ok, sorry about btw</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/447">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/447</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-447</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Disqualified.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/446">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/446</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-446</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gypyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>and what does “DQ’ed” mean?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/445">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/445</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-445</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Indeed! I’ll have a fun time!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/444">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/444</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-444</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zone_Q11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/man_facepalming.png?v=9" title=":man_facepalming:" class="emoji" alt=":man_facepalming:"> I see. Then, I wish that you have a pleasant time watching us suffer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/443">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/443</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-443</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah. Mod messed up and showed me a role card I wasn’t supposed to see. Then invited Luxy to the PM…so now we’re both DQ’ed! Yay!</p>
<p>But it’s fine. Just means we’re able to infect this forum with more Nuffians.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/442">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/442</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-442</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zone_Q11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lack of time?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/441">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/441</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-441</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fossil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah, that was the NUF Private Academy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/440">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/440</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-440</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yuzen.19]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No wonder you became like this, your current Fossil state explains everything lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/439">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/439</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-439</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gypyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ok, thanks for the answers</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/438">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/438</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-438</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yuzen.19]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s an active forum specified for light novels around the world. But when you play mafia in the forum. no doubt you are bound to loose your brain cells.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/437">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748/437</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80748-437</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfm-rokugan-fm-22-22-started/80748.rss">[SFM] Rokugan FM (22/22) - Started</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
