<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster (NK)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149</link>
    <description>**The Spymaster (Neutral Killer) - must kill all members of the main factions in order to win**

**Passive (Information Network):**
See the contents of all whispers (this will NOT see private matters)

**Passive (Unstoppable):**
Immune to death at night. Immune to Nightshade and bleeding.

**Day Ability (Hire Hitman):**
Your attack tonight will pierce night immunity and cannot be healed. (1 use - If the target is guarded by a knight the attack will fail but the Spymaster himself will not be killed. The Hitman will attack the target even if the Spymaster is occupied but not if the target is in jail or guarded by a Mercenary. The Hitman is a &quot;separate entity&quot; from the Spymaster and is still prone to redirection from a CW, Sage, or Ritualist but not from a Drunk, Alcoholic, or Invoker. )

**Day Ability (Perfect Forgery):**
Tonight you will receive a blank logbook that can be edited at will. This logbook will appear instead of theirs if you successfully kill your target tonight. (2 uses)


**Night Ability (Eliminate Target)**
Kill the target player. (Infinite uses)

**Night Ability (Master of Disguise):**
Choose a class. For the rest of the game investigative classes will see you as appearing to be that class. (1 use -  this ability will not be consumed if you are occupied)
 




This would ideally be accompanied by a change to maid spy seeing how strong current noble is.  This would also give EK more room to potentially out to unseen while potentially revealing to a Spymaster that he is evil and therefore easy to kill.  

Sorcerer has the ability to win with evils and kill very fast, Possessor can get a new reliable claim multiple times as well as being very hard to find, and Reaper is unstoppable in the late game.
The Spymaster&#39;s niche would be to have a fantastic fake claim that&#39;s very hard to disprove.  He has the ability to read all whispers to gather a lot of information as well as disguise himself and manipulate info with Perfect Forgery. I feel like this could help put the current hated whisper meta in a better place.  I gave him the Hire Hitman ability because without it I feel he just loses to king every game.  It gives him one unstoppable attack with which to dispose of a priority target he could not otherwise.

First time I&#39;ve tried creating a class for any game so this might be awful but I would really appreciate feedback.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 22:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No I just forgot to put it in thank you for pointing that out</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 22:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71149-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He has no way of dealing with nightshade or can l not read.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 22:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71149-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Spymaster (Neutral Killer) - must kill all members of the main factions in order to win</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive (Information Network):</strong><br>
See the contents of all whispers (this will NOT see private matters)</p>
<p><strong>Passive (Unstoppable):</strong><br>
Immune to death at night. Immune to Nightshade and bleeding.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability (Hire Hitman):</strong><br>
Your attack tonight will pierce night immunity and cannot be healed. (1 use - If the target is guarded by a knight the attack will fail but the Spymaster himself will not be killed. The Hitman will attack the target even if the Spymaster is occupied but not if the target is in jail or guarded by a Mercenary. The Hitman is a “separate entity” from the Spymaster and is still prone to redirection from a CW, Sage, or Ritualist but not from a Drunk, Alcoholic, or Invoker. )</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability (Perfect Forgery):</strong><br>
Tonight you will receive a blank logbook that can be edited at will. This logbook will appear instead of theirs if you successfully kill your target tonight. (2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability (Eliminate Target)</strong><br>
Kill the target player. (Infinite uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability (Master of Disguise):</strong><br>
Choose a class. For the rest of the game investigative classes will see you as appearing to be that class. (1 use -  this ability will not be consumed if you are occupied)</p>
<p>This would ideally be accompanied by a change to maid spy seeing how strong current noble is.  This would also give EK more room to potentially out to unseen while potentially revealing to a Spymaster that he is evil and therefore easy to kill.</p>
<p>Sorcerer has the ability to win with evils and kill very fast, Possessor can get a new reliable claim multiple times as well as being very hard to find, and Reaper is unstoppable in the late game.<br>
The Spymaster’s niche would be to have a fantastic fake claim that’s very hard to disprove.  He has the ability to read all whispers to gather a lot of information as well as disguise himself and manipulate info with Perfect Forgery. I feel like this could help put the current hated whisper meta in a better place.  I gave him the Hire Hitman ability because without it I feel he just loses to king every game.  It gives him one unstoppable attack with which to dispose of a priority target he could not otherwise.</p>
<p>First time I’ve tried creating a class for any game so this might be awful but I would really appreciate feedback.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 21:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71149-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster-nk/71149.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster (NK)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
