<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal sharing?</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998</link>
    <description>Journal sharing can be a pain in the butt as it is. It often takes more than one copy and paste to get everything, and even then when the log is concise. Some roles can have really long logs-- obs and sheriff in particular, but also psychic and noble if they&#39;re recording info from dead or logs.

Could we not just have an option to share a link to our journal, in the same manner the noble can now see saved journals? Maybe tied to a command like /j?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Journal sharing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[methomps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think what is needed is for copy/paste to preserve/show line breaks when pasted into chat.  I know there is a spam concern, but at least for the person on trial pasting the log should make a clean presentation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35998-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998.rss">Journal sharing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Journal sharing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FidelCastro" data-post="4" data-topic="35998">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/fidelcastro/40/2983_2.png" class="avatar"> FidelCastro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t most people keep their fake journal in the journal page anyway</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Prior to the noble change I kept my fake journal in my private notes, because 1. I usually had 2 or 3 claims. 2. one of them usually had semi-realistic information that still could aid BD, if I died to NK or something no sense giving something that could potentially help the BD.</p>
<p>Again though, noble change changes the game in how fake logs can be kept. Having 2+ classes in your journal is now a possible trap.</p>
<p>I would strongly oppose this, if it weren’t for the noble change that I already oppose. I really don’t like snoop on BD, it really cuts down on flexibility in claiming. Normally the rule of thumb for evil is to keep your claims liquid and changable until forced to claim when it becomes concrete. People seeing your actual journal when alive basically means you may have already claimed without knowing it, and thus need to stick to that story.</p>
<p>Say if you are mastermind, and you get called out by a princess as special/investigative, having a sheriff or princess journal is what you want, but if a drunk/butler calls you out, you’d need a hunter/drunk/butler journal ready, so having both USED to be the smart play.</p>
<p>Adding in a 1 button show logs button, would add extra work if badguys are doing what used to be the smart way to play, which is keeping a liquid claim, multiple claims ready etc… making a 1 button to show the logs hurts that playstyle as the added delay to edit the logs and take the right one could be proof of guilt when good guys would just have a single button (normally the difference in human reaction times and computer speeds make judging that difficult, but if it’s a single button there’s no excuse for a delay)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35998-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998.rss">Journal sharing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Journal sharing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FidelCastro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t most people keep their fake journal in the journal page anyway? And we already have the private notes section for any information we want to keep private. In general you’d want to keep suspicious information out of your real journal anyway now that we have nobles peeking into them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 16:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35998-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998.rss">Journal sharing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Journal sharing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Normally I would completely oppose it, but now, it depends on if the noble is staying the way it is now. (or coming back if that was reverted and I never saw it, I haven’t seen a noble since the update). Nobles new ability already forces evils to have a single believable BD journal in their logs up at all times, and risk getting called out if they contradict or switch from that even if they’ve not publicly claimed (a change I don’t agree with from the outset).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 13:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35998-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998.rss">Journal sharing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Journal sharing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m unsure about this.  I do usually like suggestions that streamline the interface and mechanics, but this would have a lot of side-effects.</p>
<p>In particular, this would make writing and maintaining fake journals a bit more of a pain in the ass.  You would have to keep an actual, singular fake journal in your journal; you wouldn’t really have time to copy-paste in everything from the notepad (and there isn’t even enough space there to completely fill out both pages of the journal, so having a one-page journal would become a tell.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 08:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35998-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998.rss">Journal sharing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Journal sharing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FidelCastro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Journal sharing can be a pain in the butt as it is. It often takes more than one copy and paste to get everything, and even then when the log is concise. Some roles can have really long logs-- obs and sheriff in particular, but also psychic and noble if they’re recording info from dead or logs.</p>
<p>Could we not just have an option to share a link to our journal, in the same manner the noble can now see saved journals? Maybe tied to a command like /j?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 07:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35998-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/journal-sharing/35998.rss">Journal sharing?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
