<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463</link>
    <description>Presenting... a classic dungeon creature...

**The Slime!**

Passive 1:
**Hive Mind** - Players you kill are &quot;absorbed&quot;. They can only hear you and your other absorbed victims in dead chat. Absorbed players can &quot;help&quot; choose who you kill at night.

_^ In other words, people you absorb can&#39;t hear other ghosts, and other ghosts can&#39;t hear the people you absorbed. No new chat tab is needed, dead chat is just separate. Psychic can&#39;t hear people you&#39;ve absorbed. Players you&#39;ve absorbed will see you listed as &quot;Slime:&quot; and nt your actual in-game name. Absorbed players made into a Death Knight will be immediately un-absorbed and returned to normal dead chat. Absorbed players can &quot;choose&quot; who you kill at night, which will be counted like voting. The Slime player&#39;s vote breaks any ties in his favor. Absorbed players won&#39;t see who other players or the Slime are voting/choosing to kill. Players voting to make the Slime attack himself are not counted, and are NOT notified that they didn&#39;t count._

Passive 2:
**Through the Cracks** - When you are attacked, you will survive as long as you have one player absorbed. Each time you are attacked, the earliest remaining player you absorbed will be un-absorbed and returned to normal dead chat.

_^ Let&#39;s say you absorb Bob night one, David night 2, and Steve night 3. Then you&#39;re attacked on night 4. You survive, and Bob is taken away from you and returned to normal dead chat. If you&#39;re attacked again, you will survive and David will be taken away. Etc._

Day Ability:
**Purge** - If you are Poisoned or Bled at any time, you may instantly pass the effect on to another player, removing it from yourself. (3 uses.)

_^ Best to wait a day or two so Unseen/Cult don&#39;t notice you passed it off you. ;) The player you pass it to has the full amount of time before they die, and does not inherit the time you had left on your poison/bleed._

Night Ability 1:
**Absorb** - Kill a player, absorbing them into your own separate dead chat and preventing them from talking to the Psychic and other ghosts. (Unlimited uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**Digest** - Select a player you&#39;ve absorbed to un-absorb them and take on their investigative results for that night. You will also appear to be the dead player if seen by Princess or Observer. (4 uses.)

_^ Un-absorbing a player like this returns them to normal dead chat and frees them._

----

Comments:
The main power of this class is preventing ghosts from organizing and sharing info with the Psychic or Death Knight. As the Slime, you will also have a chance of getting information from the players you absorb. For example, an absorbed Sheriff might want the Slime to kill the Unseen member he found. ;) I think this would be a fun class in general, as people who are absorbed will be given a chance to either taunt the Slime... or start working on his &quot;team&quot; to pass the time during the round. &quot;I&#39;d kill 4, Slime. He was mean to me. Thank you, you&#39;re the best!!&quot; You might even be able to trick the Slime into killing in a way that helps your team beat him... &lt;_&lt;

**Absorbed players are NOT converted. They retain their original class and goal. They can merely try to influence who you attack, probably based on their own preferences.**</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:46:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve made some changes to the Day Ability and second Night Ability. I think it hangs together a bit better, now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Added the “vote” thing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It seems like a more gelatinous version of the reaper, but it still is interesting, and has enough differences from the reaper that I don’t think any of the description was copy-pasted. If it was my class, I might add:<br>
<strong>Hardened</strong>- Prevents you from being killed the first night.<br>
<strong>Acidic</strong>- You can not get healed or protected. Your protector will not be notified that their protection had no effect.<br>
Both of these are passive.<br>
I’m not an expert at making roles though, so you probably wouldn’t want to use my suggestions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 02:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It seems like an interesting idea. Only change I can think of right now is making the day ability un-absorb the player if you want the previous (or two) night’s info from the player and being hid by that player for the night so it balances it out a bit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 01:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s also the possibility of letting absorbed players ‘vote’ for who the Slime kills at night, with ties being broken by going for the actual Slime player’s choice. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eh.  When you boil everything down, the separate dead chat is a minor thing.  Jelly Mold just lets you avoid Observers or Princesses.  And you can survive deaths + cure poison / bleeding, but most NKs are immune anyway.</p>
<p>Beyond that it’s just a generic serial killer with a few gimmicks.  It doesn’t actually play uniquely, and it doesn’t actually require any special strategies to fight it.  Absorbing people into a separate dead chat nerfs Psychic a little bit, but doesn’t really change how you play from the perspective of most players (or the slime itself.)</p>
<p>Also, unlike the Reaper, you don’t start with any charges for your defense, so you can die N1.  That’s not good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 20:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It seems alright, but I object to the separate absorbed chat. First of all, if you can’t talk to people, you kind of just have to wait in the dead chat. Since this splits the dead groups, it’s less likely to have someone to talk to.</p>
<p>It also feels like an arbitrary way to counter Psychic/DK.</p>
<p>Other than that it is a good class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s no incentive to help the Slime, yes, but as I mentioned it’s just a fun option people might take. Helping the Slime kill their enemies, etc. The Slime isn’t making a team of people on his side, he’s preventing his victims from going to the “real” dead chat. Also, you can’t invest once you’re dead, when I spoke of Sheriff, I meant if he found someone before he died, he could tell the Slime.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 17:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I made a class based on a similar idea before called the Necromancer. One of the main problems here currently is that any absorbed player has no incentive to aid the Slime and can just leave or not invest anyone. I fixed that with mine to tie the win condition of any absorbed players to the Slime.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 10:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Presenting… a classic dungeon creature…</p>
<p><strong>The Slime!</strong></p>
<p>Passive 1:<br>
<strong>Hive Mind</strong> - Players you kill are “absorbed”. They can only hear you and your other absorbed victims in dead chat. Absorbed players can “help” choose who you kill at night.</p>
<p><em>^ In other words, people you absorb can’t hear other ghosts, and other ghosts can’t hear the people you absorbed. No new chat tab is needed, dead chat is just separate. Psychic can’t hear people you’ve absorbed. Players you’ve absorbed will see you listed as “Slime:” and nt your actual in-game name. Absorbed players made into a Death Knight will be immediately un-absorbed and returned to normal dead chat. Absorbed players can “choose” who you kill at night, which will be counted like voting. The Slime player’s vote breaks any ties in his favor. Absorbed players won’t see who other players or the Slime are voting/choosing to kill. Players voting to make the Slime attack himself are not counted, and are NOT notified that they didn’t count.</em></p>
<p>Passive 2:<br>
<strong>Through the Cracks</strong> - When you are attacked, you will survive as long as you have one player absorbed. Each time you are attacked, the earliest remaining player you absorbed will be un-absorbed and returned to normal dead chat.</p>
<p><em>^ Let’s say you absorb Bob night one, David night 2, and Steve night 3. Then you’re attacked on night 4. You survive, and Bob is taken away from you and returned to normal dead chat. If you’re attacked again, you will survive and David will be taken away. Etc.</em></p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Purge</strong> - If you are Poisoned or Bled at any time, you may instantly pass the effect on to another player, removing it from yourself. (3 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ Best to wait a day or two so Unseen/Cult don’t notice you passed it off you. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> The player you pass it to has the full amount of time before they die, and does not inherit the time you had left on your poison/bleed.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Absorb</strong> - Kill a player, absorbing them into your own separate dead chat and preventing them from talking to the Psychic and other ghosts. (Unlimited uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Digest</strong> - Select a player you’ve absorbed to un-absorb them and take on their investigative results for that night. You will also appear to be the dead player if seen by Princess or Observer. (4 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ Un-absorbing a player like this returns them to normal dead chat and frees them.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Comments:<br>
The main power of this class is preventing ghosts from organizing and sharing info with the Psychic or Death Knight. As the Slime, you will also have a chance of getting information from the players you absorb. For example, an absorbed Sheriff might want the Slime to kill the Unseen member he found. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> I think this would be a fun class in general, as people who are absorbed will be given a chance to either taunt the Slime… or start working on his “team” to pass the time during the round. “I’d kill 4, Slime. He was mean to me. Thank you, you’re the best!!” You might even be able to trick the Slime into killing in a way that helps your team beat him… &lt;_&lt;</p>
<p><strong>Absorbed players are NOT converted. They retain their original class and goal. They can merely try to influence who you attack, probably based on their own preferences.</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 07:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45463-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-slime-neutral-killer/45463.rss">[Class Suggestion] The SLIME! (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
