<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist (A Work of Art)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist-a-work-of-art/72491</link>
    <description>**A Work of Art**
The Unseen threat plaguing Castle Adiart gradually grows as more corpses lie within the corridors. The Princess’ usual fair skin had turned pale from a fatal stab wound a few days ago. The loyal Butler’s clothes had been drenched by his own blood as he leaned limp against the door to the Library. Finally, just last night, the Court found a Mercenary with her neck snapped. In her pocket were four Brilders each marked with the emblem of the Unseen: A detailed purple rose that has shown immense power in the past.

The Physician knew that he should feel scared about this as this goes against his very nature of saving souls from the edge of death, but for some reason, he felt quite the opposite.The masked man was calm and unmoving. He was intrigued by the bodies that used to be filled with life. It was almost like they were a form of art. A collection that will keep on growing as time passes. Such a sight to behold.

Before he could think any deeper, a bearded and well-dressed man rushed up to the King on the throne with a document in his right hand.

“My lord! I have found some critical evidence on the Unseen scum that plan to take over the Kingdom!” He shouted with confidence.

“On what evidence did you find that could possibly affect such a devious organization?” The King looked a bit skeptical as he had been lied to once before which drew suspicions on him as working against his citizens.

“I am the Sheriff of Adiart, one of the best investigators in the kingdom.” The Sheriff took a bow as he spoke. “I found a contract that bears the forbidden mark inside the commons of Captain Verrat. He must be working alongside them!” He points at a man heavily cladded with armor with his helmet covering his face.

For a moment, the King glared at Verrat in silent disapproval unsure on what to do. Finally, he pointed his finger at the armored man and commanded as hard as he could ”Get this man on the stand at once!”

Along with murmurs of panic and anger, the Court started to follow the King like a flock of sheep as they voted for the Captain. Soon enough, enough votes have been placed for him to stand in the middle of the Court where everyone can see him.

“H-Hold on a minute! I’ve never seen such parchment in my life!” Verrat&#39;s voice was unsteady with his body following suit. “That m-man isn’t a true Sheriff! He has a-a hatred against me!”

After the Captain’s defense, the King went up to him and placed a hand underneath his chin. “You may be the Captain of the Royal Guard….. but we know the truth of your intentions. You shall be executed.”
Everyone else in the room stared in silence as the King grabbed an ax from the side of his ruby throne. As the armored man stared at the sharp weapon, all the tension in him started to disappear.

“So, is this really how you treat criminals? You kill them in cold blood and feel no guilt afterwards?” The man in armor chuckled. “You’re not so different from me after all.”

Before Verrat could say another word, the King threw him onto the marble floor and sliced off his head. Everyone was in shock as the man was no longer moving surrounded by crimson liquid. Everyone….except for the Physician. To him, it was a new way to create a new state of being. A state where an individual was not a person; they were an object to celebrate or mourn depending on the occasion. His thoughts continue to swirl around his head as night falls and everyone leaves the room where the Captain remained.

The masked man sat in his room still in deep thought over what happened a few hours ago. The thought of the corpses continue to consume him until he hears a knock on his door. He slowly opened it as he saw a cloaked figure on the other side. The figure looked old but surprisingly toned for his age underneath the black and purple cloak.

“Good evening, good sir. It seems you’ve been doing pretty well the past few days despite the amount of your fellow neighbors dying. I like that type of perspective.” The cloaked man took a step closer to the man in the mask. “I am the head of the Unseen, the Mastermind of chaos and destruction, and I want you to stand by me on my journey to dominate the kingdom.” 

No response came from the Physician. He continued to look at the man straight in the eyes.

“The silent type, huh? How interesting.” The Mastermind gets a sudden hold of the Physician’s mask. “All the corpses in the world will be yours to view. You can drug everyone to have them praise you for saving their lives. Wouldn’t you like that, dear?” The grin on his face grew even wider with each second passing.

The masked man remained still. The thoughts of the dead have started to overwhelm him. More and more, the ideas the cloaked figure had given him became more pleasant. He felt that it was time to see what he could do besides healing the sick and injured. He gave a small nod towards the man.

“Excellent choice, wise one! You shall be given true power that will prove your worth in this kingdom!” The old man guided the Physician out of his room as they began to move towards a new location. On that night, the unknown man behind the mask became a Physician no longer. Instead, he was now a Herbalist, a man that would lie to others about his work and make new corpses that gave them a different appearance. The man now took actions based on what he viewed others: a work of art.
**Explanation/Comments**
Sorry that the title isn&#39;t in the format it needs to be in, since someone else already had it in the supposed format, I had to change it a bit so that I can post this lore suggestion onto here. I took inspiration from the Physician lore I created a few months ago and added onto that. I actually liked how I planned things out, but it&#39;s obvious that it&#39;s really long. I hope you enjoy this as much as I did making it :slight_smile:
Part 2: Since this lore suggestion was not picked up by the lore bot, I had to get the original post deleted, but this gave me an opportunity to change a detail that was suggested by @Silent_Ace1778. The Captain of the Royal Guard now has a name! I must say, I like coming up with names for characters, so it was interesting compared to the repeated phrase of Captain.  Anyway, thank you for the suggestion, Ace. I also would like to thank the people that commented on the original post for the support. If this inspires more to create lore suggestions, then I&#39;ll be glad. Thanks again and I hope you enjoy.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 17:09:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist-a-work-of-art/72491.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist (A Work of Art)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PoisonedSquid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>A Work of Art</strong><br>
The Unseen threat plaguing Castle Adiart gradually grows as more corpses lie within the corridors. The Princess’ usual fair skin had turned pale from a fatal stab wound a few days ago. The loyal Butler’s clothes had been drenched by his own blood as he leaned limp against the door to the Library. Finally, just last night, the Court found a Mercenary with her neck snapped. In her pocket were four Brilders each marked with the emblem of the Unseen: A detailed purple rose that has shown immense power in the past.</p>
<p>The Physician knew that he should feel scared about this as this goes against his very nature of saving souls from the edge of death, but for some reason, he felt quite the opposite.The masked man was calm and unmoving. He was intrigued by the bodies that used to be filled with life. It was almost like they were a form of art. A collection that will keep on growing as time passes. Such a sight to behold.</p>
<p>Before he could think any deeper, a bearded and well-dressed man rushed up to the King on the throne with a document in his right hand.</p>
<p>“My lord! I have found some critical evidence on the Unseen scum that plan to take over the Kingdom!” He shouted with confidence.</p>
<p>“On what evidence did you find that could possibly affect such a devious organization?” The King looked a bit skeptical as he had been lied to once before which drew suspicions on him as working against his citizens.</p>
<p>“I am the Sheriff of Adiart, one of the best investigators in the kingdom.” The Sheriff took a bow as he spoke. “I found a contract that bears the forbidden mark inside the commons of Captain Verrat. He must be working alongside them!” He points at a man heavily cladded with armor with his helmet covering his face.</p>
<p>For a moment, the King glared at Verrat in silent disapproval unsure on what to do. Finally, he pointed his finger at the armored man and commanded as hard as he could ”Get this man on the stand at once!”</p>
<p>Along with murmurs of panic and anger, the Court started to follow the King like a flock of sheep as they voted for the Captain. Soon enough, enough votes have been placed for him to stand in the middle of the Court where everyone can see him.</p>
<p>“H-Hold on a minute! I’ve never seen such parchment in my life!” Verrat’s voice was unsteady with his body following suit. “That m-man isn’t a true Sheriff! He has a-a hatred against me!”</p>
<p>After the Captain’s defense, the King went up to him and placed a hand underneath his chin. “You may be the Captain of the Royal Guard…… but we know the truth of your intentions. You shall be executed.”<br>
Everyone else in the room stared in silence as the King grabbed an ax from the side of his ruby throne. As the armored man stared at the sharp weapon, all the tension in him started to disappear.</p>
<p>“So, is this really how you treat criminals? You kill them in cold blood and feel no guilt afterwards?” The man in armor chuckled. “You’re not so different from me after all.”</p>
<p>Before Verrat could say another word, the King threw him onto the marble floor and sliced off his head. Everyone was in shock as the man was no longer moving surrounded by crimson liquid. Everyone….except for the Physician. To him, it was a new way to create a new state of being. A state where an individual was not a person; they were an object to celebrate or mourn depending on the occasion. His thoughts continue to swirl around his head as night falls and everyone leaves the room where the Captain remained.</p>
<p>The masked man sat in his room still in deep thought over what happened a few hours ago. The thought of the corpses continue to consume him until he hears a knock on his door. He slowly opened it as he saw a cloaked figure on the other side. The figure looked old but surprisingly toned for his age underneath the black and purple cloak.</p>
<p>“Good evening, good sir. It seems you’ve been doing pretty well the past few days despite the amount of your fellow neighbors dying. I like that type of perspective.” The cloaked man took a step closer to the man in the mask. “I am the head of the Unseen, the Mastermind of chaos and destruction, and I want you to stand by me on my journey to dominate the kingdom.”</p>
<p>No response came from the Physician. He continued to look at the man straight in the eyes.</p>
<p>“The silent type, huh? How interesting.” The Mastermind gets a sudden hold of the Physician’s mask. “All the corpses in the world will be yours to view. You can drug everyone to have them praise you for saving their lives. Wouldn’t you like that, dear?” The grin on his face grew even wider with each second passing.</p>
<p>The masked man remained still. The thoughts of the dead have started to overwhelm him. More and more, the ideas the cloaked figure had given him became more pleasant. He felt that it was time to see what he could do besides healing the sick and injured. He gave a small nod towards the man.</p>
<p>“Excellent choice, wise one! You shall be given true power that will prove your worth in this kingdom!” The old man guided the Physician out of his room as they began to move towards a new location. On that night, the unknown man behind the mask became a Physician no longer. Instead, he was now a Herbalist, a man that would lie to others about his work and make new corpses that gave them a different appearance. The man now took actions based on what he viewed others: a work of art.<br>
<strong>Explanation/Comments</strong><br>
Sorry that the title isn’t in the format it needs to be in, since someone else already had it in the supposed format, I had to change it a bit so that I can post this lore suggestion onto here. I took inspiration from the Physician lore I created a few months ago and added onto that. I actually liked how I planned things out, but it’s obvious that it’s really long. I hope you enjoy this as much as I did making it <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Part 2: Since this lore suggestion was not picked up by the lore bot, I had to get the original post deleted, but this gave me an opportunity to change a detail that was suggested by <a class="mention" href="/u/silent_ace1778">@Silent_Ace1778</a>. The Captain of the Royal Guard now has a name! I must say, I like coming up with names for characters, so it was interesting compared to the repeated phrase of Captain.  Anyway, thank you for the suggestion, Ace. I also would like to thank the people that commented on the original post for the support. If this inspires more to create lore suggestions, then I’ll be glad. Thanks again and I hope you enjoy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist-a-work-of-art/72491/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist-a-work-of-art/72491/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 17:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72491-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-herbalist-a-work-of-art/72491.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Herbalist (A Work of Art)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
