<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Succubus (NK)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-succubus-nk/70519</link>
    <description>&gt; # [color = &quot;orchid&quot;] The Succubus [/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Killer [/color]** 
**Dependency (Passive)** - If the Succubus dies during the night or is executed, all drained players will also die with her the following night.
**Transfer Life (Day)** - Allows the Succubus to kill a drained player overnight, provided they are not healed or night immune, during the coming night and transfer their remaining life in turns to another drained player. This will also heal the latter player. If the Succubus transfers to herself, then she will gain a charge of Love’s Malady instead. If the first player is healed then the ability will still function but without the first player dying. - Infinite uses 
**Infatuation (Day)** - When this ability is activated, all drained players will vote to pardon the Succubus if she is put on trial. Usable while on trial. - 3 uses 
**Vital Drain (Night)** - Learns the target player’s class type and will drain them to death over the next two nights. While there is at least one player being drained then the Succubus will heal herself if she is attacked. If a drained player is healed then their timer until they are drained to death will not lower for the night but neither the healer nor the player will be notified. Does not count as an attack for abilities such as Will o’ Wisp, Defend, and Bear Companion. - Infinite uses 
**Love&#39;s Malady (Night)** - Instantly kills a player while bypassing Night Immunity, healing, and does not count as visiting. - 0 uses 
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*

Theme: A neutral killer with a focus on keeping drained players alive as a resource, similarly to a mixture of a ToS Arsonist or the Reaper&#39;s souls.
Survivability: Self-heal against poisoning/bleed in case a player is drained. Can&#39;t be killed by bears or Knights as Vital Drain doesn&#39;t count as an attack.
Late-game: Can survive the late-game via Infatuation providing she has a majority. Also can fake Princess provided the King doesn&#39;t die with Vital Drain&#39;s investigative abilityies.

Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:17:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-succubus-nk/70519.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Succubus (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="orchid"> The Succubus </font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Dependency (Passive)</strong> - If the Succubus dies during the night or is executed, all drained players will also die with her the following night.<br>
<strong>Transfer Life (Day)</strong> - Allows the Succubus to kill a drained player overnight, provided they are not healed or night immune, during the coming night and transfer their remaining life in turns to another drained player. This will also heal the latter player. If the Succubus transfers to herself, then she will gain a charge of Love’s Malady instead. If the first player is healed then the ability will still function but without the first player dying. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Infatuation (Day)</strong> - When this ability is activated, all drained players will vote to pardon the Succubus if she is put on trial. Usable while on trial. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Vital Drain (Night)</strong> - Learns the target player’s class type and will drain them to death over the next two nights. While there is at least one player being drained then the Succubus will heal herself if she is attacked. If a drained player is healed then their timer until they are drained to death will not lower for the night but neither the healer nor the player will be notified. Does not count as an attack for abilities such as Will o’ Wisp, Defend, and Bear Companion. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Love’s Malady (Night)</strong> - Instantly kills a player while bypassing Night Immunity, healing, and does not count as visiting. - 0 uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Theme: A neutral killer with a focus on keeping drained players alive as a resource, similarly to a mixture of a ToS Arsonist or the Reaper’s souls.<br>
Survivability: Self-heal against poisoning/bleed in case a player is drained. Can’t be killed by bears or Knights as Vital Drain doesn’t count as an attack.<br>
Late-game: Can survive the late-game via Infatuation providing she has a majority. Also can fake Princess provided the King doesn’t die with Vital Drain’s investigative abilityies.</p>
<p>Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-succubus-nk/70519/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-succubus-nk/70519/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70519-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-succubus-nk/70519.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Succubus (NK)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
