<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Two Major Bugs - Issues with Unseen and Mercenary</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/two-major-bugs-issues-with-unseen-and-mercenary/32856</link>
    <description>#### What happened?

There were two major bugs in a game I just played (username: TinyDeer). I was unable to take screenshots but will describe them in detail.

1. I was playing as Mercenary. Around night 5 I received a prompt at the end of the night that player 10 was converted to the Unseen. Discussing afterward, we had no answer to this major issue.

2. After the game ended, when I asked Unseen players why I saw that, the Mastermind said that he had tried to convert me a previous night but it had &quot;bugged out&quot;. Also, Unseen said that I appeared to them as Unseen the entire game even though I was Mercenary. They said &quot;your name was purple&quot;.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?

1. I should under no circumstances have seen as a Mercenary (not Sheriff, not Unseen) that another player was converted.

2. My role should not have appeared next to my name for Unseen players, and I should not have appeared to have been a part of their faction.

#### Steps to reproduce:

I don&#39;t know how we would reproduce this issue. Perhaps take a look at the coding regarding how Unseen see Mercenaries to see if there is some small loophole somewhere. If it helps, I was player number 1.

#### Comments:

I&#39;m sorry I can&#39;t provide screenshots. I could only see issue 1 - issue 2 was told to me by the Unseen after the game ended.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 23:04:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/two-major-bugs-issues-with-unseen-and-mercenary/32856.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Two Major Bugs - Issues with Unseen and Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TinyDeer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>There were two major bugs in a game I just played (username: TinyDeer). I was unable to take screenshots but will describe them in detail.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>I was playing as Mercenary. Around night 5 I received a prompt at the end of the night that player 10 was converted to the Unseen. Discussing afterward, we had no answer to this major issue.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>After the game ended, when I asked Unseen players why I saw that, the Mastermind said that he had tried to convert me a previous night but it had “bugged out”. Also, Unseen said that I appeared to them as Unseen the entire game even though I was Mercenary. They said “your name was purple”.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<ol>
<li>
<p>I should under no circumstances have seen as a Mercenary (not Sheriff, not Unseen) that another player was converted.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>My role should not have appeared next to my name for Unseen players, and I should not have appeared to have been a part of their faction.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<p>I don’t know how we would reproduce this issue. Perhaps take a look at the coding regarding how Unseen see Mercenaries to see if there is some small loophole somewhere. If it helps, I was player number 1.</p>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>I’m sorry I can’t provide screenshots. I could only see issue 1 - issue 2 was told to me by the Unseen after the game ended.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/two-major-bugs-issues-with-unseen-and-mercenary/32856/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/two-major-bugs-issues-with-unseen-and-mercenary/32856/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 23:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32856-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/two-major-bugs-issues-with-unseen-and-mercenary/32856.rss">Two Major Bugs - Issues with Unseen and Mercenary</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
