<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658</link>
    <description># Locations List

## Major Landmarks of Interest

### Continent : Lineara

- Northern Forest - Untouched Greenery
    - Jannis Falls - Waterfall of Light
    - Borio&#39;s Plains - Natural Nature
    - Terrian&#39;s Trees - Towering Canopies
- Millias State- Border State; Sandwich between Adiart and Telias. 
- Adiart Kingdom - Central Castle of the Grands, symbol of power.
    - Thashopolis - The Northeastern city of technology. 
      - Lavis Mines - A Mine full of resources, pumping out raw materials needed for the advancement of the land.
      - Contrast Building - The tallest building in the city. Houses the main offices for the Contrast organisation.
      - Factories of Contrast - Refining raw materials from the mines and manufacturing weapons of varying intensities.
      - Falch&#39;s Keep - A renowned store in the middle of the path from Lavis Mines to Thashopolis.
  - Terrion - The biggest City in Adiart.
      - Castle Argus - Palace of the Royals.
      - Adiart&#39;s Plaza - A Plaza that encompasses the entrance to the Palace.
      - Vaenqueer&#39;s Clothing Flagship Store - The flagship store of one of the highest clothesmaker companies.
      - Residential Areas - With different areas (streets) for the nobles and the commoners.
   - Finera - A small and quiet town located to the west of the nation.
      - **Forsyth&#39;s Military Academy** - Where you&#39;ll be going. 
      - Fine Radio - A radio station that delivers the news to the nation.
   - Tempor - A fishing port south of the nation. Often shrouded in mist from the ocean. 
   - Liberl Hub - A busy marketplace where merchants come to gather. The marketplace is a tourist attraction beholden to all.
      - Liberia Marketplace - A collection of stalls that make up some of the finest products for a relatively good price.
   - Garrelia Fortress - A Military Base, said to be the largest in the world. It is stated at the eastern border of the nation, protecting the nation from Telias. 
  - Fallair - A small town in the east that produces the country&#39;s food stock. 

- Southern Renderers.
   - Agravain Highlands - Vast plains that stretch over the south. Home to the founders of the two nations. Considered as ancestral land. The steeds there are considered the finest in the continent. Wandering Nomads live in these parts, living each day in a humble manner.

ABOVE ARE THE LOCATIONS YOUR CHARACTER CAN ORIGINATE FROM.
BELOW ARE THE LOCATIONS YOUR CHARACTER CANNOT ORIGINATE FROM.

- Westlands - Oceans, Abundance of Seafood.
- Eastlands- The Republic
    - Telias - The nation across Millias State. A Republican Nation that opposes Adiart rule. Its size is similar to Adiart, with its fair share of complexity.


Histories of each place will be covered in their own individual posts below.
Lore will be posted here as well. 
New locations will be added.

https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/5?u=shurian
https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/6?u=shurian</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 15:43:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Roleplaying</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Big Bump.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 15:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-37</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Clubs</h2>
<p>Riding Club - Lacrosse Club - <strong>Fields</strong></p>
<p>Fishing Club - Lower and Upper Class Chess Clubs - Literature Club - Photography Club - Student Council - <strong>Student Union</strong></p>
<p>Engineering Club - <strong>Engineering Building</strong></p>
<p>Wind Orchestra - Art Club - Culinary Club - <strong>Main Building 2nd Floor</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 02:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>The School Buildings.</h2>
<p>There are a number of buildings to note of.</p>
<h3>Main School Building.</h3>
<p>Central.<br>
The Infirmary, Teacher’s Lounge, Principal’s Office and Conference Room are on the right of the first floor. Second Year classrooms are on the left. Both ways have a staircase that leads to the second floor. The building is shaped like a Ushape.<br>
On the second floor, we have Club Rooms on the right and First Year Classrooms on the left. And the third floor is a roof, allowing anyone to look over the place itself.<br>
Club rooms include the Wind Orchestra Room, Art Room, Home Economics Room (Cooking Club) and the Computer Room (usually locked up).</p>
<h3>Student Union</h3>
<p>East of the school building.<br>
The canteen is on the first floor. Together with a weapons shop, that coincidentally sells quartz as well, you won’t be missing much from this shop. On the second floor, you’ll find more club rooms and the student council room at the end of the hallway. And on the third floor, we have a quiet study session area.<br>
Club rooms include… Lower and Upper chess clubs. Literature Club, Photography Club and Fishing Club.</p>
<h3>The Library</h3>
<p>Straight East of the entrance.<br>
Southwest of the building.<br>
Study here, with much information about the world’s history, one can never go wrong here.<br>
Library is open.</p>
<h3>The Auditorium</h3>
<p>Southwest of the school building.<br>
Usually locked up when not in use, this is for students to practice their fine arts.<br>
Locked.</p>
<h3>The Gymnasium.</h3>
<p>North of the school building.<br>
Sporting the club room for the Fencing Club, as well as a swimming pool, this place can be popular at times. Also, on the second floor are several storerooms for the Gardening Club and the clubs forementioned. The swimming club is having their meet now.</p>
<h3>The Garden</h3>
<p>North of the school building.<br>
A haven for the Gardening Club, this place is where the flowers grow. There is a small pond for fishing enthusiasts to fish on. This is besides the Gymnasium and north of the school building. The Gardening Club does not seem to have a meeting for today.</p>
<h3>The Fields</h3>
<p>West of the School Building.<br>
A place where students train in the aspect of fighting, where the Riding and Lacrosse clubs belong.<br>
Current Status: Riding Club and Lacrosse Clubs are up.</p>
<h3>Engineering Building.</h3>
<p>Northeast of the School Building. Houses the Engineering Club. Open.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 01:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>If you want a bit, drink a glass. If you want to be drunk, drink a pint. If you want to knock yourself out, drink a Vale-stein.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 08:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Principal Vandyke Ferlias</h2>
<p>A member of the Ferlias family, a commoner whose ancestors fought with the first Emperor Adiart to unite the western lands. He is known for being one of the strongest commanders in Adiart. After retiring from service as the High Commander of the Imperial Armies, he made his way to education. A strong advocate for peace, he trains the next generation for his homeland’s protection.</p>
<p>He is said to be able to bring a tank down in a single blow, but that was while he was in his prime. Now? He could be just a feeble old man.</p>
<h2>Josephine Rogner</h2>
<p>A teacher focusing on the political side of education. She teaches and oversees each student’s training. She has her pride as a noble, yet she does things as she sees fit. A black sheep in her family, her father and her are not on good terms.</p>
<h2>Thomas Rieveldt</h2>
<p>A history teacher. Extremely carefree, often bringing down the house with his ramblings of history. Speaks often of history and history. Too much history. People doubt he even has some kind of history.</p>
<h2>Leonardo Reinhardt</h2>
<p>A military lieutenant in the Imperial Army 2nd Armored Division. He is a serious person, often butting heads with one particular teacher, for her unusual personality as an instructor. He teaches the military tactics class in the school.</p>
<h2>Sara Valestein</h2>
<p>A teacher who oversees the combat training of each student. She is known to be flippant, relaxed and easy-going.</p>
<h2>Beatrice Le Louche</h2>
<p>A nurse that was a combat nurse in her service. She is adept at treating wounds, as she had her fair share of stories to tell. She is the kind and caring wife of the principal Vandyke.</p>
<h2>Herschel Leif</h2>
<p>This kind and gentle teacher can’t hurt a fly! She is the soft-handed teacher that teaches art classes here in this academy. Not only that, she is an adept at nursing as well!</p>
<h2>Harst Boldrun</h2>
<p>This is the vice-president of the school, harsh and militaristic. He prides himself as a noble and is convinced that all nobles are better than commoners. He is strict to all, meting out punishments to those that do not follow school regulations. His sharp tongue has left many in tears.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 08:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-33</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Forsyth’s Military Academy</h2>
<p>Auditorium<br>
<a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-main-thread/76732/101?u=shurian" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-main-thread/76732/101?u=shurian</a></p>
<p>Entrance<br>
<a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-main-thread/76732/28?u=shurian" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-main-thread/76732/28?u=shurian</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 04:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Ousting of the Bracers</h1>
<p>In recent years, the provincial armies have ousted the Bracer guilds one by one from the country, forcing Bracers to leave the country or change professions.<br>
The official reason is that they were overarching their rights on the people, infringing on the noble’s territory. Yet, many say that they were afraid of bracers taking over the trust of the people, thus removing them.<br>
There is only one Bracer guild left, residing in Tempor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 01:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Orbal Revolution</h2>
<p>Just 50 years ago, Contrast was founded by Gywn Contrast with his group of mechanics. They spearheaded the Orbal Revolution, making usage of quartz orbs to power our everyday lives. An explosive age where modernization occured, they quickly raked in money.</p>
<h2>The Great Divide</h2>
<p>In the year 1575, the union Lineara split to become Adiart, Telias and Agravain respectively. Through the next 2 centuries, wars often broke out between the two nations Adiart and Telias. It was only in 1782 when the two nations made peace with one another,  through the Transcontinental Ceasefire Agreement. Even so, the two nations have been at odds with one another, the conflict still brews even till today.</p>
<h2>Northern Forest</h2>
<p>Many know of the Forest. But they never set foot in it. There is a rumor. Once you get in, you never get out.</p>
<h2>Jaegar Corps</h2>
<p>These mercenaries corporations are all about the money. They do the job, no matter how dirty. The opposite of the humanitarian Bracers. Gold, is all that speaks for them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 15:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s true.<br>
Is a guy on a boat allowed?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 09:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ohhhhh<br>
<em>Too bad you’re students. What is this? Isekai dreams?</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-character-sheets/76665/2" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/academy-character-sheets/76665/2</a><br>
All of them are in the Roleplaying Section of this forum.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whats the link to the character?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="James" data-post="21" data-topic="76658">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/james/40/16062_2.png" class="avatar"> James:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>axe murderer god</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As in being a god, not murdering gods.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Axe (Yes)<br>
Murders Gods (Even if you could there are not gods here lol)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was kidding. Sorta.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="James" data-post="21" data-topic="76658">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/james/40/16062_2.png" class="avatar"> James:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>god!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>Looks at self. Starts weeping. Praying the murdering god part was a lie.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cool.<br>
<em>Rubs hands together.</em><br>
Prepare to face an axe murderer god!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>DMs are much appreciated <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about a dm?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can make a draft in the CS thread, but dont post it</p>
<p>I’ll be unlocking it soon. Give or take 3 hours.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 07:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can i make one?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 07:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Character Sheets will be up soon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fireslol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yup, sign me up for this, I’m already into it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 06:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not exactly. This is the future of the ToL you know.</p>
<p>So… :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 06:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fireslol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OMG I JUST REALIZED…This is a ToL roleplay!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 06:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76658-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/academy-locations-background-inprog/76658.rss">Academy - Locations &amp; Background {INPROG}</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
