<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Make the first (and second?) Cult conversion be &quot;free&quot;, with no skipped night after it</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027</link>
    <description>Cult seems a bit weak relative to Unseen (and all the stats and reports I&#39;ve seen have backed this up, though granted that they&#39;re limited and anecdotal.)  It&#39;d be interesting to buff them in a way that makes them more powerful while making them more distinct from the Unseen.

Additionally, the Cult&#39;s unique features - larger maximum size, sacrifices - rarely come up because their population just doesn&#39;t reach that point.

Therefore, I suggest the following buff:  The first Cult conversion, and [i]maybe[/i] the second, does not impose a one-day cooldown.  After that, they cool down and can only convert every other night as usual.  This would cause the Cult to expand rapidly early on and ensure that they actually have more numbers than the Unseen (making up for their weaker abilities, more difficult fakeclaiming, and heavy dependence on the jailable / occupiable CL.)

Although it sounds powerful, realize that even if they get two such &quot;free&quot; converts, it amounts to just +1 person (an extra convert on one night when they otherwise couldn&#39;t have, with conversions N1, N2, and N3 instead of just N1 and N3), and it comes at the expense of not killing N2 and probably confirming that it&#39;s a Cult game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 22:14:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Make the first (and second?) Cult conversion be &quot;free&quot;, with no skipped night after it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this idea, but it can only have 1 free convert without a cool down the second must have a cool down, but the concept is interesting.<br>
<strong>/support</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 22:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51027-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027.rss">Make the first (and second?) Cult conversion be &quot;free&quot;, with no skipped night after it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Make the first (and second?) Cult conversion be &quot;free&quot;, with no skipped night after it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cult seems a bit weak relative to Unseen (and all the stats and reports I’ve seen have backed this up, though granted that they’re limited and anecdotal.)  It’d be interesting to buff them in a way that makes them more powerful while making them more distinct from the Unseen.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Cult’s unique features - larger maximum size, sacrifices - rarely come up because their population just doesn’t reach that point.</p>
<p>Therefore, I suggest the following buff:  The first Cult conversion, and <span class="bbcode-i">maybe</span> the second, does not impose a one-day cooldown.  After that, they cool down and can only convert every other night as usual.  This would cause the Cult to expand rapidly early on and ensure that they actually have more numbers than the Unseen (making up for their weaker abilities, more difficult fakeclaiming, and heavy dependence on the jailable / occupiable CL.)</p>
<p>Although it sounds powerful, realize that even if they get two such “free” converts, it amounts to just +1 person (an extra convert on one night when they otherwise couldn’t have, with conversions N1, N2, and N3 instead of just N1 and N3), and it comes at the expense of not killing N2 and probably confirming that it’s a Cult game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 22:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51027-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/make-the-first-and-second-cult-conversion-be-free-with-no-skipped-night-after-it/51027.rss">Make the first (and second?) Cult conversion be &quot;free&quot;, with no skipped night after it</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
