<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mastermind</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394</link>
    <description>http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Mastermind
 **Writing on the Wall**
Sometimes we can see the Unseen&#39;s messages in the castle, planned by who we can assume is the Mastermind.
__________________________________________________
_Isn&#39;t it peculiar that the Royals have been so inactive lately? Why are they so reluctant to execute criminals and potential criminals until they become a crisis? In this Castle we&#39;re so focused on redemption and feelings that we lack protection for ourselves. Where have all the Merchants gone? All of these unnecessary regulations have effectively frozen the economy, and where has it just happened to fall? With the Royalty. Where are your wages? How can we feed our children if starvation is going to kill us all? Look around, people! The king does not have nourishment for everyone, and has decided to starve the poor fool to insanity so that the rest of us can barely scrape by, and don&#39;t think you aren&#39;t next! This begs the question: Why must we be completely dependent on Royalty?  It&#39;s time someone has started asking questions about the corrupt government taking control of the people. For real freedom, you come with me._
_- The Mastermind_

________________________________________________________
_Save your fair castle._
_-The Unseen_



______________________

**Comments/Explanations**

This helps to give a reason as to why the Black Rose do what they do.

I read the lore of the (Unseen) king very closely, and what I found was he was depicted as a man with a heart of darkness, but that wouldn&#39;t explain how the Mastermind converts people so easily. There has to be some reason he can shake up loyalty to the Blue Dragon. Perhaps the Blue Dragon is an oppressive force, or is making a fatal mistake that goes uncorrected due to arrogance.

Look at the Lore for the Court Wizard and Sage. It is here that the Wizard accuses the King of treason, but after his conversion he is more calm. Perhaps it is because he now knows the truth. Perhaps in that (game) timeline the King is either afraid for his life, pointing his finger at every little thing, or he is a member of the Unseen himself, feigning ignorance for the purposes of evil. But is the Unseen truly evil?

Who knows? Look no further, citizens.

_____

I did some more postulating of the game&#39;s structure.. 

The Blue Dragon ARE liars! 


You see, if you look at the King&#39;s various forms (BD-N-UN)

And the various roles, you&#39;ll actually see the Deep-State Shadow-Government Aristo-Oligarchy going on within the secret society of the Nobles.
Three Nobles (typically the max amount for an oligarchy) that have tons of money

The King isn&#39;t even barely trusted (See every game where they question the king early on) 
Blue Dragon King literally has to prove himself as loyal to the system of government every time an invasion happens
Neutral King has had enough pretending and just wants to leave
Unseen King wants to reform the government

The &quot;Aristocrat&quot; is literally just a derogatory name for a Capitalist who took over the financial structure for a remake of the castle once the Unseen take over. In fact, most Unseen names are just derogatory remarks or words with negative connotation instead of legitimate occupations..

Knight- **Enforcer** (That just sounds bad)
Observer-**Nightwatch** (Nightwatches or &quot;lookouts&quot; make sure no-one watches during a crime)
Princess-**Duchess** (There&#39;s no Duke. There is only a Prince. Therefore Duchesses are bad.)
Mercenary-**Sellsword** (Mercs are neutral, but look at Sellsword. That sounds like someone who would trade honor, morality, and everything just for  a few shillings, while a Mercenary just has a job.

All of the bolded Unseen titles spell ENDS. The Blue Dragon fear the Unseen because their superior logic trumps the Blue lie, and will spell their doom if they aren&#39;t shut down.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 15:48:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mastermind</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you very much,</p>
<p>I added a bit more to it, and I’m cleaning about the unnecessary portions to make it more… streamlined. I hope you enjoy.</p>
<p>(Changing it again to give some classes their own segments)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 15:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1394-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Mastermind</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mastermind</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow, that quote from the mastermind at the end is crazy</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="B_Psycho2" data-post="1" data-topic="1394">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/b_psycho2/40/645_2.png" class="avatar"> B_Psycho2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Isn’t it peculiar that the Royals have been so inactive lately? Why are they so reluctant to execute criminals and potential criminals until they become a crisis? In this Castle we’re so focused on redemption and feelings that we lack protection for ourselves. Look at this objectively, I am one of them myself, but the cause is just. Speaking of protection, where have all the Merchants gone? All of these unnecessary regulations have effectively frozen the economy, and where has it just happened to fall? With the Royalty. Where are your wages? Why is it that you are completely dependent on the Royals to feed your children? It’s time someone has started asking questions about the corrupt government taking control of the people. For real freedom, you come with me.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Mastermind</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username='"Rogue"' data-post="2" data-topic="1394">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 "Rogue":</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I support it becoming lore.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 23:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1394-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Mastermind</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mastermind</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Mastermind" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Mastermind</a><br>
<strong>Writing on the Wall</strong><br>
Sometimes we can see the Unseen’s messages in the castle, planned by who we can assume is the Mastermind.</p>
<hr>
<p><em>Isn’t it peculiar that the Royals have been so inactive lately? Why are they so reluctant to execute criminals and potential criminals until they become a crisis? In this Castle we’re so focused on redemption and feelings that we lack protection for ourselves. Where have all the Merchants gone? All of these unnecessary regulations have effectively frozen the economy, and where has it just happened to fall? With the Royalty. Where are your wages? How can we feed our children if starvation is going to kill us all? Look around, people! The king does not have nourishment for everyone, and has decided to starve the poor fool to insanity so that the rest of us can barely scrape by, and don’t think you aren’t next! This begs the question: Why must we be completely dependent on Royalty?  It’s time someone has started asking questions about the corrupt government taking control of the people. For real freedom, you come with me.</em><br>
<em>- The Mastermind</em></p>
<hr>
<p><em>Save your fair castle.</em><br>
<em>-The Unseen</em></p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Comments/Explanations</strong></p>
<p>This helps to give a reason as to why the Black Rose do what they do.</p>
<p>I read the lore of the (Unseen) king very closely, and what I found was he was depicted as a man with a heart of darkness, but that wouldn’t explain how the Mastermind converts people so easily. There has to be some reason he can shake up loyalty to the Blue Dragon. Perhaps the Blue Dragon is an oppressive force, or is making a fatal mistake that goes uncorrected due to arrogance.</p>
<p>Look at the Lore for the Court Wizard and Sage. It is here that the Wizard accuses the King of treason, but after his conversion he is more calm. Perhaps it is because he now knows the truth. Perhaps in that (game) timeline the King is either afraid for his life, pointing his finger at every little thing, or he is a member of the Unseen himself, feigning ignorance for the purposes of evil. But is the Unseen truly evil?</p>
<p>Who knows? Look no further, citizens.</p>
<hr>
<p>I did some more postulating of the game’s structure…</p>
<p>The Blue Dragon ARE liars!</p>
<p>You see, if you look at the King’s various forms (BD-N-UN)</p>
<p>And the various roles, you’ll actually see the Deep-State Shadow-Government Aristo-Oligarchy going on within the secret society of the Nobles.<br>
Three Nobles (typically the max amount for an oligarchy) that have tons of money</p>
<p>The King isn’t even barely trusted (See every game where they question the king early on)<br>
Blue Dragon King literally has to prove himself as loyal to the system of government every time an invasion happens<br>
Neutral King has had enough pretending and just wants to leave<br>
Unseen King wants to reform the government</p>
<p>The “Aristocrat” is literally just a derogatory name for a Capitalist who took over the financial structure for a remake of the castle once the Unseen take over. In fact, most Unseen names are just derogatory remarks or words with negative connotation instead of legitimate occupations…</p>
<p>Knight- <strong>Enforcer</strong> (That just sounds bad)<br>
Observer-<strong>Nightwatch</strong> (Nightwatches or “lookouts” make sure no-one watches during a crime)<br>
Princess-<strong>Duchess</strong> (There’s no Duke. There is only a Prince. Therefore Duchesses are bad.)<br>
Mercenary-<strong>Sellsword</strong> (Mercs are neutral, but look at Sellsword. That sounds like someone who would trade honor, morality, and everything just for  a few shillings, while a Mercenary just has a job.</p>
<p>All of the bolded Unseen titles spell ENDS. The Blue Dragon fear the Unseen because their superior logic trumps the Blue lie, and will spell their doom if they aren’t shut down.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 23:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1394-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-mastermind/1394.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Mastermind</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
