<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NK survival guide</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013</link>
    <description>I saw another guide, but it works completely around the meta of becoming king.

----------------
**Possessor**

- **Do not** take use possess until after the psychic is gone, and all physicians have either used their reanimates or are dead.
 - **Do not** kill the knights directly. The best way to kill multiple people is to use puppet strings on a non-knight and send them into someone the knight is guarding.
- **In regards** to the above statement, if someone claims &quot;Possessed!&quot; then most knight who have played a possessor game before will stop guarding. To prevent this, you can either possess yourself early game (this is risky as then the knights could simply kill you), or not do anything. It is important to mention that a knight who has a log full of &quot;no one&quot; will likely be executed as they are useless.
 - **If you want** to kill the king, the best time to do so is nights 1-4, while they are using allies. The only time you should kill the king is if it would prevent blue dragon from voting you, or you want to be come neutral king 
 - **If you** come across someone is immune, try possessing that player into people who are likely guarded by knights.
- **Try puppet stringing** important people into the hunter. Either the hunter will die, or the person you stringed will die to bears

To sum it up: Don&#39;t use possess until physician and psychic cannot do anything about it, don&#39;t bother directly killing knights as thy are your tools, and if you want to be king, kill him nights 1-4 (preferably 3 or 4, phys/alch have a new target)

--------------
**Reaper**

 - **your goal** is to get as many souls as possible early game (5-6). The best way to do this is to kill people who claim poisoned/bleeding, as they will die naturally and so you will remain hidden, and a knight is unlikely to be on them, and you will bypass anyone who tries to heal their affect.
- **Once** you have enough souls, you can either do the lame method (consume a soul, attack king and ask to be king in death note) or you can be a real man and be as reckless as you want, because you don&#39;t need to worry about bears, knights, or the like
 - **Chill** People who say &quot;I think I found the reaper.&quot; A smart player will just out you in one message, but most players aren&#39;t smart yet
 - **Chill** People who are accusing someone else and people who are about to put on stand. If the person is about to be on stand, they will likely go in jail the next night (possibly instead of yourself), or be executed if the prince is dead
 - **Chill** Someone during a reaper check to make others think they are dead. If you reaped someone, then 2 people will be silent, and some new players will try to get one of them to speak by voting them.
 - **If you** come across a death immune player, it is best to just out them in your death note; your priority is to kill everyone, not just them. Consume darkness is best used to kill king.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:48:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NK survival guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 15:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-13013-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013.rss">NK survival guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NK survival guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aurelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice One! :3 I like it!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-13013-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013.rss">NK survival guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NK survival guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I saw another guide, but it works completely around the meta of becoming king.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Possessor</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Do not</strong> take use possess until after the psychic is gone, and all physicians have either used their reanimates or are dead.</li>
<li>
<strong>Do not</strong> kill the knights directly. The best way to kill multiple people is to use puppet strings on a non-knight and send them into someone the knight is guarding.</li>
<li>
<strong>In regards</strong> to the above statement, if someone claims “Possessed!” then most knight who have played a possessor game before will stop guarding. To prevent this, you can either possess yourself early game (this is risky as then the knights could simply kill you), or not do anything. It is important to mention that a knight who has a log full of “no one” will likely be executed as they are useless.</li>
<li>
<strong>If you want</strong> to kill the king, the best time to do so is nights 1-4, while they are using allies. The only time you should kill the king is if it would prevent blue dragon from voting you, or you want to be come neutral king</li>
<li>
<strong>If you</strong> come across someone is immune, try possessing that player into people who are likely guarded by knights.</li>
<li>
<strong>Try puppet stringing</strong> important people into the hunter. Either the hunter will die, or the person you stringed will die to bears</li>
</ul>
<p>To sum it up: Don’t use possess until physician and psychic cannot do anything about it, don’t bother directly killing knights as thy are your tools, and if you want to be king, kill him nights 1-4 (preferably 3 or 4, phys/alch have a new target)</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Reaper</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>your goal</strong> is to get as many souls as possible early game (5-6). The best way to do this is to kill people who claim poisoned/bleeding, as they will die naturally and so you will remain hidden, and a knight is unlikely to be on them, and you will bypass anyone who tries to heal their affect.</li>
<li>
<strong>Once</strong> you have enough souls, you can either do the lame method (consume a soul, attack king and ask to be king in death note) or you can be a real man and be as reckless as you want, because you don’t need to worry about bears, knights, or the like</li>
<li>
<strong>Chill</strong> People who say “I think I found the reaper.” A smart player will just out you in one message, but most players aren’t smart yet</li>
<li>
<strong>Chill</strong> People who are accusing someone else and people who are about to put on stand. If the person is about to be on stand, they will likely go in jail the next night (possibly instead of yourself), or be executed if the prince is dead</li>
<li>
<strong>Chill</strong> Someone during a reaper check to make others think they are dead. If you reaped someone, then 2 people will be silent, and some new players will try to get one of them to speak by voting them.</li>
<li>
<strong>If you</strong> come across a death immune player, it is best to just out them in your death note; your priority is to kill everyone, not just them. Consume darkness is best used to kill king.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 14:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-13013-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/nk-survival-guide/13013.rss">NK survival guide</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
