<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Crashing Today</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-crashing-today/7466</link>
    <description>Anybody else having problems with the game crashing today? Never happened to me before today.  Now 2 times within the last couple hours it crashed at the same moment in the game.  Game starts, i open my journal and write my name and class, D1 turns to N1, and then my sword curser turns into that blue spinning loading curser and nothing happens until i close the games window and it says the program isn&#39;t repsonding.  First time i was a drunk so i didn&#39;t feel TOO bad for the team i left hanging, but this time i was prince and so i&#39;m sure everybody was pretty upset.  Anybody have any idea what is going on?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 17:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-crashing-today/7466.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game Crashing Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Anybody else having problems with the game crashing today? Never happened to me before today.  Now 2 times within the last couple hours it crashed at the same moment in the game.  Game starts, i open my journal and write my name and class, D1 turns to N1, and then my sword curser turns into that blue spinning loading curser and nothing happens until i close the games window and it says the program isn’t repsonding.  First time i was a drunk so i didn’t feel TOO bad for the team i left hanging, but this time i was prince and so i’m sure everybody was pretty upset.  Anybody have any idea what is going on?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-crashing-today/7466/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-crashing-today/7466/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 17:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7466-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-crashing-today/7466.rss">Game Crashing Today</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
