<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443</link>
    <description>**&quot;Dragon&quot;** is a new Neutral Killing class.

There are also different _types_ of Dragon. Dragon is unique, and would take the usual Neutral Killing spot. (So no rounds with Dragon AND another NK.)

Please note: **This class is a bit OP on purpose. It&#39;s a Dragon. I can always scale (lol) it back, though...**

----

**Basic Dragon abilities shared by all types of Dragon:**

Passive 1: [BLUE VEIN ICON]
**Cold Blooded** - Players who visit you are marked as having touched your treasure hoard. You cannot be stopped from killing anyone who has visited you on any previous night. (Cannot be occupied, removes target&#39;s death immunity.) Notice to Dragon: &quot;Someone has been near your hoard! If you find out who they are, you cannot be stopped from killing them.&quot;

Passive 2: [GIANT DRAGON FANGS ICON]
**Omnivorous** - Every two players you kill will give you one additional use of your &quot;Radiant Scales&quot; day ability.

Day Ability: [SHIMMERING SCALE ICON]
**Radiant Scales** - You will be immune from death the following night. (2 uses, recharged with &quot;Omnivorous&quot; passive.)

Night Ability 1: [DESTROYED CHEST PLATE ICON]
**Midnight Snack** - Choose a player to kill. (Unlimited use.)

The &quot;Midnight Snack&quot; ability will cause effects to anyone who visits your victim, depending on what type of Dragon you are:

- Flame Dragon: Visitors to your target are Wisped to you. (You see the visitors to target.)
- Ice Dragon: Visitors to your target are occupied. (Prevents saving/watching target, etc.)
- Iron Dragon: Visitors to your target begin bleeding.
- Rock Dragon: Visitors to your target are &quot;dazed&quot;. (Can speak only once &amp; can&#39;t use day abilities, but only for 2 days. Status can be healed. Added this status as part of my &quot;Barbarian&quot; class suggestion, think it could be cool.)
- Shadow Dragon: Visitors to your target are &quot;terrified&quot;. (Any limited action they try to use the next day/night requires double cost. IE: Takes up 2 uses, and if they only have 1 use left it cannot be used because 2 is required.)
- Some of these could be reworked, and more types of Dragon could be added, as well. ;)

Night Ability 2: [CRACKING DRAGON EGG ICON]
**Hatchling** - Send a Drake to inhabit the home of a target player, causing them to have the same investigative results as you for the night. (3 uses.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:25:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean…  how do you picture it playing?  What’s the strategy involved?</p>
<p>As far as I can tell, you just kill people, activate your immunity when you think you’re likely to be attacked, and maybe occasionally send out hatchlings if you think someone is going to be investigated.  It doesn’t come together in any interesting way - it just feels like a bunch of abilities thrown together at random around a shell that’s ultimately just a generic killer.</p>
<p>How does a dragon game play differently than a Reaper, Possessor, or Sorcerer game?  It’s missing any of the things that make those unique, but beyond that it mostly just feels like a “generic NK” - from the perspective of everyone else in the game, the dragon is mostly just going to be someone who kills every so often and occasionally frames.</p>
<p>Adding a class is a lot of work and will shift the game’s balance; additionally, each class that they add increases the game’s complexity and makes it harder for new players to pick up.  To make up for that, the class has to add something new and interesting in a way that introduces new strategic depth.  Basically, you should be able to articulate what you want the class to <span class="bbcode-i">accomplish</span>, not just how they’ll work mechanically.  What does this class accomplish?  What does it add to the game?</p>
<p>(eg. possessors provide another reason to doubt previously-confirmed people, including conversion-immune ones; Reapers require that people deal with reaped people; Sorcerers have a unique dynamic with other evils.)</p>
<p>Also, I’m extremely skeptical about having so many dragon variations.  Again, this adds a lot of complexity without much payoff that I can see.  In a game as big and complicated as this, I think it’s useful to view complexity as a resource to be spent - there’s a limit to how complicated the game can get before it becomes impenetrable for new players, so when a class adds a lot of complexity, you have to be able to justify that it provides depth or improves the game in some other way to make it worth all that.  This seems like a lot of added complexity thrown in just because you can, or just for flavor reasons or whatever.</p>
<p>Flavorful isn’t <span class="bbcode-i">bad</span>, but a role should offer more than just that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35443-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443.rss">[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They’re BD after all. XD</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 23:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35443-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443.rss">[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He isn’t hiding. People are just really unobservant.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 23:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35443-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443.rss">[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How do people not know who the Prince is? How can the Princess be thrown in the dungeon without the Prince knowing who his sister is? How is a Reaper passing for human? How do you do something to someone with everyone standing around the same table without anyone seeing you? How are people with pumpkins for heads standing around with Santa Claus? How does a Hunter have a pet bear but it can only guard him two nights instead of forever? How–</p>
<p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Before I answer your questions, could you perhaps elaborate on how this is a ‘random collection of abilities’?</p>
<p>(Though if you don’t see what it does that other NKs don’t, I can’t help you with that one. It’s spelled out pretty thoroughly.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35443-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443.rss">[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But, thematically…  how is the dragon passing as human?  <span class="bbcode-i">Why</span> is it passing as human?</p>
<p>The dragon can be thrown in jail by a Prince?  And executed?  Or voted up and executed by the court?</p>
<p>Beyond that, I’m just not seeing what it adds to the game.  It looks like just a random collection of abilities to me - what’s the overarching concept?  What does it bring to the table, in terms of how it plays and how it works when you’re playing against it, that other NKs don’t offer?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 23:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35443-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443.rss">[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>"Dragon"</strong> is a new Neutral Killing class.</p>
<p>There are also different <em>types</em> of Dragon. Dragon is unique, and would take the usual Neutral Killing spot. (So no rounds with Dragon AND another NK.)</p>
<p>Please note: <strong>This class is a bit OP on purpose. It’s a Dragon. I can always scale (lol) it back, though…</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Basic Dragon abilities shared by all types of Dragon:</strong></p>
<p>Passive 1: [BLUE VEIN ICON]<br>
<strong>Cold Blooded</strong> - Players who visit you are marked as having touched your treasure hoard. You cannot be stopped from killing anyone who has visited you on any previous night. (Cannot be occupied, removes target’s death immunity.) Notice to Dragon: “Someone has been near your hoard! If you find out who they are, you cannot be stopped from killing them.”</p>
<p>Passive 2: [GIANT DRAGON FANGS ICON]<br>
<strong>Omnivorous</strong> - Every two players you kill will give you one additional use of your “Radiant Scales” day ability.</p>
<p>Day Ability: [SHIMMERING SCALE ICON]<br>
<strong>Radiant Scales</strong> - You will be immune from death the following night. (2 uses, recharged with “Omnivorous” passive.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: [DESTROYED CHEST PLATE ICON]<br>
<strong>Midnight Snack</strong> - Choose a player to kill. (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p>The “Midnight Snack” ability will cause effects to anyone who visits your victim, depending on what type of Dragon you are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Flame Dragon: Visitors to your target are Wisped to you. (You see the visitors to target.)</li>
<li>Ice Dragon: Visitors to your target are occupied. (Prevents saving/watching target, etc.)</li>
<li>Iron Dragon: Visitors to your target begin bleeding.</li>
<li>Rock Dragon: Visitors to your target are “dazed”. (Can speak only once &amp; can’t use day abilities, but only for 2 days. Status can be healed. Added this status as part of my “Barbarian” class suggestion, think it could be cool.)</li>
<li>Shadow Dragon: Visitors to your target are “terrified”. (Any limited action they try to use the next day/night requires double cost. IE: Takes up 2 uses, and if they only have 1 use left it cannot be used because 2 is required.)</li>
<li>Some of these could be reworked, and more types of Dragon could be added, as well. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">
</li>
</ul>
<p>Night Ability 2: [CRACKING DRAGON EGG ICON]<br>
<strong>Hatchling</strong> - Send a Drake to inhabit the home of a target player, causing them to have the same investigative results as you for the night. (3 uses.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35443-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-dragons-differently-flavored-neutral-killers/35443.rss">[Class Suggestion] DRAGONS (Differently Flavored Neutral Killers)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
