<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791</link>
    <description>This guide will be helpful for people completely new to the game.
Note: This is a basic guide I wrote, it does not include every class by any means just describes the basic dynamics of the game and the important classes

Factions:

Blue Dragon - the “good guys”, majority of people are blue dragon. Goal: Defeat unseen/cult (whichever one is in game) and the neutral killer.

Unseen/Cult - the “bad guys”, only one or the other will be in a specific game (in a game with unseen there will not be a cult and vice versa), two members start as unseen/cult but more can be converted. Goal: Defeat blue dragon and the neutral killer.

Neutral - Not allied to either faction. Goals drastically vary depending on the neutral. Certain neutrals are harmless to either class, while others are harmful. Depending on the neutral one is, they may or may not want to fake a claim. Cannot be converted to unseen/cult. 2-3 regular neutrals can appear in game, as well as one neutral killer. (So 3-4 neutrals total). Goal of the neutral killer is to defeat the blue dragon and cult/unseen (but other neutrals can live).

Kings - Allied to their respective faction. Good king - allied to blue dragon, unseen/cult king (evil king) allied with unseen/cult. Neutral king - any regular neutral that becomes king. Goal is just to simply survive. Pretender king - any pretender that becomes king. Pretender’s goal is to become king and survive. Psycho king - any neutral killer that becomes king. Goal is to eliminate blue dragon and unseen/cult. Note: Starting kings are always either good king or evil king, never any type of neutral king. If any member of blue dragon becomes king, they become a good king. If any member of unseen/cult becomes king, they become evil king. If a king dies, then elections are held for the new king. If a pretender is present they almost always win these elections.

Note: Blue dragon names are written in blue, cult in red, unseen in purple, and neutrals in white.

General game dynamics:

Every character has actions that can be done at night, these vary depending on class. You will be expected to keep logs of what you did at night. If you are an evil class or a neutral that does not want to reveal their true identity, you must make fake logs and pretend to be a blue dragon class or a harmless neutral. Certain characters have day abilities as well. If you are a character with day abilities, you will often be expected to use them and will in addition be expected to write these in your logbook. Though the classic logbook setup is n1, n2 etc you can edit it to say something like n1, d2, n2 etc. Note: Only one ability can be used per day, and only one ability can be used per night.

Uniqueness - certain characters are “unique” - there can be only one in a game at a time. These characters are marked with a star in the character menu.

Occupation - Certain characters can “occupy” others at night. In other words, they can stop a player from taking action at night. For example, if I am a class that can occupy others, and you are a sheriff, you might try to investigate someone at night, but if I occupy you, you do not investigate anybody. Certain characters are immune to occupation. These characters are marked with a purple swirly thing with a red x over it in the character menu.

Redirection - Certain characters can “redirect” others at night. In other words, they can choose a player’s target for them. For example, if I am a class that can redirect others, and you are a sheriff, you might try to investigate 8 at night, but if I redirect you to 6, you will instead investigate 6 that night. Certain characters are immune to redirection. They are marked with the same icon as occupy immune characters. Note: Characters that are immune to occupation are also immune to redirection, and vice versa.

Conversion - At night, the unseen/cult can convert one new member. After a member is converted, there is a one night cooldown to convert another member (as in, if the unseen converts a member on night 1 successfully, they cannot convert again until night 3). The unseen can have three members at a time, while the cult can have four members at a time. Any member of the blue dragon can be converted, with the exception of the prince. Neutrals cannot be converted. The king cannot be converted. If you do not want to memorize this, characters immune to conversion are marked with an orange “fire” symbol in the character menu. 

Death - certain characters can kill others at night. (for the most part, unseen/cult and the neutral killer, with exceptions). While most characters will die when attacked, certain characters are death immune. These characters will be marked with a green helmet in the character menu. Note: Even characters who are not death immune can avoid deaths in other ways.

Character types:

Killer, Offensive, Social, Support, Special, Investigative

The starting king has abilities at night that can tell him the class type of any character he chooses. If the king is good, special classes will appear as investigative. If the king is bad, special classes will appear as special. If you are an evil king and you find someone as a special class, you should write them in your logbook as investigative. Note: Future elected kings do not have these abilities. There are other classes that can see class types as well, but when they investigate certain characters, they will see two possible class types. These are always paired as such - Killer/Offensive, Social/Support, Special/Investigative. For example, if I choose to investigate you, and you are a social class, you will appear to me as social/support. This should be taken into account when fake claiming.

Important characters:

Blue Dragon - There is guaranteed to be one and only one prince, one or more paladin/sheriff (depending on the game type), and 7-8 other blue dragons

Prince - Type: Killer

Can imprison others at night. So long as a prince is alive, someone will be jailed that night (unless the prince is afk and/or dumb). The prince chooses who to imprison during the day, and at night, the jailed person is expected to give logs and a claim. The prince can then choose to execute the jailed person. Note: The jailed person cannot be executed until night 3. The prince can only execute up to three people. If the prince executes a blue dragon member, he loses the ability to execute others. Also, the prince must choose who to jail before the last five seconds of the day. A prince should avoid claiming unless they are put on trial or a mystic asks for claims (more on that later). When a prince jails someone, the jailed person does not know who the prince is, he just knows that he was jailed by the prince.

Sheriff - Type: Investigative NOTE: ONLY APPEARS IN UNSEEN GAMES

Has many abilities. Can put “scouts” on people during the day. Scouts will stay on a person indefinitely until either you choose another target or your target dies. Scouts tell you if the unseen visited your target at the end of each night. If the unseen visited your target, and the target did not die, it would be a good idea to share this with the court as your target likely has been converted. In addition, at night a sheriff can investigate others. This tells them if the person is unseen, or not suspicious. Note: Neutral killers appear as not suspicious. Sheriffs can only find members of the unseen. In addition, the sheriff has an ability called surveil, which is used if a sheriff is sure someone is unseen. This ability tells them what class they are (Example: Assassin). However, this has finite uses, and it goes to waste if the target is not unseen, so it should only be used if the sheriff is sure the target is unseen. If a sheriff finds someone as unseen, or finds their class type, they should always share with the court. If a sheriff finds someone as not suspicious, there is little reason to share unless the person is accused of treason or you are asked to share logs. Note: if the game is known to be a cult game and someone claims sheriff, they are lying.

Paladin - Type: Investigative NOTE: ONLY APPEARS IN CULT GAMES

The equivalent of the sheriff, but in a game with cult. Does not have the ability to put scouts on people. Can “Test Faith” people at night, which is the equivalent of the sheriff’s investigate ability (finds people either as cult or not suspicious). Also has an ability called “smite”. If it is “convert night (nights 1, 3, 5 etc)”, this ability will often be used. The smite ability allows you to choose a target. If the cult leader tries to convert either you or your target, you will kill the cult leader. Your target should be someone who you suspect will be converted/are an important blue dragon class (often this ability will be used on fellow paladins). Note: if the game is known to be an unseen game and someone claims paladin, they are lying.

Mystic - Type: Social

The “claim collector”. At night, can link people. Linking someone allows you to talk to them and get a claim. You do not have to reveal who you are, but you will know who your target is. In addition, another night ability is to conduit two people. They will be able to talk to each other during the night, and they will know the other person. You can watch the conversation but cannot join in. During the day, a mystic can use an ability called private matter to hide all whispers from the public. (Whispers are usually hidden from the public, but you will see something like “2 whispered to 4” etc. Also, certain classes can use abilities to read your whispers during the day, however the mystic’s private matter ability counters both of these). Often times someone will say something like “mystic here pm on send claims”, this means they turned on private matter. You should whisper them your claim by typing “/w [player number] [message/claim]”. Another ability is called telepathy, which causes a mystics next message to appear in the chat differently. Instead of saying something like “Alex [12]: Mooooooo” It will instead say “Telepathy: Mooooooo”. This allows a mystic to convey extremely important messages to the crowd, as telepathy catches people’s attention. It can also be used to say something without revealing who you are. Often times you will be asked to send a message using telepathy to prove you are not converted.

Unseen - starting characters will be the mastermind and the assassin

Mastermind - Type: Special (Often appears as investigative, see character types above)

The head of the unseen. During the day, has an ability to choose a target. Once this target is chosen, the mastermind will see all whispers to and from the target for the rest of the day. At night, the mastermind can convert other players to the unseen. If this action fails (target cannot be converted), nothing will occur and the mastermind can attempt again the following night on a different player. If this action succeeds, the target will become unseen, and you will have to wait a night before being able to use the ability again (if success on night 1, can be used again night 3, etc). Also note that if the unseen has three members, no new conversions can occur. During cooldown nights (nights where you cannot convert anyone) the mastermind has an ability called foresight, which basically tells him if a certain player can be converted, and if they can be then it gives him their converted class type (the class type that they would have if they were converted. The mastermind also has a day ability called dirty work, but this is practically never used nor should it be. If the mastermind dies, and the starting assassin is still alive, the starting assassin will become the mastermind. Note: If there is an assassin, but he was not the starting assassin (the original assassin), he will not become the mastermind.

Assassin - Type: Killer

The killer of the unseen. At night, he can choose a target to assassinate. This will kill them, on the assumption that they were not healed, protected or death immune. In addition, he can use an ability called 2-for-1, which allows him to kill two players instead of one on that night, but he can only use this ability once per game. During the day, the assassin can bleed a target. The target will be alerted that they are bleeding and often will tell the chat. If this person is not healed, they will die tomorrow night (example: if u bleed someone on day two, they will die on night three with no heal). In addition, the assassin has an ability called silence. If the assassin silences a target, they will not be able to speak or use day abilities for 20 seconds. This is often used on people who are accused of treason, to make them seem suspicious when in fact they are not. If the mastermind dies, and the current assassin is the original, the assassin will become the mastermind. If the assassin dies or becomes mastermind, and there are any converts (any other unseen class), they will become the assassin. This new assassin cannot become mastermind. If an assassin is not present, and someone is converted, they will become the assassin instead of the usual class they would become. 

Cult - starting characters will be the cult leader and any other random cult character.

Cult leader - Type: Special (Often appears as investigative, see character types above)

The powerhouse of the cult. Has a night ability called brainwash, which is the equivalent of the mastermind’s convert ability; converts another player, 1 night cooldown, yada yada yada. On cooldown nights (no conversions possible), the cult leader can use an ability called eradicate, which is the same as the assassin’s 2-for-1 ability (kills two players). However, unlike the assassin, who can only use 2-for-1 once, the cult leader can use eradicate three times. If a cult leader dies, and there is at least one other cult member, the oldest cult member will become the cult leader. Unlike the mastermind, which can only exist twice (original and starting assassin), the cult leader can exist many times, as even those who are converted can become cult leader. Also, unlike the unseen, which has a separate class for each possible blue dragon converted, the cult categorizes them by class type. For example, both a court wizard and a physician would become a ritualist when converted, because both court wizard and physician are support classes, and ritualist is the cult equivalent of any support class.

Kings - Only one person will start as the king, and it is always whoever’s number is 1. However, if a king dies, there will be elections and whoever is elected will become the new king. NOTE: STARTING KING WILL ALWAYS BE EITHER GOOD KING OR EVIL KING. Every STARTING king has an ability called allies (No elected kings have this ability); this is talked about under character types. Another ability of the kings is called guards, which basically makes them death immune for a night. Every king can use a day ability called point at someone when accusing them of treason; this adds another accusation (you will count as two people accusing said person of treason). The king also has a day ability called decide fate, which can be used to choose the fate of a certain person on trial without a vote. However, this ability can only be used once per game, and can only be used if the king has not used the point ability during that day. Most kings usually have little reason to ever use decide fate; Evil kings will use it if a prince is on trial. Because the win condition of an evil king is simply just for the unseen/cult to win, they can sacrifice themselves to get rid of a prince, as a prince is just as powerful if not more powerful than a king. Note: Every king’s character type is special, but this hardly matters.

Good king - Allied with blue dragon. Has 3 guards if he is the starting king, otherwise has 2 guards. If a blue dragon member becomes king, they become good king. Note: One guard = one night you can use the guards ability. 

Evil king - Allies with the cult/unseen. May be called cult king/unseen king, but usually referred to as evil king. Has 2 guards. If a cult/unseen member becomes king, they become evil king.

Pretender king - If a pretender becomes king, they become a pretender king. They must simply just survive until the end to win. Has 1 guard.

Psycho king - If a neutral killer becomes king, they become psycho king. They must eliminate all blue dragon members and all cult/unseen members. Unlike the other kings, psycho king is death immune and does not need guards. He has infinite guards and he uses his guards to kill other people (basically the same as an assassin’s assassinate ability) (Note: infinite meaning it can be used every night, he cannot kill more than one person per night).

Neutral king - Any other neutral that becomes king. Must survive until the end of the game. Has 2 guards.

Neutrals - 2-3 regular neutrals in addition to a neutral killer per game. Below are the objectives, not the abilities.

Alchemist - Type: Support

Just needs to survive until the end of the game. If one is an alchemist they should publicly claim this early on; alchemists are not allied with anyone and are typically harmless. Both blue dragon and evils will usually leave you alone, though in the beginning of the game you will be expected not to go against the blue dragon’s will.

Fool - Type: Social

Must get yourself executed on trial. Never publicly claim fool - the prince will simply execute you at night and you will lose. Do not claim an evil class either, as you will probably be recognized as a fool and be executed by the prince. Instead, claim a blue dragon class, but make sure to fill your logs with errors and information that is known to be incorrect, enough to get you executed but not enough for people to recognize you as a fool.

Inquisitor - Type: Investigative

If an inquisitor is in a game, then three players will randomly be marked as heathens. These players will know that they are heathens. You will be told what classes every heathen is, but not who they are (example: you know that your heathens are a sheriff, a mystic, and a butler). Your goal is to essentially kill every heathen, but realistically you just need to outlive them (they can be killed by others or die on trial). Whether or not you claim inquisitor depends on the situation - if all heathens are blue dragon classes, its probably best not to claim inquisitor, but if any cult members/unseen members are heathens, you might be able to get away with openly claiming inquisitor.

Mercenary - Type: Support

Needs to get six brilders. You start with two brilders, so you really only need to get four. You get brilders mostly by protecting people. When you guard a person, everyone targeting them will be occupied. You get a brilder for every person you occupy when guarding a person. In addition you can shield someone, and if someone tries to kill them you gain 3 brilders, but this cannot be used after it has succeeded. Mercenaries can safely open claim to the court and should do so early on to avoid suspicion.

Possessor - Type: Killer

Is a neutral killer. Needs to defeat the blue dragon and the unseen. Never openly claim any neutral killer, as BOTH sides want you dead. 

Reaper - Type: Killer

Is a neutral killer. Needs to defeat the blue dragon and the unseen. Never openly claim any neutral killer, as BOTH sides want you dead. 

Scorned - Type: Social

Similar to fool, but must frame others instead of themselves. Each night, they have certain abilities, and whoever they use their abilities on becomes their target, but only for the day. By the end of the game (or by the time they die), they must successfully get two of their targets executed. Never openly claim scorned, as scorned totally screws up blue dragon investigative classes. If you are a blue dragon class and it is known that a scorned is in game it may be worth executing as it messes with information greatly.

Sellsword - Type: Offensive

Not very useful until lots of information is known. Simply needs to defeat blue dragon; that is, sellsword can win with unseen/cult or with the neutral killer. Has abilities to occupy people. Never openly claim sellsword, as they are against blue dragon.

Sorceror - Type: Killer

Is a neutral killer. Needs to defeat the blue dragon and the unseen. Never openly claim any neutral killer, as BOTH sides want you dead.

Note: The Scorned and The Fool both have an ability called trollbox, which is a day ability and can only be used once per day (as with every day ability). This can be used to force players to say something into the chat without them knowing that they said it and is often used to throw suspicion (example: I am a fool, I trollbox the sheriff to say that I am unseen). Note: The devs can see a trollbox, so if you make someone else say something agains the rules you will be the person in trouble, not your target.

Language used in the game (slang, abbreviations, etc):

bd = blue dragon

nk = neutral killer

ek = evil king

gk = good king

pk = psycho king

tb = trollbox

dnd = did not die

dnr = did not require

wo = watched over

k/o = refers to the pairing of killer/offensive

s/s = refers to the pairing of social/support

s/i = refers to the pairing of special/investigative

cl = cult leader

mm = mastermind (note: if used in the logs of a maid, can also be referring to the matchmake ability)

poss = possessor

sorc = sorceror

pret = pretender

Let me know what I should add in the future</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 16:54:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Only trust level 3 users can do that iirc. I can do it for them if they permit me too however.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 16:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you’re gonna spend the hours to write this, why not also format it nice?</p>
<p>If you’re unfamiliar with Discourse formatting, if you make it a wiki one of us can do it for you <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/+1.png?v=9" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m surprised a first time poster has such a detailed guide. Welcome!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 05:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="hkittell14" data-post="1" data-topic="76791">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/invoker-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> hkittell14:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The powerhouse of the cell</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 02:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Welcome to the forums and awesome job you have there, it is clear the effort put into it<br>
Make yourself at home</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 01:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Isn’t unseen and neutral killer the good guys to a sellsword?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This might benefit from some formatting. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Welcome to the fora.</p>
<p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/post-formatting-tips/76746" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/post-formatting-tips/76746</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throne of Lies Basic Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hkittell14]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This guide will be helpful for people completely new to the game.<br>
Note: This is a basic guide I wrote, it does not include every class by any means just describes the basic dynamics of the game and the important classes</p>
<p>Factions:</p>
<p>Blue Dragon - the “good guys”, majority of people are blue dragon. Goal: Defeat unseen/cult (whichever one is in game) and the neutral killer.</p>
<p>Unseen/Cult - the “bad guys”, only one or the other will be in a specific game (in a game with unseen there will not be a cult and vice versa), two members start as unseen/cult but more can be converted. Goal: Defeat blue dragon and the neutral killer.</p>
<p>Neutral - Not allied to either faction. Goals drastically vary depending on the neutral. Certain neutrals are harmless to either class, while others are harmful. Depending on the neutral one is, they may or may not want to fake a claim. Cannot be converted to unseen/cult. 2-3 regular neutrals can appear in game, as well as one neutral killer. (So 3-4 neutrals total). Goal of the neutral killer is to defeat the blue dragon and cult/unseen (but other neutrals can live).</p>
<p>Kings - Allied to their respective faction. Good king - allied to blue dragon, unseen/cult king (evil king) allied with unseen/cult. Neutral king - any regular neutral that becomes king. Goal is just to simply survive. Pretender king - any pretender that becomes king. Pretender’s goal is to become king and survive. Psycho king - any neutral killer that becomes king. Goal is to eliminate blue dragon and unseen/cult. Note: Starting kings are always either good king or evil king, never any type of neutral king. If any member of blue dragon becomes king, they become a good king. If any member of unseen/cult becomes king, they become evil king. If a king dies, then elections are held for the new king. If a pretender is present they almost always win these elections.</p>
<p>Note: Blue dragon names are written in blue, cult in red, unseen in purple, and neutrals in white.</p>
<p>General game dynamics:</p>
<p>Every character has actions that can be done at night, these vary depending on class. You will be expected to keep logs of what you did at night. If you are an evil class or a neutral that does not want to reveal their true identity, you must make fake logs and pretend to be a blue dragon class or a harmless neutral. Certain characters have day abilities as well. If you are a character with day abilities, you will often be expected to use them and will in addition be expected to write these in your logbook. Though the classic logbook setup is n1, n2 etc you can edit it to say something like n1, d2, n2 etc. Note: Only one ability can be used per day, and only one ability can be used per night.</p>
<p>Uniqueness - certain characters are “unique” - there can be only one in a game at a time. These characters are marked with a star in the character menu.</p>
<p>Occupation - Certain characters can “occupy” others at night. In other words, they can stop a player from taking action at night. For example, if I am a class that can occupy others, and you are a sheriff, you might try to investigate someone at night, but if I occupy you, you do not investigate anybody. Certain characters are immune to occupation. These characters are marked with a purple swirly thing with a red x over it in the character menu.</p>
<p>Redirection - Certain characters can “redirect” others at night. In other words, they can choose a player’s target for them. For example, if I am a class that can redirect others, and you are a sheriff, you might try to investigate 8 at night, but if I redirect you to 6, you will instead investigate 6 that night. Certain characters are immune to redirection. They are marked with the same icon as occupy immune characters. Note: Characters that are immune to occupation are also immune to redirection, and vice versa.</p>
<p>Conversion - At night, the unseen/cult can convert one new member. After a member is converted, there is a one night cooldown to convert another member (as in, if the unseen converts a member on night 1 successfully, they cannot convert again until night 3). The unseen can have three members at a time, while the cult can have four members at a time. Any member of the blue dragon can be converted, with the exception of the prince. Neutrals cannot be converted. The king cannot be converted. If you do not want to memorize this, characters immune to conversion are marked with an orange “fire” symbol in the character menu.</p>
<p>Death - certain characters can kill others at night. (for the most part, unseen/cult and the neutral killer, with exceptions). While most characters will die when attacked, certain characters are death immune. These characters will be marked with a green helmet in the character menu. Note: Even characters who are not death immune can avoid deaths in other ways.</p>
<p>Character types:</p>
<p>Killer, Offensive, Social, Support, Special, Investigative</p>
<p>The starting king has abilities at night that can tell him the class type of any character he chooses. If the king is good, special classes will appear as investigative. If the king is bad, special classes will appear as special. If you are an evil king and you find someone as a special class, you should write them in your logbook as investigative. Note: Future elected kings do not have these abilities. There are other classes that can see class types as well, but when they investigate certain characters, they will see two possible class types. These are always paired as such - Killer/Offensive, Social/Support, Special/Investigative. For example, if I choose to investigate you, and you are a social class, you will appear to me as social/support. This should be taken into account when fake claiming.</p>
<p>Important characters:</p>
<p>Blue Dragon - There is guaranteed to be one and only one prince, one or more paladin/sheriff (depending on the game type), and 7-8 other blue dragons</p>
<p>Prince - Type: Killer</p>
<p>Can imprison others at night. So long as a prince is alive, someone will be jailed that night (unless the prince is afk and/or dumb). The prince chooses who to imprison during the day, and at night, the jailed person is expected to give logs and a claim. The prince can then choose to execute the jailed person. Note: The jailed person cannot be executed until night 3. The prince can only execute up to three people. If the prince executes a blue dragon member, he loses the ability to execute others. Also, the prince must choose who to jail before the last five seconds of the day. A prince should avoid claiming unless they are put on trial or a mystic asks for claims (more on that later). When a prince jails someone, the jailed person does not know who the prince is, he just knows that he was jailed by the prince.</p>
<p>Sheriff - Type: Investigative NOTE: ONLY APPEARS IN UNSEEN GAMES</p>
<p>Has many abilities. Can put “scouts” on people during the day. Scouts will stay on a person indefinitely until either you choose another target or your target dies. Scouts tell you if the unseen visited your target at the end of each night. If the unseen visited your target, and the target did not die, it would be a good idea to share this with the court as your target likely has been converted. In addition, at night a sheriff can investigate others. This tells them if the person is unseen, or not suspicious. Note: Neutral killers appear as not suspicious. Sheriffs can only find members of the unseen. In addition, the sheriff has an ability called surveil, which is used if a sheriff is sure someone is unseen. This ability tells them what class they are (Example: Assassin). However, this has finite uses, and it goes to waste if the target is not unseen, so it should only be used if the sheriff is sure the target is unseen. If a sheriff finds someone as unseen, or finds their class type, they should always share with the court. If a sheriff finds someone as not suspicious, there is little reason to share unless the person is accused of treason or you are asked to share logs. Note: if the game is known to be a cult game and someone claims sheriff, they are lying.</p>
<p>Paladin - Type: Investigative NOTE: ONLY APPEARS IN CULT GAMES</p>
<p>The equivalent of the sheriff, but in a game with cult. Does not have the ability to put scouts on people. Can “Test Faith” people at night, which is the equivalent of the sheriff’s investigate ability (finds people either as cult or not suspicious). Also has an ability called “smite”. If it is “convert night (nights 1, 3, 5 etc)”, this ability will often be used. The smite ability allows you to choose a target. If the cult leader tries to convert either you or your target, you will kill the cult leader. Your target should be someone who you suspect will be converted/are an important blue dragon class (often this ability will be used on fellow paladins). Note: if the game is known to be an unseen game and someone claims paladin, they are lying.</p>
<p>Mystic - Type: Social</p>
<p>The “claim collector”. At night, can link people. Linking someone allows you to talk to them and get a claim. You do not have to reveal who you are, but you will know who your target is. In addition, another night ability is to conduit two people. They will be able to talk to each other during the night, and they will know the other person. You can watch the conversation but cannot join in. During the day, a mystic can use an ability called private matter to hide all whispers from the public. (Whispers are usually hidden from the public, but you will see something like “2 whispered to 4” etc. Also, certain classes can use abilities to read your whispers during the day, however the mystic’s private matter ability counters both of these). Often times someone will say something like “mystic here pm on send claims”, this means they turned on private matter. You should whisper them your claim by typing “/w [player number] [message/claim]”. Another ability is called telepathy, which causes a mystics next message to appear in the chat differently. Instead of saying something like “Alex [12]: Mooooooo” It will instead say “Telepathy: Mooooooo”. This allows a mystic to convey extremely important messages to the crowd, as telepathy catches people’s attention. It can also be used to say something without revealing who you are. Often times you will be asked to send a message using telepathy to prove you are not converted.</p>
<p>Unseen - starting characters will be the mastermind and the assassin</p>
<p>Mastermind - Type: Special (Often appears as investigative, see character types above)</p>
<p>The head of the unseen. During the day, has an ability to choose a target. Once this target is chosen, the mastermind will see all whispers to and from the target for the rest of the day. At night, the mastermind can convert other players to the unseen. If this action fails (target cannot be converted), nothing will occur and the mastermind can attempt again the following night on a different player. If this action succeeds, the target will become unseen, and you will have to wait a night before being able to use the ability again (if success on night 1, can be used again night 3, etc). Also note that if the unseen has three members, no new conversions can occur. During cooldown nights (nights where you cannot convert anyone) the mastermind has an ability called foresight, which basically tells him if a certain player can be converted, and if they can be then it gives him their converted class type (the class type that they would have if they were converted. The mastermind also has a day ability called dirty work, but this is practically never used nor should it be. If the mastermind dies, and the starting assassin is still alive, the starting assassin will become the mastermind. Note: If there is an assassin, but he was not the starting assassin (the original assassin), he will not become the mastermind.</p>
<p>Assassin - Type: Killer</p>
<p>The killer of the unseen. At night, he can choose a target to assassinate. This will kill them, on the assumption that they were not healed, protected or death immune. In addition, he can use an ability called 2-for-1, which allows him to kill two players instead of one on that night, but he can only use this ability once per game. During the day, the assassin can bleed a target. The target will be alerted that they are bleeding and often will tell the chat. If this person is not healed, they will die tomorrow night (example: if u bleed someone on day two, they will die on night three with no heal). In addition, the assassin has an ability called silence. If the assassin silences a target, they will not be able to speak or use day abilities for 20 seconds. This is often used on people who are accused of treason, to make them seem suspicious when in fact they are not. If the mastermind dies, and the current assassin is the original, the assassin will become the mastermind. If the assassin dies or becomes mastermind, and there are any converts (any other unseen class), they will become the assassin. This new assassin cannot become mastermind. If an assassin is not present, and someone is converted, they will become the assassin instead of the usual class they would become.</p>
<p>Cult - starting characters will be the cult leader and any other random cult character.</p>
<p>Cult leader - Type: Special (Often appears as investigative, see character types above)</p>
<p>The powerhouse of the cult. Has a night ability called brainwash, which is the equivalent of the mastermind’s convert ability; converts another player, 1 night cooldown, yada yada yada. On cooldown nights (no conversions possible), the cult leader can use an ability called eradicate, which is the same as the assassin’s 2-for-1 ability (kills two players). However, unlike the assassin, who can only use 2-for-1 once, the cult leader can use eradicate three times. If a cult leader dies, and there is at least one other cult member, the oldest cult member will become the cult leader. Unlike the mastermind, which can only exist twice (original and starting assassin), the cult leader can exist many times, as even those who are converted can become cult leader. Also, unlike the unseen, which has a separate class for each possible blue dragon converted, the cult categorizes them by class type. For example, both a court wizard and a physician would become a ritualist when converted, because both court wizard and physician are support classes, and ritualist is the cult equivalent of any support class.</p>
<p>Kings - Only one person will start as the king, and it is always whoever’s number is 1. However, if a king dies, there will be elections and whoever is elected will become the new king. NOTE: STARTING KING WILL ALWAYS BE EITHER GOOD KING OR EVIL KING. Every STARTING king has an ability called allies (No elected kings have this ability); this is talked about under character types. Another ability of the kings is called guards, which basically makes them death immune for a night. Every king can use a day ability called point at someone when accusing them of treason; this adds another accusation (you will count as two people accusing said person of treason). The king also has a day ability called decide fate, which can be used to choose the fate of a certain person on trial without a vote. However, this ability can only be used once per game, and can only be used if the king has not used the point ability during that day. Most kings usually have little reason to ever use decide fate; Evil kings will use it if a prince is on trial. Because the win condition of an evil king is simply just for the unseen/cult to win, they can sacrifice themselves to get rid of a prince, as a prince is just as powerful if not more powerful than a king. Note: Every king’s character type is special, but this hardly matters.</p>
<p>Good king - Allied with blue dragon. Has 3 guards if he is the starting king, otherwise has 2 guards. If a blue dragon member becomes king, they become good king. Note: One guard = one night you can use the guards ability.</p>
<p>Evil king - Allies with the cult/unseen. May be called cult king/unseen king, but usually referred to as evil king. Has 2 guards. If a cult/unseen member becomes king, they become evil king.</p>
<p>Pretender king - If a pretender becomes king, they become a pretender king. They must simply just survive until the end to win. Has 1 guard.</p>
<p>Psycho king - If a neutral killer becomes king, they become psycho king. They must eliminate all blue dragon members and all cult/unseen members. Unlike the other kings, psycho king is death immune and does not need guards. He has infinite guards and he uses his guards to kill other people (basically the same as an assassin’s assassinate ability) (Note: infinite meaning it can be used every night, he cannot kill more than one person per night).</p>
<p>Neutral king - Any other neutral that becomes king. Must survive until the end of the game. Has 2 guards.</p>
<p>Neutrals - 2-3 regular neutrals in addition to a neutral killer per game. Below are the objectives, not the abilities.</p>
<p>Alchemist - Type: Support</p>
<p>Just needs to survive until the end of the game. If one is an alchemist they should publicly claim this early on; alchemists are not allied with anyone and are typically harmless. Both blue dragon and evils will usually leave you alone, though in the beginning of the game you will be expected not to go against the blue dragon’s will.</p>
<p>Fool - Type: Social</p>
<p>Must get yourself executed on trial. Never publicly claim fool - the prince will simply execute you at night and you will lose. Do not claim an evil class either, as you will probably be recognized as a fool and be executed by the prince. Instead, claim a blue dragon class, but make sure to fill your logs with errors and information that is known to be incorrect, enough to get you executed but not enough for people to recognize you as a fool.</p>
<p>Inquisitor - Type: Investigative</p>
<p>If an inquisitor is in a game, then three players will randomly be marked as heathens. These players will know that they are heathens. You will be told what classes every heathen is, but not who they are (example: you know that your heathens are a sheriff, a mystic, and a butler). Your goal is to essentially kill every heathen, but realistically you just need to outlive them (they can be killed by others or die on trial). Whether or not you claim inquisitor depends on the situation - if all heathens are blue dragon classes, its probably best not to claim inquisitor, but if any cult members/unseen members are heathens, you might be able to get away with openly claiming inquisitor.</p>
<p>Mercenary - Type: Support</p>
<p>Needs to get six brilders. You start with two brilders, so you really only need to get four. You get brilders mostly by protecting people. When you guard a person, everyone targeting them will be occupied. You get a brilder for every person you occupy when guarding a person. In addition you can shield someone, and if someone tries to kill them you gain 3 brilders, but this cannot be used after it has succeeded. Mercenaries can safely open claim to the court and should do so early on to avoid suspicion.</p>
<p>Possessor - Type: Killer</p>
<p>Is a neutral killer. Needs to defeat the blue dragon and the unseen. Never openly claim any neutral killer, as BOTH sides want you dead.</p>
<p>Reaper - Type: Killer</p>
<p>Is a neutral killer. Needs to defeat the blue dragon and the unseen. Never openly claim any neutral killer, as BOTH sides want you dead.</p>
<p>Scorned - Type: Social</p>
<p>Similar to fool, but must frame others instead of themselves. Each night, they have certain abilities, and whoever they use their abilities on becomes their target, but only for the day. By the end of the game (or by the time they die), they must successfully get two of their targets executed. Never openly claim scorned, as scorned totally screws up blue dragon investigative classes. If you are a blue dragon class and it is known that a scorned is in game it may be worth executing as it messes with information greatly.</p>
<p>Sellsword - Type: Offensive</p>
<p>Not very useful until lots of information is known. Simply needs to defeat blue dragon; that is, sellsword can win with unseen/cult or with the neutral killer. Has abilities to occupy people. Never openly claim sellsword, as they are against blue dragon.</p>
<p>Sorceror - Type: Killer</p>
<p>Is a neutral killer. Needs to defeat the blue dragon and the unseen. Never openly claim any neutral killer, as BOTH sides want you dead.</p>
<p>Note: The Scorned and The Fool both have an ability called trollbox, which is a day ability and can only be used once per day (as with every day ability). This can be used to force players to say something into the chat without them knowing that they said it and is often used to throw suspicion (example: I am a fool, I trollbox the sheriff to say that I am unseen). Note: The devs can see a trollbox, so if you make someone else say something agains the rules you will be the person in trouble, not your target.</p>
<p>Language used in the game (slang, abbreviations, etc):</p>
<p>bd = blue dragon</p>
<p>nk = neutral killer</p>
<p>ek = evil king</p>
<p>gk = good king</p>
<p>pk = psycho king</p>
<p>tb = trollbox</p>
<p>dnd = did not die</p>
<p>dnr = did not require</p>
<p>wo = watched over</p>
<p>k/o = refers to the pairing of killer/offensive</p>
<p>s/s = refers to the pairing of social/support</p>
<p>s/i = refers to the pairing of special/investigative</p>
<p>cl = cult leader</p>
<p>mm = mastermind (note: if used in the logs of a maid, can also be referring to the matchmake ability)</p>
<p>poss = possessor</p>
<p>sorc = sorceror</p>
<p>pret = pretender</p>
<p>Let me know what I should add in the future</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 18:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76791-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/throne-of-lies-basic-guide/76791.rss">Throne of Lies Basic Guide</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
