<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Leech (Neutral Killing)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472</link>
    <description>**Leech** - A sickly, sadistic killer with a really bad parasite infection...

Passive 1:
**Consumed Young** - You are immune to murder as long as you have a current, living &quot;Writhing Brood&quot; target. However, if you are attacked, it will remove the effect from that target. (Double-edged sword. Helps get it off you, but likely shortens how long your target lives.)

Passive 2:
**Perverse Osmosis** - Conditions placed on you such as bleeding or poisoning will be passed on to your next &quot;Writhing Brood&quot; target.

Day Ability:
**Writhing Brood** - Select a player to infect with your broodlings. They will die in two nights. Target is not notified when you select them, but is notified of their cause of death when they die. (4 uses, only recharges after the necessary nights, even if target is somehow saved.)

Night Ability 1:
**Suck Dry** - Choose a player to kill. (Unlimited use.)

Night Ability 2:
**Egg-Filled Husk** - Choose a player to kill, causing their visitors to be infected like your &quot;Writhing Brood&quot; day ability. (2 uses. Usable if you have no living &quot;Writhing Brood&quot; target.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 01:37:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Leech (Neutral Killing)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Basically like any NK, losing is essentially “not winning”. XD Dying, being voted up at the end, whatever.</p>
<p>Egg-Filled Husk is a desperation maneuver, basically. The day ability may not take for any number of reasons. I probably should’ve went into them. Like “This can be stopped like Bleed/Poison, and people immune to those are probably immune to this as well”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52472-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472.rss">[Class Suggestion] Leech (Neutral Killing)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Leech (Neutral Killing)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[reRun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dig it, but the name Family Business doesn’t make too much sense… Other than that, quick question. How does it lose, aside from death? And what makes the Egg-Filled Husk even worth using, if you have the day ability?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52472-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472.rss">[Class Suggestion] Leech (Neutral Killing)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Leech (Neutral Killing)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Leech</strong> - A sickly, sadistic killer with a really bad parasite infection…</p>
<p>Passive 1:<br>
<strong>Consumed Young</strong> - You are immune to murder as long as you have a current, living “Writhing Brood” target. However, if you are attacked, it will remove the effect from that target. (Double-edged sword. Helps get it off you, but likely shortens how long your target lives.)</p>
<p>Passive 2:<br>
<strong>Perverse Osmosis</strong> - Conditions placed on you such as bleeding or poisoning will be passed on to your next “Writhing Brood” target.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Writhing Brood</strong> - Select a player to infect with your broodlings. They will die in two nights. Target is not notified when you select them, but is notified of their cause of death when they die. (4 uses, only recharges after the necessary nights, even if target is somehow saved.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Suck Dry</strong> - Choose a player to kill. (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Egg-Filled Husk</strong> - Choose a player to kill, causing their visitors to be infected like your “Writhing Brood” day ability. (2 uses. Usable if you have no living “Writhing Brood” target.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52472-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-leech-neutral-killing/52472.rss">[Class Suggestion] Leech (Neutral Killing)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
