<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506</link>
    <description>#### What happened?
So in a cult game, I claimed that being able to step forward with royal blood means that those units are not yet converted and therefore, guaranteed to be of the Blue Dragon faction. However, another blue dragon claimed that the Noble Blood passive&#39;s description says that you keep this passive even after conversion, which lead to my execution

I have used this fact to successfully find/execute converted enemies in the past, however, it has come to my attention that I should not be able to deduct enemy factions in this manner

After looking at the description of the Noble Blood, it claims that this passive is maintained on conversion, but it doesn&#39;t allow you to be a candidate in the &quot;Priority Voting&quot; round in which only those with the Noble Blood passive can be nominated.

----------

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?
The description of royal blood claims that:  &quot;...If converted to  **Unseen**  or  **Cult**  you will keep this passive.&quot; meaning that a character with a noble blood passive should be able to partake in the &quot;Priority Voting&quot; round for a new king.
 
----------

#### Steps to reproduce:
1 - be a character with the Noble Blood passive that can be converted i.e. Drunk, Princess, noble etc
2 -  be converted so that there are only two members with the unseen ( so they don&#39;t become duchess, alcoholic, etc) or in a cult game
3 - kill the king
4 - have the recently converted character with the Noble Blood passive try to partake in the priority voting round for the next king (i.e. the round when those with the Noble Blood passive ability can step forward over anyone else)

----------

#### Comments:
I&#39;m not sure if the noble blood is just a text error because the unseen converted counterpart classes (i.e. aristocrat, alcoholic, duchess)  still have the royal blood passive in their descriptions AND don&#39;t say anything about this passive being maintained upon conversion on those description screens.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:41:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TryphonX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7506-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506.rss">Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markio16]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That makes sense, although I consider that to be intuitive because I thought that changing from the converted classes to assassin was a demotion rather than a promotion. I’ll have to play around and see if I can step forward as a converted cult before being promoted to cult master.</p>
<p>Thanks for the clarification though</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7506-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506.rss">Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Methnor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You won’t keep Royal Blood if you’re promoted to Assassin/Mastermind/Cult Leader, but you will have it if your class normally does (Alcoholic, Aristocrat, etc) or if you’re converted into a Cult class that doesn’t normally have it (Apostle from Noble, Invoker from Drunk, etc).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7506-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506.rss">Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markio16]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>So in a cult game, I claimed that being able to step forward with royal blood means that those units are not yet converted and therefore, guaranteed to be of the Blue Dragon faction. However, another blue dragon claimed that the Noble Blood passive’s description says that you keep this passive even after conversion, which lead to my execution</p>
<p>I have used this fact to successfully find/execute converted enemies in the past, however, it has come to my attention that I should not be able to deduct enemy factions in this manner</p>
<p>After looking at the description of the Noble Blood, it claims that this passive is maintained on conversion, but it doesn’t allow you to be a candidate in the “Priority Voting” round in which only those with the Noble Blood passive can be nominated.</p>
<hr>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>The description of royal blood claims that:  “…If converted to  <strong>Unseen</strong>  or  <strong>Cult</strong>  you will keep this passive.” meaning that a character with a noble blood passive should be able to partake in the “Priority Voting” round for a new king.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<p>1 - be a character with the Noble Blood passive that can be converted i.e. Drunk, Princess, noble etc<br>
2 -  be converted so that there are only two members with the unseen ( so they don’t become duchess, alcoholic, etc) or in a cult game<br>
3 - kill the king<br>
4 - have the recently converted character with the Noble Blood passive try to partake in the priority voting round for the next king (i.e. the round when those with the Noble Blood passive ability can step forward over anyone else)</p>
<hr>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>I’m not sure if the noble blood is just a text error because the unseen converted counterpart classes (i.e. aristocrat, alcoholic, duchess)  still have the royal blood passive in their descriptions AND don’t say anything about this passive being maintained upon conversion on those description screens.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7506-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/royal-blood-passive-does-not-transfer-when-converted-to-unseen-cult/7506.rss">Royal blood passive does not transfer when converted to unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
