<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A new gamemode (A bit far off, but worth the try)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-new-gamemode-a-bit-far-off-but-worth-the-try/24803</link>
    <description>How about there&#39;s a gamemode where there are BD&#39;s, neutrals, Cult AND Unseen. I made this thread to discuss this fun idea and give it even more conversation :P 

I would say that there should be more BD&#39;s, since there are two factions, Cult and Unseen both start with their leader, and they slowly start building up their factions. Imagine how cool it would be to have the factions kill off each other and have a massive battle :P, no one could trust each other :smiley:

I know this is a bit of a crazy idea, but please do consider it and at least let&#39;s give it some discussion :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 02:53:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-new-gamemode-a-bit-far-off-but-worth-the-try/24803.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A new gamemode (A bit far off, but worth the try)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Monkke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about there’s a gamemode where there are BD’s, neutrals, Cult AND Unseen. I made this thread to discuss this fun idea and give it even more conversation <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I would say that there should be more BD’s, since there are two factions, Cult and Unseen both start with their leader, and they slowly start building up their factions. Imagine how cool it would be to have the factions kill off each other and have a massive battle :P, no one could trust each other <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>I know this is a bit of a crazy idea, but please do consider it and at least let’s give it some discussion <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-new-gamemode-a-bit-far-off-but-worth-the-try/24803/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-new-gamemode-a-bit-far-off-but-worth-the-try/24803/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 22:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24803-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-new-gamemode-a-bit-far-off-but-worth-the-try/24803.rss">A new gamemode (A bit far off, but worth the try)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
