<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New neutral special class, the Kingpin</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-neutral-special-class-the-kingpin/10852</link>
    <description>I got some ideas for a new class. It most likely won&#39;t be fitting as it is, but hopefully with some further ideas it can become useful.

Name: The Kingpin (or some other name of a person with lot of money and power)
Faction: Neutral (unique)
Type: Special (maybe social?)
Win Condition: Survive the game 
Passive skill: Underlings (or bodyguards?). Immune to death once and occupation at night due to being out of the reach because of all the workers he commands.
Day ability: Money is Power (unlimited uses). Select 2 (or 3?) players during a vote, their votes will be &quot;flipped&quot; (execute to pardon and vice versa). Basically just bribe them to vote the opposite. This can be used when you are being accused for a treason.
Night ability: Claim the Mercenary (one use). If there is a mercenary in the game, you will become its target. Outpay the previous owner to get the protection of the mercenary. In case of 2 mercs, only one will be affected at random.
Night ability 2: Renew the Contract (unlimited uses, 2 (1?)-day cooldown). Pay your merc for the job well done and add him another charge for the Stand Guard ability.

Basically the idea is to have a neutral class who has ability to control votes (but not to get away with it very well) and be very hard to take down. It would often require a majority of the votes to get him down. And combined with the merc, he would be very hard to kill at night as well. However, the class would not be convert immune (unless merc guarding at night). 
The class would give evil factions another target to convert (there seem to be quite a lot of convert immune neutrals), and also useful claim for MM/CL, especially against the princess check. The day ability could be used to help either faction and creating enough doubt to not have everyone vote against you, it could be enough to save you from the execution (unless you missread the game and flip the wrong votes).
I think the class itself would turn the balance of the game a bit in favour of the evil factions, the lesser chance of neutral killers would counter this slightly (although i think there is guaranteed neutral killer in 16 people games).

Unseen converted class would retain the same abilities, being able to create even more havoc after knowing for certain which players are unseen and which are not. The name Kingpin would be great for unseen version as well, so maybe some other name for the main class?

Cultist conversion would convert the class to the Apostle i think (open for better ideas).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 07:27:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-neutral-special-class-the-kingpin/10852.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New neutral special class, the Kingpin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sir_Yodi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got some ideas for a new class. It most likely won’t be fitting as it is, but hopefully with some further ideas it can become useful.</p>
<p>Name: The Kingpin (or some other name of a person with lot of money and power)<br>
Faction: Neutral (unique)<br>
Type: Special (maybe social?)<br>
Win Condition: Survive the game<br>
Passive skill: Underlings (or bodyguards?). Immune to death once and occupation at night due to being out of the reach because of all the workers he commands.<br>
Day ability: Money is Power (unlimited uses). Select 2 (or 3?) players during a vote, their votes will be “flipped” (execute to pardon and vice versa). Basically just bribe them to vote the opposite. This can be used when you are being accused for a treason.<br>
Night ability: Claim the Mercenary (one use). If there is a mercenary in the game, you will become its target. Outpay the previous owner to get the protection of the mercenary. In case of 2 mercs, only one will be affected at random.<br>
Night ability 2: Renew the Contract (unlimited uses, 2 (1?)-day cooldown). Pay your merc for the job well done and add him another charge for the Stand Guard ability.</p>
<p>Basically the idea is to have a neutral class who has ability to control votes (but not to get away with it very well) and be very hard to take down. It would often require a majority of the votes to get him down. And combined with the merc, he would be very hard to kill at night as well. However, the class would not be convert immune (unless merc guarding at night).<br>
The class would give evil factions another target to convert (there seem to be quite a lot of convert immune neutrals), and also useful claim for MM/CL, especially against the princess check. The day ability could be used to help either faction and creating enough doubt to not have everyone vote against you, it could be enough to save you from the execution (unless you missread the game and flip the wrong votes).<br>
I think the class itself would turn the balance of the game a bit in favour of the evil factions, the lesser chance of neutral killers would counter this slightly (although i think there is guaranteed neutral killer in 16 people games).</p>
<p>Unseen converted class would retain the same abilities, being able to create even more havoc after knowing for certain which players are unseen and which are not. The name Kingpin would be great for unseen version as well, so maybe some other name for the main class?</p>
<p>Cultist conversion would convert the class to the Apostle i think (open for better ideas).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-neutral-special-class-the-kingpin/10852/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-neutral-special-class-the-kingpin/10852/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 07:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10852-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-neutral-special-class-the-kingpin/10852.rss">New neutral special class, the Kingpin</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
