<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521</link>
    <description>**The Spymaster - New Neutral Class Idea**
**The Spymaster**
**Unique Neutral - Offensive Class.**
**Conversion immune.**


**Win condition**: Survive until the end of the game

**Passives:**

**Masterful Mind** - You will recieve a message when a neutral killer targets you with an attack. _(This message will appear as soon as your number is chosen by a neutral killer; Alchemist, Sorcerer, Possessor or Reaper)_ 
**Charismatic** - You blend in easily with a new court therefore you cannot be visited night 1 making you immune to any action even the psychic link. _(Much like fool&#39;s ability to hide)_ 

**Day ability:**

**Subterfuge** - You become immune to occupation tonight.  2x Use only.
**Scapegoat**  - Poison or Bleed inflicted onto you today will instead target the person of your choice instead. You cannot use this ability while already poisoned or bleeding. 3x Use only. 

**Night abilities:**

**Grand Scheme** - An attack or attacks heading in your direction this night will instead target the person of your choice. 3x Use Only. 
**Bribe the Court** - Bribe a person of your choice (not yourself) to attack another of your choice. The bribed player gains night immunity during this but his original action is blocked. _(This includes occupy immune classes)_  2x Use Only. 
_(The bribed player will recieve the message [you were forced to attack a player])_


**Strategy:**

The Spymaster is a very unique class that is aligned with nobody therefore can side with anyone. His abilities focus heavily on benefitting those he wishes to support while having necessary tools to ensure his own survival. 

His **Charismatic** passive ensures he survives night 1 and there wont be any succesful investigations on him by day 2. This gives him time to mingle with the court and figure out classes. **Masterful Mind** protects the Spymaster from Neutral Killers to a certain degree and allows him to preform his **Grand Scheme** ability more accurately to deflect an attack. 

During the day the Spymaster has choices to make and he needs to think ahead quickly. Does he want to be immune to and redirect bleeding/poison with **Scapegoat** or does he want to ensure his night abilities go through with **Subterfuge**?  

At night your primary choice is whether to deflect an attack with **Grand Scheme** or not since you only have limited uses. You can wait for a confirmation via your passive but this is limited as Knights, Hunter attacks and Evil faction supporters dont show up. 

**Bribe the Court** is a unique and powerful bargaining chip for the Spymaster. It allows you to make someone night immune for a night while killing another with it _(much like a possessor attack)_. Use it on a high priority Blue Dragon like a Prince to ensure he survives the night while killing an Unseen/Cult with it to gather trust as a &#39;&#39;Good&#39;&#39; Spymaster. Or contact an Unseen/Cult member to ensure his survival from a Knight or Neutral killer attack while slaying an extra Blue Dragon with it. In return they wont target you the rest of the game, hopefully. At critical moments it can cause a swing for either faction in votes when used. It does however sacrifice the ability to deflect an attack at night when used _(since you can only use one ability at night)_. 

**The new problem it creates:**

First of all the Spymaster lacks abilities that can easily &#39;&#39;confirm&#39;&#39; him. Most of his abilities target himself alone and other players wont necessarily see he used it. This means that a Spymaster claim is difficult to tackle but not impossible. Succesfully occupy him once and attempt it again but suddenly he is occupy immune? Most likely you found the spymaster that just used his day ability. 

Because **Bribe the Court** is such a powerful ability its not always in Blue Dragon&#39;s interest to immediately hang a Spymaster claim. Night Immunity once and an attack onto someone can be very beneficial. This makes it possible for Neutral Killers to attempt to convince the court they are a Spymaster rather than always defaulting to the Alchemist claim. 

However know that the Spymaster can at any moment turn against you as he can support Blue Dragon, Neutral Killers or even Evils. This makes him an elusive and uneasy presence. 

**Reminder**: _The Spymaster doesnt stand in the way of a Neutral Killer&#39;s victory and it may be in the best interest of the NK to ally himself with the Spymaster if possible._ 

**Side note:** _If the Spymaster uses **Grand Scheme** he wont actually visit the person he directs an attack to. He wont have to worry about hunters and knights. Same goes for **Bribe the Court** as its similar to a possessor attack._

Please leave a comment or recommendations as you please :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 19:22:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cleanfear]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm I listened to your reasoning and I think you are right. Ill change it to 3 uses that way surviving becomes a little easier.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 19:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21521-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you are worried about 3 uses of night Immunity being too much then don’t be. Most survivor roles (ToS Surv, Neut king, Alch, Merc) have 4 uses of night Immunity and they still have to think about it. Plus this isn’t night Immunity but a redirect. This means that poss and Hunter are immune to it. At the same time reaper is always vulnerable to it. 3 is a good number for an ability like that and would not make the class mindless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 19:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21521-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cleanfear]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you for your feedback! I had the same thing in mind with Bribe the Court giving that flavor text, however i appear to have forgotten to add it. Will edit it in right now! For the increase of ability use I agree he could maybe get an extra Bribe the Court and Scapegoat. But I dont want to give him too much occupy immunity and night immuntity. Otherwise you can simply spam those and win without having to think. Which defeats the purpose of a class thats about tactical choices.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21521-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think that all of his Ability’s need one more use. Bribe the court should also be given the same text as puppet strings. “You were forced to attack [Player]”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21521-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cleanfear]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Spymaster - New Neutral Class Idea</strong><br>
<strong>The Spymaster</strong><br>
<strong>Unique Neutral - Offensive Class.</strong><br>
<strong>Conversion immune.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong>: Survive until the end of the game</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Masterful Mind</strong> - You will recieve a message when a neutral killer targets you with an attack. <em>(This message will appear as soon as your number is chosen by a neutral killer; Alchemist, Sorcerer, Possessor or Reaper)</em><br>
<strong>Charismatic</strong> - You blend in easily with a new court therefore you cannot be visited night 1 making you immune to any action even the psychic link. <em>(Much like fool’s ability to hide)</em></p>
<p><strong>Day ability:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Subterfuge</strong> - You become immune to occupation tonight.  2x Use only.<br>
<strong>Scapegoat</strong>  - Poison or Bleed inflicted onto you today will instead target the person of your choice instead. You cannot use this ability while already poisoned or bleeding. 3x Use only.</p>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Grand Scheme</strong> - An attack or attacks heading in your direction this night will instead target the person of your choice. 3x Use Only.<br>
<strong>Bribe the Court</strong> - Bribe a person of your choice (not yourself) to attack another of your choice. The bribed player gains night immunity during this but his original action is blocked. <em>(This includes occupy immune classes)</em>  2x Use Only.<br>
<em>(The bribed player will recieve the message [you were forced to attack a player])</em></p>
<p><strong>Strategy:</strong></p>
<p>The Spymaster is a very unique class that is aligned with nobody therefore can side with anyone. His abilities focus heavily on benefitting those he wishes to support while having necessary tools to ensure his own survival.</p>
<p>His <strong>Charismatic</strong> passive ensures he survives night 1 and there wont be any succesful investigations on him by day 2. This gives him time to mingle with the court and figure out classes. <strong>Masterful Mind</strong> protects the Spymaster from Neutral Killers to a certain degree and allows him to preform his <strong>Grand Scheme</strong> ability more accurately to deflect an attack.</p>
<p>During the day the Spymaster has choices to make and he needs to think ahead quickly. Does he want to be immune to and redirect bleeding/poison with <strong>Scapegoat</strong> or does he want to ensure his night abilities go through with <strong>Subterfuge</strong>?</p>
<p>At night your primary choice is whether to deflect an attack with <strong>Grand Scheme</strong> or not since you only have limited uses. You can wait for a confirmation via your passive but this is limited as Knights, Hunter attacks and Evil faction supporters dont show up.</p>
<p><strong>Bribe the Court</strong> is a unique and powerful bargaining chip for the Spymaster. It allows you to make someone night immune for a night while killing another with it <em>(much like a possessor attack)</em>. Use it on a high priority Blue Dragon like a Prince to ensure he survives the night while killing an Unseen/Cult with it to gather trust as a ‘‘Good’’ Spymaster. Or contact an Unseen/Cult member to ensure his survival from a Knight or Neutral killer attack while slaying an extra Blue Dragon with it. In return they wont target you the rest of the game, hopefully. At critical moments it can cause a swing for either faction in votes when used. It does however sacrifice the ability to deflect an attack at night when used <em>(since you can only use one ability at night)</em>.</p>
<p><strong>The new problem it creates:</strong></p>
<p>First of all the Spymaster lacks abilities that can easily ‘‘confirm’’ him. Most of his abilities target himself alone and other players wont necessarily see he used it. This means that a Spymaster claim is difficult to tackle but not impossible. Succesfully occupy him once and attempt it again but suddenly he is occupy immune? Most likely you found the spymaster that just used his day ability.</p>
<p>Because <strong>Bribe the Court</strong> is such a powerful ability its not always in Blue Dragon’s interest to immediately hang a Spymaster claim. Night Immunity once and an attack onto someone can be very beneficial. This makes it possible for Neutral Killers to attempt to convince the court they are a Spymaster rather than always defaulting to the Alchemist claim.</p>
<p>However know that the Spymaster can at any moment turn against you as he can support Blue Dragon, Neutral Killers or even Evils. This makes him an elusive and uneasy presence.</p>
<p><strong>Reminder</strong>: <em>The Spymaster doesnt stand in the way of a Neutral Killer’s victory and it may be in the best interest of the NK to ally himself with the Spymaster if possible.</em></p>
<p><strong>Side note:</strong> <em>If the Spymaster uses <strong>Grand Scheme</strong> he wont actually visit the person he directs an attack to. He wont have to worry about hunters and knights. Same goes for <strong>Bribe the Court</strong> as its similar to a possessor attack.</em></p>
<p>Please leave a comment or recommendations as you please <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21521-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-spymaster/21521.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Spymaster</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
