<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fool Lore/Story</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477</link>
    <description>The Fool used to have it all. He was a honored war hero, and having vanquished the cult members from Castle Adiart, was respected by everyone in the court. The war veteran had been at the top of his game, and everyone loved him! The King even told him stuff that he wouldn&#39;t tell his son, the prince! However, that all came to an end one fateful day.
That night, the court wizard came to visit him, but brought unwanted company unknown to him. Suddenly, the war veteran saw something that scarred him for life. There, in the court wizard&#39;s stomach, was a knife. Terrified, the renowned hero thought for a second, and decided to hide. He watched the court wizard collapse, and saw the blood glistening knife exit his old friend&#39;s body.
After the assassin left, the war veteran started to sob, he experienced the PTSD from the cult war he thought had gone away. He knew he should&#39;ve helped the old wizard out, and felt his mind start to break. &quot;It needs to be over, I must pay for my mistakes.&quot; The once-hero thought. &quot;I&#39;m useless in Castle Adiart.&quot; All I am now is... a fool.

Comments/Explanations: The fool&#39;s wanting to be executed seems to suggest (to me) that he has personal regrets, and feels the only way to make it right was be formal execution. Also, like the fool from ToL, they can hide from their attackers, or other people. I find that the war veteran story explains the fool entirely, and justifies his goals and abilities. (This is my first lore, I tried my best!)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fool Lore/Story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lily]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Icibalus" data-post="3" data-topic="59477" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/icibalus/40/31215_2.png" class="avatar"> Icibalus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fool best class 2k18.</p>
<p>The end</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59477-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477.rss">Fool Lore/Story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool Lore/Story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>and then it was removed from the game for being a shitty class that deincentives scumreading</p>
<p>The end</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 15:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59477-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477.rss">Fool Lore/Story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool Lore/Story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Basic, but I like the concept.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59477-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477.rss">Fool Lore/Story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool Lore/Story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Enchiladas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Fool used to have it all. He was a honored war hero, and having vanquished the cult members from Castle Adiart, was respected by everyone in the court. The war veteran had been at the top of his game, and everyone loved him! The King even told him stuff that he wouldn’t tell his son, the prince! However, that all came to an end one fateful day.<br>
That night, the court wizard came to visit him, but brought unwanted company unknown to him. Suddenly, the war veteran saw something that scarred him for life. There, in the court wizard’s stomach, was a knife. Terrified, the renowned hero thought for a second, and decided to hide. He watched the court wizard collapse, and saw the blood glistening knife exit his old friend’s body.<br>
After the assassin left, the war veteran started to sob, he experienced the PTSD from the cult war he thought had gone away. He knew he should’ve helped the old wizard out, and felt his mind start to break. “It needs to be over, I must pay for my mistakes.” The once-hero thought. “I’m useless in Castle Adiart.” All I am now is… a fool.</p>
<p>Comments/Explanations: The fool’s wanting to be executed seems to suggest (to me) that he has personal regrets, and feels the only way to make it right was be formal execution. Also, like the fool from ToL, they can hide from their attackers, or other people. I find that the war veteran story explains the fool entirely, and justifies his goals and abilities. (This is my first lore, I tried my best!)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59477-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-lore-story/59477.rss">Fool Lore/Story</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
