<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595</link>
    <description>Xblade, here. While balance is subjective, and the patch dust is settling, tons of people are starting to understand the patch, why we did it, and the positive impact it had (Yes, there were some balance disagreements, but there are always those -- this is **not** like it&#39;s our last patch ;D).

For those that don&#39;t understand the new new quality-of-life additions that was the biggest reason for the streamlined patch, let me explain more. Tons of stuff here is in **bold** to skim this blog (it&#39;s not me yelling :stuck_out_tongue: ).

## Simplified or Streamlined?
![anim|480x182](upload://oEY5Ww9WOwE8qHxZV6ZRkxuqhDq.gif) 

We initially made the mistake of calling the patch &#39;simplified&#39; &gt;&gt; then immediately rebranded it as &#39;streamlined&#39; for what it truly is.

## But--you simplified things!
What was truly simplified beyond the _Alchemist_? While the old Alchemist had more fun buttons to click, most would agree that this was pretty necessary. If additional button options are more important than your own wit, you may be playing the wrong game ;D

...But I digress, we&#39;re talking about **simplified vs streamlined**. Simplified implies that we watered down the game, while **streamline** involves making the game more intuitive for not only new players, but **everyone**.

## Ok, well, what did you streamline?

* We wanted to make the game more **intuitive**.
* We wanted to add a **consistent glossary of terms**.
* We wanted to remove **unintended tediousness**.
* We wanted to **reduce RNG** (Random factors).
* We wanted new players to be **onboarded faster**.
* We wanted new **patches to be easier/faster to understand.**
* We wanted **less gamethrowing** from new and returning players.

## But you aren&#39;t listening to the vets!

**But we are!** What is the #1 concern from the average veteran player? **Gamethrowing.** This is a game where you HAVE to rely on your teammates or it&#39;s not fun. It&#39;s a game where your adversaries need to know what they&#39;re doing, or it&#39;s not challenging. 

You&#39;re not playing with 5 total people, but **16 people**. Every single one of them has to stay inside the game, know what they are doing, and not gamethrow for this to be fun for veterans. By the time you&#39;re a veteran, you don&#39;t really care about gp anymore -- you just want a quality game. This means your enemies you even want to be challenging.

**THIS MEANS:**

* New players play with veterans. Therefore, new players that know what they are doing = better allies, more-challenging adversaries, **less gamethrowing** all-around.

* Vets always wanted their own queue, right? Remember when Casual Mode (RIP) was public? Yeaaaa.... about that. **We need a constant flow of new players in order for us to even _think_ about something like this** or it&#39;ll just be another &#39;casual mode&#39; with a 2-hour queue. **New players = potential for future goodies.**

* Don&#39;t forget about **returning players**. Before the streamlined patch, it was incredibly intimidating to play the game after you haven&#39;t played for ages. We&#39;ve already seen tons of veteran players make their return and find themselves settling in. This patch was tough to learn from an old player, but imagine future patches. **Take a break, come back, np.**

* **Continuous updates.** New players don&#39;t care about updates since they don&#39;t even know the game yet, but veterans do. It can be easy to forget we&#39;re an indie game, and anyone can Google Steam&#39;s share. Then taxes. Then split with the team. Then reinvestment back into the game: In the end, we don&#39;t actually make much. We don&#39;t focus on our microtransactions and don&#39;t want to. **New players = devs can continue being full-time.** Did you know the only actual  _programmers_ are me + Ellie?* If we can&#39;t afford servers/rent, that would be bad. **New players = GOOD for EVERYONE!**

## So, the Yogscast Jingle Jam Charity Bundle... Surprise!

![yogscast-charity-promo-drunk|500x500](upload://idYeGxLHqrMwYLd6wQpcuk7OW3P.jpeg) 

**While we were under NDA** when we released the streamlined patch, you can probably further understand why it had to be done. The NDA made it awkward that we couldn&#39;t say anything and the average person still has no idea that our population dramatically boosted with new players because of this bundle. **Literally about doubled in active population**, not even including the +population that activated their key but are yet to play!

This is one of those patches that **&quot;you want it, even if you don&#39;t know it yet&quot;.** 

We have already seen a decline in gamethrowing reports, a decline in &quot;this game&#39;s just too hard&quot;, reviews that complain the game is tough (the major new player complaint is not-forgiving players for newb mistakes), queue times have lowered, **and overall has been healthy for the game.**

Now, imagine that we donated up to **250,000 charity keys** to that bundle and we didn&#39;t have this patch. The first thing on your mind, GO!

&gt; Gamethrowing new players!

....this may still be the case :blush: BUT! Certainly not as much as you imagined. Yogs has already raised over $5 million. Even at 5 mil, `$5mil / $35 = 142,857` new copies have been given away. There are tons over the holidays to play, so there&#39;s a good chance many of these will be activated in January. Whoa!

 ## Unintended Tediousness? Less RNG?

Without looking it up, name pre-patch every combination of who can occupy, who is occupy immune, and who can override this, even though you&#39;re &quot;immune&quot;? It hurts **my** brain to even think about it.

These were not intended to be confusing: Just over time, with our changes, this just so happened to end up this way. At launch, you wouldn&#39;t find this confusing mess. It&#39;s not there for challenge - it never was! It was simply &quot;leftover&quot; to add another layer of confusion. Not even the devs remember this, let alone our most senior vets.

Most people just sort of guess or assume (and not in a fun way). The streamlined patch lowers RNG since there&#39;s less of this confusing mess.

Then inconsistency everywhere! Imagine if a card game like Hearthstone had 10 expansions with 0 consistent terms -- all named something super unique, 99% doing the same thing but 1% doing something slightly different. While it&#39;s cool that abilities are unique, it limits us severely -- things get confusing for new players AND vets (even devs). This is not what anyone wants.

![image|690x405](upload://5kzTUR6lcY12psZBsBuUUFYT0bK.jpeg) 

**CONSISTENCY = SECURING THRONE&#39;S FUTURE**

While the names are certainly COOL and it looks unique, and may even be viable in the first set (pretend those are vanilla). However, what about the future? What about 10 expansions later? What about 5 years later? Imagine memorizing not &quot;Taunt&quot; or &quot;Deathrattle&quot;, but if all of these consistencies didn&#39;t exist. Imagine patch notes, how long it would take to adapt. Imagine that a simple mechanic like &quot;Taunt&quot; was called something different each time. **Consistency ensures a future** for Throne.

## Securing The Future

* Wanted a new class? It wouldn&#39;t happen before the streamlined patch. We reached a maximum complexity.
* Want a new mechanic? We already have too many unique ones. It wouldn&#39;t have ever happened. However, now, it&#39;s possible in the future.
* Want us to explode so we can upgrade our art? Our animations? Our armor and weapons? The environment? It wouldn&#39;t happen because new players and returning veterans are intimidated. **New players keep us alive and raise the budget** so we have the capability to do these things.
* Want to bring your friend aboard? Tons of my friends won&#39;t even play the game, even though I made it, simply because they&#39;re intimidated by the complexity (and my buds play D&amp;D! That&#39;s so hard to learn, imo! So much to micromanage). With this patch, you can tell them we finally became more **intuitive** and **easier to understand**. While a select few abilities may have been watered down, the majority still remains the same. 

____________

# TL;DR: 

Long story short, the streamlined patch = new (and returning) players = benefits both veterans AND players = does EVERYONE a favor + secures the future of the game.

![image|690x351](upload://ftqG0j6CUlnzW6ieArMpaFwFs3x.png)

**EDIT**: Toss around this short link to this post @ https://toli.es/streamlined</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 12:59:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Official Announcements</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-54</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m going to lock this thread since it’s heavily derailed, talking about balance when <strong>Non-Balance</strong> is in the title <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Please make a new thread in <span class="hashtag">#lore</span> to discuss balance~</p>
<p>(For feedback relevant to OP, thanks folks!)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 12:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-53</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="15" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is a post for Armae to answer as it deals with balance (as OP is titled <strong>“Non-Balance”</strong> ). I don’t ask many questions when it comes to this since it’s not really my department, to be transparent. I’ll pass this along to encourage a devblog.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That would be appreciated. Waiting for it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 09:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-52</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That could work, but it would leave the prince with no counterplay.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="38" data-topic="74595" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(also tbh just make jail an AOE occupy like the other similar effects)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed.  That’s mainly why I disliked the prevention overhaul.  The point of adding more prevention in the first place was to not confirm jailed targets.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shrimpy" data-post="46" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shrimpy/40/15828_2.png" class="avatar"> Shrimpy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I strongly oppose giving Hunter Retribution back. Especially with the proposed change of allowing him to arrow his desired target, he would be literally a Jester.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And what’s wrong with that?  Trading a hunter for MM is a great trade.  Plus it allows the hunter to still act aggressively even after he runs out of bears.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Icibalus" data-post="48" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/icibalus/40/31215_2.png" class="avatar"> Icibalus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I disagree with the Sheriff and Paladin merge simply because if you merge them then the complaints about the Unseen and Cult being the same will be tripled and the game will feel more same-y because of it</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That problem lies with the factions themselves though, not the cops.  The cops have their own issues(outing the opposing faction instantly, only being useful while the enemy faction is still alive, and smite is overpowered).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/51</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-51</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually ToS has the same replacement system as the Unseen</p>
<p>Spacifically a specific generic mafia (mafioso) can promote and not any other mafia members</p>
<p>the starting mafioso is the equivalent to the starting assassin and acts identical in this context</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/50</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 18:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-50</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And that’s why I’m still a fan of making one hardcounter unconvertible even though that’s way harder to balance</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/49</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 17:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-49</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree with the Sheriff and Paladin merge simply because if you merge them then the complaints about the Unseen and Cult being the same will be tripled and the game will feel more same-y because of it</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/48</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 17:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-48</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree on this point, since what made Jester kills bad was that they were arbitrary due to being on a kingmaker, and generally failed at their attempt to harm village for actually playing the game and lynching peo-</p>
<p>oh sorry i’m going on a Jester/Fool rant again</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/47</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 17:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-47</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I strongly oppose giving Hunter Retribution back.  Especially with the proposed change of allowing him to arrow his desired target, he would be literally a Jester.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>To prevent Distract from being unfun I allowed the blackmailed player to talk to their blackmailer.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This is a fantastic idea, I support it 100%.  Also, there’s actually potential for practical utility here.  You can often negotiate with evils especially if the Neutral Killer is still alive.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Icy Touch(2 souls): Consume 2 souls to Blackmail, Distract, and Bewilder your target for the rest of the day.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I support this 100%.</p>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Great change. Though why are you willing to merge these yet keep Sheriff and Paladin separate? They have the exact same problem.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
<p>I would also like to see Sheriff and Paladin merged, or at least able to spawn regardless of whether it were Unseen or Cult game.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Can’t Touch This nerf</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I wish Mastermind would simply be unique (no new one) and permanently unsuspicious.  Like in Town of Salem.  It’s simple, and involves no artificial time limit and complication like “starting Assassin will become Mastermind but not new Assassin,” or “Mastermind is unsuspicious until Night 4 and the Assassin will become Mastermind if the Mastermind dies before then.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/46</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 14:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-46</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, I wouldn’t show the survey results. It would solely be feedback for the devs, not players. Now people wonder why we don’t show survey results, this is why <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> sort of like this patch, there are way more considerations than just player feedback that goes into changes. Not everyone can see that – and those that can’t get really pissed and <em>“voice” their opinion louder than others</em>, so to say.</p>
<p>Really, the only balance priorities… goes to the balance dev, who probably gives priority to me + Ellie’s feedback, but we don’t really get in the way (I didn’t get in the way of Ellie’s balancing over the past 2 years, either (maybe only at the beginning), and I like the direction we’ve gone in – while there will always be those that disagree). We consider both new and veteran player feedback.</p>
<p>The fact is, the level of complexity was not this high during launch, and we did have a certain level of consistency. It was already pretty intuitive, without any official system. Over time, there just became a big heap of garbage “leftovers” that was never meant to be, sometimes mistaken to be done on purpose as if we’re trying to add a new layer of complexity (we were not).</p>
<p>This is also why <a class="hashtag" href="/c/feedback/12">#<span>feedback</span></a> in Discord defaults to only a thumbs UP. We’re interested how many people are INTERESTED, not “not interested”. It’s often the same group of people that mass votes down, but varieties of people that upvote. Sort of like Steam reviews: People only upvote if they REALLY WANT TO. People will downvote if they get a 1 minute mute or merely disagreed with their idea ;p</p>
<p>As for balance, every single balance patch is subjective. Even for AAA games that will change OP mechanics by 0.1% get super flamed by people. It’s been this way since the dawn of this game. There will always be more patches. And there will always be more patches that you’ll both love and hate. As devs, we just have to find the best balance, do what we think is best for everyone, and observe. We simply do the best we can, and we’re indie. The weight of feedback is strong.</p>
<p>This is why we’re so strict about the way feedback is <em>delivered</em> (not that it’s good or bad, just simply <strong>constructive and civil</strong>): Ellie was already burned out. We don’t want to burn out Armae: She’s the last we got lol. This is why she hasn’t said anything yet, I honestly didn’t ask her to write a blog yet, as I know she’ll do it when she’s comfortable. I’m not going to force her, either, because she may lose her passion if I did that. Give her some time ;p No matter what she says, <strong>the patch is it what it is and there will be improvements.</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 13:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-45</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="15" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wonder if an <strong>in-game survey</strong> would get more accurate results of what the community wants. Maybe only show it if you played xx hours to prevent trolls or random clicks.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>OSRS does this if 75% of players agree. The player must have played for a specific amount of hours there as well and have a specific skill level (and be a member but the two later ones cannot and shouldn’t apply to tol)<br>
I’d also suggest if a player has had a warning recently. They should wait 1-2 days but a ban should have to wait 1-2 weeks after their ban before voting on a poll.</p>
<p>I think it’s a great idea to get everyone. Especially if you just do it</p>
<p>*<em>Also DON’T make anyone have more priority. It’ll just piss off the people in the community. Devs, Mods, Judges, Guides, Kickstarter Backers and Patreon Supporters should not have an extra say. Everyone should be equal like communism for this system or votes will unfairly pass even if the majority doesn’t want it.</em></p>
<p>Also I’d suggest doing a poll for every single change. Even new events or skins. Even if you think they’ll pass anyway.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Loser talks about one specific event that should be handled extremely carefully</summary>
<p><strong>Please do not assume from this passage that I dislike the idea of this event entirely and don’t call me the H word and ban me. Yes I’m an extremely controversial member in the community (around orangeandblack level) but I’m just doing this so you can learn from previous mistakes from other devs.</strong></p>
<p>There’s one specific event that I’ve seen cause controversy within games and other things so I’d possibly say poll that one before doing it if you ever want to.<br>
I mean, you dont really have those type of people playing from what I’ve seen but if that event ever does happen without the community support. The mods probably wont have fun while banning these said people.</p>
<p>Many of the mods would support this as I can see already since some of them are part of it and inclusive and I can only tell that two of the devs are there too.</p>
<p>Hell even 3 of the classes have been confirmed to fit into this group. Prince, Alch and Merc.</p>
<p>I dont care if this event is added in personally. It’s not really one for me and I won’t be mad if it passes.<br>
I’ll just probably look at it and say. “Oh cool.”</p>
<p>Just from seeing OSRS and the SCP wiki’s controversy with this specific event.<br>
Even Overwatch’s first Christmas comic with one specific reveal.</p>
<p>I’m only wanting to warn you.<br>
<em>also Russia might hate your game even more</em></p>
<p>I’m not against any LGBT people (hell I have friends in that group). I’m just warning about how this event is a controversial addition and might paint you in a bad light if you handle it the wrong way.</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 03:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-44</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Somewhere like 80% of people voted to keep the Spy the same and the community then exploded because vets really really hate spy but casual players just voted yes out of what I can only call ignorance</p>
<p>To rectify this the devs had to change Spy anyways and now nobody is happy</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 02:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-43</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What happened</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/42</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 02:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-42</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="15" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wonder if an <strong>in-game survey</strong> would get more accurate results of what the community wants</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ToS tried that</p>
<p>It did not go well</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/41</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 02:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-41</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also the majority of people aren’t interested in suggesting ideas all the time, I just always like to voice my opinion instead of screaming “bad patch lol” I feel mixed about the patch and I’m sure you guys will work something out that will attract new players but also let Veterans who have spent many hours feel at home. (lol I’m over 2000 at this point I’m one of your biggest fans) I feel like I want to help the community out and I’ll always do my part in making suggestions and trying to help as much as I can so I can see this game have success.</p>
<p>just want a game that has its old complexity and charm it’s hard because my favourite class the old Mercenary was removed and reworked into a fun class it’s just not the same and I get upset with things getting completely removed aswell as starting Neutral King while contriversal I’d argue that it gave king more complexity of course I’d limit other Neutrals down to 2 because at that point it would become throne of whoever has the most neuts sided.</p>
<p>I feel like it’s more rng click da button to win instead of social dudection sometimes, once change I really want to see is noble twin removal it confirms noble easily imagine Mastermind being able to claim noble making the noble class have to put effort into proving. Prince of course is needed for balance but we can’t have super confirmable classes without counters aka Sellsword always is going to make butlers suspicious but drunks will get a free pass.</p>
<p>There are a lot of ways TOL could go I just don’t like seeing classes always completely reworked to the point they don’t even feel the same.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 19:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-40</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Problem is there is inconsistently with the icons hunters wolf is the same thing as bleed but doesn’t share the same icon</p>
<p>Cult like Invokers occupation or “puppet strings” which is debauchery.</p>
<p>Or for example alchemists heal ect.</p>
<p>All occupy immune classes have different icons but then with the newer icons they are same as others</p>
<p>I feel like you shouldn’t have a mix of both either every class gets different icons or they share the same ones for the same Abilites.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 19:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-39</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(also tbh just make jail an AOE occupy like the other similar effects)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-38</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Especially since they removed occ immunity on the classes that occ immunity can’t ignore (besides Prince)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/37</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-37</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Temporary occ immunity</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How else can you bypass them then?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also stop talking like immunity bypass is the only way to counterplay an occupier.</p>
<p>There is a reason why the first thing I suggested when this patch came out is more temporary occupy immunity sources</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RHCube" data-post="32" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/ritualist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> RHCube:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Isn’t it already in the class card?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think it’s in innoculate but it should be in the keyword description cuz it’s true with other classes too</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-33</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="1" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What was truly simplified beyond the <em>Alchemist</em> ? While the old Alchemist had more fun buttons to click, most would agree that this was pretty necessary. If additional button options are more important than your own wit, you may be playing the wrong game ;D</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s true, but the current alchemist is just a neutral physician.  You should try to avoid making classes too similar to already existing classes(unless they have opposing win conditions).</p>
<aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="1" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>CONSISTENCY = SECURING THRONE’S FUTURE</strong></p>
<p>While the names are certainly COOL and it looks unique, and may even be viable in the first set (pretend those are vanilla). However, what about the future? What about 10 expansions later? What about 5 years later? Imagine memorizing not “Taunt” or “Deathrattle”, but if all of these consistencies didn’t exist. Imagine patch notes, how long it would take to adapt. Imagine that a simple mechanic like “Taunt” was called something different each time. <strong>Consistency ensures a future</strong> for Throne.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree that consistency is a good thing, but you should only be merging abilities for consistency if they have the same purpose.</p>
<aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="1" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We wanted to <strong>reduce RNG</strong> (Random factors).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What RNG was there?</p>
<p>Also, here are my thoughts on the patches now that some time has passed:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>prevention changes</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>I’m neutral on this one.  There were several differences between prevention and occupation(If a two-target ability targeted a prevented player then only one target would be prevented while prevention affected both.  Prevention affects targeters and not just visitors.  Prevention also bypassed immunity), but I can see how this can be confusing, and I understand why they did it.  I would personally prefer a revert, but if it stays then can you at least add back the ability for old prevention abilities to bypass occupation immunity?  All classes need counterplay(including prince).  Oh and can you also still have the same message for jailing and occupation(It should be “You were prevented from BLANKing X”)?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>No more immunity-bypassing abilities</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Bad change.  All classes need counterplay.  I do like the current happy hour more since it fits with Debauchery better, but I love the concept of the old Happy Hour.  Maybe it could be on a new Offensive?  And it could only remove immunities/disable passives?  We need a fakeclaimable Offensive anyways</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Distract changes</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>I like that they are making distract more common to reduce confirmation, but I disagree with merging distract, bewilder, and Icy Touch.  Distract and Bewilder had a similar purpose, and I agree that Bewilder was weak, but 25 seconds vs the entire day is a huge difference.  As long as it’s a temporary effect people will be able to say that they were silenced(Yes, I know that it’s not fun to be silenced.  I have another solution for that).  And Icy Touch and Distract have completely different purposes.  Distract is usually used for executing players/making players suspicious.  Icy Touch is used to prevent players from spreading info, and to give reaper the upper hand in voting lategame.  Sure, reaper is a rare class, but that doesn’t mean that you should ignore it.  NKs are just as important as every other class.  Here’s how I would fix it, while solving the issue of it not being fun:  Split distract into 3 abilities(Butler, Servant, Invoker, and Pretender would have Bewilder.  Scorned and assassin would have Distract.  Reaper would have Icy Touch) :</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Bewilder(1 use): Disable your target’s day abilities for the rest of the day.  They will not be notified until they attempt to use a day ability.  Still consumes the use/cost of the ability, if any.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Reasoning: Gives Prince and day confirmation counterplay while reducing confirmation.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Distract(1 use): Blackmail(prevent them from speaking to anyone but yourself.  You will appear as the Blackmailer) and Silence(prevents them from voting and accusing) your target for the rest of the day.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Reasoning: As long as Distract is temporary people will be able to say that they were distracted.  To prevent it from being unfun I allowed the blackmailed player to talk to their blackmailer.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Icy Touch(2 souls): Consume 2 souls to Blackmail, Distract, and Bewilder your target for the rest of the day.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Reasoning: Allows reaper to stand a chance lategame while still making Icy Touch fun.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Bleed/poison merge</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Great change.  Though why are you willing to merge these yet keep Sheriff and Paladin separate?  They have the exact same problem.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Mind Warp Change</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Bad change.  No feedback should be infallible, and nerfing for non-balance reasons should only be a last resort, if ever.  There were plenty of other solutions.  If consistency was the issue, then you could just make all Frames an AoE mind warp.  This would also increase the commonness of it so people are more ready for it.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Can’t Touch This nerf</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Bad change.  Can’t touch this was there since there are enough unconvertables already.  The hidden part was since there are no investigative classes that had occupation immunity, and it was honestly no more confusing than framings.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>In the Shadows removal</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>I can understand why they did this because of Apprentice, but the unseen is much more easily found since both members can be found by Sheriffs.  IMO this should be given to the starting assassin instead, and it should be permanent.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Apprentice</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>I like this better than the timed limit, but only working on the starting assassin is too weak.  It should work on anyone, or replace it with this:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Apprentice: If you die and the oldest living unseen has been apart of the unseen for at least 3 days then they will become the mastermind</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Reasoning:  Still allows the sheriff to kill the MM early, but now they will do better lategame since any player can become the MM.  Which is good since lategame is when scum should be strongest.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Frame can now affect follow</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Great change.  Now frame can work on any investigative ability.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>No longer being able to edit logs on trial.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Bad change.  I don’t see the point of this at all.  This is just an unnecessary nerf for evils</li>
</ul>
<p>PS.  I like that you’re making an effort to communicate with the community.  This is easily the best dev team that I have ever seen.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Hunter is now not unique and retribution is gone</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Bad change.  I loved retribution, and it allowed Hunters to still act aggressively even when they are out of bears.  I can see how it might be a bit RNG-based, but Icibalus’s solution would be perfect.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Hunter and poacher are no longer immune to occupation and redirection</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Bad change.  I can see why you want to make Butlers and Drunk more useful as there were a ton of immune classes, but it should be reserved for classes that can occupy, and both Hunter and Poacher have occupation abilities</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Wolf is now a day ability</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Bad change.  2 days vs one day is huge.  People are also more frequently using wolf as confirmation, which shouldn’t be done(It’s a waste of a powerful ability, and there are too many negative variables).  If evils not being able to fake this was an issue, then just rework Drug so it can fake any message.</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="6" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>ToL was becoming a touch like ToS</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="6" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>not only is that game worse because of the complexity (4 levels of attack and defense? Seriously?)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I dislike a lot about ToS, but that’s one of the few things that I actually like.  What’s so bad about it?  It’s better than our system, where there are a ton of different defenses.</p>
<aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="15" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is where balance gets difficult to judge early via a community since it’s generally the same ~30 people out 10s of thousands of players. Just brainstorming, I wonder if an <strong>in-game survey</strong> would get more accurate results of what the community wants. Maybe only show it if you played xx hours to prevent trolls or random clicks.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That would be great.  Not everyone knows about the forum(Maybe you could have an in-game tip about the forum and discord?)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marluxion" data-post="27" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marluxion/40/10921_2.png" class="avatar"> Marluxion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>no direct counterplay</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Occupation and redirection.  There’s also conversion if you can’t find another way around.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="31" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh yeah you should probably mention somewhere that bleed immunity does not cure an existing bleed</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Isn’t it already in the class card?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="15" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>what are others’ thoughts on this? Is there an even-better compromise within?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Personally I’m fine with reusing icons. I just don’t like the specific icons used.</p>
<p>The bleeds just kinda look like a plain red background and I think the old distract icon would be better than the bewilder icon.</p>
<p>Also I personally think a good idea would be to select a keyword in the guide book and have it take you to the class list with all of the classes without that keyword in the card grayed out</p>
<p>Oh yeah you should probably mention somewhere that bleed immunity does not cure an existing bleed</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 16:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pug" data-post="29" data-topic="74595">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/pug/40/20893_2.png" class="avatar"> Pug:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>visit prevention back</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>+1</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 15:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74595-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devblog-behind-the-streamline-patch-non-balance/74595.rss">[DevBlog] Behind the Streamline Patch (Non-Balance)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
