<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808</link>
    <description>Just finished a game where I was CW, and already on a large losing streak due to other players struggling, so I said to myself &quot;Oh great, useless class, let&#39;s gooo...&quot;  But actually the game was looking pretty good because we killed off a lot of cult rather quickly; however, this one psychic kept calling to execute me just because I questioned one of his claims.  So he got everyone to accuse me somehow and I had to confirm myself with switches.  
     Now remember, this is a cult game, so if I&#39;m converted, I lose my switches, yet SOME PEOPLE were still saying I might be converted...  So even after that, the psychic kept calling to execute me, even linking me just to trash talk me one night, and not really being a big help to hunt down the remaining baddies.  
     Eventually it got down to a couple people, including the psych, and the possessor had jumped and we assumed it was to king.  So me and the one other intelligent BD kept calling for him to use his finger, but he didnt for a while and the psychic kept calling to execute me even though I had just gotten a cult leader killed through switching (useless class ikr?).  So just with the psych&#39;s accusation, the one remaining cult leader&#39;s, and the king&#39;s, i got put on trial and they executed me, effectively throwing, which the one other BD realized too late.  
     And then long story short from there, the psychic got converted on the last night, netting a win... 
HE THREW BD THE WHOLE GAME AND GOT A WIN JUST BECAUSE HE GOT CONVERTED ON THE LAST NIGHT 
....
so yeah when is this getting patched out??</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 19:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Luckily for you, the only difference between a win and a loss is 30 gold. This is pretty much why Ranked should never be a thing.</p>
<p>Also, why disrespect CW? It’s a powerful and immensely useful class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19808-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808.rss">When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jabba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even then, I had proven myself by getting one of the cult killed with a swap at the end, and I claimed it, too.  And furthermore, once I got executed, all the dead were calling out the psychic for throwing when he linked the last night, the night he got converted.  He doesn’t deserve that win…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 18:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19808-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808.rss">When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ulkesh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel this happens quite frequently. People getting all upset, calling people ‘dumb’ or ‘idiot’, and in the end they are in the wrong themselves.</p>
<p>I get it, this is a great and immersive game. Sometimes, this doesn’t bring out the best in us (yes, I’m guilty too, no excuses).</p>
<p>In this game you have control over some things, and you don’t have control over lots of other things. Often, the feeling that others are ‘dumb’ start when things don’t go your way and you feel you don’t have enough means to influence that. But remember, there is information asymmetry.</p>
<p>It is natural to think you are right and others are wrong, but that does not have to be the case. This is called motivated reasoning. For those interested, this is a great YouTube video about it:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w4RLfVxTGH4" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w4RLfVxTGH4</a></p>
<p>(Why you think you’re right, even when you’re wrong)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19808-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808.rss">When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Methnor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jabba" data-post="1" data-topic="19808">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> jabba:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Now remember, this is a cult game, so if I’m converted, I lose my switches</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Court Wizard gets converted into Ritualist, which has Teleportation, a 3-use Tornado clone.<br>
Just saying <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smirk.png?v=9" title=":smirk:" class="emoji" alt=":smirk:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 11:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19808-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808.rss">When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jabba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just finished a game where I was CW, and already on a large losing streak due to other players struggling, so I said to myself “Oh great, useless class, let’s gooo…”  But actually the game was looking pretty good because we killed off a lot of cult rather quickly; however, this one psychic kept calling to execute me just because I questioned one of his claims.  So he got everyone to accuse me somehow and I had to confirm myself with switches.<br>
Now remember, this is a cult game, so if I’m converted, I lose my switches, yet SOME PEOPLE were still saying I might be converted…  So even after that, the psychic kept calling to execute me, even linking me just to trash talk me one night, and not really being a big help to hunt down the remaining baddies.<br>
Eventually it got down to a couple people, including the psych, and the possessor had jumped and we assumed it was to king.  So me and the one other intelligent BD kept calling for him to use his finger, but he didnt for a while and the psychic kept calling to execute me even though I had just gotten a cult leader killed through switching (useless class ikr?).  So just with the psych’s accusation, the one remaining cult leader’s, and the king’s, i got put on trial and they executed me, effectively throwing, which the one other BD realized too late.<br>
And then long story short from there, the psychic got converted on the last night, netting a win…<br>
HE THREW BD THE WHOLE GAME AND GOT A WIN JUST BECAUSE HE GOT CONVERTED ON THE LAST NIGHT<br>
…<br>
so yeah when is this getting patched out??</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 09:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-19808-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/when-are-dumb-players-getting-patched-out/19808.rss">When are Dumb Players Getting Patched Out?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
