<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Possible Drunk new deb bug?</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563</link>
    <description>#### What happened?
On n1, I deb&#39;d what was later found to be a phys. He claimed possessed so I called him out for lying. A CW also targeted him but was made to target me. Does deb not affect possession?

On n2-n4 I deb&#39;d another role. Forgot what he was but he was leading the charge against unseen and the final screen showed he was originally BD. On day 5, the king accused him of being evil. I, of course, defended him saying it&#39;s impossible he could&#39;ve been converted. CW and another phys confirmed they targeted him but were redirected rewards me. Sure enough, he was just converted to unseen. He claims it was on n4. I can understand the King being immune to deb, but shouldn&#39;t have the MM gone after me instead? In both cases, the CW ice warded the target. I was not occupied once in those nights. 

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?
As far as I know,  shouldn&#39;t have the possessor and MM been redirected to me as the drunk?

#### Steps to reproduce:
Possess/convert, ice ward, and deb the same target to see if the attack goes through.

#### Comments:
I might be misunderstanding the limits of the new deb. I&#39;m unsure if possession is meant to go through but I&#39;m fairly sure the tooltip said conversions should be redirected.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:55:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Possible Drunk new deb bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>CW is not occupy immune, so it acts as if the CW targetted the drunk, and succeeds.</p>
<p>Offensive attacks would be nullified assuming the attacker was not occupy immune, however both mastermind and Possesor are occupy immune, and thus hit their target.</p>
<p>So just hypothetical here<br>
1 - CW, walls 5<br>
2. Drunk - Deb - 5<br>
3. Possesor - Posseses 5 throws to 9.<br>
4. MM - targets 5<br>
5 Princess, Whisps.<br>
6. Assasain targets 5.</p>
<p>In this hypothetical scenerio.</p>
<ol>
<li>CW - His wall would be redirected to 2</li>
<li>Drunk would know he redirected the targets</li>
<li>As an occupy immune role, the possesor would succesfully throw 5 at 9.</li>
<li>MM would succesfully convert the princess, he is uneffected by the debauch, and the ice wall is on 2</li>
<li>Whisp - would announce the visit by the drunk, the possesor and the mastermind</li>
<li>Assasain would be redirected to 2, his attack would be negated.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10563-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563.rss">Possible Drunk new deb bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible Drunk new deb bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sixation]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Best explanation we came up with was the ice wall made me immune so the offensive attack defaulted to the original target. It does work on CL, right? I’m still new and can’t check if they’re immune at the moment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10563-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563.rss">Possible Drunk new deb bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible Drunk new deb bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yup a lot of people don’t understand that debauchery does not effect those with occupy immunity, spent 15 minutes trying to explain to someone how his debauching steals my ice wall, but lets the master mind waltz right past to convert.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10563-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563.rss">Possible Drunk new deb bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible Drunk new deb bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sixation]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I was misunderstanding it. Got it. No-one in my game knew what the problem was either. The tooltip was misleading me. Thanks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10563-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563.rss">Possible Drunk new deb bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible Drunk new deb bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Debauch does not affect Occupy Immune classes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10563-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563.rss">Possible Drunk new deb bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible Drunk new deb bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sixation]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>On n1, I deb’d what was later found to be a phys. He claimed possessed so I called him out for lying. A CW also targeted him but was made to target me. Does deb not affect possession?</p>
<p>On n2-n4 I deb’d another role. Forgot what he was but he was leading the charge against unseen and the final screen showed he was originally BD. On day 5, the king accused him of being evil. I, of course, defended him saying it’s impossible he could’ve been converted. CW and another phys confirmed they targeted him but were redirected rewards me. Sure enough, he was just converted to unseen. He claims it was on n4. I can understand the King being immune to deb, but shouldn’t have the MM gone after me instead? In both cases, the CW ice warded the target. I was not occupied once in those nights.</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>As far as I know,  shouldn’t have the possessor and MM been redirected to me as the drunk?</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<p>Possess/convert, ice ward, and deb the same target to see if the attack goes through.</p>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>I might be misunderstanding the limits of the new deb. I’m unsure if possession is meant to go through but I’m fairly sure the tooltip said conversions should be redirected.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 17:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10563-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possible-drunk-new-deb-bug/10563.rss">Possible Drunk new deb bug?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
