<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Boy who Played Reaper</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-boy-who-played-reaper/68879</link>
    <description>A stormy night brew outside of castle adiart. The court had already been tainted with the fear of the unseen. Darkness was everywhere, it was inevitable.
One small boy, mother and father a mystery, only had his nurse to raise him. And on the same day, the boy was playing ball around the village. A dark man approached him and said, &quot;young boy, you can&#39;t just keep playing ball. You have to grow up someday.&quot; The boy was confused about that statement. He had spent his whole life playing a little game of ball. 
The castle doors became shut to prevent the corruption of the unseen. The boy began to play just outside the doors. He kicked on the ball and it bounced on the castle walls. 
&quot;Why do I have to grow up? Why can&#39;t I just be a kid forever?&quot;
The kid grew with insanity. As he grew older, he just wanted to play. And play. And play. And play until he lost his mind completely.
&quot;Let&#39;s play. Let&#39;s play Castle.&quot;
He gazed upon the walls, shut for almost his entire life. As insanity creeped up him, he raised his hand to meet the door. The hand passed right through it.
And that was when he realized who the black man was.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 22:40:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-boy-who-played-reaper/68879.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Boy who Played Reaper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Planterror]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A stormy night brew outside of castle adiart. The court had already been tainted with the fear of the unseen. Darkness was everywhere, it was inevitable.<br>
One small boy, mother and father a mystery, only had his nurse to raise him. And on the same day, the boy was playing ball around the village. A dark man approached him and said, “young boy, you can’t just keep playing ball. You have to grow up someday.” The boy was confused about that statement. He had spent his whole life playing a little game of ball.<br>
The castle doors became shut to prevent the corruption of the unseen. The boy began to play just outside the doors. He kicked on the ball and it bounced on the castle walls.<br>
“Why do I have to grow up? Why can’t I just be a kid forever?”<br>
The kid grew with insanity. As he grew older, he just wanted to play. And play. And play. And play until he lost his mind completely.<br>
“Let’s play. Let’s play Castle.”<br>
He gazed upon the walls, shut for almost his entire life. As insanity creeped up him, he raised his hand to meet the door. The hand passed right through it.<br>
And that was when he realized who the black man was.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-boy-who-played-reaper/68879/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-boy-who-played-reaper/68879/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68879-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-boy-who-played-reaper/68879.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Boy who Played Reaper</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
