<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897</link>
    <description>So I&#39;ve got several hundred hours logged in this game, and I&#39;ve conferred with other people with similar XP, and when I first started the game, I thought &quot;lower impact&quot; classes were the worst, things like noble/butler/CW/etc, but then I learned I was just bad.

I&#39;ve been kinda hoping that the same sort of revelation would occur with hunter, but nope, I&#39;m still convinced it&#39;s the least fun class in the game, and here&#39;s why:

You get two abilities. You can trap, or you can wolf.

If you lay traps down, you&#39;re just as likely to snare your allies (well, more likely to snare them really if you use them early, but that&#39;s the only button you can press on the first 2 nights so you usually do it). If you wolf someone, you want to be pretty sure they&#39;re evil, but if you&#39;re pretty sure they&#39;re evil, so is everyone else, so you usually end up wasting a wolf on a prince jail target.

The class just isn&#39;t fun in its current incarnation. You&#39;re just this chaotic thing that&#39;s as likely if not more likely to hurt your own team than to help it. I get that for nearly every class, having good social skills and piecing together the puzzle is more important than the actual class abilities, but nearly every game I play hunter I either yolo trap n1 and n2 because I&#39;m bored and what else am I going to do, or I sit around doing nothing till I figure out someone is against me, but then that person either gets strung up or executed in jail.

What role is the hunter supposed to fill? You have a delayed kill that&#39;s really only useful if the prince screws up or is dead (and now that there&#39;s always a priest, the prince usually just comes back up anyway), and you have traps that are more likely to bleed your teammates than evil people.

I&#39;m not sure what could be done to make the class more fun to play, maybe something like a &quot;follow the trail&quot; ability that tells you if you&#39;re hot or cold (number of positions away from a non-BD on the list) that you&#39;ve clicked. Like, if you click on the person and they&#39;re not BD it says you&#39;ve found your prey, if you click 1 position away it says that you can almost taste your prey, 2 away is warming up, 3 away is the trail goes cold, etc.

I don&#39;t know, maybe my idea isn&#39;t great, but I do think out of all the classes hunter is by far the least engaging to play and is a good target for a rework.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/e/eb326373ba9d63496a2c3cc759cf39ad0c7f1f29.jpg" alt="1yrq3q" data-base62-sha1="xyEa4d7yYpY70M4kTJs6hKse1dL" width="570" height="300"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good points made in this thread.</p>
<p>I feel like the point is that Hunter’s early-game is unengaging and weak. You just stare at a fireplace and hope you don’t die or get converted.</p>
<p>Some sort of day ability would be nice, or make wolfing a day activity and give them something else to do at night.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t really argue ‘fun’ since that’s subjective, but Hunter is a very strong role. It actually plays fairly similar to the Prince.  Hunter along with Prince are the only two BD with a kill power capable of taking out Night immune.  On top of that, it isn’t a visit, and you’re occupy immune, so it’s basically unstoppable. A hunter claim is very solid, since it’s a unique role and evil won’t risk claiming it because if they do they’re getting wolf’d by the real hunter.  On top of that, you kill your first accuser so people are very hesitant to challenge your claim anyway.  About the only risk in a hunter claim is if the hunter is converted, and you can save your wolves to prove that.</p>
<p>So Hunters are rarely ever executed during the day while BD still has the majority. And then at night they have 2 immunes that not only make them immune to kill whoever visits them.  So attacking or converting a Hunter at night is also risky.  If you’re unseen, do you really want to go for a Hunter and potentially not only lose your kill but also die?  You can roll those dice, or you can go attack someone else.</p>
<p>All of this makes Hunter a power class.  Hard to get rid, and really dangerous if he sticks around. It’s just that Hunter requires communicating with the BD to get your targets and avoid trapping friendlies, and having the will not to just trap on N1 and N2 but saving them for the critical mid to late game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 20:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cool ideas! I will try the Prince thing next time. Could work with Priest as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 16:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wolf Physician (or alch) claims.</p>
<p>If they bleed, you just found an evil.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 11:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One fun thing you can do if you meet the prince early days is ask permission to claim prince . Then claim prince and watch the good times role as the bad guys come knocking at your door .</p>
<p>Alternatively .<br>
I know this is really hard for some people<br>
Almost impossible in many cases .</p>
<p>Here it is though</p>
<p>Try not pressing any buttons for the first three nights .</p>
<p>Once the herd is thinned a bit look through the chat  and see who has said nothing so far and ask them to claim a role in public or private message .</p>
<p>If they are not forthcoming send in the wolf .</p>
<p>Keep a list of everyone and their claims , work out who has dodgy claims . then send in the wolves .</p>
<p>If you last to about turn 6 declare yourself as hunter and set traps for 2 nights .</p>
<p>Or try just outright threatening folk in private messages if they are not speaking much in public .<br>
( hi I am going to send a wolf at you tonight unless you tell me who you are !)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="WutangRZA" data-post="1" data-topic="7897">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/wutangrza/40/2113_2.png" class="avatar"> WutangRZA:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“follow the trail” ability that tells you if you’re hot or cold (number of positions away from a non-BD on the list) that you’ve clicked.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I love that idea.</p>
<p>Hunter is very weak at the moment because he is more prone to killing BD than he is evils. His killing power is only useful if the Prince is dead since you’re the only one who can kill night immune baddies now.</p>
<p>Using Traps during the first two nights is almost always a bad idea mathematically speaking. There are no phrases or sentences you can say that will attract only evil players but keep the good players from investigating you as well.</p>
<p>The issue with Hunter is that they can’t use their wolf Night 2 which encourages players to use their traps that night even though it is a bad idea most of the time. I agree with Wolf being disabled night 1, but disabling it night 2 really hinders this class. This causes players to trap because they feel like they <em>need to press a button every night.</em></p>
<p>The Hunter’s strength lies in forcing players to claim a class after you wolf them. Since they are going to die anyway, you can get a claim or let them die if they don’t claim or have a terrible claim. If they sound trustworthy, you can ask a Physician or Alchemist to save them. You’re also confirming the Physician or Alchemist in this way, so that helps too.</p>
<p>But yes, Hunters kill way more BD right now, but that may be due to newer players.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 22:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>random chance for people with the trail</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 21:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter is not a fun class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WutangRZA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’ve got several hundred hours logged in this game, and I’ve conferred with other people with similar XP, and when I first started the game, I thought “lower impact” classes were the worst, things like noble/butler/CW/etc, but then I learned I was just bad.</p>
<p>I’ve been kinda hoping that the same sort of revelation would occur with hunter, but nope, I’m still convinced it’s the least fun class in the game, and here’s why:</p>
<p>You get two abilities. You can trap, or you can wolf.</p>
<p>If you lay traps down, you’re just as likely to snare your allies (well, more likely to snare them really if you use them early, but that’s the only button you can press on the first 2 nights so you usually do it). If you wolf someone, you want to be pretty sure they’re evil, but if you’re pretty sure they’re evil, so is everyone else, so you usually end up wasting a wolf on a prince jail target.</p>
<p>The class just isn’t fun in its current incarnation. You’re just this chaotic thing that’s as likely if not more likely to hurt your own team than to help it. I get that for nearly every class, having good social skills and piecing together the puzzle is more important than the actual class abilities, but nearly every game I play hunter I either yolo trap n1 and n2 because I’m bored and what else am I going to do, or I sit around doing nothing till I figure out someone is against me, but then that person either gets strung up or executed in jail.</p>
<p>What role is the hunter supposed to fill? You have a delayed kill that’s really only useful if the prince screws up or is dead (and now that there’s always a priest, the prince usually just comes back up anyway), and you have traps that are more likely to bleed your teammates than evil people.</p>
<p>I’m not sure what could be done to make the class more fun to play, maybe something like a “follow the trail” ability that tells you if you’re hot or cold (number of positions away from a non-BD on the list) that you’ve clicked. Like, if you click on the person and they’re not BD it says you’ve found your prey, if you click 1 position away it says that you can almost taste your prey, 2 away is warming up, 3 away is the trail goes cold, etc.</p>
<p>I don’t know, maybe my idea isn’t great, but I do think out of all the classes hunter is by far the least engaging to play and is a good target for a rework.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 21:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7897-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/hunter-is-not-a-fun-class/7897.rss">Hunter is not a fun class</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
