<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>When to be Aggressive</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223</link>
    <description>OK I don&#39;t understand BD&#39;s mindset sometimes.  Explain to me how if prince is outed it is a bad idea to vote for class. It is just inherently good. If you make everyone have a claim and everyone knows what everyone is claiming this can allow for some scum reading and validation of logs. Usually Passive=Evils Aggressive=Scorned/BD or at least in theory. See for every day that passes by that BD do nothing it allows a night for evils to try to convert or kill if they are not stopped.So why the fuck do BD immediately suspect anyone who starts voting for class. It&#39;s a good strategy at one point in the game being once Prince is dead or outed. It was so good that trials got nerfed. So why is being aggressive a bad thing? Well most people will argue that &quot;you are outing important BD classes&quot; and my point stands. What classes? Prince is outed when you start voting for class so the most important class you could possibly be outing is a physician or sheriff both of which are common fake claims as they are easy to fake claim. Just explain to me why being aggresive is bad thing. I was in a game as drunk and we voted up the MM who claimed sheriff. I asked if anyone counterclaimed and no one did. We pardoned but then some retard claimed sheriff 2 days later with no leads. We hung him and he was sheriff. He refused to cooperate with BD leading to the MM staying alive longer. Why the fuck wouldn&#39;t he CC? Also I was wolfed by a Hunter because I was so obviously evil by voting for class. What the fuck is that mindset? People who vote for class are usually BD are they not? Why would evils do it? They risk having an evil hung and even if they do get off they&#39;re now stuck with a claim. Just someone explain to me how being aggressive is usually scum.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 18:58:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>When to be Aggressive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fool actually benefits from being aggressive in an unfocused way. Trying to tick one player off won’t get you anywhere, but being generically angry at other players for existing is a reasonable strat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 18:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52223-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223.rss">When to be Aggressive</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>When to be Aggressive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Aggresive =/= Scum</p>
<p>Aggresive with no adequate reasoning = Scum</p>
<p>Like if I was playing agressively that’s not a scumtell, but if I was being aggresive randomly and not foousedly that’s scum. Aggresive play ticks new players off but it’s actually NAI.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52223-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223.rss">When to be Aggressive</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>When to be Aggressive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>TBH you should always be aggressive regardless of class because there are 3 main benifits:</p>
<p>1: If you are leading you are controlling who get’s VFCed meaning that you can control the lynch fairly well.</p>
<p>2: If you are leading then Protectives will know to be on you as a leader is a high priority target.</p>
<p>3: It makes for a good defense if people start to turn on you that you have been progressing the game and properly scum hunting.</p>
<p>The only class which does not benefit from these things is fool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 16:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52223-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223.rss">When to be Aggressive</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>When to be Aggressive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeathReaperRH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OK I don’t understand BD’s mindset sometimes.  Explain to me how if prince is outed it is a bad idea to vote for class. It is just inherently good. If you make everyone have a claim and everyone knows what everyone is claiming this can allow for some scum reading and validation of logs. Usually Passive=Evils Aggressive=Scorned/BD or at least in theory. See for every day that passes by that BD do nothing it allows a night for evils to try to convert or kill if they are not stopped.So why the fuck do BD immediately suspect anyone who starts voting for class. It’s a good strategy at one point in the game being once Prince is dead or outed. It was so good that trials got nerfed. So why is being aggressive a bad thing? Well most people will argue that “you are outing important BD classes” and my point stands. What classes? Prince is outed when you start voting for class so the most important class you could possibly be outing is a physician or sheriff both of which are common fake claims as they are easy to fake claim. Just explain to me why being aggresive is bad thing. I was in a game as drunk and we voted up the MM who claimed sheriff. I asked if anyone counterclaimed and no one did. We pardoned but then some retard claimed sheriff 2 days later with no leads. We hung him and he was sheriff. He refused to cooperate with BD leading to the MM staying alive longer. Why the fuck wouldn’t he CC? Also I was wolfed by a Hunter because I was so obviously evil by voting for class. What the fuck is that mindset? People who vote for class are usually BD are they not? Why would evils do it? They risk having an evil hung and even if they do get off they’re now stuck with a claim. Just someone explain to me how being aggressive is usually scum.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 16:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52223-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/when-to-be-aggressive/52223.rss">When to be Aggressive</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
