<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980</link>
    <description>Just an idea some friends and I came up with, sounded neat. We didn&#39;t have specific names for the abilities, but the idea was cool enough that we wanted to share it.


THE ROGUE:

Faction: Neutral (neutral killer)
Win Condition: Survive to see both good and evil factions eliminated.

Passives:
1. Immune to occupation and target changing. (not immune to death at night)
2. When you sneak into a player&#39;s room using day ability 1, any abilities targeting you will fail. However, any abilities targeting the player whose room you sneaked into will target you instead. This is not a target change, so target change immune classes will still target the Rogue.

Day Abilities
1. Choose a player. You will attempt to sneak into that player&#39;s room the next night, allowing you to speak with that player without revealing your number and to see the room they occupy (similar to the Prince&#39;s jail, but it does not occupy the target). If you sneak into the prince&#39;s room or the room of an evil faction, you will be able to talk to all players in that room.
2. The Rogue will lurk in the shadows, granting him death immunity the next night. This can be used at the same time as day ability 1. This would have limited uses (similar to the Alchemist&#39;s stoneskin).

Night Abilities
1. Kill the player whose room you sneaked into. If there are multiple, you may choose which one to target. This removes the player&#39;s immunities and erases his logs. This would have limited uses.
2. Attempt to kill a player whose room you are not in. You will not appear to visit the target, but you will still appear to visit the player whose room you sneaked into.

The catch to the rogue is that he is not death immune. He has to think on his feet to prevent himself from being targeted by other killers, no matter if they are cult or blue dragon. Using his first day ability, he can visit players to try and find friendly neutral classes, building a network of neutral players silently. He has a limited number of uses for death immunity, just in case a difficult situation arises. This could help him frame other players by making them appear death immune, or it could simply keep him alive through a Knight&#39;s cold steel.


Anyway, neat idea, hope you like it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 01:37:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Curaga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Someone would have to guess who you visit in order to kill you, essentially.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 01:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-38980-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980.rss">[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Curaga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When you sneak into another player’s room, anyone targeting that player would target you instead. It isn’t a target change, and it wouldn’t show up as one, but it would happen none the less. Glad you like it, by the way! Thanks for the question.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 01:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-38980-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980.rss">[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TinyDeer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think this is an idea with a lot of potential and one of the better suggestions I’ve seen on the forums.</p>
<p>Can you clarify for me: The Rogue is not death immune, but all abilities targeting you fail when you enter someone’s room (which is going to be almost every night). How can you be killed at night, then? It seems pretty strong to have killers need to predict whose room you will be in so they can kill you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 01:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-38980-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980.rss">[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Curaga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just an idea some friends and I came up with, sounded neat. We didn’t have specific names for the abilities, but the idea was cool enough that we wanted to share it.</p>
<p>THE ROGUE:</p>
<p>Faction: Neutral (neutral killer)<br>
Win Condition: Survive to see both good and evil factions eliminated.</p>
<p>Passives:</p>
<ol>
<li>Immune to occupation and target changing. (not immune to death at night)</li>
<li>When you sneak into a player’s room using day ability 1, any abilities targeting you will fail. However, any abilities targeting the player whose room you sneaked into will target you instead. This is not a target change, so target change immune classes will still target the Rogue.</li>
</ol>
<p>Day Abilities</p>
<ol>
<li>Choose a player. You will attempt to sneak into that player’s room the next night, allowing you to speak with that player without revealing your number and to see the room they occupy (similar to the Prince’s jail, but it does not occupy the target). If you sneak into the prince’s room or the room of an evil faction, you will be able to talk to all players in that room.</li>
<li>The Rogue will lurk in the shadows, granting him death immunity the next night. This can be used at the same time as day ability 1. This would have limited uses (similar to the Alchemist’s stoneskin).</li>
</ol>
<p>Night Abilities</p>
<ol>
<li>Kill the player whose room you sneaked into. If there are multiple, you may choose which one to target. This removes the player’s immunities and erases his logs. This would have limited uses.</li>
<li>Attempt to kill a player whose room you are not in. You will not appear to visit the target, but you will still appear to visit the player whose room you sneaked into.</li>
</ol>
<p>The catch to the rogue is that he is not death immune. He has to think on his feet to prevent himself from being targeted by other killers, no matter if they are cult or blue dragon. Using his first day ability, he can visit players to try and find friendly neutral classes, building a network of neutral players silently. He has a limited number of uses for death immunity, just in case a difficult situation arises. This could help him frame other players by making them appear death immune, or it could simply keep him alive through a Knight’s cold steel.</p>
<p>Anyway, neat idea, hope you like it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 01:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-38980-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-class-the-rogue/38980.rss">[Suggestion] New Class: The Rogue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
