<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151</link>
    <description>Perhaps I&#39;m in the minority here, but I feel very strongly about this. I recognize that there is currently no Ranked mode, but *to my knowledge* I have not seen a denial of this possibility from the devs.

Having played MOBAs as well as Town of Salem, I realize that Ranked modes significantly increase the toxicity within a community. One of the qualities I love most about Throne of Lies - and one of the central reasons I&#39;ve switched over entirely from ToS - is the commitment to a sportsmanlike, respectful environment. It is a breath of fresh air to have developers take the culture of the community seriously and to actually punish people whose behavior ruins the experience for everyone. Ranked mode would increase competitiveness, which would increase saltiness and personal insults.

Why can&#39;t we just have a game for fun? Why does everything have to be competitive? What is the point of adding a Ranked mode in the future?

For those who would say, &quot;Just stick to unranked if you don&#39;t want to deal with ELO,&quot; I say that is avoiding the issue. Would you really say that League of Legends would be the same game were it not for their Ranked mode? If you took Ranked away, do you think the culture would be different? Of course it would. Once you add a competitive atmosphere to a game, it increases the competitiveness of players overall. Your rating - Silver, Gold, Platinum, Diamond, etc. - comes to define your identity as a player, even when playing unranked games. They&#39;re seen as &quot;not as serious.&quot;

Furthermore, this is a genre that does not reward Ranked play fairly. While one has influence over the outcome of the game, much of the result is beyond one player&#39;s control. Luck plays a role, both in class assignments as well as nighttime results, and the team A vs. team B vs. Neutrals format provides too much variation to reliably assign an ELO. In Chess, the ELO system works very well, as the white and black sides are almost totally evenly matched, and the result of the match is completely dependent upon a single player&#39;s play, and so their resulting ELO gain or loss is the responsibility of the two players alone. Throne of Lies should view the ridiculous, highly variable nature of Town of Salem&#39;s ELO system as a model of how not to structure the game.

I hope that these points resonate with others. Not every game has to be competitive. I&#39;ve put 65+ hours into Throne of Lies so far and have greatly enjoyed the experience. I don&#39;t need an ELO rating to make me feel better about my skills. I would hate to see such a unique, great community devolve into the competitive, self-advancing, toxic environment that is Ranked systems.

Now back to intrigue and lies!
-TinyDeer</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 14:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think this is a great <strong>IDEA</strong>, but it would be terrible in execution. People don’t like grinding especially as terrible classes. All in all this would be more hostile to new players imo</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 14:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lord_monkeystyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Problem is there are lots of “wrong” ways to play, which trigger hostility in game. Particularly for a class like king.</p>
<p>Getting abused just because you’re inexperienced isn’t fun.  And it’s not fun for a savvier court to have to suffer fools who are in over their heads.</p>
<p>Unlocking the more clutch, or complicated classes over time, could be a solution to this pain point.  While providing meaningful progression, and a tangible incentive for better play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 08:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TinyDeer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not a fan of this idea - I love the equalizing nature of the class selection. It feels random and that avoids the development of a “right” way to play the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 07:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lord_monkeystyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>just spit balling here…</p>
<p>What if instead of ranks unlocking more competitive leagues,  ranked play would unlock class spawns?</p>
<p>For example, you would only have a chance to spawn as king, if you’re not a total n00b…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 07:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If we do add Ranked Mode, we definitely can’t use ELO. I don’t really care about its existence besides that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 03:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m just going to take a second to point out that this is currently the forum’s top post if you exclude patch notes, announcements, wiki guides, FoL, and meme threads specifically about likes. So basically, it’s the single-most liked suggestion on the entire forum. I’d say that’s decently indicative of the popularity of this sentiment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TinyDeer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not surprisingly, I agree with the arguments against Ranked. The ToL community is not just good - it’s outstanding compared to other games. One of the <em>features</em> of ToL as it stands is that experienced players mix with new players. That’s a good thing! It helps remove the stigma of being new! I LOVE helping new players get to know the game through explaining their beginner mistakes. That opportunity is something special.</p>
<p>I play multiple games a day and all of them feel competitive, like people are trying their best. Sure, often one person will leave, but it doesn’t meaningfully impact the game for me - the punishment system is really stellar here. And I think it’s <strong>FUN</strong> to have a mix of serious players and people just playing for kicks (not trolls, but to have a good time) because gamethrowers and toxic players are <em>actually punished</em> here. It adds a layer of unpredictability, surprise, and good cheer to have someone unexpectedly have “jailed by a hawt pwince” in their logs instead of only seeing the kind of bland and concise logs that I write as an experienced player ("N1 - Jailed  |  N2 - heal [3], etc.). If everyone was good, the game would be far less interesting. It would feel like a competition and not a game. That being said, I find that 80% of the time, enough people are good that it feels like a balanced match.</p>
<p>I think it’s a <strong>good thing</strong> and a wonderful thing that the community is decent and friendly enough to help newer players get better and to just have fun playing the game. Adding a ‘serious mode’, Veterans or otherwise, would destroy that beautiful feature.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 08:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is, however, a pretty bad way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 01:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly I just want a way to not play with noobs. Anything that can do to accomplish that works in my book. An Elo system isn’t the only way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 23:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also, please, I don’t give a damn about my ToS Elo, but I give a <strong>lot</strong> about having a Ranked mode play like a balanced game that isn’t complete bullshit due to things like the Spy or Amnesiac. Tweaking things to make Ranked balanced is inherently the point of a game with that mode. Arguing otherwise is just asinine.</p>
<p>Other than that one general insult (I struggle to call it a “point”), you’re basically on the right track here relating to ToL tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 23:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please scroll up and read my post.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 23:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="19" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Slow down updates!  Test everything for six months!  Don’t do anything that could threaten my precious, precious numbers!”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Look at the R8 Revolver in CS:GO, that changed everything for all of 48 hours. It launch it had the same base damage as the AWP. Thats my prime example of people not play testing things that could hugely impact the game. Small balance fixes and such is fine, but not huge things that could change balance hugely.</p>
<p>The one thing I don’t like is how you talk down to people who want ranked and like ranked like they are try hard babies</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>Ok so it sounds like if you fix the Elo hell problem then ranked is fine. If such a solution exists would you then be fine with ranked?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It’s not a fixable problem; other games have uselessly torn apart their mechanics and reassembled them in all sorts of ridiculous configurations and have gotten nowhere.  The reason it can’t be fixed is because trying to “fix” it goes against the basic concept of ranks - the whole reason people want ranked is because they want higher ranks to mean something; and that can only be done by (attempting to) dump worse players into lower ELO brackets.  In team games, ELO hell is a <span class="bbcode-i">feature</span> of ranked, not a bug.  The fact that it sucks for almost everyone as a result is unavoidable.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>No shit they will want to control it, if they can control the flow of the game they can win easier, using DbD as an example, if the killer late game can pull off a three gen strat, it becomes nearly impossible without SOMEHOW SAVING A BRAND NEW PART to do one more gen to escape, if the killer can’t control the late game like this the survivors have better odds. (Same goes with Hex:Ruin early game to buy yourself time for the late game)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>My point is that the burning, endless thirst that ranked players have for controlling the game is a <span class="bbcode-i">terrible thing</span>.  Making the game more controlled means taking away strategies and making every game more similar.  Ranked players - in every game that has them, without exception - routinely push for terrible ideas that ought to be ignored; but because catering to ranked shifts the game towards that audience, you end up with that games governed by that obsessive need to control every variable (to have each game be completely predictable and solvable with the same mechanical strategies, again and again.)</p>
<p>Unpredictability is a vital part of the game; once you start encouraging players to fixate on win / loss ratios, you’re setting up a section of your audience that will always be hostile to it and who will want every single game to play out the same boring way.  Ranked players care more about their stupid meaningless numbers than about whether the game is fun or not, and therefore should never, <span class="bbcode-i">ever</span> be given any weight in suggestion or balance discussions.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>If you playtest things cough R8 Revolver cough it wouldn’t be a problem. I don’t mind slow updates if they are quality</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And there you have it.  “Slow down updates!  Test everything for six months!  Don’t do anything that could threaten my precious, <i>precious</i> numbers!”  That mentality is exactly why they should never, ever implement a Ranked mode.  You’re asking for everyone else - regardless of what mode they play, because all modes have to use the same mechanics - to have their updates dramatically slowed so you can maintain your meaningless internet points.</p>
<p>You’re not even trying to hide it - Ranked hasn’t even been implemented yet, it might <i>never</i> get implemented, you’re in a discussion where logically you’d be trying to argue that it wouldn’t cost anyone else anything in order to try and quell some of the objections top it - and instead you’re <i>already</i> demanding that anyone who plays other modes make serious sacrifices so you can maintain your meaningless internet points.</p>
<p>I have a better idea:  They never implement Ranked.  They spend that time improving the game, instead.  Then they roll out new ideas rapidly, and if they don’t work, they roll them back just as rapidly - which they’ll be able to do, in a world where meaningless internet points aren’t a thing and they don’t have hundreds of players obsessed with their ELO breathing down their neck.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>It is if ToL wants to survive, look at ToS it is still alive after many years due to it’s ranked and other game modes. (AND THEIR BS CARDGAMES)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>ToL is doing amazing as-is.  There’s no reason to try and cater to the exact same audience as everyone else, especially an audience as toxic as ranked players.  Additionally, if you’ve actually looked at ToS, they’ve recently devoted almost all their resources to stupid, pointless tinkering with Ranked, all driven by the endless whining of players who don’t care anything about the impact of the things they’re requesting beyond how it influences their meaningless internet points.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>We demand it, as we want to have some stakes in-game. Right now there is none.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>There are no meaningful stakes in any game (outside of the game sucking if your ELO drops too much, which is <i>supposedly</i> not a feature - ha ha ha.)  It’s a game.  The purpose is to have fun.  The only risk is that you might not have fun.  Let go of your obsession with Internet Points and just enjoy it.  You shouldn’t need the game patting you on the back and telling you what an awesome player you are to have fun with a game like this.</p>
<p>Beyond that…  you’re playing the game now, as it is.  So these internet points can’t be as important as you think they are.  If they just hold fast and don’t implement it, maybe people will start to get cured of their obsession with it, and other games can point to this one to show that that sort of ranking isn’t necessary in a game of this nature.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>So TL;DR ranked is necessary for the long life of this game</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It’s doing fine now.  If it starts to nosedive, I suppose they can consider it as a desperation move, but I don’t think that will happen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People who obsess over their ELO are going to want to be able to control as much of each game as possible,</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No shit they will want to control it, if they can control the flow of the game they can win easier, using DbD as an example, if the killer late game can pull off a three gen strat, it becomes nearly impossible without SOMEHOW SAVING A BRAND NEW PART to do one more gen to escape, if the killer can’t control the late game like this the survivors have better odds. (Same goes with Hex:Ruin early game to buy yourself time for the late game)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It splits the player base, leading to longer wait times in every mode.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just look at CS:GO comp and DbD Killer, it exists every where there are more than 1 game mode.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Because people are terrified of losing ELO and falling into low-ELO hell</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s a thing, ELO hell is a thing. Even in DbD It scares the shit out of me if I depip.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>high-ranked play becomes very repetitive and uninteresting - people use the same proven strategies again and again, and anyone who deviates sees the rest of the group rapidly turn against them</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>100% agree here, at high ranks in DbD pallet looping is an epidemic.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It slows new additions and balance changes, since Ranked players will reflexively oppose anything that disrupts the established, stultified modes of play</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you playtest things <em>cough</em> R8 Revolver <em>cough</em> it wouldn’t be a problem. I don’t mind slow updates if they are quality</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ranked play is poisonous</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Low ranked ranked is poisonous due to toxicity and other things</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not necessary</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is if ToL wants to survive, look at ToS it is still alive after many years due to it’s ranked and other game modes. (AND THEIR BS CARDGAMES)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="16" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Players reflexively demand it because they’ve seen it elsewhere</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We demand it, as we want to have some stakes in-game. Right now there is none.</p>
<p>So TL;DR ranked is necessary for the long life of this game</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 18:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok so it sounds like if you fix the Elo hell problem then ranked is fine. If such a solution exists would you then be fine with ranked?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally, I think a Ranked mode is a terrible idea.  The current community is excellent.  Ranked modes in a game like Throne of Lies, meanwhile, lead to lots of problems:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Your success is often not contingent on your own actions, and can vary a lot based on luck (what roles are present, what people do in the first few nights when they have little information, etc.)  This is <span class="bbcode-i">especially</span> true when everyone in the game is low-skill, of course - so this tends to result in something like the Town of Salem “low ELO hell” that anyone can fall into at any time.  At the same time, you still end up with some complete idiots at high ranks, defeating the purpose of a ranked mode.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It distorts the game’s balance.  People who obsess over their ELO are going to want to be able to control as much of each game as possible, even if it reduces strategic depth - look at Town of Salem again, where the Ranked list has steadily had roles removed from it and become more and more generic as the game progressed.  This would be bad enough on its own, but then Ranked players demand that the game’s balance be designed around this crippled Ranked role list, which damages every other mode.  And even if you resist their demands, the game becomes harder to balance with so many different modes and role lists.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It splits the player base, leading to longer wait times in every mode.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Because people are terrified of losing ELO and falling into low-ELO hell, high-ranked play becomes very repetitive and uninteresting - people use the same proven strategies again and again, and anyone who deviates sees the rest of the group rapidly turn against them (which is fatal in a social game.)  Ranked play is strategically <span class="bbcode-i">less</span> interesting due to the constraints it places on experimentation - people decide on what the “proper” way to play the game is and force out everything else.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The obsession with maintaining that number leads players to treat each other more harshly, both within and outside of games.  Additionally, Ranked players themselves feel comfortable expressing open contempt towards other game modes (and, again, will insist that <span class="bbcode-i">only</span> Ranked matters when discussing balance, which is foolish when other modes still make up a huge part of gameplay.)  While moderation can help with this to an extent, there are limits to what it can accomplish when the basic structure of a ranking system pushes players towards toxicity.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It slows new additions and balance changes, since Ranked players will reflexively oppose anything that disrupts the established, stultified modes of play - after all, that’s what got them to where they are, and they’re terrified that a change could dump them into low-ELO hell.  Those few suggestions that do get support will inevitably be ones that make the game more predictable or more boring, since, again, what Ranked players want is not a fun game but one that they can reliably grind to maintain their ranking.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Ranked play is poisonous.  It’s not necessary, it wouldn’t improve the gameplay or strategic depth of the game at any level, it would divide the player base and it makes development painfully difficult going forwards.  Don’t do it.  Players reflexively demand it because they’ve seen it elsewhere, but if you look at Throne of Lies’ gameplay <span class="bbcode-i">right now</span>, in the one mode we have, it is as good as or superior to Ranked play in Town of Salem’s highest levels - which is unsurprising, since everything about Ranked play discourages interesting gameplay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 17:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="14" data-topic="33151" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s also been several months since they have said anything about the feature, which would lead me to hope that it has been rightly dropped, potentially in favor of a system more akin to “Veteran Lobbies”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Unfortunately on the steam forums, I’ve found more statements to the opposite… IE they don’t want to impliment a “veterans mode” because too many modes will divide the player base too much and ranked is intended down the line as the only planned split. trying to find the post but I believe it was a month or 2 ago at the most.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 16:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s also been several months since they have said anything about the feature, which would lead me to hope that it has been rightly dropped, potentially in favor of a system more akin to “Veteran Lobbies”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The devs have repeatedly stated it. They never backed down on these statements later and they are active enough that I would expect them to do so if they changed their mind.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 14:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Source?</p>
<p>As in one from under several months ago.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Comp can be so toxic, (look at CS:GO and OW) so I think you should have to pass a test to play ranked. Like you aren’t a fucking idiot test</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The devs are adding ranked. Get the game now so you won’t be a noob when it comes out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 14:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you read my post? Trust me, although I’d normally agree, Ranked would not work in this game. Rather, we’ll probably get Veteran lobbies or something similar at some point, which will allow you to seek the same improvement but without a lot of the drawbacks Ranked would cause.</p>
<p>Either way, don’t let that be the reason you don’t get Throne of Lies. I have a distinct feeling that, much like myself, you may well find that the game is fun enough on its own to be worth the money. Plus, you’re going to be a newbie no matter when you join. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Community-run tournaments like <a class="mention" href="/u/lunamink">@lunamink</a>’s (which is in under a week btw) can help satiate any hyper-competitiveness you may have, and all in all ToL is a great value proposition for $10 if you already have prior experience and enjoy playing real-time Mafia games (which it sounds like you do).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 11:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think they are adding ranked no matter what.</p>
<p>Just wait, I guess.</p>
<p>I am not really sure.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Trilby" data-post="7" data-topic="33151">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Trilby:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A game without it is basically just a pinball type game you play to kill time</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Are you very sure about it?</p>
<p>You could still improve your skill at there.</p>
<p>The game is about fun, not about competitive.</p>
<p>Isn’t all the game’s goal is that?</p>
<hr>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trilby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m only still holding out from buying this game because it doesn’t have a ranked mode, I was ready to donate to the kickstarter until I saw it wasn’t even planned. Even if this is a better game than ToS, I don’t much care if there is nothing to play for. Town of salem unranked was terrible both before and after they added ranked, and hardly anyone ever took it serious.</p>
<p>I guess ranked doesn’t appeal to everyone, but look at it this way. A game without it is basically just a pinball type game you play to kill time, and a game with it is something worth investing time into improving, learning, mastering, grinding, etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 08:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33151-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151.rss">Please do NOT add a Ranked mode</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
