<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore suggestion] The Retired Inquisitor and the Failed Mercenary</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-retired-inquisitor-and-the-failed-mercenary/71923</link>
    <description>### Mercenary lore:

*Failed contract 1: The Mastermind (Contract died)*

Failed contract 2: The Blue Dragon*

As he wrote down his former clients, he thought to himself what had happened that day. The king approached him and fired him for one reason: hindrance. His only talent was to prevent people from visiting, and that&#39;s it. And most of the time it helps the unseen more.

The mercenary was no more. She sat down with her baby, Lucy, crying.

&quot;Honey, I can&#39;t take this. I failed 2 contracts already.&quot;

&quot;If you want to make it, do what you do best. People need to see your potential.&quot;

Later after feeding her baby the mercenary decides to take a breather. She&#39;s exiled from the castle now, and nobody can get her back in.

&quot;Nobody? Why such dark thoughts?&quot; A hooded figure appeared just behind her.

&quot;Are you The mastermind? You seem familiar.&quot;

The hooded figure lay down his cape. The face was of a beautiful woman and a powerful witch, rolled into one. She seemed abnormal.

&quot;Don&#39;t be a fool. I&#39;m giving you a chance again.&quot; What could this person possibly want? &quot;I&#39;m giving you a chance to be you. To do what you do best; to hinder.&quot;

&quot;Will this contract expire after a few weeks?&quot;

&quot;We shall see...&quot;

The mercenary gave a slight glimmer of hope Finally she can make enough money to support her family.

### The Inqusitor

&quot;Age is a powerful thing. It can turn tides of battle, it can be a powerful weapon if you can use it right.&quot; - Rasmodius, Grand Wizard of Adiart

The Inqusitor was getting old. The hunt for the Sorcerer was endless. It was almost time to retire from the church.

&quot;Don&#39;t tell me you&#39;re going on another chase, we need your help.&quot; His bishop complained.

&quot;I can&#39;t chase this sorcerer anymore. The least I can do now is make people believe.&quot;

&quot;So you shall. Your effort to the church is valuable.&quot;

The Inqusitor grinned sinisterly.

--------------------

When he reached the castle, he saw his former nemesis. He appeared to have new spells, in ways which he couldn&#39;t comprehend.

That wasn&#39;t his era anymore. That wasn&#39;t his mission. Let the Blue Dragon kill the sorcerer on their own. He needs to recruit more followers of the church.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 22:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-retired-inquisitor-and-the-failed-mercenary/71923.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] The Retired Inquisitor and the Failed Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Planterror]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h3>Mercenary lore:</h3>
<p><em>Failed contract 1: The Mastermind (Contract died)</em></p>
<p>Failed contract 2: The Blue Dragon*</p>
<p>As he wrote down his former clients, he thought to himself what had happened that day. The king approached him and fired him for one reason: hindrance. His only talent was to prevent people from visiting, and that’s it. And most of the time it helps the unseen more.</p>
<p>The mercenary was no more. She sat down with her baby, Lucy, crying.</p>
<p>“Honey, I can’t take this. I failed 2 contracts already.”</p>
<p>“If you want to make it, do what you do best. People need to see your potential.”</p>
<p>Later after feeding her baby the mercenary decides to take a breather. She’s exiled from the castle now, and nobody can get her back in.</p>
<p>“Nobody? Why such dark thoughts?” A hooded figure appeared just behind her.</p>
<p>“Are you The mastermind? You seem familiar.”</p>
<p>The hooded figure lay down his cape. The face was of a beautiful woman and a powerful witch, rolled into one. She seemed abnormal.</p>
<p>“Don’t be a fool. I’m giving you a chance again.” What could this person possibly want? “I’m giving you a chance to be you. To do what you do best; to hinder.”</p>
<p>“Will this contract expire after a few weeks?”</p>
<p>“We shall see…”</p>
<p>The mercenary gave a slight glimmer of hope Finally she can make enough money to support her family.</p>
<h3>The Inqusitor</h3>
<p>“Age is a powerful thing. It can turn tides of battle, it can be a powerful weapon if you can use it right.” - Rasmodius, Grand Wizard of Adiart</p>
<p>The Inqusitor was getting old. The hunt for the Sorcerer was endless. It was almost time to retire from the church.</p>
<p>“Don’t tell me you’re going on another chase, we need your help.” His bishop complained.</p>
<p>“I can’t chase this sorcerer anymore. The least I can do now is make people believe.”</p>
<p>“So you shall. Your effort to the church is valuable.”</p>
<p>The Inqusitor grinned sinisterly.</p>
<hr>
<p>When he reached the castle, he saw his former nemesis. He appeared to have new spells, in ways which he couldn’t comprehend.</p>
<p>That wasn’t his era anymore. That wasn’t his mission. Let the Blue Dragon kill the sorcerer on their own. He needs to recruit more followers of the church.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-retired-inquisitor-and-the-failed-mercenary/71923/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-retired-inquisitor-and-the-failed-mercenary/71923/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 13:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71923-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-retired-inquisitor-and-the-failed-mercenary/71923.rss">[Lore suggestion] The Retired Inquisitor and the Failed Mercenary</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
