<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Bloodletter</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238</link>
    <description>
Class: killer/cult or could be social/cult because he distracts everyone and does not kill anyone himself.

This class has a 25% chance as a starting class with the cult leader and has a 50% chance to be converted from any class type, with 1 max being on cult at any time. 

Day Ability 1:
Martyrdom - 1 use - if Set up/ For the Fall is successful and the target is hung, sacrifice yourself and your god will smite 1 random BD/Neutral class. Also grant your cult leader 1 extra use of eradicate. 

Day Ability 2 (Optional):
None

Night Ability 1:
Set Up - 1 use - pick one target and create multiple blood remnants that will act as the target for one night. Whenever For the Fall is triggered.

Night Ability 2 (Optional)
For The Fall - 1 use - all remnants will visit all remaining players (including king) as the targeted character to disrupt one night of information. If Set Up&#39;s target is hung the next day then martyrdom is granted. 

Lore:
The cult are ever infatuated with blood. And Mithras grants them powers through their worship. Some are so lost to his power that their only mission is to give everything they are just the see the gods grace. That&#39;s has been stories told of the god even showing himself to thoes willing to follow his law. 

Comments:
Some interactions I wanted to touch on. 1 uses for all of his abilities  keeps him from breaking the game obviously and multiple nights of disruption is op.op. 
The way For The Fall works if there are 10 people alive then 10 remnants each visit 1 person and show up as visitors. (Example: If Set Up was used on 11 and then for the fall was used. It would show up on any observer/will o wisp as visiting whoever their watching. If An observer or princess scout more then one remnant only 1 will show up as to help disguise the cult at nighttime, because they would know right away that this ability was used if 3 of the same person showed up. Thoes immune to occupy will be immune to the affects.  The goal is to get the target Set Up was used on to get hung then that same day martyrdom is earned and can be used. 

If the stars align and Set Up and For The Fall are successful and the target gets hung martyrdom is earned because of tricky it is to succeed mithras is so impressed that when martyrdom is used he will call out in red to the while table (like the old crier ability)  and he says somthing like &quot; The Blood.... it runs in everything, and soon you shall know my name&quot; the Blood God sacrifices the bloodletter in brutal fashion and uses his life force to kill a random Bd/Neutral member.

 Now martyrdom&#39;s kill power im not sure how strong it should be. Should it bypass all immunity (including reaper and hunter traps) or have the chance that it can be healed but bypasses any protections. If it does not kill then they could bleed instead? I&#39;m not too sure how strong this should be. 

But I made this character because I saw cult did not have a lot of characters and I really liked their lore around a blood god. Also the other cult members more or less confuse members and support the cult leader while this character (should be unique) is able to make a connection with the Blood God on his own. 

It&#39;s also like a scorned, they can set up the target &quot;frame&quot; in hopes to get him hind the next day. This will most likely be powerful in the early game because that is when everyone is alive and as the game goes on then it&#39;s less likely to succeed as more BD die.

Let me.know what you think!

Edit: spelling and more explanation
Edit2: added another stipulation for when it spawns</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 15:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Bloodletter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandy_Claws]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Edit for spelling</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 15:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8238-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238.rss">[Class Suggestion] Bloodletter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Bloodletter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandy_Claws]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Class: killer/cult or could be social/cult because he distracts everyone and does not kill anyone himself.</p>
<p>This class has a 25% chance as a starting class with the cult leader and has a 50% chance to be converted from any class type, with 1 max being on cult at any time.</p>
<p>Day Ability 1:<br>
Martyrdom - 1 use - if Set up/ For the Fall is successful and the target is hung, sacrifice yourself and your god will smite 1 random BD/Neutral class. Also grant your cult leader 1 extra use of eradicate.</p>
<p>Day Ability 2 (Optional):<br>
None</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
Set Up - 1 use - pick one target and create multiple blood remnants that will act as the target for one night. Whenever For the Fall is triggered.</p>
<p>Night Ability 2 (Optional)<br>
For The Fall - 1 use - all remnants will visit all remaining players (including king) as the targeted character to disrupt one night of information. If Set Up’s target is hung the next day then martyrdom is granted.</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
The cult are ever infatuated with blood. And Mithras grants them powers through their worship. Some are so lost to his power that their only mission is to give everything they are just the see the gods grace. That’s has been stories told of the god even showing himself to thoes willing to follow his law.</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
Some interactions I wanted to touch on. 1 uses for all of his abilities  keeps him from breaking the game obviously and multiple nights of disruption is op.op.<br>
The way For The Fall works if there are 10 people alive then 10 remnants each visit 1 person and show up as visitors. (Example: If Set Up was used on 11 and then for the fall was used. It would show up on any observer/will o wisp as visiting whoever their watching. If An observer or princess scout more then one remnant only 1 will show up as to help disguise the cult at nighttime, because they would know right away that this ability was used if 3 of the same person showed up. Thoes immune to occupy will be immune to the affects.  The goal is to get the target Set Up was used on to get hung then that same day martyrdom is earned and can be used.</p>
<p>If the stars align and Set Up and For The Fall are successful and the target gets hung martyrdom is earned because of tricky it is to succeed mithras is so impressed that when martyrdom is used he will call out in red to the while table (like the old crier ability)  and he says somthing like " The Blood… it runs in everything, and soon you shall know my name" the Blood God sacrifices the bloodletter in brutal fashion and uses his life force to kill a random Bd/Neutral member.</p>
<p>Now martyrdom’s kill power im not sure how strong it should be. Should it bypass all immunity (including reaper and hunter traps) or have the chance that it can be healed but bypasses any protections. If it does not kill then they could bleed instead? I’m not too sure how strong this should be.</p>
<p>But I made this character because I saw cult did not have a lot of characters and I really liked their lore around a blood god. Also the other cult members more or less confuse members and support the cult leader while this character (should be unique) is able to make a connection with the Blood God on his own.</p>
<p>It’s also like a scorned, they can set up the target “frame” in hopes to get him hind the next day. This will most likely be powerful in the early game because that is when everyone is alive and as the game goes on then it’s less likely to succeed as more BD die.</p>
<p>Let me.know what you think!</p>
<p>Edit: spelling and more explanation<br>
Edit2: added another stipulation for when it spawns</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8238-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-bloodletter/8238.rss">[Class Suggestion] Bloodletter</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
