<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902</link>
    <description>If you know anything about me, you know that I like megathreads. So, I figured it was time to update my old megathread, what with it having been three months and us having a new main balancer. Here&#39;s what I&#39;ve got:

&gt;# General
&gt;Occupying classes no longer see if their target was immune. This makes them too investigative.
&gt;
&gt;[url=https://forum.imperium42.com/t/how-to-fix-all-of-our-issues/47584?u=orangeandblack5]In general, minimize notifications and make the ones you do get as generic as possible.[/url]
---
&gt;# King
&gt;Remove Allies from the Good King. This ability focuses the gameplay on the King a bit *too* strongly, and leads to everybody blindly following the King instead of playing the game.
&gt;
&gt;[url=https://forum.imperium42.com/t/king-rework-orangeandblack5-edition/40698]Here is my personal suggestion of what the King should be.[/url] It involves some drastic changes, especially to Royal Finger, but ultimately I feel it would be more fun to play as and more fun to play against. Plus, it&#39;s still plenty strong, and its inherent double-vote allow it to act as a strong leader.
---
&gt;# Assassin
&gt;Nightshade is replaced with Hidden Blade, which now makes its target bleed instead of being poisoned. This prevents poisoning from immediately revealing the faction and allows Assassin to fake-claim Hunter.
---
&gt;# Herbalist
&gt;Is now a Social (or Support) class. Don&#39;t let it just be instantly found by Princess.
---
&gt;# Scorned
&gt; New wincon: &quot;See three Blue Dragon executed during the day, or live to see the Blue Dragon lose.&quot; This allows the Scorned to act as both an aversion to blindly following investigative claims while also giving them a fallback wincon (the issue when it was just to see BD executed was that it was too hard - this will allow them to act for both new winconditions at once).
---
&gt;# Inquisitor
&gt;Change &quot;Nobody Expects the Spanish Inquisition&quot; to &quot;Unexpected&quot; - an absolutely great reference, but it could stand to be a little less ham-fisted lol
---
&gt;# Sorcerer
&gt;Bomb Swap can now be used in addition to Walking Bomb. Bomb Swap uses reduced to 3. Makes bombs a bit more consistent, useful because Sorcerer is currently the weakest apparently.
---
&gt;# Hunter
&gt;Wolf Companion is now a day ability.
&gt;
&gt;Add a new passive, Food Supply, that prevents you from using Wolf Companion on the day after you used Bear Companion and prevents you from using Bear Companion the night after you used Wolf Companion.
&gt;
&gt;Remove Retribution.
&gt;
&gt;Make Hunter non-Unique.
&gt;
&gt;Not strictly necessary, but I&#39;d really prefer a weaker Hunter than can appear in games more often, and isn&#39;t instantly a &quot;vote each other&quot; if somebody fake-claims it with a real one in the game.
---
&gt;# Poacher
&gt;Now has Rabid Wolves, a day ability that acts exactly like Hunter&#39;s Wolf Companion. The second use requires and expends a use of Assassin&#39;s Nightshade/Hidden Blade.
&gt;
&gt;Snare Trap now prevents their target from visiting anybody on the night it is used, regardless of immunities, but may only be used on any individual player one time. Now has four uses.
&gt;
&gt;Spike Traps now has two uses.
&gt;
&gt;Currently Poacher really lacks its own identity. I feel these changes would help bring it into its own. Additionally, as a Timesnatcher gives the Unseen an extra kill, it only makes sense to add somebody that gives them an extra bleed.
---
&gt;# Sheriff and Paladin
&gt;These next few require a lot of work, and are hotly contested, but I personally feel that the game would benefit from the increased variety.
&gt;
&gt;Make Paladin unconvertible.
&gt;
&gt;Make Paladin unique.
&gt;
&gt;Make Paladin Special instead of Investigative.
&gt;
&gt;Balance from here, allowing the Unseen to convert their Sheriffs but making the Cult work around the singular Paladin. As long as the Paladin is somewhat hard to confirm, this should work just fine and be more varied and interesting. Is this necessary? No. I just think it would be cool.
---
&gt;# Alchemist
&gt;Truth Potion is removed. You can replace it if you want, but I&#39;m still not a fan of a Neutral that can make itself immune also acting as an investigator. It&#39;s similar to why I dislike Allies, but on a much smaller scale.
---
&gt;# Possessor
&gt;Reduce Mind Control uses to two.
&gt;
&gt;Blackened Shield no longer protects against kills made by members of the Blue Dragon.
&gt;
&gt;Puppet Strings no longer lets you read whispers to the person you controlled.
&gt;
&gt;Recent stats show that Possessor is *way* too strong. Three small nerfs (against whispers, against Knights, and against late-game vote control) should help bring it more in line with the other NKs.
---
&gt;# Sellsword
&gt;Now has a new passive, &quot;Undercover&quot;, which automatically redirects any attempt made by the Unseen, Cult, or NK to kill the Sellsword to the Sellsword&#39;s target. This will not activate if the Sellsword&#39;s target is not a member of the Blue Dragon. It will also not activate if the kill attempt on the Sellsword is made by a member of the Blue Dragon or a non-NK neutral class.
&gt;
&gt;Now has a new day ability, &quot;Bribery&quot;, which allows its night abilities to work through occupation immunity the following night. Two uses.
&gt;
&gt;Must now survive to win. Or maybe not. I don&#39;t particularly care on this point.
&gt;
&gt;Somehow Sellsword actually *raises* the BD winrate by being in the game. It is possible that this is due to the spawning algorithm giving the BD more/better classes if a Sellsword is spawned. If that is not the case, it needs a buff - I suggest making the scum attacking it much less likely to waste their kill, and giving it a bit more utility against occupy-immune classes.
---
&gt;# Cult
&gt;Honestly I&#39;m no expet on Cult balance at the moment. But if I remember correctly one convert (Ritualist?) was objectively the best. So buff the rest! (I&#39;m open to other suggestions)
---
&gt;# Invoker
&gt;Add a new single-use day ability, &quot;Enrage&quot;, which allows your night abilities to pierce immunites the night after it is used.
---
&gt;# Seeker
&gt;Gaze now returns target&#39;s faction alongside their class type.
---
&gt;# Princess
&gt;Will-O-Wisp is now a day ability that tells you if your target killed anybody at the end of the next night. Should make the ability less relatively useless (Flirt is better in almost every single case).
---
&gt;# Duchess
&gt;Dark Wisp is now a day ability, and to prevent overlap with the Timesnatcher, it now tells you the name of the next non-Unseen player to use a day ability.
---
&gt;# Observer
&gt;Follow re-split into Watch (see who visits your target) and Follow (see who your target visits).
&gt;
&gt;Window Peek is changed into a day ability, but is dropped to only one use. You are given results at the *start* of the next night.
&gt;
&gt;These should help bring Observer more in line with Maid and Princess, while Window Peek&#39;s huge buff prevents it from becoming too weak.
---
&gt;# Nightwatch
&gt; Watch Carefully is changed to a one-use day ability, to match the change to Observer. You are given results immediately.
&gt;
&gt;Follow is renamed to &quot;Stalk&quot;, but is otherwise unchanged. (It still gives visits and visitors)
---
&gt;# Maid
&gt; New day ability, name to be determined, that is only available to be used on Day 1 but allows you to control who your first sample for Matchmake is (replacing the current random one).
&gt;
&gt;New day ability, name to be determined, that is only available from Day 2 and on, that selects a new target to be your baseline comparison. One use.
&gt;
&gt;Nosy Servants is removed.
&gt;
&gt;This cuts an almost entirely useless ability (Nosy Servants) and places a bigger focus and a bit more control over your matchmaking, without significantly changing Maid&#39;s power and role.
---
&gt;# Handmaiden
&gt;Prying servants now shows all players to ever visit the target, not just those who visited on the night of their death. This gives a bit more power to an otherwise weaker convert.
---
&gt;# New Blue Dragon Roles
&gt;Currently, there are a lot of BD Investigatives, and a decent number of Supports, but if you exclude Prince there&#39;s only two each of BD Social, Killer, and Offensive. I suggest we add a new role to each of these categories to help spice up the game. Some of my own ideas are below.
&gt;
&gt;**Killer:** https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-the-ranger-and-the-bandit/73903?u=orangeandblack5
&gt;
&gt;**Offensive:** https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-the-gladiator-and-the-renegade/73905?u=orangeandblack5
&gt;
&gt;**Social:** https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-the-priest-and-the-heretic-v2/73904?u=orangeandblack5
---
&gt;# More coming soon!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 20:42:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="60" data-topic="73902">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And that wasn’t good moreso because of the mechanics of the Unseen than because unconvertible investigatives are inherently bad</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But that is true.  The only BD that should be unconvertable(aside from abilities that give a temporary conversion immunity) is Prince.  There are enough unconvertables already.  Plus this just results in easy confirmability, especially since you’re also making it unique.  The best counter for confirmability is conversion.<br>
Paladin won’t be mechanically confirmable, but it will have a prince effect where people are unlikely to fakeclaim it.  The major problem with an unconvertable unique sheriff was that it was impossible to fakeclaim.  And don’t say you can suicide to eliminate them.  The only good thing about an unique paladin is that it’s an indirect nerf to smite, which is overpowered and needs a rework.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="64" data-topic="73902">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>While that is fair, the replaceable nature of the Cult means that they can more easily CC a Paladin claim.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But what if you get voted up before the Pally?  Or they confirm themselves before you out?  And remember the unconvertable unique sheriff.  Assassin was replaceable, yet I didn’t see assassins claiming sheriff to kill the real sheriff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/70</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 20:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-70</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="64" data-topic="73902">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>While you’re here, do you mind commenting on the threads for each of my class suggestions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol, for the most part I don’t do classes themselves, beyond skimming in and going “nope that better not happen” <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> , usually I’m more focused on remakes, which I do say I like all of yours so far on this, the pali one is my one major hold out (I think failed conversions are a huge screw over for cult, as effectively a failed convert is both a failed convert, and a delayed kill, bottom line nothing sucks more than the start of day 3 and realizing that your side hasn’t accomplished ANYTHING. IE 0 kills, 0 converts.</p>
<p>Let me take a look at some of the classes though lol guess that would be more appropriate in their own thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/69</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 18:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-69</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Except I don’t want to attempt that when the initial change is so drastic</p>
<p>Probably you’d replace any conversion blocking from Smite with just a kill of some sort but idek</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/68</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-68</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="66" data-topic="73902">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Balance from here</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>do that</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/67</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-67</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok</p>
<blockquote>
<h1>Sheriff and Paladin</h1>
<p>These next few require a lot of work, and are hotly contested, but I personally feel that the game would benefit from the increased variety.</p>
<p>Make Paladin unconvertible.</p>
<p>Make Paladin unique.</p>
<p>Make Paladin Special instead of Investigative.</p>
<p>Balance from here, allowing the Unseen to convert their Sheriffs but making the Cult work around the singular Paladin. As long as the Paladin is somewhat hard to confirm, this should work just fine and be more varied and interesting. Is this necessary? No. I just think it would be cool.</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/66</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-66</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I want to see your paladin suggestion</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/65</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-65</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While that is fair, the replaceable nature of the Cult means that they can more easily CC a Paladin claim. Making sure Paladin cannot prevent conversions seems like the best way to minimize this issue.</p>
<p>While you’re here, do you mind commenting on the threads for each of my class suggestions? I want to make sure they’re good, as I don’t really <em>do</em> classes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/64</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-64</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Vandalay" data-post="62" data-topic="73902">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/vandalay/40/1393_2.png" class="avatar"> Vandalay:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hypothetical scenerio here. Unseen fails to convert n1, n2, finally nails it on n3. assuming they didn’t get caught, this unseen is at the same power as one that managed to convert on n1.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>not when I’m playing it. The Unseen is 2 kills ahead if I’m in the Unseen (assuming a N1 convert)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/63</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-63</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>honestly though I’d have to say it’s possibly more problematic on cult than unseen.</p>
<p>Hypothetical scenerio here. Unseen fails to convert n1, n2, finally nails it on n3. assuming they didn’t get caught, this unseen is at the same power as one that managed to convert on n1.</p>
<p>Cult… fails to convert n1. They have to either give up both of their kills N2. or retry, they chose to not use their kills on n2… and fail again, then say that succeeds on n3…, effectively they are out 4 kill attempts and they are 1 member short of where they’d have been had they converted on n1. Cult was hands down worse to play IMO during the "oh crap why the heck is everything unconvertable, part of the game (back when priest existed and was unconv, and CW had 2 targets)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/62</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-62</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What’s your idea specifically?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/61</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-61</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shrimpy" data-post="59" data-topic="73902">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shrimpy/40/15828_2.png" class="avatar"> Shrimpy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I strongly oppose making Paladin unconvertable however. We’ve been there with the with Sheriff. Terrible idea, as bad as Allies.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Except we haven’t really</p>
<p>Either both were convertible, or just Sheriff wasn’t</p>
<p>And that wasn’t good moreso because of the mechanics of the Unseen than because unconvertible investigatives are inherently bad</p>
<p>And when we had a single Paladin it was <em>really</em> overpowered</p>
<p>So there is definitely a yet-unexplored middle ground that I would very much like to find.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/60</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-60</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In general I like your suggestions.  I strongly oppose making Paladin unconvertable however.  We’ve been there with the unconvertable Sheriff.  Terrible idea, as bad as Allies.</p>
<p>Regarding Hunter, I would also like to eliminate the “hunters vote each other” meta.  But I definitely don’t support removing Retribution, it’s just too fun.  What I would support is some sort of nerf to it.  Like perhaps making it a limited-use (single-use?) passive that you have to manually activate.  This way there is more counterplay:  Assassin could, for instance, distract Hunter before voting him up so that he doesn’t get arrowed.  Or bait Hunter into wasting Retribution, then vote up Hunter the next day.</p>
<p>I don’t see a problem with Alchemist truth potion.  I think it’s a worse idea to let Observer keep it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/59</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-59</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I don’t particularly care about that one tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/58</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-58</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also ss surviving is bad you silly man</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/57</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 09:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-57</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Paladin and Sheriff should be reworked.<br>
Paladin into a new killer class.<br>
Sheriff has a unseen and cult finder</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/56</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 09:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-56</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Change probe back to the meat</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/55</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 06:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-55</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="1" data-topic="73902">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Change “Nobody Expects the Spanish Inquisition” to “Unexpected” - an absolutely great reference, but it could stand to be a little less ham-fisted lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>NETSI is the best named ability or passive Orange. Many people including me would be much aggrieved if it was changed</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/54</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 06:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-54</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Isn’t that a game where there’s a fire and a dude working on something there’s a cave…summer job? I have vague memories I think</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/53</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-53</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>then it’s renamed to Firewatch and is a great game :^)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/52</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-52</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yes</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/51</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 02:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-51</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good change right?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/50</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 02:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-50</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ok</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/49</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 02:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-49</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nightwatch is named to daywatch</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/48</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 02:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-48</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But <strong>Night</strong>watch</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 02:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-47</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just Some (More) Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bam</p>
<p>Observer gets results at night</p>
<p>Nightwatch gets them immediately</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902/46</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 02:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73902-46</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-some-more-ideas/73902.rss">Just Some (More) Ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
