<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Offline friends showing, hundreds of times</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/offline-friends-showing-hundreds-of-times/73653</link>
    <description>#### What happened?

Login and the friends list shows me all my offline friends. OK... However, it&#39;s showing me each friend dozens upon dozens of time, causing my client to completely freeze. I cannot interact with it for up to 30 seconds at a time, and only gives me a short, few second window to click anything in between freezes. While this is happening, dozens upon dozens of more duplicated offline friends appear. Game is unplayable as it can take me up to 15 minutes to try to join a lobby depending on how focused i am on sitting there and spam clicking &#39;Connect&#39;

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?

Log in, don&#39;t see hundreds of the same person offline and my client shouldn&#39;t be frozen.

#### Steps to reproduce:

1. Be me
2. Login
3. Get rekt
4. ?????
5. repeat

#### Comments:

Things I&#39;ve done:

1. Verify integrity of game files
2. Reinstall
3. Update all drivers
4. Try it on my other CPU (same issue)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:15:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/offline-friends-showing-hundreds-of-times/73653.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Offline friends showing, hundreds of times</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elemfao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>Login and the friends list shows me all my offline friends. OK… However, it’s showing me each friend dozens upon dozens of time, causing my client to completely freeze. I cannot interact with it for up to 30 seconds at a time, and only gives me a short, few second window to click anything in between freezes. While this is happening, dozens upon dozens of more duplicated offline friends appear. Game is unplayable as it can take me up to 15 minutes to try to join a lobby depending on how focused i am on sitting there and spam clicking ‘Connect’</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>Log in, don’t see hundreds of the same person offline and my client shouldn’t be frozen.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<ol>
<li>Be me</li>
<li>Login</li>
<li>Get rekt</li>
<li>???</li>
<li>repeat</li>
</ol>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>Things I’ve done:</p>
<ol>
<li>Verify integrity of game files</li>
<li>Reinstall</li>
<li>Update all drivers</li>
<li>Try it on my other CPU (same issue)</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/offline-friends-showing-hundreds-of-times/73653/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/offline-friends-showing-hundreds-of-times/73653/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73653-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/offline-friends-showing-hundreds-of-times/73653.rss">Offline friends showing, hundreds of times</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
