<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Making Cult Leader Stronger</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432</link>
    <description>I still think the cult is underpowered the revamp did make them stronger, however, the black rose is still stronger in every way the only thing cult has over the black rose is that each member can become the cult leader

I had a few ideas to change the cult up and will explain my reasoning 
1, * Unlimited Uses, but 1-day cooldown. I suggest you remove the day 1 cooldown. the cult leader has both the job of killing and converting and if the cult starts with 2 members, the leader and another. at night 2 they will have 3 members but will 1 will die making their total 2. 

if they could also convert night 2 they will have 4 members and convert is like killing only you get help. they will die later of course and it may be pointless
removing the day 1 cooldown would change the cults play style making it more different than the black rose. it will also help them deal with the losses from killing their own members and other killers like the paladin. without this, they are a glass cannon that shatters easily

2, make it that when the cult leader kills a cult member to kill someone he can choose anyone even himself. this will let the cult kill off members who are suspicious. of course, the cult can&#39;t bypass immune so they may just waste a life for nothing

sometimes killing your newest member when he is your best hope will not always work out</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:14:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Making Cult Leader Stronger</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ellie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>2 is already a thing. We made that clear when we made the announcement, except he can’t target himself.<br>
1 isn’t going to happen. It would be too hard to defeat the Cult if they can replenish their numbers every night. You’d have to kill 1 at night and 1 during the day just to get them down 1 member. We’ll see how things go in the alpha, and if the Cult is really weak, we will make adjustments.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-432-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432.rss">Making Cult Leader Stronger</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making Cult Leader Stronger</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I still think the cult is underpowered the revamp did make them stronger, however, the black rose is still stronger in every way the only thing cult has over the black rose is that each member can become the cult leader</p>
<p>I had a few ideas to change the cult up and will explain my reasoning<br>
1, * Unlimited Uses, but 1-day cooldown. I suggest you remove the day 1 cooldown. the cult leader has both the job of killing and converting and if the cult starts with 2 members, the leader and another. at night 2 they will have 3 members but will 1 will die making their total 2.</p>
<p>if they could also convert night 2 they will have 4 members and convert is like killing only you get help. they will die later of course and it may be pointless<br>
removing the day 1 cooldown would change the cults play style making it more different than the black rose. it will also help them deal with the losses from killing their own members and other killers like the paladin. without this, they are a glass cannon that shatters easily</p>
<p>2, make it that when the cult leader kills a cult member to kill someone he can choose anyone even himself. this will let the cult kill off members who are suspicious. of course, the cult can’t bypass immune so they may just waste a life for nothing</p>
<p>sometimes killing your newest member when he is your best hope will not always work out</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 04:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-432-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/making-cult-leader-stronger/432.rss">Making Cult Leader Stronger</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
