<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Night of the Sorcerer</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931</link>
    <description>In the darkest corners of Adiart there are stories of a mysterious wanderer. The legend says it&#39;s a young women that is wise beyond her years. However, everyone agrees on one thing, this “Sorcerer” needs to be found and stopped from killing more subjects of The Court. 

No one is sure why she went on a killing spree, but the whispers between some of the servants of the court echo that the mentor of the Sorcerer was once a Wizard of the Court and after many years of service the royal court of the Blue Dragon has accused him of betraying them for the vile Unseen. 

The Sorcerer watched as the only inspiring  figure in her life was cut down by a wild mob throwing around accusations. After the Sorcerer witnessed this act of violence she quietly, “No More.” 

She rushed back to the Court Wizard&#39;s room, picking up anything that could aid in her quest to end the Blue Dragon and avenge her mentor. She picked up Magic Dust, an old cloak that made her nearly invisible, a few ancient books containing the forbidden spells, and a very old staff to channel her spellcasting. 

To this day it is said to not travel alone in Adiart, especially if you were a part of the mob that pronounced the Court Wizard guilty, for many witnesses of that execution have found their demise at night, struck by a blinding flash of purple energy. 

Some say that the Sorcerer is a figure of change merely seeking vengeance, others say that she is a ruthless killer that deserves to be cut down along with the Unseen and their allies, but the truth is up to you to decide...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 15:34:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Night of the Sorcerer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thunder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good stuff Ace. I really like the idea of the Sorcerer learning from the CW and corrupting his items to her uses, especially since she is a resurrected character.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 15:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68931-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Night of the Sorcerer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Night of the Sorcerer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Silent_Ace1778]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In the darkest corners of Adiart there are stories of a mysterious wanderer. The legend says it’s a young women that is wise beyond her years. However, everyone agrees on one thing, this “Sorcerer” needs to be found and stopped from killing more subjects of The Court.</p>
<p>No one is sure why she went on a killing spree, but the whispers between some of the servants of the court echo that the mentor of the Sorcerer was once a Wizard of the Court and after many years of service the royal court of the Blue Dragon has accused him of betraying them for the vile Unseen.</p>
<p>The Sorcerer watched as the only inspiring  figure in her life was cut down by a wild mob throwing around accusations. After the Sorcerer witnessed this act of violence she quietly, “No More.”</p>
<p>She rushed back to the Court Wizard’s room, picking up anything that could aid in her quest to end the Blue Dragon and avenge her mentor. She picked up Magic Dust, an old cloak that made her nearly invisible, a few ancient books containing the forbidden spells, and a very old staff to channel her spellcasting.</p>
<p>To this day it is said to not travel alone in Adiart, especially if you were a part of the mob that pronounced the Court Wizard guilty, for many witnesses of that execution have found their demise at night, struck by a blinding flash of purple energy.</p>
<p>Some say that the Sorcerer is a figure of change merely seeking vengeance, others say that she is a ruthless killer that deserves to be cut down along with the Unseen and their allies, but the truth is up to you to decide…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 14:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68931-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-night-of-the-sorcerer/68931.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Night of the Sorcerer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
