<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818</link>
    <description>I&#39;m new to this, so I apologize if I&#39;m stepping on toes or if this clashes with existing lore:

With the curtains drawn, just a sliver of light broke through and came to rest on the altar at the head of the chapel. The Priest spoke the final words of his sermon to the silent room.

“May God watch over the noblemen and women of Castle Adiart and protect those who are brave enough to defend our walls, both from the inside and out.”

He made the sign of the cross with his right hand, closed his eyes and hung his head in silent prayer. In the past, his parishioners flocked to the church in such times of strife. Now, the old wooden pews sat empty and the offertory collected nothing but dust.

The sound of the door creaking open brought light to the gray haired man, but he could see only despair on the face of the young Paladin through the dark haze of the room. 

“High Priest, I come to you for strength and wisdom. Darkness is spreading over our land, and I fear that tonight it will strike at the heart of Castle Adiart. I will give my life to protect the King, but there is only so much that one man can do to hold back the great strength of this Cult that worships Blood and Darkness. The royal family is in grave danger.

“Why has God forsaken this land?”

“God has only forsaken those who choose not to praise Him alone,” said The Priest. “Do not think because the light shines meekly on this altar that He cannot quickly throw back the curtain and cleanse those who dare speak his name in vain. 

“You are never alone as long as the word of our Lord rings true in your heart. His protection is all that our royal family needs, and it is through the strength of his servants that he projects his might over the land.

“Go quietly from this place of worship, my son. I can feel the Powers of the Lord on your side. It is forever your ally. The royal family will not be dragged to their graves so lightly.”

-------

Inside of his chambers, the Priest fell to his knees and poured out a chalice of wine in front of him. 

“Lord, heed this prayer. Agents of evil strike swiftly at our heels, but the night is always darkest just before the light.  Bind the Soul of our young and noble Prince to this goblet, and spare him from the clenches of the Cultists who seek to dethrone our great and noble King on this cursed night.”


-------

The next morning, The Priest rose sharply from his bed. The foul stench of death hung in the air, and he rushed to the main hall. Upon seeing the King sat sturdily on his throne with his son by his side, the Priest was greatly relieved. It must be the blood of the Cult Leader that was spilled in the dark of night.

“Good morning, merciful King. A great terror struck me in my chambers, but I am glad to see the Royal Family has not suffered injury. Can you raise the young Paladin? I have many things to discuss with him.”

“The Paladin, you say? Have you not heard the grave news? The secretive Leader of the Cult eradicated him last night. We found him lying in a pool of blood, punctured with a jagged edge.

“I have little faith in a Priest who cannot feel when the blood of the innocent has been spilled inside the walls of Castle Adiart. Has God truly forsaken this place?

&quot;When my forefathers received their divine mandate, they had no need for Knights or Paladins to protect them. The clergy were all that they needed. 

&quot;I have long wondered if God has left these lands behind. Perhaps a stronger hand is needed in these troubled times… or perhaps the prayers coming from the castle walls are lacking in divine passion. 

&quot;I think you should pray for the people of this land, Priest. Pray for strength. Pray for Unity. Pray for Light. Pray that a new herald to the Lord is not necessary.&quot;

-------

Sleep eluded the Priest that night. He prayed for it to come, but the voices in his head grew more intense as each hour passed.

&quot;I pray to thee, my Lord. Bring silence and calm to my thoughts, and when I wake let the light shine through the heavy curtains of Castle Adiart and flush out the darkness. Manifest the protection for my people that they deserve. We have always served you, my Lord. Repay our faith in kind.&quot;

But the voices did not stop. The Priest could feel their pain, though he could not hear their words.

&quot;I will pray for you all,&quot; he said. &quot;Please let me rest on this night.&quot;

&quot;No sleep,&quot; he heard. &quot;Come to us.&quot;

The Priest&#39;s face drained of blood and his skin matched the pale moonlight that bled into his room. He dared to peak out his chamber’s window and looked upon the graveyard. The ghostly apparitions that always hung faintly in the air circled around a central figure.

&quot;I will pray for you all,&quot; he said once again. “Just let me rest on this troubled night.”

&quot;The Lord says that the time for rest has passed,” he heard in a familiar voice. “Only action will appease him.”

The ghost at the center of the graveyard rose up and revealed himself to the Priest. The young Paladin appeared without any wounds, but blood pooled at the bottom of his tunic. It dripped down his legs and into his boots.

“The darkness has reached further than we could imagine. As I stood with my eyes trained on threats from the outside, I was stabbed in the back and left for dead. The Cult leader has the King’s ear, and before long he will be corrupted, too. 

“You must leave this veil of solemn piety behind and revel in your true might. Revive me on this night and I will bring them to their knees. Any man who fails my test of faith will feel this sharpened steel. I will not use the shadows to plunge it into their back. On that night, I will put an end to their wicked toil. 

“They will see me coming and look into my eyes as they shed this mortal coil. The Cultist’s blood will serve only to nourish this barren soil.”</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:39:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Only_Loremaster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually went to read the whole role.<br>
All I can say is…<br>
I’m very impressed.<br>
I think someone from i42 should put this as an actual lore,already in this state of beginning of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2818-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PolikShadowbliss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do the Soulcatcher.  You need to do the Cult and the Unseen versions of this now.</p>
<p>Because holy shit.  This …  is …</p>
<p>Just …</p>
<p>No words.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 20:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2818-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is very beautiful and well-written lore. Very long, must’ve taken a long time to write O_O<br>
<img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7b1b0a59484b1c1b1f634c2baee3e33c7f3b50e8.gif"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 19:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2818-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thunder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m new to this, so I apologize if I’m stepping on toes or if this clashes with existing lore:</p>
<p>With the curtains drawn, just a sliver of light broke through and came to rest on the altar at the head of the chapel. The Priest spoke the final words of his sermon to the silent room.</p>
<p>“May God watch over the noblemen and women of Castle Adiart and protect those who are brave enough to defend our walls, both from the inside and out.”</p>
<p>He made the sign of the cross with his right hand, closed his eyes and hung his head in silent prayer. In the past, his parishioners flocked to the church in such times of strife. Now, the old wooden pews sat empty and the offertory collected nothing but dust.</p>
<p>The sound of the door creaking open brought light to the gray haired man, but he could see only despair on the face of the young Paladin through the dark haze of the room.</p>
<p>“High Priest, I come to you for strength and wisdom. Darkness is spreading over our land, and I fear that tonight it will strike at the heart of Castle Adiart. I will give my life to protect the King, but there is only so much that one man can do to hold back the great strength of this Cult that worships Blood and Darkness. The royal family is in grave danger.</p>
<p>“Why has God forsaken this land?”</p>
<p>“God has only forsaken those who choose not to praise Him alone,” said The Priest. “Do not think because the light shines meekly on this altar that He cannot quickly throw back the curtain and cleanse those who dare speak his name in vain.</p>
<p>“You are never alone as long as the word of our Lord rings true in your heart. His protection is all that our royal family needs, and it is through the strength of his servants that he projects his might over the land.</p>
<p>“Go quietly from this place of worship, my son. I can feel the Powers of the Lord on your side. It is forever your ally. The royal family will not be dragged to their graves so lightly.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Inside of his chambers, the Priest fell to his knees and poured out a chalice of wine in front of him.</p>
<p>“Lord, heed this prayer. Agents of evil strike swiftly at our heels, but the night is always darkest just before the light.  Bind the Soul of our young and noble Prince to this goblet, and spare him from the clenches of the Cultists who seek to dethrone our great and noble King on this cursed night.”</p>
<hr>
<p>The next morning, The Priest rose sharply from his bed. The foul stench of death hung in the air, and he rushed to the main hall. Upon seeing the King sat sturdily on his throne with his son by his side, the Priest was greatly relieved. It must be the blood of the Cult Leader that was spilled in the dark of night.</p>
<p>“Good morning, merciful King. A great terror struck me in my chambers, but I am glad to see the Royal Family has not suffered injury. Can you raise the young Paladin? I have many things to discuss with him.”</p>
<p>“The Paladin, you say? Have you not heard the grave news? The secretive Leader of the Cult eradicated him last night. We found him lying in a pool of blood, punctured with a jagged edge.</p>
<p>“I have little faith in a Priest who cannot feel when the blood of the innocent has been spilled inside the walls of Castle Adiart. Has God truly forsaken this place?</p>
<p>"When my forefathers received their divine mandate, they had no need for Knights or Paladins to protect them. The clergy were all that they needed.</p>
<p>"I have long wondered if God has left these lands behind. Perhaps a stronger hand is needed in these troubled times… or perhaps the prayers coming from the castle walls are lacking in divine passion.</p>
<p>“I think you should pray for the people of this land, Priest. Pray for strength. Pray for Unity. Pray for Light. Pray that a new herald to the Lord is not necessary.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Sleep eluded the Priest that night. He prayed for it to come, but the voices in his head grew more intense as each hour passed.</p>
<p>“I pray to thee, my Lord. Bring silence and calm to my thoughts, and when I wake let the light shine through the heavy curtains of Castle Adiart and flush out the darkness. Manifest the protection for my people that they deserve. We have always served you, my Lord. Repay our faith in kind.”</p>
<p>But the voices did not stop. The Priest could feel their pain, though he could not hear their words.</p>
<p>“I will pray for you all,” he said. “Please let me rest on this night.”</p>
<p>“No sleep,” he heard. “Come to us.”</p>
<p>The Priest’s face drained of blood and his skin matched the pale moonlight that bled into his room. He dared to peak out his chamber’s window and looked upon the graveyard. The ghostly apparitions that always hung faintly in the air circled around a central figure.</p>
<p>“I will pray for you all,” he said once again. “Just let me rest on this troubled night.”</p>
<p>"The Lord says that the time for rest has passed,” he heard in a familiar voice. “Only action will appease him.”</p>
<p>The ghost at the center of the graveyard rose up and revealed himself to the Priest. The young Paladin appeared without any wounds, but blood pooled at the bottom of his tunic. It dripped down his legs and into his boots.</p>
<p>“The darkness has reached further than we could imagine. As I stood with my eyes trained on threats from the outside, I was stabbed in the back and left for dead. The Cult leader has the King’s ear, and before long he will be corrupted, too.</p>
<p>“You must leave this veil of solemn piety behind and revel in your true might. Revive me on this night and I will bring them to their knees. Any man who fails my test of faith will feel this sharpened steel. I will not use the shadows to plunge it into their back. On that night, I will put an end to their wicked toil.</p>
<p>“They will see me coming and look into my eyes as they shed this mortal coil. The Cultist’s blood will serve only to nourish this barren soil.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 18:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2818-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-return-of-the-light/2818.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Return of the Light</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
