<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201</link>
    <description># **SFoL 63: Triple Threat: Virtuous** 

## Rules and Punishments

[Standard FOL/FM Rules ](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926)


##### Hosted by @Amelia and @Jane

## Gameplay

* You will be provided with a DM containing your class card. You will send your actions there.
* Days will be 48 hours long, and Nights will be 24 hours long.
* There is an execution Day 1.
* Executions are both majority and plurality.
* The Blue Dragon and Hand of Byzantium will speak through private forum messages or discord servers
* The Soulcatcher/Blasphemer/Priest/Saint will speak with the dead through a private forum message.
* The Exiled will speak through a private forum message.
* The Archivist/Princess/Librarian&#39;s log network will be held in a private forum message.
* Both evil factions will cap at 4 members.
* If both evil factions attempt to convert the same player in the same night, the faction with less members will convert that player. If both factions have equal amounts of members, the Blue Dragon will convert that player.
* The maximum amount of non-unique duplicate classes is 3, barring those with the Prestige passive.
* There may be up to 3 classes with Prestige in the game. All Unseen classes with Prestige besides the Exiled are unique. If a starting member of the Blue Dragon or Hand of Byzantium has Prestige, then the Unseen equivalent with Prestige cannot spawn. 
* If the King ever chooses to use Royal Pardon, it will be publicly announced.
* Any time the word “antithetical” is used, it means that redchecks become greenchecks, greenchecks become redchecks, and class types change based on: 
Killer = Social
Offensive = Investigative
Investigative = Killer
Support = Offensive
Social = Special
Special = Support
## Executions

* To accuse someone say “/vote [player]”. Please make the life of the hosts easier by bolding it (by putting ** ** around it)
* Should the votes reach the majority, that player will be executed and the day will end.
* When the day ends, the player with the most votes will be executed.
* Voting “/no execution” is an option.
* You are allowed to vote yourself.

## Picking a new King

* If there are less than 4 players a new king will not be selected.
* When the king dies a 12 hour period starts. In this, players may vote in their class PM for who they want to become the next king.
* Whoever receives the most votes in this period will be crowned king. If votes are tied, a king election will be held the next day to determine it.

## Journals 

DM the host what you want on your journal. When you die, the last update to your journal will be revealed to everyone. It has a character limit of 1000 characters.


## Classlist
King (60% [color = purple] **Corrupted**[/color], 20% [color = steblue] **Righteous**[/color], 20% [color = goldenrod] **Purified**[/color])
[color = steblue] **Visionary** [/color]
[color = steblue] **Heroine** [/color] 
[color = steblue] **Random Blue Dragon** [/color]
[color = goldenrod] **Arbiter** [/color]
[color = goldenrod] **Champion** [/color]
[color = goldenrod] **Random Hand of Byzantium** [/color]
[color = purple] **Duke** [/color]
[color = purple] **Torturer** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]
[color = purple] **Random Unseen** [/color]

# **Classes:**

[details=&quot;Kings&quot;]
&gt; # [color=purple]The Corrupted King :shield: :fire: [/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Special**[/color]
**Pass The Torch (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are executed for treason, all players will lose their Royal Blood passive. You can use both day abilities in the same day.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make a player unable to be voted today. This ability can only used during the first half (24 hours) of each day. Cannot target yourself. - 2 uses
**Royal Allies (Day) -** Choose up to three players. Tonight, they will share a night chat with you. Infinite uses
**Royal Guard (Night)** - Sends a guard to a player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses :crown:
**Royal Advisers (Night)** - Sends an adviser to a player. They will be immune to conversions for the night. - 3 uses
**Permanent Scheme (Night)** - Target player will be immune to conversion for the rest of the game - One use (Starting King Only)
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Unseen.
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Righteous King :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Special**[/color]
**Pass The Torch (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. You can use both day abilities in the same day.
**Royal Allies (Day) -** Choose up to three players. Tonight they will share a night chat with you. Infinite uses
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make a player unable to be voted today. This ability can only used during the first half (24 hours) of each day. Cannot target yourself. - 2 uses
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose a player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses :crown:
**Swear Fealty (Night)** - All [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] players will appear to be a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] tonight. - One use
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium*

&gt;Crowned From:
&gt; * Any member of the Blue Dragon.
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Purified King :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Special** [/color]
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. You can use both day abilities in the same day.
**Imperial Allies (Day) -** Choose up to three players. Tonight they will share a night chat with you. Infinite uses
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make a player unable to be voted today. This ability can only used during the first half (24 hours) of each day. Cannot target yourself. - 2 uses
**Champion&#39;s Council (Night)** - Sends a champion (An assistant champion, different than the real [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], does not affect the current [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color]&#39;s actions) to attack a player. This attack does not count as a visit and cannot be stopped. Can only be used on the second night or after that you are crowned. - One use
**Hero&#39;s Immunity (Night)** - Permanently makes a player be seen as a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] to faction checks. - 2 uses
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon*

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Hand of Byzantium.
---

[/details]

[details = Unseen]
&gt; # [color = purple] **The Marshal** :shield: :crossed_swords: [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**Tireless (Passive)** - If you do not perform an action at night, you will learn if any of your previous uses of Expert Investigation and Case Closed showed incorrect results and which ones were incorrect.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Scout (Day)** - Your scout will inform you whether a particular player has been visited by a member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] or the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] tonight and the faction of the player that visited your target if so. This ability can detect the visits of the starting [color = steblue] **Visionary** [/color] and the [color = goldenrod] **Arbiter** [/color]. - Infinite uses
**Peerless Confidant (Day)** - Employ your most trusted confidant to keep watch on two players at once tonight. This confidant will tell you if either or both players are visited by a member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] or the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] tonight and the faction of the player(s) that visited your target(s) if so. This ability can detect the visits of the starting [color = steblue] **Visionary** [/color] and the [color = goldenrod] **Arbiter** [/color].- One use
**Expert Investigation (Night)** - If a player is a member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] or the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color], learn their faction. - Infinite uses
**Case Closed (Night)** - Very carefully examine a player tonight. If they are a member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] or the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color], learn their exact class. This ability can detect the starting [color = steblue] **Visionary** [/color] and the [color = goldenrod] **Arbiter** [/color] - 2 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Sheriff**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Agent**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Duke :shield: :crossed_swords: [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Unstoppable (Passive)** - Immune to being occupied and redirected at night.
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become king count as two for you.
**Kidnap (Day)** - Choose a player to kidnap at night, This occupies them while bypassing occupation immunity and preventing all visits to targeted player. You and them may also exchange up to two 1000 character messages. - Infinite uses
**Execute (Night)** - Kill the kidnapped player bypassing any and all immunites as the most powerful form of night attack in the game. If you kill a member of the Unseen with this ability, you will lose all uses of it. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Prince**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Warden**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple] The Torturer [/color] :shield: :crossed_swords: 
&gt;
&gt; [color=purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become King count as two for you.
**The Duke’s Assistant (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection and keep this part of the passive on class change. Additionally, if the player who started as the Duke dies, you will instantly become the new Duke. You will have the same amount of Execute charges as the Duke did when they died.
**Solitary Confinement (Day)** - Prevent a player from using day abilities today. Two uses
**Incarcerate (Night)** - Occupy a player and prevent all visits to them tonight. Infinite uses
**Enhanced Interrogation (Night)** - Remove all uses of your target’s limited usage abilities. This will secretly fail on the [color=steblue] **Visionary** [/color] or the [color=goldenrod] **Arbiter** [/color] but you will not know if this is the case. One use
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts to [color=steblue] **The Prince** [/color] or [color=goldenrod] **The Warden** [/color]
- - -
&gt; # [color = purple] The Marchioness [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count twice.
**VIP List (Day)** -  By the end of the coming night, you will know how many players of different factions visited you but will not be told which factions. - 2 uses
**Social Links (Night)** - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets’ class type groupings match. Groups are Special/Investigative, Social/Support, and Killer/Offensive. You will receive either no match if they are from different groups, a good match if they are in the same group, and a perfect match if they are the same class type. For this ability, any [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color] and the first [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color] will appear to be the class they have asked to appear as to the host at the start of the game. - Infinite uses
**Night Waltz (Night)** - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets’ alignments match; otherwise a negative result. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Maid**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Socialite**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Minstrel [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Support** [/color]
**Pure Wits (Day)** - In the coming night you will be immune to being occupied at night and immune to redirection. - 3 uses
**Ballad (Night)** - Cure a player’s bleeding. They will also be occupation, redirection, conversion, and night immune tonight. - 2 uses :crown:
**Crescendo (Night)** - If your target is redirecting, occupying, or attacking, then they will bypass immunities during this night. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Chronomancer**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Bard**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Archivist :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Social** [/color]
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Repository (Passive)** - You start in a public log network by yourself. Players in the network will be allowed to read the logs of any other player in the network. The Repository remains open while the archivist is still alive regardless if they have been converted.
**Archive (Day)** - Invites a player to the log network. The player must accept before joining and can choose to leave at anytime. Can only invite two players per day. - Infinite uses
**Revoke (Night)** - Removes a player from the log network. - Infinite uses
**Censorship (Night)** - Deactivates the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] and [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] day chat for the next day and night. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Princess**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Librarian**[/color]
---

&gt; # [color = purple] The Auditor [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Support** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes for you to become the next King are doubled.
**Confiscated Funds (Day)** - If your target has 0 uses in any limited usage abilities, silently add an extra use to them. One use
**Black Market (Night)** - If your target has any limited usage abilities, silently add another use to them. Infinite uses
**Audit (Night)** - If your target attempts to use a limited usage ability tonight, occupy them bypassing occupation immunity. Two uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium*
- - -
&gt; Converts to [color = steblue] **The Tavernkeeper** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **The Patron** [/color]

&gt; # [color = purple] The Baronet [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count twice.
**Gerissen (Passive)** - If you have killed any [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]-aligned players in the match, then you will not be allowed to receive votes to become the King.
**Missgunst (Day)** - Grants night immunity for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then you will gain a use of Vom Tach. - 2 uses
**Mittelhau (Night)** - Redirects the selected player’s action to you while also granting yourself immunity to all redirected attacks and conversions, then attack the player. If you successfully kill a player then you will gain a use of Vom Tach. Disables your night abilities if the target is aligned with the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]. - Infinite uses
**Vom Tach (Night)** - Prevents you from being occupied or redirected, then attacks your target and kills them, bypassing healing and night immunity. Disables your night abilities if the target is aligned with the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]. - 0 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Hunter**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Duelist**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Blasphemer :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Social** [/color]
**Incantations (Passive)** - You may speak with the dead during the night.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Heretical Decree (Day)** - If target player is executed today and is a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] with a non-unique, non-Prestige class, you will remove them from dead chat. - One use
**Spirit Swap (Day)** - Tonight, you will resurrect the player you removed from dead chat using Heretical Decree and sacrifice yourself if you succeed. You may not use any night abilities tonight. - One use
**Black Mercy (Night)** - Select a dead [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]-aligned player and force them to use their primary night action on a living one. Cannot be used on Killer classes. - Infinite uses
**Bind Soul (Night)** - Bind a dead player to yourself, allowing them to speak while dead for as long as you are alive, but removing them from dead chat. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Priest**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Saint**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Bureaucrat [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Overrule (Day)** - Causes your first target to select your second target if they use any day abilities later today. If you choose the same target on a second day, any day abilities they use later today will instead redirected to themselves. - 2 uses
**Red Tape (Day)** - The King&#39;s night actions will fail tonight. - 2 uses :crown:
**Order of Relocation (Night)** - Forces your first target’s night action to be redirected to your second target. - Infinite uses
**Order of Exchange (Night)** - Select two players and force them to target each other, bypassing immunity to redirection. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Drunk**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Overseer**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Exiled :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Social** [/color]
**Unseen Traditions (Passive)** - The Exiled may only roll in groups of two. You will have an all-day and all-night chat with the other Exiled. You are immune to conversion while the other Exiled is still alive.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Letter with no Sender (Day)** - Sends an anonymous message of up to 1000 characters to a player. - Infinite uses
**Cryptic Communications (Night)** - Sends an anonymous message of up to 1000 characters to a player and they will be able to post a reply of up to 1000 characters. - Infinite uses
**Influence of the Black Rose (Night)** - If alive, the other Exiled will silently not be able to be executed tomorrow. - One use :crown:
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Mystic**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Cabalist**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Fanatic [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Piety (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] faction visits you this coming night, they will be prevented and bled. You cannot use Malleus Maleficarum after using Piety.- One use
**Martyrdom (Day)** - If a player is executed this day, the Fanatic can choose to sacrifice themselves in order to stop the execution and save the accused player while also bleeding their first accuser. - One use
**Malleus Maleficarum (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] visits them they will be bled by you. This does not stop their actions. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Regicide (Night)** - Attacks and kills two targets. You will also die of exhaustion the night you use this ability regardless of the ability’s outcome. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Knight**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Crusader**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Forest Witch [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Isolation (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Nightshade Curse (Day)** - Selects a player and for the next two nights they will not be able to be healed. - 2 uses :crown:
**Wall of Roots (Day)** - For the following night prevents non-[color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] classes from visiting you and will Bleed them. The Bleeding will kill them if they are not healed the next night. -One use
**Curse of Lethargy (Night)** - You will occupy a player for tonight. - Infinite uses
**Curse of Sloth (Night)** - You will occupy two players for tonight. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Court Sorceress**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Druid**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Infiltrator [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Alert (Day)** - Grants immunity to occupation and to redirection the coming night. - 3 uses
**Detainment (Night)** - Silently removes all of the passives and night immunity from your target. The Detainment will also last until the end of the next night except when it comes to removing Royal Blood, which lasts two days. This ability secretly fails if used on the Visionary or Arbiter. - Infinite uses
**Off-Limits (Night)** - Occupies your target if they attempts to attack or convert a player. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Butler**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Sentinel**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Judge :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Social** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count twice.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Judicial Decree (Day)** - Reset all votes and choose a player. Only you or that player may be executed today. Can only be used within the first 24 hours of the day. - 2 uses
**Disenfranchise (Night)** - Target player will secretly require two fewer votes to be executed tomorrow. If twelve or less players remain, they will require one less to be executed tomorrow. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Usurp (Night)** - Only usable on Night 3 or later. Attack the King. If you are successful, you automatically become The Corrupted King. - One use :crown:
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Noble**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Magistrate**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Marauder [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Carnage (Passive)** - If you are attacked during the first two nights, you will be immune and will counterattack instead of dying.
**Aura of Dread (Passive)** - For every successful kill, you will gain an additional night of Carnage.
**Boastful Rampage (Night)** - Attacks and kills a player. If the target was [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]-aligned, then you will lose your night abilities and they will be shown as [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] to faction checks. - Infinite uses
**Glare (Night)** - Redirects the target’s night action to yourself. Redirects past the second night will trigger Carnage. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Archer**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Warrior**[/color]
---

&gt; # [color = purple] The Mortician[/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Special** [/color]
**The Harvest (Passive)** - You will get a soul for every player that dies at night. You will always be aware of the soul amount you have. You begin with two souls.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Terror (Day)** - Spend two souls and cause a player’s day abilities to fail. This will not work on the [color=steblue] **Visionary** [/color] or the [color=goldenrod] **Arbiter**[/color].
**Clarity (Day)** - Spend two souls to ensure a player gets correct results from their abilities tonight.
**Transfusion (Night)**  - Send your souls to gaze at a player. You may augment this ability by spending souls. For each soul you spend, you may choose an additional effect. You cannot spend more than two souls at a time, and you cannot choose the same effect twice. If you do not spend any souls, the ability does nothing aside from being a visit.
&gt; * Learn who a player visits, or if they did not visit anyone
&gt; * Learn a player’s class type
&gt; * Learn a player’s alignment
&gt; * Learn if the result you got was correct
&gt;
&gt;**Amalgamation (Night)** - Mash three souls into a monster and send it to kill a player. If you kill a member of the Unseen with this ability, you will be unable to gain more souls permanently.
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*
- - -
&gt; Converts to [color = steblue] **The Alchemist** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **The Exorcist** [/color]
- - -
&gt; # [color = purple] The Plague Doctor [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Support** [/color]
**Self-Aid (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
**Reverse-Hemophilia (Day)** - You will grant a player immunity to bleeding. - One use :crown:
**Herbal Medicine (Night)** - Heals a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and curing any bleeding and poisons they were suffering from. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Remarkable Quarantine (Night)** - You will heal a player, giving them the effect of Herbal Medicine for this and the coming night. - One use :crown:
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Physician**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Surgeon**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Stalker [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**Tracking (Day)** - You will learn if your target left their room last night. - 2 uses
**Vigilant Stalking (Night)** - You will learn who your target visits this night. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Observer**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Watchman**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Arbalist [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Killer** [/color]
**Volley (Day)** - If you fire an arrow at one of your marks tonight, remove all marks and attack any other player whose mark was removed. You are immune to redirection this night. - 2 uses
**Raven Shot (Night)** - Fire an arrow to kill your target. This ability is disabled if you kill a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] with it. - Infinite uses
**Pin Down (Night)** - Place a mark on target player. A marked player is no longer passively death immune. You may have up to three marks. Targeting a marked player with this ability will remove the mark. Targeting yourself will remove all marks. Marks disappear on death or class change. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Archer**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Warrior**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Alcoholic[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Offensive**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become King count as two for you.
**I Am The Liquor (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Debauchery (Night)** - Redirect a player to another. You can make a player visit yourself. You are only seen visiting the first player. - Infinite uses
**Happy Hour (Night)** - Remove a player’s occupation and night immunity, then occupy them. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Drunk**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Overseer**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]**The Aristocrat**[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Social**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become King count as two for you.
**Court Spies (Day)** - Choose two players. If either of them is a member of the evil faction or both are, they will be removed from their faction chat until the next night. However, they will be immediately informed that Court Spies was used on them. - 2 uses
**Gossip (Night)** - Target a player and learn if any and which of these things happens to them tonight. - Infinite uses
***They were successfully Investigated.***
***They were successfully Occupied.***
***Their target was successfully swapped.***
**Bounty (Night)** - If target player is executed tomorrow and is a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color], the day will continue and an additional execution will be possible. Only one Bounty may take effect per day. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Noble**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Magistrate**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Duchess[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Investigative**[/color]
&gt; **Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become king count as two for you.
**Bat Eyelashes (Night)** - Check to see what class type the selected player is. You will receive two results, one of which will be their real type, and one won’t be. - Infinite uses
**Dark Wisp (Night)** - Uncage a Dark Wisp, making any attack attempts your target makes fail. If they try to kill somebody, you will know. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Princess**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Librarian**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Enforcer[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Killer**[/color]
**Armored (Passive)** - Your first successful use of Protect will not kill you.
**Protect (Night)** - Protect a player, giving your life to kill their attackers. - Infinite Uses :crown:
**Cold Steel (Night)** - Kill a target player. If they are a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color], you will die. - Unlimited uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Knight**[/color] or [color=goldenrod]**The Crusader**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color = purple] The Handmaiden [/color]
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Investigative** [/color]
**Change Sheets (Day)** - Target two dead players. At the end of the night, you will learn if they were killed by the same player, as well as which factions visited the players the night they died.- 2 uses :crown:
**Rumor (Day)** - You cannot use this ability on day 1. Make a player “last checked” in regards to Matchmake. - 2 uses
**Matchmake (Night)** - Test if a player is compatible with the player you last checked. - Infinite uses
**Prying Servants (Night)** - Choose a living player and a dead player. At the end of the night, you will learn if the living player visited the dead player on the night they died. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Maid**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Socialite**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Herbalist[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Support**[/color]
**Remedy Studies (Passive)** - Immune to bleeding.
**Inoculate (Day)** - Target player will be immune to bleeding - One use :crown:
**Exhume (Day)** - At the end of tonight. See what class killed target dead player or if they committed suicide. - 2 uses :crown:
**Heal (Night)** - Heal a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and cures poison and bleeding. Infinite uses :crown:
**Self-Care (Night)** - Heal yourself tonight. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Physician**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Surgeon**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Illusionist [/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Social**[/color]
**Telepathy (Day)** - Send an anonymous 1000 character message to target player. You may not target the King with this - 3 uses
**Link Destinies (Night)** - Two target players will benefit from the same positive and negative effects other than killing and conversion tonight, like healing or occupation. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Mystic**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Cabalist**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Nightwatch[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Investigative**[/color]
**Follow (Night)** - Observe a player to see who visits them at night. - Infinite uses
**Window Peek (Night)** - Learn a target&#39;s faction. - 2 Uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Observer**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Watchman**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Page [/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Support**[/color]
**Defensive Youth (Passive)** - You are night immune for the first three nights, until you are attacked for the first time, or until you remember a class - whichever happens first.
**Train (Night)** - Allows you to select a non-unique, non-Prestige [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]-aligned class from the Graveyard. The Page in turn will become that class by the end of the night. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Squire**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Squire**[/color]
---

&gt; # [color = purple] The Plaguebearer [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Special** [/color]
**Brew Potion (Day)** - Brew a potion to use at night. Each potion must be used before the same one can be brewed again. Infinite uses
**Apply Potion (Night)** - Use the potion you have brewed. Infinite uses
&gt; * Truth Potion: Get a player’s class type grouping.
&gt; * Tar Potion: Occupy a player. You will be immune to occupation and redirection while using this.
&gt; * Health Potion: Heal a player and cure any bleeding they might have. :crown:
&gt; * Volatile Potion: Attack a player. If they are aligned with the [color = purple] **Unseen** [/color] you will commit suicide.
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts to [color = steblue] **The Alchemist** [/color] or [color = goldenrod]  **The Exorcist** [/color]
- - -
&gt; # [color=purple]The Poacher :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Killer**[/color]
**Loner’s Retribution (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this part of the passive if your class changes. If you are executed, you will kill your first accuser in broad daylight before you are executed.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Rabid Wolf (Day)** - Summon a wolf companion to maul a target player, making them bleed and die in two nights unless healed. - 2 uses
**Spike Traps (Night)** - Put spike traps outside your room, granting you death and conversion immunity for the night. You will kill any attackers who attempt to kill you, bypassing night immunity - 3 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Hunter**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Duelist**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Sage[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Support**[/color]
**Shock (Day)** - Shock the target player, causing them to target themselves if they use their day ability today. - 2 uses
**Dark Rune (Night)** - Prevent any negative affects from affecting the player tonight. - Infinite uses
**Wall of Fire (Night)** - Summon a wall of fire at a player’s door, preventing everyone from visiting them. - 2 uses :crown:
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Court Sorceress**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Druid**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Servant[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Offensive**[/color]
**Dutiful (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. You will keep this passive on class change.
**Chaotic Wine (Day)** - Starting Day 2, Poison the King. He will not know this, and will die tonight if not healed. If the King is a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color], you will take your own life. - One use :crown:
**Serve Wine (Night)** - Occupy a player by getting them drunk. - Infinite uses
**Concentrated Wine (Night)** - Throw a party, occupying all players who visit you tonight. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Butler**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Sentinel**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Soulcatcher :shield:[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Support**[/color]
**Incantations (Passive)** - You may speak with the dead during the night.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Bind Soul (Day)** - Make yourself and target player night immune tonight. - One use :crown:
**Collect Soul (Night)** - If target player dies tonight, you will obtain their soul (you start with 2 souls). - Infinite uses :crown:
**Reanimate (Night)** - Bring a dead [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] member with a non-unique, non-Prestige class back to life. Each night they remain alive, a soul will be consumed. When you run out of souls or die, the resurrected player dies. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Priest**[/color] or [color=goldenrod]**The Saint**[/color]
---
&gt; # [color=purple]The Timesnatcher[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Support**[/color]
&gt; **Time Snatch (Day)** - If you were to die tonight by a healable cause. Redirect tonight&#39;s death to targeted player as a healable attack. - 2 uses 
&gt; **No Time to Waste (Day)** - Target player will become immune to occupation and redirection  for the rest of the game. You may not target yourself. - One use
&gt; **Temporal Distortion (Night)** - Delays a player’s death for 2 days. This will delay ongoing bleeding in addition to attacks. You can prevent a death multiple times. Cannot delay unhealable attacks or suicide. - Infinite uses :crown:
&gt; **Dark Dimension (Night)** - Guarantee that all feedback regarding target player is accurate. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; Converts into [color=steblue]**The Chronomancer**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**The Bard**[/color]

&gt; # [color = purple] The Wench [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color = purple] **Unseen Offensive** [/color]
**Steadfast (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection. Keep this passive on class change.
**Dose (Day)** - If your target attempts to use a day action today, it will secretly fail. This will not work on the [color = steblue] **Visionary** [/color] or the [color = goldenrod] **Arbiter**[/color]. One use
**Mix Rooms (Night)** - Choose two players. Redirect all actions targetting one to the other, and vice versa. Cannot select the same player twice in a row. Infinite uses
**Serve Ale (Night)** - Redirect a player to themself. Two uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Hand of Byzantium*
- - -
&gt; Converts to [color = steblue] **The Tavernkeeper** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **The Patron** [/color]

[/details]

[details=&quot;Blue Dragon&quot;]
&gt; # [color = steblue] The Visionary :shield: :crossed_swords:   [/color]
&gt; [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon Special** [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**Undercover Rebel (Passive) (Starting Visionary Only)**  - You will receive the following passives:
&gt;* You will always appear as a class of your choice to investigations
&gt;* Each night, you may select 1-2 players you will appear to be visiting at night. If you do not do this, you will be seen visiting your actual targets.
&gt;
&gt;**Path of Leadership (Passive)** - If you are the original or second [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color] and die, the youngest non killing [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] member will become the new [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color]. If there is no non Killing members of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color], it will instead be the Youngest [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] Killer. There can always be a second and third [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color] unless the current [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color] dies as the last member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color]. A fourth [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color] will never happen, however.
&gt;
&gt;**Avenge (Day)** - You will turn into the [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color] at the start of the night when you use this ability. Target [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] player will become the new [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color]. If there are more than 2 [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] members alive and the [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color] uses that ability on a player who is not the [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color], the [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color] will either revert to their convert class (if not the original [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color]) or become a non-unique, non-prestige [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] convert class of their choice (if the original [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color]).
&gt;
&gt;**Call to Arms! (Day)** - Call the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] to arms, empowering them tonight. The [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] will receive a message when this is activated. The individual effects can be found on each class card. - Infinite Uses, 1 day cooldown.
&gt;
&gt;**Persuade (Night)** - Persuade someone to join the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color]. - Infinite uses, Two night cooldown on success, unusable Night 1
&gt;
&gt;**Insight of the Worthy (Night)** - Select a player and learn their converted class type if they are convertible. If they are not convertible, learn two class types that are not their class type. - Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt;**Focused Visions (Call to Arms | Night)** - Learn the [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon** [/color] version of a player&#39;s class. - Infinite uses
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---

&gt; # [color = steblue] The Heroine :shield: :crossed_swords:[/color]
&gt; [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon Killer** [/color]
**Hero&#39;s Blessing (Passive)** - You are occupy and redirection immune. You keep this passive for as long as you are alive, even if your class changes.
**Promotion (Passive)** - If the Heroine dies, the oldest non-Visionary member of the Blue Dragon will become the new Heroine, except in the case where there were three members of the BD alive but the Visionary and Heroine die at the same time, in which the remaining member will become a Visionary.
**Vengeance (Day)** - Your attack will pierce night immunity tonight. - 0 uses, Gains One use for each dead member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color].
**Slit Skin (Day)** - Targeted player will bleed and die in 2 nights unless healed. - 3 uses (shared) :crown:
**Eliminate (Night)** - Kill a target player. If they are a member of the [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium** [/color] you will additionally occupy them. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Valiant Smite (Call to Arms | Night)** - Kill a target player bypassing any and all forms of immunity and protection. You will take their journal, making it appear as though they didn’t leave one, and you will be able to read it. - 3 uses (shared) :crown:
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---

&gt; # [color=steblue] The Alchemist [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=steblue] **Blue Dragon Special** [/color]
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = steblue]**Alchemist**[/color] is converted from the [color = purple]**Plaguebearer**[/color], however, then this does not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Mixology (Passive)** - You can use both day abilities in the same day.
**Hurl Potion (Day)** - Create a potion to hurl at someone today. You must use each potion from this list once before using the same one again. Infinite uses
&gt; * Hypnotic Potion - Cause a player to receive entirely antithetical feedback tonight.
&gt; * Slick Potion - If target player attempts to use a day ability today, they will be forced to target themself with it.
&gt; * Misty Potion - All day abilities used on target player today will secretly fail.
&gt; * Emerald Potion - Cause a player to begin bleeding. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. :crown:
&gt;
&gt; **Brew Potion (Day)** - Brew a potion for use tonight. You must use each potion on the list before brewing the same one again. Infinite uses
**Apply Potion (Night)** - Use the potion you have brewed. Infinite uses
&gt; * Health Potion - Heal a player and cure any bleeding they were suffering from. If you target a member of the [color=steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] with this ability, you may additionally disguise them as a class of your choice. :crown:
&gt; * Tar Potion - Occupy a player tonight and cause any day abilities they use tomorrow to fail. You are immune to occupation and redirection while using this.
&gt; * Truth Potion - Learn a player’s alignment and class type.
&gt; * Molten Potion - Bleed all non-[color=steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] players visiting your target tonight. Their actions will not be stopped, however. :crown:
&gt;
&gt; **Poison Potion (Call to Arms | Night)** - In addition to the potion you brewed with Brew Potion, use a Poison Potion to kill a player. Two uses :crown:
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*

- - -
&gt; # [color = steblue] The Archer [/color]
&gt; [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon Killer** [/color]
**Multi-shot (Day)** - If you shoot a marked player tonight, you will be redirection immune and additionally attack all other marked players. - Uses shared with Vengeance
**Eagle Shot (Night)** - Shoot a bolt to kill your target without visiting them. If the [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color] attempts to carry out a kill, you will shoot her target in place of her attack. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Bullseye (Night)** - Mark a player. Marked players are unhealable, lose night immunity and cannot become night immune. Up to three players can be marked at any given time. Targeting a marked player with this ability will remove the mark. Targeting yourself will remove all marks. Marks disappear on death or class change. - Infinite uses
**Absolute Precision (Call to Arms | Night)** - Kill all marked players, bypassing all forms of protection and immunity. If there are fewer than 3 living marked players, you may mark an additional player before attacking. It will not count as an additional visit of any kind. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Butler[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Offensive**[/color]
**Dutiful (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Eager Service (Day)** - Occupy a player until the end of the day, causing any day actions they attempt for the rest of the day to fail. - 2 uses
**Serve Wine (Night)** - Occupy a player by getting them drunk. - Infinite uses
**Concentrated Wine (Night)** - Throw a party, occupying all players who visit you tonight. - 2 uses
**Intoxicated Wine (Call to Arms | Night)** - Occupy a player for two nights in a row, bypassing immunity to occupation. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Chronomancer[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Support**[/color]
**Pocket Dimension (Day)** - If target member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] would die tonight, delay their death for 2 nights. This will delay bleeding in addition to attacks. - 3 uses
**Time Warp (Night)** - Choose a player. All abilities that target them tonight will not take effect until the next night. Conversions, investigative abilities and abilities that bypass immunities or healing will not be delayed. Time Warp cannot delay a single ability multiple times. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Distort Reality (Night)** - Redirect all abilities delayed by Time Warp to a player of your choice. - 3 uses
**Paradox (Call to Arms | Night)** - Choose a player. All other abilities used on that player tonight will automatically fail aside from [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon** [/color] abilities. Abilities prevented this way will be considered delayed and can be redirected with Distort Reality on the following night. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Court Sorceress[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Offensive**[/color]
**Earthquake (Day)** - Cast an earthquake under a player. If they use a day ability today, they will be redirected to themselves. - 2 uses
**Ice Ward (Night)** - Prevent all other players from visiting a player of your choice tonight. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Tornado (Night)** - Redirect two players to one another. - 3 uses
**Frozen Door (Call to Arms | Night)** - Freeze a player’s room, occupying them. Only [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] members will be able to visit them tonight; all other attempted visits will be prevented. - 3 uses :crown:
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Drunk[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Offensive**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become King count as two for you.
**I Am The Liquor (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Debauchery (Night)** - Redirect a player to another. You can make a player visit yourself. You are only seen visiting the first player. - Infinite uses
**Happy Hour (Night)** - Remove a player’s occupation and night immunity, then occupy them. - 2 uses
**Hangover (Call to Arms | Night)** - Redirect your target to themselves for this and the following night, bypassing redirection immunity. Redirected abilities will bypass immunities. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Hunter[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Killer**[/color]
**Isolation (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If [color = steblue]**Hunter**[/color] is converted from the [color = purple]**Baronet**[/color], however, then this does not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Wolf Companion (Day)** - Summon a wolf to attack a player, making them start bleeding. They will die in two nights if not healed. If the target is already bleeding, it will kill them tonight. - 2 uses :crown:
**Spike Trap (Night)** - Choose a member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] other than yourself. All [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] members who visit them tonight will start bleeding and die in two nights if not healed. Their actions will not be prevented. - 3 uses
**Bear Trap (Call to Arms | Night)** - Set up a protective bear in your home to hurt all intruders. All players who attempt harmful actions on you tonight will be occupied and die, bypassing night immunity. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Knight[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Killer**[/color]
**Ultimate Sacrifice (Day)** - If a player is executed today, you will be executed instead and make that player’s first accuser start bleeding. They will die in two nights if not healed. - One use
**Defend (Night)** - Guard a member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color]. All other visits to that player tonight will be prevented. - 3 uses
**Dragon’s Blade (Night)** - Attack a player. - One use :crown:
**Stalwart Defense (Call to Arms | Night)** - Guard all other members of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color]. All visits to them aside from those of the [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon** [/color] tonight will be prevented. This counts as a visit to yourself - Two uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color = steblue] The Maid [/color]
&gt; [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon Investigative** [/color]
**Change Sheets (Day)** - Target two dead players. At the end of the night, you will learn if they were killed by the same player. - 2 uses :crown:
**Servant Spies (Day)** - Choose two players. If one of them visits the other tonight, you will be informed. You can target yourself. - 2 uses
**Matchmake (Night)** - Check two players to see if they are the same class type. You will only be seen visiting the first player. - Infinite uses
**Nosy Servants (Night)** - Choose a player. You will receive their full feedback, including information they would not normally learn (such as being occupied if they are not an Investigative class) except you will not learn who they visited or tried to visit. - 2 uses
**Housekeeping (Call to Arms | Night)** - Choose a player. You will receive their full feedback tonight, including who they visited or tried to visit. You will also receive feedback they would not normally receive, such as being bled but immune. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue] The Mystic [/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Social**[/color]
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = steblue]**Mystic**[/color] is converted from an [color = purple]**Illusionist**[/color], however, then they do not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Exile (Passive)** - If you were converted from the [color = purple] **Exiled** [/color]you will regain **Cryptic Communications**
**Telepathy (Day)** - Send a 1000 character message to target player. You may not target the King with this - 3 uses
**Link Fates (Night)** - Clone any action taken by another member of the Blue Dragon this night onto an additional player of your choice, except killing or conversion. - Infinite uses
**Influence of the Blue Dragon (Night) -** Silently make another member of the [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon** [/color] unable to be executed tomorrow. One use
**Accurate Fates (Call to Arms | Night)** - Clone all actions taken by other members of the Blue Dragon this night onto an additional player of your choice, except conversion. You may choose a different player for each member&#39;s action, and you will not visit any of your targets. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Noble[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Social**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become King count as two for you.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = steblue]**Noble**[/color] is converted from an [color = purple]**Aristocrat**[/color], however, then they do not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Incriminate (Day)** - Slip a player forged documents, making them appear to investigators as a member of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] tonight. - Infinite uses
**Bounty (Day)** - If target player is executed today and is a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color], the day will continue and an additional execution will be possible. Only one Bounty may take effect per day. - 2 uses
**Gossip (Night)** - Target a player and learn if any and which of these things happens to them tonight. - Infinite Uses
***They were successfully Investigated.***
***They were successfully Occupied.***
***Their target was successfully swapped.***
**Pull Rank (Night)** - Tomorrow, the player you vote will secretly require two fewer votes to be executed. If twelve or less players remain, they will only require one vote less to be executed. - 2 uses
**Forceful Order (Call to Arms | Night)** - Silently Negate the votes of a target player the next day. They can’t accuse anyone or vote tomorrow. They will also secretly require two fewer votes to be executed, unless twelve or less players remain, in which case they will require one vote fewer to be executed. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Observer[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Investigative**[/color]
**Blue Bird (Day)** - The next time a player uses a day ability today, you will be immediately informed who it was. - Infinite uses
**Little Bird (Day)** - Choose a player. At the end of the night, you will learn if they left their room. - Infinite uses
**Follow (Night)** - Learn a player’s visitors and who they visited. You may target members of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color]. - Infinite uses
**Window Peek (Night)** - Learn a player’s alignment and all of their current **status effects**, including bleeding, passive removal, etc. You do not learn when the status effects wear off. If a status effect is applied on the night you use Window Peek, it will not be detected. You may not target members of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color]. - 2 uses
**Stare Down (Call to Arms | Night)** - Learn a player’s class and who they visit tonight. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Physician[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Support**[/color]
**Remedy Studies (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
**Medical Attention (Day)** - You will assist the [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color] tonight. If she would be attacked or bled while visiting a player, you will automatically heal her even if you are occupied or redirected. - 2 uses
**Heal (Night)** - Heal a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and curing poison and bleeding. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Exhume (Night)** - Choose a dead player. Learn what effects were applied to them on the night they died, and additionally learn which class killed them or if they committed suicide. If multiple classes killed that player, you will learn the names of all of them. - 3 uses :crown:
**Concentrated Nightshade (Call to Arms | Night)** - Poison a player with a concentrated dose of nightshade, causing them to die tonight. - Two uses :crown:
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Princess[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Investigative**[/color]
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = steblue]**Princess**[/color] is converted from an [color = purple]**Duchess**[/color], however, then they do not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become King count as two for you.
**Royal Studies (Passive)** - If your original class was [color = purple]**The Archivist**[/color], you retain your “Archive” and “Revoke” abilities until your class changes.
**Contrived Discourse (Day)** - Learn if a player visited someone last night and if they used a day ability yesterday. - 3 uses
**Light Wisp (Night)** - All members of the [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] will appear to investigators as members of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] tonight. - 2 uses
**Flirt (Night)** - Learn a player’s class type. If you were converted from [color = purple]**The Archivist**[/color], you may only use this ability on players inside your log network. - Infinite uses
**Date (Call to Arms | Night)** - Learn a player’s class. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Prince :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Killer**[/color]
**Unstoppable (Passive)** - Immune to being occupied and redirected at night.
&gt; **Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become king count as two for you.
**Imprison (Day)** - Choose a player to imprison at night, This occupies them while bypassing occupation immunity and preventing all visits to targeted player. You and them may also exchange up to two 1000 character messages. - Infinite uses
**Interrogate (Night)** - Interrogate your imprisoned player, finding out their class type. - 2 uses
**Execute (Call to Arms | Night)** - Execute your imprisoned player, bypassing night immunity. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Priest [/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Support**[/color]
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Soul Protector (Passive)** - If you started the match as the [color = steblue]**Priest**[/color] or were converted from the [color = purple]**Blasphemer**[/color], you initially have 2 souls. If you were converted from the [color = purple]**Soulcatcher**[/color], you have as many souls as you had when you were converted. You may speak to the dead at night.
**Bind Soul (Day)** - Make a [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] member other than yourself night immune tonight. - Infinite uses, costs 1 soul to use
**Soul Trap (Night)** - Permanently trap a player’s soul. When that player dies, you will gain 1 soul if you are still alive. - Infinite uses
**Revive (Call to Arms | Night)** - You may only use this ability if there are three or fewer [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] members alive and the [color = steblue]**Visionary**[/color] is not converting a player tonight. Resurrect a dead  **Unseen**  member with a non-unique, non-Prestige class while converting them simultaneously. Each night they remain alive, a soul will be consumed. When you run out of souls or die, the resurrected player dies. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Sheriff :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Investigative**[/color]
**Perception (Passive)** - As long as you are alive, you passively assist the [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color]. Whenever her Eliminate fails to kill a player, you will automatically learn that player’s class. This can detect the [color = goldenrod] **Arbiter** [/color]. Whenever a player bled by the [color = steblue]**Heroine**[/color] is healed, you will also be informed.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Scout (Day)** - Have a scout follow a player. You will learn their faction tomorrow. - 2 uses
**Stakeout (Night)** - Stake out a player’s room. At the end of the night, you will learn how many players visited them and which factions they belonged to. - Infinite uses
**Hideout (Call to Arms | Night)** - Hide near a player’s room. At the end of the night, you will learn how many players visited them, what classes they had, and which abilities they used as their visit. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*
---
&gt; # [color=steblue]The Squire [/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Support**[/color]
**Train (Night)** - Become the non-unique, non-Prestige [color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] equivalent of a class of a deceased player, if they have one. - Infinite uses
**Other Means (Call to Arms | Night)** - Become the non-unique[color = steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] equivalent class of any living or deceased player, if they have one. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*

&gt; # [color = steblue] The Tavernkeeper [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color=steblue] **Blue Dragon Offensive** [/color]
**Steadfast (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection. Keep this passive on class change.
**Dose (Day)** - If target player attempts to use a day ability it will secretly fail. This does not work on the [color=steblue] **Visionary** [/color] or the [color=goldenrod] **Arbiter**[/color]. Two uses
**Tab Money (Day)** - If the [color=steblue] **Heroine** [/color] uses a day ability today they will not consume a use of it. One use
**Mix Rooms (Night)** - Choose two players. Redirect everyone targetting the first player to the second and vice versa. Cannot target the same player twice in a row. Infinite uses
**Serve Ale (Night)** - Redirect a player to themself. Two uses
**House Brew (Call to Arms | Night)** - Redirect a player to themself, bypassing redirection immunity, as well as removing all uses of their limited usage abilities. This will not remove the abilities of the [color=steblue] **Visionary** [/color] or the [color=goldenrod] **Arbiter**[/color] but it will still redirect them. Two uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and the Hand of Byzantium.*

[/details]

[details=&quot;Hand of Byzantium&quot;]
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Arbiter :shield: :crossed_swords:[/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Special** [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**Battle-Tested (Passive)**  - You are passively:
&gt;* Immune to death at night.
&gt;* You are occupation and redirection immune. This effect is kept upon class change
&gt;
&gt;**Inside Seclusion (Passive)**  - You have access to the following effects:
&gt;* At the start of the game or when promoting to arbiter, you can choose any class to appear as to investigative abilties.
&gt;* Each night you may submit 1-2 players who you will to appear to visit to investigative abilities. If none are chosen you will appear to visit your real target.
&gt;* You may choose one day ability from any non-unique Unseen to add to your classcard.
&gt;* Should the starting or second arbiter die, the original champion or third starting member will take your place. There can never be a fourth arbiter by any means.
&gt;
&gt;**Imperial Urgency (Day)** - Become the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color] at the start of the night; if there is a current [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], if they are the original [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], they were the third starting member, or they were promoted from a [color = goldenrod]**Socialite**[/color], they will become the new [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color]; if not, they will become their convert class again. Cannot be used before day 4. - One use
&gt;
&gt;**Entrust (Night)** - Convince someone to join the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color]. - Infinite uses, Two night cooldown on success, unusable Night 1
&gt;
&gt;**Imperial Judgment (Night)** - Target a player. You may redirect them to another player, or redirect them to themself. If they are redirected to themself, they will instead be occupied. You will also know who visits them. - Infinite Uses
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Champion :shield: :crossed_swords:[/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Killer** [/color]
**I am the Hand (Passive)** - If you were a previous class before becoming the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], choose one limited use ability with 2 or more starting uses from any of your previous classes and gain it again as the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], with one fewer use than it began with in its original class. If you are the original [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], did not have any limited use abilities with two or more uses in any of your previous classes, then this passive does not apply.
**Swift Swipe (Day)** - Targeted player will bleed and die in 2 nights unless healed. - 3 uses (shared) :crown:
**Corpse Swap (Day)** - Choose a player. If you successfully kill them tonight, they will flip as a class of your choice with a logbook of your choosing or an empty logbook. - One use
**Merciless Attack (Night)** - Attack a player with the might of your blade - Infinite uses :crown:
**Supreme Strike (Night)** - Attack two players in the same night. - One use (shared) :crown:
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Agent :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Investigative** [/color]
**Eyes of the Hand (Passive)** - At the end of each night, you learn which members of the  [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] were visited by members of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] and how many visits occurred per member.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Go Undercover (Day)** - Activate a Sleeper Agent to pursue a player sneakily into the night. They will discover who a player visits and who visits them at the end of the night. - 4 uses
**Secret Service (Night)** - Employ your secret service to keep tabs on three specific players tonight. If any of them target one another, you will learn exactly what ability(s) was/were used, from who within these three and onto who within these three. - Infinite uses
**Untraceable (Night)** - Your efforts as an agent are so effective that no one can trace you or your team. Hide the entirety of the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] from any and all investigative checks for the night. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Socialite [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Investigative** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count twice.
**The Woman Behind the Hand (Passive)** - You will appear as [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] to faction checks and will be promoted straight to [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color] if the [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color] dies, regardless of when they die or if the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color] is still alive. This passive is not lost when you are promoted to a [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], only when you become the [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color].
**Guest List (Day)** - By the end of the coming night, you will know how many players of each faction visited you. - 2 uses
**VIP List (Day)** - By the end of the next night you will know which players visited the [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color] that night. - 3 uses
**Social Links (Night)** - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets’ class type groupings match. Groups are Special/Investigative, Social/Support, and Killer/Offensive. You will receive either no match if they are from different groups, a good match if they are in the same group, and a perfect match if they are the same class type. - Infinite uses
**Faction Links (Night)** - Instantly reduce the cooldown of the [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color]’s conversion by one night. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Bard [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Support** [/color]
**Goldentongue (Passive)** - You appear to investigators as a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color].
**Pure Wits (Day)** - You will be occupation and redirection immune tonight. - 3 uses
**Song of Triumph (Day)** - If a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] is executed today, choose another member of the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color]. One use of all of their limited abilities will be restored. - One use
**Crescendo (Night)** - Make another member of the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] appear as a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] to investigators tonight. - Infinte uses
**Allegro (Night)** - Choose a player. If they redirect, occupy or attack someone tonight, their night action will be guaranteed to succeed. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Librarian [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Social** [/color]
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = goldenrod]**Librarian**[/color] is converted from a [color = purple]**Duchess**[/color], however, then they do not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Righteous Access (Passive)** - You may use both day abilities during the same day and both night abilities on the same night.
**Archive (Day)** - Invite a player to the log network. The player must accept before joining and can choose to leave at any time. You can only invite two players per day. - Infinite uses
**Defender’s Notes (Day)** - At the end of the night, you will obtain a copy of all messages in private shared chats you do not have access to besides the [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon** [/color] chat. - 3 uses
**Revoke (Night)** - Remove a player from your log network. - Infinite uses
**Dalliance (Night)** - Choose a player. You will receive a grouping of two classes at the end of the night. One of those classes will be that player’s exact class. If you were converted from [color = purple]**The Archivist**[/color], you may only use this ability on players inside your log network. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [Color = goldenrod] The Duelist [/color]
&gt; [Color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Killer** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count as two.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If [color = goldenrod]**Duelist**[/color] is converted from the [color = purple]**Baronet**[/color], however, then this does not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Schuld (Passive)** - If you become King, the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color] gains an additional use of Supreme Strike.
**Schwach (Day)** - Choose a player. You will learn all of their immunities at the end of the day. - 2 uses
**Versetzen (Night)** - Deflects any incoming attack against all members of the Hand of Byzantium and kills the attackers. - Three uses
**Zornhau (Night)** - Permanently remove Royal Blood from a player if they have it. If they receive even a single vote in a King election, you will automatically attack them on the following night, bypassing all forms of protection, healing and death immunity. You can still use Versetzen on the same night if this occurs. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Saint [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Social** [/color]
**Intercession (Passive)** - You may speak with the dead during the night.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn).
**Faithful Decree (Day)** - If target player is executed today and is a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] with a non-unique, non-Prestige class, you will remove them from dead chat. - One use
**Act of Faith (Day)** - Tonight, you will resurrect the player you removed from dead chat using Faithful Decree while simultaneously converting them and sacrifice yourself if you succeed. You may not use any night abilities tonight. If the ability succeeds, you will flip as [color = purple]**The Blasphemer**[/color]. You may not use this ability if you have already resurrected a player during the match. - One use
**Mercy (Night)** - Choose a dead [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]-aligned player and force them to use their primary night action on a living one. Cannot be used on Killer classes.
**Spiritual Redemption (Night)** - Bind a dead player to you, allowing them to speak while dead for as long as you are alive, but removing them from dead chat. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Overseer [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Offensive** [/color]
**Undeterred (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Oversight (Passive)** - You automatically obtain the logs of the [color = purple]**Duke**[/color]’s, [color = steblue]**Prince**[/color]’s, or [color = goldenrod]**Warden**[/color]’s conversations in jail for as long as you are alive.
**Overrule (Day)** - Choose two players. If the first player uses a day ability today, they will be redirected to the second. - 2 uses
**Red Tape (Day)** - The King’s night action will fail tonight. - 2 uses :crown:
**Order of Relocation (Night)** - Redirect a player to another. You may redirect a player to yourself. You are only seen visiting the first player. - Infinite uses
**Order of Exchange (Night)** - Redirect two players to each other. This will bypass immunity to redirection - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = Goldenrod] The Cabalist [/color]
&gt; [color = Goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Social** [/color]
**Ritual of the Hand (Passive)** - You appear to investigators as a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]. Whenever you receive a private message, anonymous or not, you will be informed if it contains a lie.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = goldenrod]**Cabalist**[/color] is converted from an [color = purple]**Illusionist**[/color], however, then they do not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Letter with no Sender (Day)** - Send an anonymous message of up to 1000 characters to a player. - Infinite uses
**Rewrite Reality (Day)** - Cause a player to receive a completely antithetical result for any investigative ability they use tonight in every way possible. - 3 uses
**Cryptic Communications (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to a player of up to 1000 characters. They may respond once. - Infinite uses
**Byzantine Connections (Night)** - Silently prevent another [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] member from being executed tomorrow. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Crusader [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Killer** [/color]
**Providence (Day)** - You will appear to investigators as a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] tonight. - 3 uses
**Heavenly Devotion (Day)** - If a player is executed today, you will be executed instead and make that player’s first accuser start bleeding. They will die in two nights if not healed. - One use
**Hand of God (Night)** - Guard a player. If they are visited tonight, you will make all of their visitors start bleeding without preventing their actions. The bleeding players will die in two nights if not healed. - 3 uses :crown:
**Deus Vult (Night)** - Sacrifice your life to attack the King, bypassing all forms of healing and immunities. If you are occupied or redirected, this ability will fail but your use of it will be refunded. - One use :crown:
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Druid [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Offensive** [/color]
**Isolation (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Wall of Thorns (Day)** - Tonight, all players who are not members of the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] will be prevented from visiting you and all prevented visitors will start bleeding. The bleeding will kill them in two nights if not healed. - 2 uses
**Glyph of Decay (Day)** - Make a player unhealable for this night and the following night. - 2 uses :crown:
**Glyph of Lethargy (Night)** - Occupy a player. - Infinite uses
**Glyph of Sloth (Night)** - Occupy two players. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Sentinel [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Offensive** [/color]
**Alertness (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Realign (Day)** - Choose a player. If they use a day ability today, they will be automatically redirected to themselves. - 2 uses
**Clear a Path (Day)** - Tonight, the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color]’s visits cannot be affected by visit prevention, occupying, or redirecting. This does not bypass Duke or Torturer imprisonment, however, as imprisonment is a supreme form of occupation that trumps everything. - 2 uses
**Detainment (Night)** - Remove all passives from a player until the end of the next night. Removing Royal Blood lasts for two days. This will secretly fail if used on the Visionary or Arbiter.- Infinite uses
**Curfew (Night)** - Prevent all other visitors to a player tonight. - 2 uses :crown:
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Magistrate [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Social** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become King count as two for you.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = goldenrod]**Magistrate**[/color] is converted from an [color = purple]**Aristocrat**[/color], however, then they do not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Judicial Decree (Day)** - Reset all votes and choose a player. Only you or that player may be executed today. Can only be used within the first 24 hours of a day. - 2 uses
**Bounty (Day)** - If target player is executed today and is a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color], the day will continue and an additional execution will be possible. Only one Bounty may take effect per day. - 2 uses
**Judicial Forgiveness (Day)** - If and only if your [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color] is the original [color = goldenrod]**Arbiter**[/color], if they are executed later today, then you will take their place. - One use
**Disenfranchise (Night)** - Choose a player. You will learn if they were investigated, occupied, and/or if their target was swapped. They will also secretly require two less votes to be executed tomorrow. If only twelve or less players remain, make them require one less vote to be executed. - Infinite uses
**Impeach (Night)** - Only usable on Night 3 or later. Attack the King. If you are successful, you automatically become a [color = goldenrod]**Purified King**[/color]. - One use :crown:
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Warrior [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Offensive** [/color]
**Combat Ready (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation, death at night, and will counterattack against attackers. This passive is lost once you are promoted to the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color].
**Mighty Vengeance (Passive)** - If you become the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color], you retain the passive ability to counterattack against attackers. You will not be night immune and occupation immune, however.
**Bloodlust (Day)** - All non-Killer classes will be prevented from visiting you tonight. - One use
**Incite Fury (Day)** - The [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color]’s attack tonight will destroy the target’s logs if successful. - 2 uses
**Taunt (Night)** - Redirect a player to yourself. - Infinite uses
**Raging Axes (Night)** - Occupy a player. If they are attacked tonight, the attack will be unhealable and bypass night immunity. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Squire [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Support** [/color]
**Cowardice (Passive)** - You appear to investigators as a member of the [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] until your class changes.
**Savant (Passive)** - Remembering a class gives you one more use of all of its limited abilities than the base version has.
**Pick up the Mantle (Night)** - Select a non-unique, non-Prestige [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color]-aligned class from the Graveyard. You will become its [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] equivalent at the end of the night. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Surgeon [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Support** [/color]
**Self-Aid (Passive)** - You are bleeding immune.
**Anti-Coagulant (Day)** - Make a player permanently unhealable. - One use :crown:
**Feign Symptoms (Day)** - Make a player believe they started bleeding and will die in two nights if not healed. - 2 uses :crown:
**Surgery (Night)** - Heals a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and curing any poison and bleeding they were suffering from. - Infinite uses :crown:
**Miracle Touch (Night)** - Heal all members of the [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color], including yourself. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Watchman [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Investigative** [/color]
**Tracking (Day)** - Tomorrow, you will learn if target player left their room last night. - 3 uses
**Spotter (Day)** - Assign an observer to a player. You will learn who visited them at the end of every night. Reusing the ability will swap the observer to a different player. You may target yourself. - Infinite uses
**Silent Stalking (Night)** - Learn a player’s visitors and who they visited. - Infinite uses
**Midnight Vigil (Night)** - Learn the visitors of two players and who they visited. You will only be seen visiting the first player. - One use
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*
---
&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Warden :shield: [/color]
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Killer** [/color]
**Brazen (Passive)** - You are occupation and redirection immune and keep this passive if your class changes.
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count twice.
**Isolate (Day)** - You will isolate a player in your prison tonight, occupying them while bypassing occupation immunity and preventing all other visits to them. You and them may also exchange up to two 1000 character messages during the night. - Infinite uses
**Divest and Removal (Night)** - Secretly remove all uses from the imprisoned player’s limited abilities. When they attempt to use an ability with no uses, they will be informed that it failed, but not why. - 2 uses
**Purge (Night)** - Execute the player you imprisoned, bypassing night immunity. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Patron [/color]
&gt;
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Offensive** [/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes for you to become the next King are doubled.
**Emergency Fund (Passive)** - Upon becoming the [color=goldenrod] **Champion**[/color], you will gain a use of Supreme Strike and two uses of Swift Swipe.
**Dedicated (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection and will keep this passive on class change.
**Barter (Day)** - If target player attempts to use a day ability today it will secretly fail. Does not work on the [color=steblue] **Visionary** [/color] or the [color=goldenrod] **Arbiter**[/color]. One use
**Deal! (Day)** - Silently remove a use from all of your target’s limited usage abilities. Two uses
**Window Shopping (Night)** - Redirect everyone targetting your first target to your second target and vice versa. Cannot target the same player twice in a row. Infinite uses
**Patronage (Night)** - Check if your target has Royal Blood. If they do, all votes for them in future King elections are nullified until you die. Two uses
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon*
- - -

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Exorcist [/color] 
&gt;
&gt; [color = goldenrod] **Hand of Byzantium Special** [/color]
**The Harvest (Passive)** - You will obtain a soul for every player that dies at night. You are always aware of how many souls you have. If you started as an Exorcist or were converted from the [color = purple] **Plaguebearer** [/color] you will have two souls to start, while if you were converted from the [color = purple] **Mortician** [/color] you will have as many souls as you did before conversion.
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to three classes with Prestige may spawn; including the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class (if the starting [color = steblue] **Blue Dragon**[/color] or [color = goldenrod]**Hand of Byzantium**[/color] class has Prestige, their equivalent [color = purple]**Unseen**[/color] class cannot spawn). If the [color = goldenrod]**Exorcist**[/color] is converted from the [color = purple]**Plaguebearer**[/color], however, then this does not contribute to this limit; only starting classes do.
**Terror (Day)** - Spend two souls to cause a player’s day abilities to fail today. This will not work on the [color = steblue] **Visionary** [/color] or the [color = goldenrod] **Arbiter**[/color]. Infinite uses
**Hypnosis (Day)** - Spend two souls to cause someone to receive entirely antithetical feedback tonight in every way possible. Infinite uses
**Transfusion (Night)** - Send souls to watch a player. You may add augments to this check using souls, each one costing one soul. You can only spend up to two souls on this ability per night. Infinite uses
&gt; * Learn who a player visits and who visits them
&gt; * Learn two classes, one of which is the target’s class
&gt; * Learn a player’s alignment
&gt; * Learn if your results are correct
&gt;
&gt; **Infusion (Night)** - Augment the [color = goldenrod]**Champion**[/color]’s attacks with souls, each augment costing two souls. Infinite uses
&gt; * Make the Champion’s attacks unhealable
&gt; * Make the Champion’s attacks bypass death immunity
&gt; * Hide the Champion’s visits from investigations
&gt; * Gain two additional souls from the Champion’s kill if it is successful
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen and the Blue Dragon.*

[/details]


[details=&quot;Conversion Chart&quot;]
[color = purple] **Alcoholic** [/color] and [color = purple] **Bureaucrat** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Drunk** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Overseer** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Aristocrat** [/color] and [color = purple] **Judge** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Noble** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Magistrate** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Duchess** [/color] and [color = purple] **Archivist** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Princess** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Librarian** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Enforcer** [/color] and [color = purple] **Fanatic** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Knight** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Crusader** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Handmaiden** [/color] and [color = purple] **Marchioness** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Maid** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Socialite** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Illusionist** [/color] and [color = purple] **Exiled** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Mystic** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Cabalist** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Marshal** [/color] (Same class no matter which scum faction) converts to either [color = steblue] **Sheriff** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Agent** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Duke** [/color] and [color = purple] **Torturer** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Prince** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Warden** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Page** [/color] (Same class no matter which scum faction) converts to either [color = steblue] **Squire** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Squire** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Nightwatch** [/color] and [color = purple] **Stalker** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Observer** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Watchman** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Poacher** [/color] and [color = purple] **Baronet** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Hunter** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Duelist** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Sage** [/color] and [color = purple] **Forest Witch** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Court Sorceress** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Druid** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Servant** [/color] and [color = purple] **Infiltrator** [/color] both converts to either [color = steblue] **Butler** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Sentinel** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Herbalist** [/color] and [color = purple] **Plague Doctor** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Physician** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Surgeon** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Soulcatcher** [/color] and [color = purple] **Blasphemer** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Priest** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Saint** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Arbalest** [/color] and [color = purple] **Marauder** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Archer** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Warrior** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Timesnatcher** [/color] and [color = purple] **Minstrel** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Chronomancer** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Bard** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Wench** [/color] and [color=purple] **Auditor** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Tavernkeeper** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Patron** [/color] depending on game type.
[color = purple] **Plaguebearer** [/color] and [color = purple] **Mortician** [/color] both convert to either [color = steblue] **Alchemist** [/color] or [color = goldenrod] **Exorcist** [/color] depending on game type.

[/details]


## Playerlist

1. an_gorta_pratai (pre-in)
2. Light (pre-in)
3. Vulgard
4. Chloe
5. Intensify
6. PsychoKang
7. Surge
8. TheBlueElixir
9. ATNoName
10. PokemonKidRyan
11. Wazza
12. Soulshade
13. Zone_Q11
14. Insanity
15. Moleland
16. Frostwolf103
17. Alice
18. Leafia
19. Whysper
20. Centuries
21. SirDerpsalot
22. Magnus
23. ash4fun
24. Clonedcheese
25. Italy
26. N.1

## Backups

1. Napoleon (Low-Priority)
3. CRichard564 (Low-Priority)

## Spectators

1. DatBird (Informed)
2. Marshal (Informed)
3. Katze (Informed)
4. Arete (Informed)
5. sulit (Informed)
6. astand (Informed)
7. KyoDaz (Informed)
8. MaximusPrime (Informed)
10. Marcus_Doodalee (Uninformed)
11. Mist1422 (Informed)
12. Appelsiini (Uninformed)

## Important Links</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 16:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Signups</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DatBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/890">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/890</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 16:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-890</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Sure</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/889">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/889</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 16:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-889</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DatBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Want me to lock thread?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/888">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/888</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-888</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>The randing process is complete and class cards shall now be sent out.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/887">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/887</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 15:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-887</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I rolled scum. Yeet me for freelo</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/886">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/886</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 15:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-886</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SirDerpsAlot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>kinky</s></p>
<h6>dont ban me</h6>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/885">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/885</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-885</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oops. You were talking to Italy that time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/884">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/884</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-884</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>The randing process shall now begin. Please stop speaking, or I, The Mastermind, shall have your heads.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/883">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/883</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-883</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That comment was a reply to italy</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/882">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/882</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-882</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks again, although I still have far to go I think, but I’ll certainly get there eventually.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/881">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/881</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-881</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hey illl move to</p>
<p><strong>/backup</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/880">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/880</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-880</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you fought brilliantly in ToL FM, i’ll never get rid of those screencaps in which you and dat feared a possible cult leader</p>
<p>and fair</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/879">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/879</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-879</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Italy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i had rendered activity based reads completely useless by ToLFM<br>
then i randed scum five times in a row and started to hate existence</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/878">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/878</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-878</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oops. List. Player list.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/877">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/877</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-877</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i mean</p>
<p>you’re getting better, but you’re still more likely to slank when scum</p>
<p>trusting you in BotF 3 was just a hail mary really, it wasn’t any skill; just luck</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/876">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/876</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-876</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re welcome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/875">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/875</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-875</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Leafia" data-post="872" data-topic="83201">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/leafia/40/25929_2.png" class="avatar"> Leafia:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lust</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/eyes.png?v=9" title=":eyes:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/874">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/874</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-874</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I never got to thank you for how hard you fought after i died in CFM2<br>
great work, you did us proud</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/873">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/873</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-873</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks and good. I was added to the player lust.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/872">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/872</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-872</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>looks back on that one time that Geyde kept the old google doc public on FoL</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/871">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/871</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-871</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Italy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wow<br>
okay</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/870">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/870</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-870</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>leafia i just want to say that you’re probably one of the fastest players i’ve ever seen to invalidate meta analysis / meta-based gut reads as a strat against you</p>
<p>i am very impressed with your level of play</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/869">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/869</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-869</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now to make double sure I was correctly added to the playerlist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/868">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/868</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-868</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh yes. This’ll be interesting.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/867">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/867</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-867</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i forgot that i originally was going to be the co-host</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/866">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201/866</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83201-866</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-63-triple-threat-virtuous-full-26-26/83201.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 63 - Triple Threat: Virtuous - FULL (26/26)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
