<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Marksman (Blue Dragon) - Cannoneer (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-marksman-blue-dragon-cannoneer-unseen/17558</link>
    <description>**Marksman** - A tried and true archer who never misses.

Passive:
**Trained Falcon** - At the end of the night, you will be told if the Cult/Unseen successfully completed a night action. (You will NOT be told what action it is. IE: &quot;The Cult or Unseen have successfully carried out at least one night action.&quot;)

Day Ability:
**Disarm** - If a player you select then tries to use a day action, you will &quot;shoot it from their hand&quot;, causing bleeding and making the action fail. (3 uses)

Night Ability 1:
**Eagle Eye** - Watch a player&#39;s room at night. If they leave their room to attack someone, you will instead attack them. If you kill a Blue Dragon, you permanently lose this ability and &quot;Split Arrow&quot;. (Unlimited use)

_^ In other words, I use Eagle Eye on Player1. Player1 decides to kill Player2 that night. I instead kill Player1, since I selected to use Eagle Eye on him. I hope Player1 wasn&#39;t a Knight! :O_

Night Ability 2:
**Split Arrow** - Attack two targets at once. If at least ONE player you kill is NOT Blue Dragon, you will not lose your &quot;Eagle Eye&quot; ability. If BOTH targets are Blue Dragon, you WILL lose &quot;Eagle Eye&quot;. (Single use.)


**Converts to...**


**Cannoneer** - A madman with a love for things that go boom.

Passive:
**Sabotaged Arsenal** - If you are executed during the day, Blue Dragon classes will not be able to use any killing abilities that following night. (Only lasts 1 night.)

Day Ability:
**Firing Squad** - When you vote to execute, all other living Unseen members are counted as voting to execute as well, regardless of how they actually voted. Everyone will still see the other Unseen members voting how they chose; abstain, pardon, etc. (3 uses.)

_^ To explain, if your Unseen members vote Pardon, but you vote Execute, everyone will SEE your Unseen members Pardoning, but their votes will be COUNTED as executions because of your ability._

Night Ability 1:
**Lead Ball** - Fire a heavy projectile at the residence of another player. The target will be blocked from using **day** abilities the next day. (3 uses)

Night Ability 2:
**Incendiary Ball** - Fire a burning projectile at the residence of another player. If they are visited, the visitors (not the target) will all be blocked from using their **day** abilities the next day. (3 uses)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 22:10:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-marksman-blue-dragon-cannoneer-unseen/17558.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Marksman (Blue Dragon) - Cannoneer (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Marksman</strong> - A tried and true archer who never misses.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Trained Falcon</strong> - At the end of the night, you will be told if the Cult/Unseen successfully completed a night action. (You will NOT be told what action it is. IE: “The Cult or Unseen have successfully carried out at least one night action.”)</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Disarm</strong> - If a player you select then tries to use a day action, you will “shoot it from their hand”, causing bleeding and making the action fail. (3 uses)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Eagle Eye</strong> - Watch a player’s room at night. If they leave their room to attack someone, you will instead attack them. If you kill a Blue Dragon, you permanently lose this ability and “Split Arrow”. (Unlimited use)</p>
<p><em>^ In other words, I use Eagle Eye on Player1. Player1 decides to kill Player2 that night. I instead kill Player1, since I selected to use Eagle Eye on him. I hope Player1 wasn’t a Knight! <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/open_mouth.png?v=9" title=":open_mouth:" class="emoji" alt=":open_mouth:"></em></p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Split Arrow</strong> - Attack two targets at once. If at least ONE player you kill is NOT Blue Dragon, you will not lose your “Eagle Eye” ability. If BOTH targets are Blue Dragon, you WILL lose “Eagle Eye”. (Single use.)</p>
<p><strong>Converts to…</strong></p>
<p><strong>Cannoneer</strong> - A madman with a love for things that go boom.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Sabotaged Arsenal</strong> - If you are executed during the day, Blue Dragon classes will not be able to use any killing abilities that following night. (Only lasts 1 night.)</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Firing Squad</strong> - When you vote to execute, all other living Unseen members are counted as voting to execute as well, regardless of how they actually voted. Everyone will still see the other Unseen members voting how they chose; abstain, pardon, etc. (3 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ To explain, if your Unseen members vote Pardon, but you vote Execute, everyone will SEE your Unseen members Pardoning, but their votes will be COUNTED as executions because of your ability.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Lead Ball</strong> - Fire a heavy projectile at the residence of another player. The target will be blocked from using <strong>day</strong> abilities the next day. (3 uses)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Incendiary Ball</strong> - Fire a burning projectile at the residence of another player. If they are visited, the visitors (not the target) will all be blocked from using their <strong>day</strong> abilities the next day. (3 uses)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-marksman-blue-dragon-cannoneer-unseen/17558/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-marksman-blue-dragon-cannoneer-unseen/17558/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-17558-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-marksman-blue-dragon-cannoneer-unseen/17558.rss">[Class Suggestion] Marksman (Blue Dragon) - Cannoneer (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
