<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225</link>
    <description>I thought the reaper to king meta was pretty annoying. But this last game just proves that it&#39;s taking the fun out of the game. King died and they vote me up because I&#39;m confirmed drunk. Cool so confirmed BD king. Everybody all pissed off because reaper didn&#39;t even step up. So the next day since there are no leads I try to get some conversation started so we can deduce who the reaper and unseen are. And someone goes this is dumb let&#39;s exe king and give reaper another chance to step up. So they vote me up. And I say or we can actually play the game and try to figure out who the reaper is. They go nah why do that when he can just step up? And then they were all confused why I was not okay with exing a confirmed BD king to let the reaper reveal himself. then they go dude calm down you&#39;ll win anyway! 

I don&#39;t understand. I&#39;m not here to win by using a cheap strategy. That&#39;s not fun! That takes away the whole purpose of the game. Why is winning and getting an extra 30 gold worth taking the social deduction out of a social deduction game? 

Would this game still be fun if all the NKs and unseen had markings next to their name like the king does? No! Letting the reaper out himself to become a NEUTRAL king is no different. If somebody says I&#39;m reaper, the only response should be oh okay let&#39;s execute you. Not oh okay you should be our king. 

Winning isn&#39;t fun if you didn&#39;t earn the win.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 04:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Damn I wish I knew that I would’ve reported them. I just don’t see how they have fun playing like that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 04:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23225-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225.rss">What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yes, I got warned recently by the plex for exing a royal who stepped forward after everyone saying ‘let reaper be king’ (he was left threat)</p>
<p>report people who kill kings they know are good</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 04:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23225-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225.rss">What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s throwing and reportable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 03:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23225-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225.rss">What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought the reaper to king meta was pretty annoying. But this last game just proves that it’s taking the fun out of the game. King died and they vote me up because I’m confirmed drunk. Cool so confirmed BD king. Everybody all pissed off because reaper didn’t even step up. So the next day since there are no leads I try to get some conversation started so we can deduce who the reaper and unseen are. And someone goes this is dumb let’s exe king and give reaper another chance to step up. So they vote me up. And I say or we can actually play the game and try to figure out who the reaper is. They go nah why do that when he can just step up? And then they were all confused why I was not okay with exing a confirmed BD king to let the reaper reveal himself. then they go dude calm down you’ll win anyway!</p>
<p>I don’t understand. I’m not here to win by using a cheap strategy. That’s not fun! That takes away the whole purpose of the game. Why is winning and getting an extra 30 gold worth taking the social deduction out of a social deduction game?</p>
<p>Would this game still be fun if all the NKs and unseen had markings next to their name like the king does? No! Letting the reaper out himself to become a NEUTRAL king is no different. If somebody says I’m reaper, the only response should be oh okay let’s execute you. Not oh okay you should be our king.</p>
<p>Winning isn’t fun if you didn’t earn the win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 02:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23225-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/what-is-the-point-of-winning-if-its-not-earned/23225.rss">What is the point of winning if it&#39;s not earned?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
