<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406</link>
    <description>These are my previous 3 neut class suggestion. You might of saw them. Just outing them together. Tell me what you think
____________________________
**Name - Peace Keeper** 
**_Faction - Neutral_** 
**_Class - offensive_**

Lore: As this silly war grew, the peace keeper felt sick. After losing his son because of the war he decides to only trust them who are Neutral in the war. Maybe they could help end this… or if all else fails the NK could get rid of them all.

**Passive 1:** 
_Little hope_ - on days where no one die, you gain death immunity that night.

**Passive 2:** 
_Failure_ - if all neutrals die then you will die the next day. If every Neutral is dead except the NK, then you will know who the NK is

**Day Ability 1:** 
_Special connections_ - send your personal mercenary to guard someone. You can guard yourself. They will be alerted that they were guarded by a mercenary. (Unlimited uses)(2 day cool down)

**Day Ability 2:** 
_Hidden dungeon_ - chat with a player of your choice tonight. Separate tab. ( does not work on prince target and can be interrupted by mystic link (unlimited uses)

**Night ability 1:** 
_Showing your true colors_ - pick 3 people and you will know how many are neutral out of the 3. If there is not enough people then you can’t use this ability. (unlimited uses)

Ex. You pick 4,6,9 Message says (“2 out of 3 of your targets are neutral”) or (&quot;No targets are neutral)

**Night ability 2:** 
_Peace treaty_ - declare no trials the next day (2 uses)

**Win condition** - you win if there is another Neutral alive with you at the end of the game(includes NK, if NK is last Neutral alive)

**Notes**: this is a class that can really help both sides. BD might want to keep him alive for protection but also might need to kill him if he is defending the NK

_________________________
**Name - Parasite** 
_**Faction - Neutral**_ 
_**Type - Killer.**_

Special notes: The host will know that they have been infected by a parasite. They now will have to work together to win. If you take a host then the host will appear as Killer to all results

**Passive 1:** 
_Stuck inside_ - if your original body dies then you will still be able to use your abilities. But you will not be able to chat or vote. If your host dies then you die too.

**Passive 2:** 
_Second thoughts_ - you will know what your host is doing. If you don’t pick a host on three days then you will die.

**Day Ability 1**: 
_A new home_ - pick someone to become your host. (1 use)

**Day Ability 2:** 
_Taking care of my body_ - heal your host tonight (4 uses)

**Night ability 1:** 
_Infection_ - infect a person. The next night Anyone who visit him or if he visits anyone else, they will also be infected. After that the next day all of them will die(2 uses). Can’t target King directly but if someone visits king then he will be infected.

_Ex;  _
_Night 1 - parasite infects 4 _
_Night 2 - 4 visits 5, 9 visits 4.  _
_Day 3 - 4,5,9 all die._

**Night ability 2:** 
_Hunger_ - feast on a player, killing them. (If your original body dies then your host body will do the killing, meaning if an observer is watching, he will see your host commit the murder and not you) (infinite uses)

**Win condition** - kill ever main faction and win with your host body

____________________________

**Name - The Vampire** 
**_Class - offensive*_* 
**_Faction - Neutral_**

At the start of the game you are given two targets, similar to scorn. The targets CAN’T have royal blood. Meaning your targets can’t be Drunk,Noble,princess, prince, etc…

**Passive 1:** 
_Quick escape_ - you are immune to death once.

**Passive 2:** 
_Failure_ - (similar to merc) if both your targets die then you will parish.

**Day Ability 1:** 
_Injection_ - give someone royal blood. When you do this it will appear as you whispering to the player. (0 uses)

**Day Ability 2:** 
_Bat messenger_ - all whispers to and from your target or any converted player will be hidden from the public.(unlimited uses)

**Night ability 1** 
 _Just a bit_ - suck someone’s blood. If they have royal blood then you will keep it and gain a use for your. Suck a players blood 3 times and they will die, goes through all kinds of immunity. (Unlimited uses).

**Night Ability 2:**
_Hypnotizing glare -_ convert a play into one of your severest. They will remain their original class but three things will change. (Two uses) (normal conversion rules are applied) (if you cant convert then your ability will not take a use)

1. they will appear Neutral to checks.
2. their win condition will change to “help the Vampire win at all cost”
3. When they are converted, they will know who the vampire is.

**Win condition** - have one of your targets become the king. Then you must help them win with their current faction

**Notes**:
* if your target becomes the king and then dies afterwords then you still have to help the faction he was apart of. Unless other target becomes king.

_Why does he have so much stuff_?? Answer: you must consider that it is going to be very hard for this class to win. Here are the steps;
1. find a player with royal blood.
2. hope your targets don’t die or hopefully you converted a knight to help guard a target.
3. give royal blood to your target without being suspicious
4. get current king killed
5. get your target to be king.
6. help his current faction win.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 17:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>Put it in boxes like this one.</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 17:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54406-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406.rss">My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I reworked some. Hopefully that’s better</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 17:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54406-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406.rss">My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s hard to read…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 16:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54406-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406.rss">My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please reply if there is any errors or typos.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 16:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54406-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406.rss">My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>These are my previous 3 neut class suggestion. You might of saw them. Just outing them together. Tell me what you think</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Name - Peace Keeper</strong><br>
<strong><em>Faction - Neutral</em></strong><br>
<strong><em>Class - offensive</em></strong></p>
<p>Lore: As this silly war grew, the peace keeper felt sick. After losing his son because of the war he decides to only trust them who are Neutral in the war. Maybe they could help end this… or if all else fails the NK could get rid of them all.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 1:</strong><br>
<em>Little hope</em> - on days where no one die, you gain death immunity that night.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2:</strong><br>
<em>Failure</em> - if all neutrals die then you will die the next day. If every Neutral is dead except the NK, then you will know who the NK is</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1:</strong><br>
<em>Special connections</em> - send your personal mercenary to guard someone. You can guard yourself. They will be alerted that they were guarded by a mercenary. (Unlimited uses)(2 day cool down)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong><br>
<em>Hidden dungeon</em> - chat with a player of your choice tonight. Separate tab. ( does not work on prince target and can be interrupted by mystic link (unlimited uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1:</strong><br>
<em>Showing your true colors</em> - pick 3 people and you will know how many are neutral out of the 3. If there is not enough people then you can’t use this ability. (unlimited uses)</p>
<p>Ex. You pick 4,6,9 Message says (“2 out of 3 of your targets are neutral”) or ("No targets are neutral)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2:</strong><br>
<em>Peace treaty</em> - declare no trials the next day (2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - you win if there is another Neutral alive with you at the end of the game(includes NK, if NK is last Neutral alive)</p>
<p><strong>Notes</strong>: this is a class that can really help both sides. BD might want to keep him alive for protection but also might need to kill him if he is defending the NK</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Name - Parasite</strong><br>
<em><strong>Faction - Neutral</strong></em><br>
<em><strong>Type - Killer.</strong></em></p>
<p>Special notes: The host will know that they have been infected by a parasite. They now will have to work together to win. If you take a host then the host will appear as Killer to all results</p>
<p><strong>Passive 1:</strong><br>
<em>Stuck inside</em> - if your original body dies then you will still be able to use your abilities. But you will not be able to chat or vote. If your host dies then you die too.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2:</strong><br>
<em>Second thoughts</em> - you will know what your host is doing. If you don’t pick a host on three days then you will die.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong>:<br>
<em>A new home</em> - pick someone to become your host. (1 use)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong><br>
<em>Taking care of my body</em> - heal your host tonight (4 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1:</strong><br>
<em>Infection</em> - infect a person. The next night Anyone who visit him or if he visits anyone else, they will also be infected. After that the next day all of them will die(2 uses). Can’t target King directly but if someone visits king then he will be infected.</p>
<p>_Ex;  _<br>
_Night 1 - parasite infects 4 _<br>
_Night 2 - 4 visits 5, 9 visits 4.  _<br>
<em>Day 3 - 4,5,9 all die.</em></p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2:</strong><br>
<em>Hunger</em> - feast on a player, killing them. (If your original body dies then your host body will do the killing, meaning if an observer is watching, he will see your host commit the murder and not you) (infinite uses)</p>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - kill ever main faction and win with your host body</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Name - The Vampire</strong><br>
<em><em>_Class - offensive</em>_</em><br>
<strong><em>Faction - Neutral</em></strong></p>
<p>At the start of the game you are given two targets, similar to scorn. The targets CAN’T have royal blood. Meaning your targets can’t be Drunk,Noble,princess, prince, etc…</p>
<p><strong>Passive 1:</strong><br>
<em>Quick escape</em> - you are immune to death once.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2:</strong><br>
<em>Failure</em> - (similar to merc) if both your targets die then you will parish.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1:</strong><br>
<em>Injection</em> - give someone royal blood. When you do this it will appear as you whispering to the player. (0 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong><br>
<em>Bat messenger</em> - all whispers to and from your target or any converted player will be hidden from the public.(unlimited uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong><br>
<em>Just a bit</em> - suck someone’s blood. If they have royal blood then you will keep it and gain a use for your. Suck a players blood 3 times and they will die, goes through all kinds of immunity. (Unlimited uses).</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2:</strong><br>
<em>Hypnotizing glare -</em> convert a play into one of your severest. They will remain their original class but three things will change. (Two uses) (normal conversion rules are applied) (if you cant convert then your ability will not take a use)</p>
<ol>
<li>they will appear Neutral to checks.</li>
<li>their win condition will change to “help the Vampire win at all cost”</li>
<li>When they are converted, they will know who the vampire is.</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Win condition</strong> - have one of your targets become the king. Then you must help them win with their current faction</p>
<p><strong>Notes</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>if your target becomes the king and then dies afterwords then you still have to help the faction he was apart of. Unless other target becomes king.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Why does he have so much stuff</em>?? Answer: you must consider that it is going to be very hard for this class to win. Here are the steps;</p>
<ol>
<li>find a player with royal blood.</li>
<li>hope your targets don’t die or hopefully you converted a knight to help guard a target.</li>
<li>give royal blood to your target without being suspicious</li>
<li>get current king killed</li>
<li>get your target to be king.</li>
<li>help his current faction win.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 16:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54406-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/my-previous-3-neutral-class-suggestions/54406.rss">My previous 3 Neutral class suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
