<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>You can update your Death Note when dead</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/you-can-update-your-death-note-when-dead/36442</link>
    <description>I&#39;m unsure if this should be considered a bug, but it&#39;s unusual enough behavior that I figured I&#39;d report it just in case.

You can update your death note after dying.  This usually gives you very little time (for a normal kill, you can send a message to the living if you rush and update it in between your death and when the person you killed comes up in the death rolecall)...

But a Butler who poisoned the king, or a Hunter who bled anyone, can update their deathnote over a day later and send important information from the dead to the living this way.  That is, you can end up in a situation where the Hunter bleeds someone, dies, gets told who an Unseen / Cult is by a dead investigator, and writes it in their deathnote, causing it to appear to the court a few days later.

Now, of course, since you don&#39;t know for sure who wrote a DN, it&#39;s possible for evils to exploit this, so it might be acceptable.  But I figured it&#39;s worth pointing out the issue.  I&#39;m indifferent to whether it&#39;s actually fixed or not, I just feel it&#39;s something that ought to be mentioned - I know Town of Salem locks your DN in the moment you die to prevent this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 01:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/you-can-update-your-death-note-when-dead/36442.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>You can update your Death Note when dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m unsure if this should be considered a bug, but it’s unusual enough behavior that I figured I’d report it just in case.</p>
<p>You can update your death note after dying.  This usually gives you very little time (for a normal kill, you can send a message to the living if you rush and update it in between your death and when the person you killed comes up in the death rolecall)…</p>
<p>But a Butler who poisoned the king, or a Hunter who bled anyone, can update their deathnote over a day later and send important information from the dead to the living this way.  That is, you can end up in a situation where the Hunter bleeds someone, dies, gets told who an Unseen / Cult is by a dead investigator, and writes it in their deathnote, causing it to appear to the court a few days later.</p>
<p>Now, of course, since you don’t know for sure who wrote a DN, it’s possible for evils to exploit this, so it might be acceptable.  But I figured it’s worth pointing out the issue.  I’m indifferent to whether it’s actually fixed or not, I just feel it’s something that ought to be mentioned - I know Town of Salem locks your DN in the moment you die to prevent this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/you-can-update-your-death-note-when-dead/36442/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/you-can-update-your-death-note-when-dead/36442/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 01:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-36442-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/you-can-update-your-death-note-when-dead/36442.rss">You can update your Death Note when dead</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
