<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can we please rework all who clicked faster interactions?</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/can-we-please-rework-all-who-clicked-faster-interactions/75880</link>
    <description>There are several important interactions that are in the game that pretty much all come down to can I click my day ability faster than you can click yours. A lot of these are with Prince, Mystic or king vs a neutral killing (Possessor or Reaper). While these situations are admittedly not going to come up a whole lot boy does it feel bad to be on the wrong side of it and it can be game losing. I don&#39;t think it&#39;s ideal for a potential game ending interaction to come down to click speed. 

I realize this is a tricky subject to handle and there might not be a real fix that is remotely feasible but it is something that I feel that leaves a negative impression when it does come up. I also realize that nk usually have it the roughest I just don&#39;t think that the game being decided because you are a second to late on your chill or you winning because you were a second faster than the mystic to chill them is compelling game play.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 04:54:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/can-we-please-rework-all-who-clicked-faster-interactions/75880.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can we please rework all who clicked faster interactions?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kylundstrom92]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There are several important interactions that are in the game that pretty much all come down to can I click my day ability faster than you can click yours. A lot of these are with Prince, Mystic or king vs a neutral killing (Possessor or Reaper). While these situations are admittedly not going to come up a whole lot boy does it feel bad to be on the wrong side of it and it can be game losing. I don’t think it’s ideal for a potential game ending interaction to come down to click speed.</p>
<p>I realize this is a tricky subject to handle and there might not be a real fix that is remotely feasible but it is something that I feel that leaves a negative impression when it does come up. I also realize that nk usually have it the roughest I just don’t think that the game being decided because you are a second to late on your chill or you winning because you were a second faster than the mystic to chill them is compelling game play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/can-we-please-rework-all-who-clicked-faster-interactions/75880/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/can-we-please-rework-all-who-clicked-faster-interactions/75880/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 04:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75880-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/can-we-please-rework-all-who-clicked-faster-interactions/75880.rss">Can we please rework all who clicked faster interactions?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
