<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665</link>
    <description>Here a new nice **Priest** class idea:
- **Prayers** (Limited to 3 - night ability): Your god will give you a set of 4 random people from which there will be at least 1 guaranteed unseen/cult player. Can only be used every 2 nights.
- **Pact with the devil** (Limited to 2 - night ability) Select a player. If they are BD, you sell their soul to the devil to reduce your set size by 1 for the prayers skill. *Would be similar to reaper effect (cannot be revived, still in play for 1 day)*
- **The hand of god** (Limited to 2 - day ability) Negate the effect of 1 execute vote.

I would describe this the high risk/high reward investigative class with a ramp up effect. Both night abilities can be used to investigate. With pact with the devil, if you pick someone that is not BD, you will get a notification saying they are not an ally. If you use your pact with the devil on 2 BDs, you can manage to reduce your Prayers set size to 2 which is can be pretty good when combined with other clues you gathered along the way at the cost of 2 BD players. In order to pick BD players with pact with the devil, you have to out them first which might be a nice challenge. As players die, you can check you previous results from prayers to find out who are the remaining unseen/cult players. Priest can prove their existence by using hand of god during the day. It won&#39;t say who used it.

This class could have some nice interaction with the reaper where people would have to ask themselves if there is a reaper or not when they lose their soul. That would probably help the reaper class which has a low win rate currently. Publicly announcing your set from the prayers result could attract some unwanted attention on you like many other investigative classes. The Prayers and the pact with the devil skills would also take into account framed players and investigative immunity skills like the In The Shadows skill on Mastermind adding some uncertainty in the results early game like the other investigative classes.

This new class would be unique. This new class would **NOT** be night immune or convert immune. I guess there would be a need for another converted priest class again.

I guess there is a lot of theory crafting that could go around to make this class well balanced. The numbers above and the mechanics are up for discussion.

This would have a chance to replace one of the current investigative class each game. It would not be guaranteed to be in each game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 15:52:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DelizSeemack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let’s assume Priest kill 2 BD and die N5 which would be one of the worst scenario. Priest would have probably use 2 of his Prayers skill as well. That gives you 2 sets (one of 3-4 players and one of 2-3 players depending in which order Priest used his skills) where you have 1 guaranteed unseen/cult player in. Assuming the Priest wrote those sets in his logs or told them to the dead speaking/revived death knight, these information can be communicated to the remaining BD team. As players die, those sets become smaller and you almost guaranty this information with out 1 or 2 unseen/cult (1 per set potentially). No other investigative class can give such good result in my humble opinion.</p>
<p>So the initial prayers result is quite RNG, but the result of that information is really good later on when players die. As players die, that RNG goes away.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 15:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10665-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665.rss">New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scoundrella]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I second what Burrito says. Rng is terrible in a game like this (haven’t you died N1 as Prince post priest removal? It’s awful or died N1 as anything really lol).</p>
<p>ALSO your pact with the devil ability sounds too volatile. You claim that it is high risk high reward. Assuming you use both charges, and then by N5 (assuming you survived this point) you have either found 2 non allies, found an non ally and killed a bd, or killed 2 bd. (Non allies could be neutrals, from the sound of your description which neuters the investigative usefullness of the ability).</p>
<p>And then you die N5. And for what? Taking 2 BD with you to prove… nothing? Not worth at all iimo</p>
<p>Its like kings "allies"ability but, youre not the king so people will call you scorn, or suspicious or something. Or worse, claiming “not ally” on a neutral  and everyone happens to go at them to find its just a poor alch.</p>
<p>The randomness of the checking ability would be even more terrible later on I feel. Would it just choose who to investigate for you? I guess I am not quite sure how it works</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 01:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10665-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665.rss">New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>RNG = Bad</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 01:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10665-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665.rss">New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DelizSeemack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here a new nice <strong>Priest</strong> class idea:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Prayers</strong> (Limited to 3 - night ability): Your god will give you a set of 4 random people from which there will be at least 1 guaranteed unseen/cult player. Can only be used every 2 nights.</li>
<li>
<strong>Pact with the devil</strong> (Limited to 2 - night ability) Select a player. If they are BD, you sell their soul to the devil to reduce your set size by 1 for the prayers skill. <em>Would be similar to reaper effect (cannot be revived, still in play for 1 day)</em>
</li>
<li>
<strong>The hand of god</strong> (Limited to 2 - day ability) Negate the effect of 1 execute vote.</li>
</ul>
<p>I would describe this the high risk/high reward investigative class with a ramp up effect. Both night abilities can be used to investigate. With pact with the devil, if you pick someone that is not BD, you will get a notification saying they are not an ally. If you use your pact with the devil on 2 BDs, you can manage to reduce your Prayers set size to 2 which is can be pretty good when combined with other clues you gathered along the way at the cost of 2 BD players. In order to pick BD players with pact with the devil, you have to out them first which might be a nice challenge. As players die, you can check you previous results from prayers to find out who are the remaining unseen/cult players. Priest can prove their existence by using hand of god during the day. It won’t say who used it.</p>
<p>This class could have some nice interaction with the reaper where people would have to ask themselves if there is a reaper or not when they lose their soul. That would probably help the reaper class which has a low win rate currently. Publicly announcing your set from the prayers result could attract some unwanted attention on you like many other investigative classes. The Prayers and the pact with the devil skills would also take into account framed players and investigative immunity skills like the In The Shadows skill on Mastermind adding some uncertainty in the results early game like the other investigative classes.</p>
<p>This new class would be unique. This new class would <strong>NOT</strong> be night immune or convert immune. I guess there would be a need for another converted priest class again.</p>
<p>I guess there is a lot of theory crafting that could go around to make this class well balanced. The numbers above and the mechanics are up for discussion.</p>
<p>This would have a chance to replace one of the current investigative class each game. It would not be guaranteed to be in each game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 23:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10665-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-priest-class-idea-investigative/10665.rss">New Priest Class Idea (Investigative)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
