<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Private match breaks when going publc</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/private-match-breaks-when-going-publc/18152</link>
    <description>#### What happened?

Every time we try to join a game as a group with a large enough private match (usually greater than 8 people) a lot of the people get kicked from the game and back to the main menu (while sometimes a few people get into a game). This breaks the lobby and segments the party. We&#39;re trying to play full games even if our party doesn&#39;t have 16 people.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?

I expect the whole private party to get into the same game with 16 people in it.

#### Steps to reproduce:

1. Start a private match
2. Get a good amount of people in it but less than 16 (usually we have around 8 to 14 players.
3. Go public.

#### Comments:

Sometimes it works sometimes it doesn&#39;t. Usually the lobby breaks somehow. Usually some people just stay in the lobby, some people get into a game, some people get kicked. But we barely ever all get into the same public game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 21:56:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/private-match-breaks-when-going-publc/18152.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Private match breaks when going publc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danny135]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>Every time we try to join a game as a group with a large enough private match (usually greater than 8 people) a lot of the people get kicked from the game and back to the main menu (while sometimes a few people get into a game). This breaks the lobby and segments the party. We’re trying to play full games even if our party doesn’t have 16 people.</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>I expect the whole private party to get into the same game with 16 people in it.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<ol>
<li>Start a private match</li>
<li>Get a good amount of people in it but less than 16 (usually we have around 8 to 14 players.</li>
<li>Go public.</li>
</ol>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>Sometimes it works sometimes it doesn’t. Usually the lobby breaks somehow. Usually some people just stay in the lobby, some people get into a game, some people get kicked. But we barely ever all get into the same public game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/private-match-breaks-when-going-publc/18152/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/private-match-breaks-when-going-publc/18152/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 21:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-18152-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/private-match-breaks-when-going-publc/18152.rss">Private match breaks when going publc</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
