<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Vampire</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267</link>
    <description>So, I&#39;ve never tried to make a class idea before but here we go

Vampire (**Special**) (**Neutral**): Objective is to live to become the king or if all royal blood is gone or have died

Passive abilites

Blood lost: If your target is bleeding and you bite them they will die

The body of a vampire: Immune to bleeding, poison, coverting and target changing

Active day abiltys

**Bat spy**: Be able to hear whispers too and from king (2 charges) (2-day cooldown)
**Smell of dragons**: Send out a bat to bite a player with royal blood, making it look like they&#39;re bleeding (1 charge)

Active night abilitys

**Bite**: Visit someone drinking some of they blood, healing you from all negative effetcs, attacks and making them lose death immunity that night. (2 charges, gain charge if bite worked succusfully)
(If you bite a person with the royal blood passive, they will lose it and you gain royal blood)
(If you bite a person you will appear as that players faction until you bite a new person)
(Same player can&#39;t be bitten twice)
(If bite 3 players without the Royal blood ablity, you won&#39;t be able to use bite, and lose your Immune effects)

**DNA sample**: Check if player has the royal blood passive (infinite charges)

Your strategy should be to find and remove all other Royal Blood courtiers so that you may climb the throne unopposed or win trying. If unable to remove all the royal blood, you can always try claim the throne for yourself. Try to side with either BD or Evil faction, as Neutrals have nothing to offer you and likewise. If jailed by prince good claims would be:
The Alchemist
Princess
Noble
The Physician

Bite is also a high risk/high reward ability as if you bite to many non-royal bloods you will become weak, but you also need to keep drinking to make sure you heal yourself incase you get attacked.

Important Info:
-If a person dies the same night you bite them, you will **not** gain the Royal blood passive but still be heald
- You will be informed, if the person you bite was Royal blood or not
- Bite cannot be used on king
- DNA sample does not tell if the Unseen/Cult/Blue dragon/Neutral
- You will not know who got the Bleed effect from Smell of Dragons as the purpose of the ability is for them to out themself to you
- People who lose they royal blood passive will not know until the king is dead and someone has to step forward

(V-1.1.0 Removed Alot of unnessacry abilities and combined some. Idea&#39;s from me and Solic &lt;3)
(V-1.2.1 Added Blood lost and Changed Bat spy to 2-day cooldown)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 23:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You cannot both be special type and offensive type.</p>
<p>At the moment it is only possible to have 2 day abilities, 2 passives and 2 night abilities. I’d suggest to just remove That’s not wine, Who Am I? Also Put Blue Blood, You are what you eat and Overflow as extra pointers under the bite skill, because they are part of that skill and not a passive ability in my opinion.</p>
<p>The concept is definitely interesting however and I am all for opposing kings more. They currently are too important in the meta.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 23:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39267-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PastaLord]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, I’ve never tried to make a class idea before but here we go</p>
<p>Vampire (<strong>Special</strong>) (<strong>Neutral</strong>): Objective is to live to become the king or if all royal blood is gone or have died</p>
<p>Passive abilites</p>
<p>Blood lost: If your target is bleeding and you bite them they will die</p>
<p>The body of a vampire: Immune to bleeding, poison, coverting and target changing</p>
<p>Active day abiltys</p>
<p><strong>Bat spy</strong>: Be able to hear whispers too and from king (2 charges) (2-day cooldown)<br>
<strong>Smell of dragons</strong>: Send out a bat to bite a player with royal blood, making it look like they’re bleeding (1 charge)</p>
<p>Active night abilitys</p>
<p><strong>Bite</strong>: Visit someone drinking some of they blood, healing you from all negative effetcs, attacks and making them lose death immunity that night. (2 charges, gain charge if bite worked succusfully)<br>
(If you bite a person with the royal blood passive, they will lose it and you gain royal blood)<br>
(If you bite a person you will appear as that players faction until you bite a new person)<br>
(Same player can’t be bitten twice)<br>
(If bite 3 players without the Royal blood ablity, you won’t be able to use bite, and lose your Immune effects)</p>
<p><strong>DNA sample</strong>: Check if player has the royal blood passive (infinite charges)</p>
<p>Your strategy should be to find and remove all other Royal Blood courtiers so that you may climb the throne unopposed or win trying. If unable to remove all the royal blood, you can always try claim the throne for yourself. Try to side with either BD or Evil faction, as Neutrals have nothing to offer you and likewise. If jailed by prince good claims would be:<br>
The Alchemist<br>
Princess<br>
Noble<br>
The Physician</p>
<p>Bite is also a high risk/high reward ability as if you bite to many non-royal bloods you will become weak, but you also need to keep drinking to make sure you heal yourself incase you get attacked.</p>
<p>Important Info:<br>
-If a person dies the same night you bite them, you will <strong>not</strong> gain the Royal blood passive but still be heald</p>
<ul>
<li>You will be informed, if the person you bite was Royal blood or not</li>
<li>Bite cannot be used on king</li>
<li>DNA sample does not tell if the Unseen/Cult/Blue dragon/Neutral</li>
<li>You will not know who got the Bleed effect from Smell of Dragons as the purpose of the ability is for them to out themself to you</li>
<li>People who lose they royal blood passive will not know until the king is dead and someone has to step forward</li>
</ul>
<p>(V-1.1.0 Removed Alot of unnessacry abilities and combined some. Idea’s from me and Solic &lt;3)<br>
(V-1.2.1 Added Blood lost and Changed Bat spy to 2-day cooldown)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 23:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39267-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-vampire/39267.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Vampire</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
