<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485</link>
    <description>This was going to be a reply to the other thread (which obviously wants to go in the other direction), but after I started writing it up I realized it was worth its own topic.

I believe we should revise the rules to allow a Mercenary to turn on their first contract (regardless of the method, including by outing them directly and deliberately) provided they still have a chance to get a second one.  This might require rewording their goal slightly (eg. &quot;survive to the end with a living contract&quot;, which is similar to what they have now, but subtly different in that it doesn&#39;t imply that they necessarily need to keep their first contract alive provided they have a second one lined up.)

Mercenaries would be required to play to a Mercenary victory still, meaning they can only betray their contract when they believe it makes them more likely to win as a Mercenary (note that this is different from being converted - you&#39;re always playing to the same goal, that goal would just be &quot;survive to the end of the game with a living contract&quot; rather than &quot;protect this particular person.&quot;)

A Mercenary would *not* be allowed to play towards a Sellsword or Ritualist victory, only to Mercenary victories.  They&#39;d only be allowed to betray their first contract in situations where they can credibly believe that doing so makes them more likely to win as a mercenary.

Here&#39;s my reasoning.

1.  Mercenaries are assigned completely at random at the start of the game.  It is better for the game if there is at least [i]some[/i] risk of betrayal to balance out that randomness - getting a mercenary assigned at the start should not be a flat, no-brainer buff.

2.  The possibility of betrayal leads to more interesting interactions with mercenaries - it gives people reasons to potentially lie to the mercenary, and therefore means that the mercenary has to sometimes doubt what their contract tells them.  Telling your mercenary that you are not BD now has more risk, which makes it a more interesting strategic decision.

3.  The more options people have, the more interesting it is to try and predict their behavior, and the more variety we get in terms of gameplay.  If a mercenary doesn&#39;t always [i]have[/i] to side with their first contract, but has the option of turning on them, it opens up a much wider array of strategies for the mercenary and for people playing against them, and adds new considerations for the person they&#39;re contracted to.

4.  Some people might fear this could lead to kingmaker scenarios with mercs.  I think that&#39;s unlikely, since a merc can only get a second contract if the game doesn&#39;t end when their first one dies (ie. a mercenary still wouldn&#39;t have the option to turn on their contract late in the game when doing so would lead to an immediate loss for them - that would still be gamethrowing.  You have to credibly believe you can get a second contract before the game ends for this to be allowed.)  I feel that with this change, mercenaries would mostly just switch sides when they want to be on a team that&#39;s more likely to win, which I feel is strategically interesting (if you want to sway a mercenary into betraying their contract, you&#39;d have to convince them you&#39;re a better bet.)  This is particularly interesting because it leads to a role that could be swung between BD and Cult / Unseen - or even, potentially, NK - without necessarily being a kingmaker in the traditional sense, since their decisions would be based on who they think is most likely to win.

5.  While this is less important than the gameplay implications...  thematically, it makes sense.  Real-world mercenaries turned on their employers all the time.  &quot;Sorry, but siding with the prince is a safer bet&quot; is a thematically appropriate thing for a mercenary to do.  The theme of the class is a *mercenary*, not a fanatical bodyguard; the very name itself means someone whose loyalties are weak and constantly-shifting based on who can pay them the best.  The potential for betrayal is a logical thematic aspect of the mercenary as a concept.

Note that this would be purely a rules change (aside from maybe the subtle rewording to the Mercenary&#39;s goal.)  It wouldn&#39;t involve any direct gameplay changes beyond indicating that betraying your first contract while they&#39;re alive is now allowed.

But anyway, basically.  ToL should be a game of backstabbing, betrayal, and secrets.  Right now the Mercenary is too straightforward.  Revising their goals slightly so they can betray their first contract (when they believe it would make them more likely to win with their second) fits in the thematic of the role and would generally make it more interesting both to play as and to play in a game with.

(Also, in case it isn&#39;t obvious:  Mercenaries would never be allowed to betray their second contract, since doing so always leads to a loss for them.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 20:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would still want to know because I have been drafting suggestions of abilitys that do. You’ve probably seen them on my butler and CW suggestions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 20:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ellie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scout does. It doesn’t really matter anyways, since there are no abilities that affect day abilities.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 20:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wait does Imprison not count as a day Ability in the code? Is the same true for Scout and Sacrifice?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 19:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ellie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Imprision isn’t really a day ability. It doesn’t work like other day abilities. Even if it did, everyone will just vote up the Merc. Then kill your target the next day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 19:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The prince can’t do that if they are immune to day ability’s too</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 17:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UncannyLuck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Kills the Merc and then exes you the next day? Yeah actually that’d probably happen frequently. Though you could just put the Merc up that day (or jail the Merc and exe their contact the next day so you can have that sweet, sweet contact)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 17:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ellie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s nice until the Prince kills them and then they execute you the next day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think merc should be buffed/reworked but not have the ability to get a new contract. It would be more interesting if he had to make sure his starting contract survives until the end.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="UncannyLuck" data-post="10" data-topic="45485">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/prince-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> UncannyLuck:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Protective Custody (1) - Force a pardon on your contact; they will be unable to vote, speak <strong>Or be targeted by day ability’s</strong> for the remainder of the day. This action will reveal you to the court.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do this</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UncannyLuck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ooo what about giving the Merc a force pardon that’s only usable on their first contact? Or other tools that make keeping your first contact alive easier than your second.</p>
<p>Maybe not force pardon but the ability to prevent them from being voted up (first contact only)? Or make it more difficult to vote them up (like an ability that makes it so your target has to be voted up by 60% of the court).</p>
<p>Edit: Actually, give them both!<br>
Warn (2) - Contact requires 60% of the court to vote to be put up for treason. The court is alerted that a mercenary has warned them to back off.<br>
Protective Custody (1) - Force a pardon on your contact; they will be unable to vote or speak for the remainder of the day. This action will reveal you to the court.</p>
<p>If your first contract dies, you lose your remaining charges of Warn and PC as well as half your remaining guard charges. My reasoning here is that it should be fairly hard for your target to die unless you’re not doing your job, so if that happens you’re punished without immediately losing. Protective Custody alerts to allow the court to go after you for doing that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 15:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I see 2 methods of making you not want to bus your first contract.</p>
<p>1 - Punishing you for losing him. You are less likely to bus him if you auto lose a guard or if you have to wait before getting a new one thus having a good chance of dying.</p>
<p>…or unintuitively</p>
<p>2 - Reduce the risks attached to losing your second contract. If your guards refresh when you change contracts then why not use all of them with the first one? Or if you can change contracts the same day he dies then the game ending first isn’t that big of a worry so you won’t be in a hurry to replace him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 11:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="6" data-topic="45485" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Personally I think that he should be mechanically changed to incentiveise whatever your intent is. However you are all arguing about was is when he is stating what should be.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed.  Whichever way the devs want it, I would like to see the mechanics reinforce that direction.</p>
<p>If you aren’t supposed to bus your contract, then… prevent them from voting them up and voting to execute them.  Also toss something in about how it’s game throwing in the description or something.</p>
<p>If busing is fine, then leave it as it is, since that’s more or less what we have now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 11:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Luxx" data-post="5" data-topic="45485">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/luxx/40/1222_2.png" class="avatar"> Luxx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re not allowed to bus your contract.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good to know, since it happened to me earlier today.  He bussed me because I was “evil” and then I lost even though Unseen had numbers with his vote, he voted against me specifically and voted to execute me, which led to my making the post about mercs not being able to kill their contracts from the mechanical end of things.</p>
<p>Maybe next patch add some text to the Merc card so people know about it?  Because no one except me in the game thought it was wrong and I only really thought it was wrong because he didn’t have time to pass his contract afterwards (though I could’ve been wrong and maybe he did pass it).  And we could have instantly won if he’d stayed loyal to me and Rebounded one of my accusers from the previous day.  Instead he voted me up (the deciding vote) and then voted to execute me (again the deciding vote).</p>
<p>I mean I get why they get a 2nd contract, it makes sense.  The problem is that mechanically they can vote up and vote to execute said contract and it actually makes sense to a lot of the time.  And for people that don’t visit the forums (and even those that do like myself) don’t realize you can’t bus your contract.  I never do because I enjoy the RP aspect of the class since it’s so different, but I’ve never batted an eye when someone has done it unless I thought it would ultimately make them lose in the end.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 11:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally I think that he should be mechanically changed to incentiveise whatever your intent is. However you are all arguing about was is when he is stating what should be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 11:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bart_Auringer" data-post="4" data-topic="45485">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/bart_auringer/40/2131_2.png" class="avatar"> Bart_Auringer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can bus your first contract as long as you think you can win with the next one as far as I know, unless it’s stated someplace on the forums or something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s against the rules to go against your win condition.<br>
Your win condition as Mercenary is to keep your contract alive.</p>
<p>The reason Merc can get a new contract is so she doesn’t automatically lose the game if her original target happens to be on the losing side (ex converted n1 and found by sheriff n2, that’d be a loss d3 for 2 people)</p>
<p>You’re not allowed to bus your contract.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 11:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean… it doesn’t even technically say that.  You can bus your first contract as long as you think you can win with the next one as far as I know, unless it’s stated someplace on the forums or something.  In game the only rule stated is you have to try to win.  You can win by busing your first contract pretty easily, especially if it’s something like the MasterMind and it’s past Day 3.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 10:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nothing says you have to guard your target at all. You are just not allowed to do anything to deliberately get them killed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 10:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As near as I can tell, they can do that currently?<br>
Cause I see them do this fairly often.  Hell, most mercs only guard the first contract once so they can save the guards for the “real” contract.</p>
<p>I’m missing the change here, but it’s late so that might be me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 10:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This was going to be a reply to the other thread (which obviously wants to go in the other direction), but after I started writing it up I realized it was worth its own topic.</p>
<p>I believe we should revise the rules to allow a Mercenary to turn on their first contract (regardless of the method, including by outing them directly and deliberately) provided they still have a chance to get a second one.  This might require rewording their goal slightly (eg. “survive to the end with a living contract”, which is similar to what they have now, but subtly different in that it doesn’t imply that they necessarily need to keep their first contract alive provided they have a second one lined up.)</p>
<p>Mercenaries would be required to play to a Mercenary victory still, meaning they can only betray their contract when they believe it makes them more likely to win as a Mercenary (note that this is different from being converted - you’re always playing to the same goal, that goal would just be “survive to the end of the game with a living contract” rather than “protect this particular person.”)</p>
<p>A Mercenary would <em>not</em> be allowed to play towards a Sellsword or Ritualist victory, only to Mercenary victories.  They’d only be allowed to betray their first contract in situations where they can credibly believe that doing so makes them more likely to win as a mercenary.</p>
<p>Here’s my reasoning.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Mercenaries are assigned completely at random at the start of the game.  It is better for the game if there is at least <span class="bbcode-i">some</span> risk of betrayal to balance out that randomness - getting a mercenary assigned at the start should not be a flat, no-brainer buff.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The possibility of betrayal leads to more interesting interactions with mercenaries - it gives people reasons to potentially lie to the mercenary, and therefore means that the mercenary has to sometimes doubt what their contract tells them.  Telling your mercenary that you are not BD now has more risk, which makes it a more interesting strategic decision.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The more options people have, the more interesting it is to try and predict their behavior, and the more variety we get in terms of gameplay.  If a mercenary doesn’t always <span class="bbcode-i">have</span> to side with their first contract, but has the option of turning on them, it opens up a much wider array of strategies for the mercenary and for people playing against them, and adds new considerations for the person they’re contracted to.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Some people might fear this could lead to kingmaker scenarios with mercs.  I think that’s unlikely, since a merc can only get a second contract if the game doesn’t end when their first one dies (ie. a mercenary still wouldn’t have the option to turn on their contract late in the game when doing so would lead to an immediate loss for them - that would still be gamethrowing.  You have to credibly believe you can get a second contract before the game ends for this to be allowed.)  I feel that with this change, mercenaries would mostly just switch sides when they want to be on a team that’s more likely to win, which I feel is strategically interesting (if you want to sway a mercenary into betraying their contract, you’d have to convince them you’re a better bet.)  This is particularly interesting because it leads to a role that could be swung between BD and Cult / Unseen - or even, potentially, NK - without necessarily being a kingmaker in the traditional sense, since their decisions would be based on who they think is most likely to win.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>While this is less important than the gameplay implications…  thematically, it makes sense.  Real-world mercenaries turned on their employers all the time.  “Sorry, but siding with the prince is a safer bet” is a thematically appropriate thing for a mercenary to do.  The theme of the class is a <em>mercenary</em>, not a fanatical bodyguard; the very name itself means someone whose loyalties are weak and constantly-shifting based on who can pay them the best.  The potential for betrayal is a logical thematic aspect of the mercenary as a concept.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Note that this would be purely a rules change (aside from maybe the subtle rewording to the Mercenary’s goal.)  It wouldn’t involve any direct gameplay changes beyond indicating that betraying your first contract while they’re alive is now allowed.</p>
<p>But anyway, basically.  ToL should be a game of backstabbing, betrayal, and secrets.  Right now the Mercenary is too straightforward.  Revising their goals slightly so they can betray their first contract (when they believe it would make them more likely to win with their second) fits in the thematic of the role and would generally make it more interesting both to play as and to play in a game with.</p>
<p>(Also, in case it isn’t obvious:  Mercenaries would never be allowed to betray their second contract, since doing so always leads to a loss for them.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 10:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-45485-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/allow-mercenaries-to-deliberately-betray-their-first-contract/45485.rss">Allow mercenaries to deliberately betray their first contract</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
