<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suggestion on post king nerf bd power level</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402</link>
    <description>With king&#39;s major nerf i feel bd feels less potent to what it used to. 
I believe one from each class type should be secured for bd in order to increase chance of healers/investigatives for bd
especially with the heavy nerf king took having investigative power secured for bd would be essentially very useful
and it would make up for the king&#39;s major loss.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 01:25:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion on post king nerf bd power level</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandy_Claws]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s kind of a nerd and a buff at the same time for the king. He is no longer expected to give investigative checks which leads to kings not being hung for 3 days of “blue dragon” checks. They have to take more of a role in leading BD in the actual game now and sifting through information.</p>
<p>The old king be it BD or evil/Neutral if they did not out unseen/cult by day 3 then they get hung. If they check someone d2 and they show evil and the scorned framed him, king gets hung. There were so many ways to not be able to control BD king because there are so many factors that go into it. I’ve heard the argument " King should save their checks for later in the game d3-6"  you tell that to the table as king and see if you are not given a free rope necklace. People are inexperienced in dealing with people who wanna play the game intelligently and their viewed as evil instead of waiting for more information.</p>
<p>With these new changes they can fact check more accurately because what is the 2 classes the MM, assassin, invoker all claim? Princess and drunk. Now if anyone claims that the king can check early instead of waiting them d1-3 unless relevant info is revealed. This saves them from being hung for no reason and gives them a fighting chance through the game. Also not to mention no more " not ally" checks will save neuts from getting murdered d1-3. And this causes the reaper and possessor and sorcerer will not have to focus the king down night after night until he does because their not gonna get checked.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 01:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15402-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402.rss">Suggestion on post king nerf bd power level</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion on post king nerf bd power level</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The more guaranteed roles there are, the more we move toward a rolelist like in ToS, which is a bad thing. If the problem is BD can’t win without investigatives (Which I’m not say is or isn’t true) then the solution is to make it so they can win, not force those classes to spawn.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 04:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15402-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402.rss">Suggestion on post king nerf bd power level</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion on post king nerf bd power level</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cuban_Pete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With king’s major nerf i feel bd feels less potent to what it used to.<br>
I believe one from each class type should be secured for bd in order to increase chance of healers/investigatives for bd<br>
especially with the heavy nerf king took having investigative power secured for bd would be essentially very useful<br>
and it would make up for the king’s major loss.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 19:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-15402-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-on-post-king-nerf-bd-power-level/15402.rss">Suggestion on post king nerf bd power level</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
