<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327</link>
    <description># Welcome to SFoL - Hand of Byzantium!

Hosted by Alice

**In a far away land, a magnanimous empire rules fairly over its land. However, familiar threats seem to be looming on the horizon…**

Welcome to Hand of Byzantium, a SFoL I was working on for a while before I took a break. The setup here is simple. The uninformed majority needs to find and execute the traditional informed minority, that is either the Unseen or the Cult, alongside the Neutral Killer. The only difference here is that the uninformed majority is a different faction than the Blue Dragon, plus I’ve added some of my own neutrals, most of them being anti-town by nature, into this match. The King is also replaced with an Emperor that is more social and active than the classic King.

# Rules

![|20x20](/user_avatar/forum.imperium42.com/queen_alfa/40/6988_1.png) [Forum of Lies Official Hub](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/forum-of-lies-official-hub/1515?u=luxy) [Forum of Lies](/c/forum-matches/forum-of-lies)

&gt; Welcome to the wonderful wacky (And sometimes stressful) world of FoL! Useful Links [Class Cards Thread!](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fol-class-cards-clean-with-no-talking/1998) [Spreadsheet of Complete, Ongoing and Planned FoL and SFoL games! Also includes information on how to sign up to host.](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1eAoQS7saD6SL-s9v0Z6A5Fthb_XrraZt_IvBuslsoBs/edit?usp=sharing) [The Forum of Lies Discord Server!](https://discord.gg/YU7aVWd) [A friendly “how to get started” guide by one of our own players! ](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/forum-of-lies-getting-started/49368) [ New player guide by our good boy](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/forum-of-lies-new-player-guide/71790) General Gameplay Infomation Rules Follow the Global Forum Rules If you haven’t posted content in 36 hours, you’ll be prodded for inactiv…

# Gameplay

Days will be 48 hours long, or shorter if someone is executed.
Nights will be 24 hours days long.
Actions are done in your class card.
Unseen or Cult members will talk through a private topic. They can talk there during both the day and night
The Cabalists will have a permanent private topic.
The Librarian, the Archivist, and the Librarian!Apostle will have their own private topic for their log network.
The Arbiter will have his own private topic that shall be usable for the entire length of the match, and they’ll be allowed to invite one player to it for the entire game.
There will be one private topic per day for the Imperial Chat as different players will be allowed to enter them by night. They can only be used during the specific night.
The Unseen class cap is 3, and the Cult class cap is 4.
The maximum amount of duplicate classes is 3, barring unique class or those with the Prestige passive.
When you receive a card you will have 24 hours to reply, confirming you have received it.

# Executions

To accuse someone say “/accuse [player]” or “/vote [player]”
Should the votes reach the majority, that player will be executed and the day will end.

# Journals

Message me your entire journal, the last draft I receive before you die shall be the one displayed

# To Join

To join, simply express interest in joining by saying something like “I want to join” or “/join” or “/in” or “sign me up, coach” or whatever you want

# Class Cards


[details=Emperors]

&gt;# [color = purple]The Corrupt Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Special[/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Assassin&#39;s Brotherhood (Night)** - Sends an assassin to a player. This attack does not count as a visit and cannot be stopped, if a Coroner checks the cause of death by this attack then it will show up as killed by an Assassin. Can only be used on the second night or after that you are crowned. - One use
**Conspiracy (Night)** - Permanently makes a player be seen as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - 2 uses
_Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Unseen.

&gt; # [color = &quot;blanchedalmond&quot;] The Decadent Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt;**[color = gray]Neutral Special[/color]**
**End of a Dynasty (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two.  If the Decadent King dies after the day he was crowned ended, then there will not be any King elections to replace him.
**Inept Government (Passive)** - In the night after the Viscount is crowned, if not executed, all faction checks will always return Hand of Byzantium and healing will always fail. After winning, the Decadent Emperor cannot accuse anyone of treason, loses his King abilities, vote in trials, and will not be factored in for the voting count required to put a player on trial.  
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
_Live to become Emperor for at least a day._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Viscount

&gt;# [color = darkred]The Devout Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt;**[color = darkred]Cult Special[/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Sacrificial Offering (Night)** - Prevents healing on a player for the rest of the match. - One use
**Priest King (Night)** - Converts a player to the Cult if there is one or less Cultist alive, if there are more then the charge of Priest King will not be used. Can only be used on the second night or after that you are crowned. - One use
_Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Cult.

&gt;# [color = mediumvioletred]The Faithful Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Special [/color]** 
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor. 
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Faithful Guard (Night)** - Sends a guard to a player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Faithful Advisers (Night)** - Sends an adviser to a player. They will be immune to conversions for the night. - 3 uses
_Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Insurgent, providing the starting Emperor was a Corrupt Emperor or a Devout Emperor.


&gt;# [color = darkkhaki]The Hunting Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = grey] Neutral Special [/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die or leave the match, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once. You are immune to death at night. If all players of your target class die at night or you miss using Imperial Ballista&#39;s both shots, then you will commit suicide.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Imperial Ballista (Day)** - Kills a player in broad daylight. - 2 uses
**Royal Detectives (Night)** - Learns your target&#39;s class type and faction. You may use this on two players the same night. - Infinite uses
**Royal Lookouts (Night)** - Learns who visited your target and who they visited. You may use this on two players the same night. - Infinite uses
*Use Imperial Ballista to kill a player whose class started out as your target.* 

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Headhunter

&gt;# [color = lightcoral]The Pacifist Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Special [/color]** 
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor. You are immune to death at night for the first three nights.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once. If a second Hand of Byzantium member is executed, you will commit suicide the following night.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Devotion (Day)** - If your target hits majority and they are a member of the Hand of Byzantium then you will die in their stead. - Two uses
**Transparency (Night)** - All investigations will net accurate results for the night. - 2 uses
**Imperial Pardon (Night)** - Prevents your target from being voted tomorrow. - 3 uses
*Make sure no more than one Hand of Byzantium member is wrongfully executed.* 

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Missionary.

&gt;# [color=red]The P[/color][color=orange]sych[/color][color=yellow]opath[/color][color=green]ic E[/color][color=blue]mper[/color][color=purple]or[/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = grey] Neutral Special [/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King.
**Insanity (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night. Additionally, your vote counts as two.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Personal Execution (Night)** - Send a guard to kill a player. - Infinite uses
_Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Basilisk
&gt; * The Berserker
&gt; * The Doppelgänger
&gt; * The Occultist
&gt; * The Ifrit
&gt; * The Lich
&gt; * The Succubus
&gt; * The Werewolf

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]The Righteous Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]Hand of Byzantium Special[/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor. If you are executed for treason your first accuser will die alongside you.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Praetorian Guard (Night)** - Sends a guard to a player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Imperial Advisers (Night)** - Sends an adviser to a player. They will be immune to conversions for the night. - 3 uses
_Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * Any member of the Hand of Byzantium
&gt;* The Senex, providing they are aligned with the Hand of Byzantium.

&gt;# [color = black]The Spiteful Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = grey] Neutral Special [/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor. 
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once. You are immune to death at night.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Embargo (Night)** - Occupies a player and prevents all non-killing or conversion actions against them. - 2 uses
**Stigmatize (Night)**  - Permanently frames the player, making them show up as Unseen or Cult to faction checks or Killer to class type checks. -  One use
*See the Hand of Byzantium defeated at any cost.* 

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Begrudged
&gt; * The Necromancer
&gt; * The Insurgent, providing the starting Emperor was a Righteous Emperor.
&gt; * The Senex, providing they are aligned against the Hand of Byzantium.


&gt;# [color = darkorchid] The Tyrannous Emperor [/color]:shield: 
&gt; **[color = grey] Neutral Special [/color]**
&gt;**Reign of Terror (Passive)** - Your guards will bypass both night immunity and healing if your target did not vote for you during the election phase. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor.
&gt;**L&amp;rsquo;etat, C&amp;rsquo;est Moi (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night and bleeding. Additionally, your vote counts as two. For the first time you are executed for treason, you will instantly pardon yourself when on trial and kill your first accuser in broad daylight. You cannot use Sadistic Guards the night after this passive activates.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Sadistic Guards (Night)** - Allows the Tyrannous King to select two players who will then be attacked and killed by his guards. - Infinite uses
_Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way._

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Archduke.

&gt;# [color = sienna]The Vengeful Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = grey] Neutral Special [/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die or leave the match, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor. Upon fulfilling your win condition, you will leave the match.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once. You are immune to death at night.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Karma (Night)** - Marks a player as a target, permanently frames them, and learns their class type. Does not work if the target is not aligned with the Hand of Byzantium. - Infinite uses
**Draconian Law (Night)** - Marks a player as a target if they are aligned with the Hand of Byzantium. They will silently require two less votes to be executed for the coming day. - 2 uses
*See two of your marked targets publicly executed.* 

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Crone

&gt;# [color = firebrick]The Vampiric Emperor[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = grey] Neutral Special [/color]**
**Dynastic Cycle (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next Emperor.
**Head of State (Passive)** - Your vote for treason counts as two. You may use both your day abilities at once. If you are using Vampiric Envoy then you will heal yourself if you would be nightkilled. You will always be under the effect of Vampirism and you will know all living players who are Bitten.
**Audience (Day)** - Select up to three players. They will be able to speak in an Imperial Chat with you tonight. Per night you may also infect an additional player in your Imperial Chat with Vampirism. - Infinite uses
**Sword of Damocles (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use
**Vampiric Envoy (Night)** - Bites a player, infecting them with Vampirism, preventing healing, and occupying them. Players infected with Vampirism will be shown as a Neutral and a Killer for investigative abilities and will have their visits hidden. - Infinite uses 
*Make sure at least half of the living remainder of the Court is infected with Vampirism by the end of the game.* 

&gt;Crowned from:
&gt; * The Strigoi

[/details]


[details=&quot;Hand of Byzantium - Investigative&quot;]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Actuary [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Sharp Eyes (Day)** - Selects a player during the day. In the following night you will be notified if they have used any Day abilities. - 2 uses
&gt;**Notice to Detail (Day)** - At the beginning of the night, you will be told how many day abilities were used the previous day. - 2 uses
&gt;**Inventory (Night)** - Selects a player and you will be informed of the total number of uses they have for both their night abilities combined. Abilities with unlimited usage will count as zero. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Taxman [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Sharp Eyes): Corax&#39;s Mirror (Day)** - Along with being notified if they used a day ability, you will also learn which ability your target used. - 2 use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Arbiter [/color] :crossed_swords: :shield:  
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Special [/color]**
&gt;**Inside Knowledge (Passive)** - At the start of the match you will know which faction the Hand of Byzantium is going agaist.
&gt;**Tenacity (Passive)** - You cannot be occcupied nor redirected, and both of your night abilities can be used at the same time. However, at the same time all protective abilities will fail on you and any kill that targetted you cannot be occupied or redirected. This passive cannot be removed.
&gt;**Entrust (Day)** - Selects a player during the day, this cannot be your n0 green check. They will be immune to conversions for the remainder of the game and will share a neighborhood with you. - One use
&gt;**Imperial Judgment (Night)** - Checks a player&#39;s alignment and kills them if they are a member of the Unseen or the Cult, but at the same time cannot bypass protecting, tailoring, and framing effects. You will be notified of your target&#39;s faction at the end of the night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Imperial Providence (Night)** - Heal and prevent conversions on a chosen player, the conversion protection. - Infinite uses.
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; Cannot be converted.

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Fortuneteller [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Numerology (Day)** - Tells you how many Hand of Byzantium-aligned players are still alive by the beginning of the coming night. Does not take the Emperor&amp;rsquo;s alignment into account. - 2 uses
**Shuffle Deck (Night)** - Grants an additional charge of Tarot Card. - Infinite uses
**Tarot Card (Night)** - Select three players. By the end of the night you will receive from one to three cards. Each card will tell the role of one of the selected player. Special-type classes will return the same result for Investigative-type classes and Killer-type classes will return the same result for Offensive-type classes. Tarot Card bypasses anything that would prevent visits but you can still be occupied. - 0 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Sibyl [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Shuffle Deck (Night)**
**Tarot Card (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Numerology): Divination by Blood (Day)** - Tells you of which Hand of Byzantium classes are still alive and how many. - 2 use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Governor [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Kingmaker (Passive)** - Your vote during Emperor elections silently counts as three votes.
**Certify (Day)** - Grants Royal Blood to your target. - 3 uses
**Trace Lineage (Night)** - Informs you whether your target has Royal Blood or not. - Infinite uses
**Background Check (Night)** - If an Emperor&amp;rsquo;s election was held during the previous day, then the Governor will be informed of how many votes each faction received. - 1 use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Chancellor [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Kingmaker (Passive)**
**Certify (Day)**
**Trace Lineage (Night)**
[color = darkred]**Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Background Check): Guidance of the Blood God (Night)** - If an election for Emperor happens tomorrow, then only votes for members of the Cult will count. - 1 use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Socialite [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Guest List (Day)** - By the end of the coming night, you will know how many players of each faction visited you. - 2 uses
**Social Links (Night)** - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets&amp;rsquo; class type groupings match. Groups are Special/Investigative, Social/Support, and Killer/Offensive. You will receive either no match if they are from different groups, a good match if they are in the same group, and a perfect match if they are the same class type. - Infinite uses
**Faction Links (Night)** - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets&amp;rsquo; alignments match. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Marchioness [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**Social Links (Night)**
**(Guest List): Gate of Blood (Day)** - You will learn whoever visits them the coming night. - 2 use
[color = darkred]**Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Faction Links): Blasphemous Waltz (Night)** - You will convert an additional player to the Cult if the Cult Leader converts tonight. - One use


&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Watchman [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Tracking (Day)** - You will learn if your target left their room last night. - 2 uses
&gt;**Silent Stalking (Night)** - You will learn who your target visits this night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Midnight Vigil (Night)** - You will learn who visits your target this night. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Stalker [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Seeker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Hand of Byzantium - Social&quot;]

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Cabalist [/color]
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Ancient Cabal (Passive)** - Cabalists may only roll in groups of two. You will have an all-day chat with the other Cabalist. You are immune to conversion while the other Cabalist is still alive.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Letter with no Sender (Day)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Cryptic Communications (Night)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player and they will be able to post a reply. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Secretive Connections (Night)** - If alive, the other Cabalist will not be able to be voted tomorrow. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Exiled [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Ancient Cabal): Cult Traditions (Passive)** - The Cult Leader will be seen as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks while you are alive.
**Letter with no Sender (Day)**
**Cryptic Communications (Night)**
**(Secretive Connections): Influence of Anstreim (Night)** - Prevents another Cultist from being voted tomorrow. - One use


&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Coroner [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Grave Focus (Day)** - In addition to the results from Exhume or Forensics, you will also learn the class of their target&amp;rsquo;s killer. If the killer is a Psychopathic or Tyrannous Emperor then it will show their previous classes instead. - 2 uses
&gt;**Exhume (Night)** - Selects a deceased player and you will learn of all effects the target received the night they died. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Forensics (Night)** - Selects a deceased player and you will learn of every player that visited them during the entire match. Can only be used on players that died the fourth night or later. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Undertaker [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Exhume (Night)**
**Forensics (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Grave Focus): Corruption of Corax (Day)** - Causes a player to flip as another class if they are executed on trial. - One use

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Librarian [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Repository (Passive)** - You start in a public log network by yourself. Players in the network will be allowed to read the logs of any other player in the network. The Repository remains open while the Librarian is still alive regardless if they have been converted.
**Archive (Day)** - Invites a player to the log network. The player must accept before joining and can choose to leave at anytime. Can only invite two players per day. - Infinite uses
**Revoke (Night)** - Removes a player from the log network. - Infinite uses
**Shutdown (Night)** - Deactivates the Unseen or Cult day chat for the next day and night. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Archivist [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Repository): Library of Corax (Passive)** - You will be able to use Archive and Revoke along with your normal night and day abilities as an Apostle, while keeping the log network. Cult members will be able to use the network as well.
**(Shutdown): Echoes of Anstreim (Night)** - The Cult will obtain a copy of the Emperor&#39;s messages in the Imperial Chat at the end of the night. - 3 uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Magistrate [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod]  Hand of Byzantium Social [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
**Judicial Decree (Day)** - Resets the votes, allowing only you and your target to be put on trial for today. - 2 uses
**Disenfranchise (Night)** - Silently reduces the amount of votes required to execute a target by one. - Infinite uses
**Impeach (Night)** - Kills the Emperor and automatically takes their place, becoming a Righteous Emperor. Cannot be used until the third night. - 1 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Judge [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Apostle [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**Judicial Decree (Day)**
**Disenfranchise (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Impeach): Rise of the Blood King (Night)** - Kills the Emperor and automatically takes their place, becoming a Devout Emperor. Cannot be used until the third night. - 1 uses

[/details]

[details=Hand of Byzantium - Killer]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Crusader [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Providence (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the Hand of Byzantium faction visits you this coming night, they will be prevented and bled. You cannot use Hand of God after using Providence.- One use
**Hand of God (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Hand of Byzantium visits them they will be bled by you. This does not stop their actions. - Infinite uses
**Deus Vult (Night)** - Attacks and kills two targets. You will also die of exhaustion the night they use this ability regardless of the ability&amp;rsquo;s outcome. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Fanatic [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Acolyte [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
&gt;**(Providence) Blood Providence (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the Cult visits you this coming night, they will be prevented and bled the next day. - 2 uses
&gt;**(Hand of God) Hand of Mithras (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Cult visits them they will be bled. This does not stop their actions. - Infinite uses
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Deus Vult): Incarnation of Mithras (Night)** - Allows the Cult Leader to kill an additional target if you are sacrificed. - 1 uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Duelist [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Schuld (Passive)** - If you have killed any Hand of Byzantium-aligned players in the match, then you will not be allowed to receive votes to become the Emperor.
**Versetzen (Day)** - Grants night immunity for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then you will gain a use of Zornhau. - 2 uses
**Mittelhau (Night)** - Redirects the selected player&amp;rsquo;s action to you while also granting yourself immunity to all redirected attacks and conversions, then attack the player. If you successfully kill a player then you will gain a use of Zornhau. Disables the your night abilities if the target is aligned with the Hand of Byzantium. - Infinite uses
**Zornhau (Night)** - Prevents you from being occupied or redirected, then attacks the your target and kills them, bypassing healing and night immunity. Disables your night abilities if the target is aligned with the Hand of Byzantium. - 0 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Baronet [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Acolyte [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**(Schuld): Grausamkeit (Passive)** - If you become a Devout Emperor, then you&#39;ll gain a second use of Sacrificial Offering. 
**(Versetzen): Opfern (Day)** - Grants night immunity to you for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then the Cult Leader&#39;s next Blood of Mithras will be free of charge. - 2 uses
**(Mittelhau): **Vergeltung** (Night)** - Redirects the player onto you. If they attack you then you will counterattack and kill them. - Infinite uses
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Zornhau): Königsmord (Night)** - Kills the Emperor, bypassing everything. If the you kill a Devout Emperor, then you will commit suicide. - 1 uses

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Thaumaturge [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Thaumaturgic Focus (Passive)** - You are immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Thunder (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Thunder on your target, causing them to explode and kill the player before they are converted while also putting the conversion on cooldown. You are notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the conversion happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses
**Sigil of Fire (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Fire on your target, causing them to explode and kill any player that attacks the target, but does not prevent any actions against them. You are notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the attack happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Arcanist [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Acolyte [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Sigil of Thunder): Thunderbolt of Corax (Night)** - If the Cult&#39;s conversion is off cooldown then you can put it on cooldown to enact an additional kill that is guaranteed to succeed. - Infinite uses
**(Sigil of Fire): Inferno of Mithras (Night)** - You will kill yourself and anyone visiting you. - One use

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Warrior [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Combat Ready (Passive)** - If you are attacked during the first two nights, you will be immune and will counterattack instead of dying.
**Bloodlust (Passive)** - For every successful kill, you will gain an additional night of Combat Ready.
**Raging Axes (Night)** - Attacks and kills a player. If the target was Hand of Byzantium-aligned, then you will lose his night abilities and they will be shown as Unseen or Cult to faction checks. - Infinite uses
**Taunt (Night)** - Redirects the target&amp;rsquo;s night action to the yourself. Redirects past the second night will trigger Combat Ready. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Marauder [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Acolyte [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Bloodlust): Blood for Blood (Passive)** - If you are sacrificed for Blood of Mithras, then the kill will bypass all forms of protection.
**(Raging Axes): Anstreim&#39;s Paranoia (Night)** - All Killer-type classes will be show as members of this Cult for this night. - One use
[/details]



[details=&quot;Hand of Byzantium - Support&quot;]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Bard [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Pure Wits (Day)** - In the coming night you will be immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. - 3 uses
&gt;**Crescendo (Night)** - If your target is redirecting, occupying, or attacking, then they will bypass immunities during this night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Allegro (Night)** - For this night, your target will be healed from Bleeding and gain both occupation immunity, conversion immunity and night immunity. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Minstrel [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Allegro): Chants of Corax (Night)** - All members of the Cult will be seen as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - 2 uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod]The Eccentric [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Magus/Steam Field (Day)** - You will deploy a M/S Field around yourself, granting you night immunity and conversion protection for the coming night. - One use
**Magus/Steam Golem (Night)** - Sends out a M/S Golem to guard your target, giving them night immunity and conversion protection for this night. - Infinite uses
**Magus/Steam Mirror (Night)** - You will send a M/S Mirror onto your target&amp;rsquo;s room, causing any player visiting them to visit themselves while also bypassing redirection immunity. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Lunatic [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Magus/Steam Golem): Mithras&#39; Automaton (Night)** - Causes a Cult members to be night immune and show as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks for the night. - Infinite uses

&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Patron [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Emergency Funds (Day)** - If your target has a limited usage ability with zero uses, then you will silently give them an additional use. Cannot target the Emperor. - One use
**Patronage (Night)** - If your target uses a limited-usage ability this coming night, then they will not consume a use of it. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Auditor [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Emergency Funds): Generosity of Mithras (Day)** - Gives an additional charge for all of the Cult&#39;s limited use abilities. - One use


&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Squire [/color]
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
**Cowardice (Passive)** - Grants night immunity to you for the first three nights or until the Squire remembers a class, whichever comes first.
**Pick up the Mantle (Night)** - Allows you to select a non-unique Hand of Byzantium-aligned class from the Graveyard. You will change your class to the selected one by the end of the night. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple]The Page [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Cowardice): Initiation (Passive)** - You will be seen as a member of the Hand of Byzantium for the first three nights to faction checks.
**(Pick up the Mantle): Corax&#39;s Guidance (Night)** -You will train to become like another cultist and become the non-unique class of a target deceased Cult player and may also target a dead Cult Leader, if they were a different non-unique cult class before they were Cult Leader, to become the class they used to be. (If they used any Cult Points, you receive the powers they chose with them, and if they had left over Cult Points you may take abilities that they could have taken) - 1 use


&gt;# [color = goldenrod] The Surgeon [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Support[/color]**
&gt;**Self-Aid (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
**Coagulant (Day)** - You will grant a player immunity to bleeding. - One use
**Surgery (Night)** - Heals a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and curing any bleeding they were suffering from. - Infinite uses
**Miracle Touch (Night)** -  You will heal a player, giving them the effect of Surgery for this and the coming night. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple]The Plague Doctor [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Ritualist [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Self-Aid): Wells of Blood (Passive)** - You will survive the first Blood of Mithras that hits you.
**(Coagulant): Cursed Blood (Day)** - Your target will not be able to be healed for the rest of the game. - One use
**(Miracle Touch): Blood Purity (Day)** - You will permanently make a player seem Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - One use
[/details]


[details=Hand of Byzantium - Offensive]
&gt;# [color = goldenrod]  The Druid [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Isolation (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt;**Wall of Thorns (Day)** - For the following night prevents non-Hand of Byzantium classes from visiting you and will Bleed them. The Bleeding will kill them if they are not healed the next night. -One use
&gt;**Glyph of Decay (Day)** - Selects a player and all healing and removal of Bleeding on them will fail for the next two nights. - 3 uses
&gt;**Glyph of Lethargy (Night)** - You will occupy a player for tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Glyph of Sloth (Night)** - You will occupy two players for tonight. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Forest Witch [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Wall of Thorns): Vines of Mithras (Night)** - For the following night prevents non-Cult classes from visiting the Ritualist and will Bleed them. The Bleeding will kill them if they are not healed the next night. -One use

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Overseer [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Overrule (Day)** - Causes your first target to select their second target if they use any day abilities today. - 2 uses
&gt;**Red Tape (Day)** - The Emperor&#39;s night actions will fail tonight. - 2 uses
**Order of Relocation (Night)** - Forces your first target&#39;s night action to be redirected to your second target. - Infinite uses
**Order of Exchange (Night)** - Select two players and force them to target each other. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Bureaucrat [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]

&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Sentinel [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Alertness (Day)** - Grants immunity to occupation and to target changing the coming night. - 3 uses
**Detainment (Night)** - Silently removes all of the passives and night immunity from your target. The Detainment will also last until the end of the next night except when it comes to removing Royal Blood, which lasts two days. - Infinite uses
**Curfew (Night)** - Occupies your target if they attempts to attack or convert a player. - 2 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Infiltrator [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Curfew): Aid of Corax (Night)** - Causes all night actions on their target to succeed. - 2 uses


&gt; # [color = goldenrod] The Warden [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = goldenrod] Hand of Byzantium Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Isolate (Day)** - Prevents your target from using Day Abilities. - 2 uses
**Incarcerate (Night)** - Occupies your target wiile at the same time preventing all visits to them. - Infinite uses
**Divest and Removal (Night)** - Removes all limited-use abilities charges from your target. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Torturer [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**Isolate (Day)**
**Incarcerate (Night)**
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(**Divest and Removal**): Offerings to Mithras (Night)** - Removes all limited-use abilities charges from their target and they will bleed in the middle of the coming day. - One use.
[/details]



[details=Unseen and Converts]
&gt;# [color = purple] The Arcanist [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Social [/color]**
**Arcane Focus (Passive)** - You are immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Illusion (Night)** - Choose a class and sets a Sigil on another Unseen player and they will show up as the chosen class to any Investigative roles that visits them. The Sigil is destroyed once the target is visited by an Investigative, requiring them to be recast. - Infinite uses
**Sigil of Madness (Night)** - Puts a Sigil of Madness on a player, permanently giving them a Mind Warp effect until you die. - 1 use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Archivist [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Social [/color]**
**Prestige (Passive)** - Only one class with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
**Concealed Access (Passive)** - Allows all Unseen members to read the logs on the public log network. Can also use both day abilities during the same day and both night abilities on the same night.
**Prosecutor&#39;s  Notes (Day)** - Allows the Unseen to gain a log on the Arbiter&#39;s posts in his chat. - 3 uses
**Archive (Day)** - Invites a player to the log network. The player must accept before joining and can choose to leave at anytime. Can only invite two players per day. - Infinite uses
**Revoke (Night)** - Removes a player from the log network. - Infinite uses
**Censorship (Night)** - Deletes a target&amp;rsquo;s logs if they die the same night. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Assassin [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Killer [/color]**
**Hidden Blade (Day)** - Cut your target, causing them to bleed. They will bleed and die in two nights if not healed. - 3 uses (shared)
**Distract (Day)** - Distract a player, rendering them unable to any day abilities for the rest of the day. - 1 use
**Assassinate (Night)** - Kill a player. - Infinite uses
**2-for-1 (Night)** - Kill two target players. - 1 use (shared)
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Auditor [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Offensive [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Black Market (Passive)** - Upon becoming the Assassin, you will gain one additional use of 2-for-1 and two additional uses of Nightshade Poison.
**Audit (Night)** - Checks if your target has the Royal Blood passive. If they have it then the target will not be able to step up during the Royalty phase while the Auditor is alive. - Infinite uses
**Confiscate (Night)** - If the target has any abilities with finite usage, then you will remove one usage from each of their abilities. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Baronet [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Gerissen (Passive)** - If you become the Emperor, then you will gain an additional use of Assassin&#39;s Brotherhood. 
**Vom Tach (Night)** - Deflects any incoming attack against all members of the Unseen and kills the attacker. - Three uses
**Missgunst (Night)** - Removes Royal Blood from a target for the remainder of the game. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Blasphemer [/color]:shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Social [/color]**
&gt;**Incantations (Passive)** - You may speak with the dead during the night.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Heretical Decree (Day)** - For the lynch today all players will be lynched at L-2. - One use
&gt;**Black Mercy (Night)** - Selects a dead Hand of Byzantium-aligned player and forces them to use their primary night action on a living one. Cannot be used on Killer classes. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Spiritual Merge (Night)** - Binds a dead player to you, allowing them to speak while dead for as long as you are alive, but they will be removed from dead chat. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Bureaucrat [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Overrule (Day)** - Causes your first target to select their second target if they use any day abilities today. - 2 uses
&gt;**Red Tape (Day)** - The Emperor&#39;s night actions will fail tonight. - 2 uses
**Order of Relocation (Night)** - Forces your first target&#39;s night action to be redirected to your second target. - Infinite uses
**Order of Exchange (Night)** - Select two players and force them to target each other. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Chancellor [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Investigative [/color]**
**Kingmaker (Passive)** - Your vote during Emperor elections silently counts as three votes.
**Forged Documents (Day)** - The Chancellor grants the Royal Blood passive to a member of the Unseen. - One use
**Overthrow (Day)** - If the Emperor at L-3, then the Chancellor can force the court to execution them. - One use
**Trace Bloodline (Night)** - Informs you whether your target has Royal Blood or not and their precise class if they do. - Infinite uses
**Stigmatize (Night)** - Removes Royal Blood from your target for two nights. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Exiled [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Social [/color]**
&gt;**Unseen Traditions (Passive)** - You will always be seen as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only up to two classes with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
&gt;**Letter with no Sender (Day)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Cryptic Communications (Night)** - Sends an anonymous message to a player and they will be able to post a reply. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Influence of the Black Rose (Night)** - Prevents another Unseen-aligned player from being voted tomorrow. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Fanatic [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Killer [/color]**
**Piety (Day)** - The Fanatic will be shown as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks if investigated the coming night. - 3 uses
**Martyrdom (Day)** - If a player is executed this day, the Fanatic can choose to sacrifice themselves in order to stop the execution and save the accused played while also bleeding their first accuser. - 1 use
**Malleus Maleficarum (Night)** - Bleeds any player that attempts to visit your target tonight. - 3 uses
**Regicide (Night)** - Attacks and kills the King while bypassing all forms of healing and immunities. Regicide will also kill the Fanatic the same night. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Forest Witch [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Offensive [/color]**
**Isolation (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
**Nightshade Curse (Day)** - Selects a player and for the next two nights they will not be able to be healed. - 2 uses
**Wall of Roots (Day)** - Causes all visits on the target to be prevented the following night. - 1 use
&gt;**Curse of Lethargy (Night)** - You will occupy a player for tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Curse of Sloth (Night)** - You will occupy two players for tonight. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Infiltrator [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Offensive [/color]**
**Alert (Passive)** - Grants you immunity to occupation at night and to target changing.
**Tamper (Day)** - Any day ability your target uses will be redirected to themselves. - 2 uses
**Detainment (Night)** - Silently removes all of the passives and night immunity from your target. The Detainment will also last until the end of the next night except when it comes to removing Royal Blood, which lasts two days. - Infinite uses
**Off-Limits (Night)** - Puts a barrier around their Mastermind or Assassin, causing the next Hand of Byzantium-aligned investigative role to automatically be prevented if they try to visit them. You will be informed when the barrier activates. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Judge [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Social [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Prestige (Passive)** - Only one class with Prestige can spawn the entire game.
**Judicial Decree (Day)** - Resets the votes, allowing only you and your target to be put on trial for today. - 2 uses
**Judicial Conspiracy (Day)** - If your Mastermind is executed today then you will take their place. - One use
**Disenfranchise (Night)** - Reduces the amount of votes required to execute a player by one. - Infinite uses
**Usurp (Night)** - Kills the Emperor and automatically takes their place, becoming a Corrupt Emperor. Cannot be used until the third night. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Lunatic [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Offensive [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**Magus/Steam Pulse (Day)** - Release a M/S Pulse around a chosen member of the Unseen, causing all players who visit them to be prevented from visited and occupied for the next night. - One use
**Magus/Steam Irradiator (Night)** - Sends out a M/S Irradiator to a target, preventing any healing on them this night. Cannot be used on the same target twice in a row. - Infinite uses
**Magus/Steam Explosive (Night)** - For the night, the Assassin will kill all players who visit their target in addition to their target themselves. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Marauder [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Offensive [/color]**
**Carnage (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation, death at night, and will counterattack against attackers. This passive is lost once you are promoted to an Assassin.
**Aura of Dread (Day)** - All non-Killer roles will be prevented from visiting the Marauder this coming night. - One use
**Boast (Night)** - Redirects the target player to yourself - Infinite uses
**Glare (Night)** - Occupies a player for the night. If your target is successfully occupied and is also attacked the same night then they cannot be healed and their night immunity will be bypassed. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Marchioness [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
**The Woman Behind the Man (Passive)** - You will appear as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks and will be promoted straight to Mastermind if the Mastermind dies, regardless of when they die or if the Assassin is still alive. This passive is not lost when you are promoted to an Assassin, only when you become the Mastermind.
**VIP List (Day)** - By the end of the next night you will know which players visited the Mastermind that night. - 3 uses
**Social Links (Night)**  - Select two players and you will receive a positive result providing both targets’ class type groupings match. Groups are Special/Investigative, Social/Support, and Killer/Offensive. You will receive either no match if they are from different groups, a good match if they are in the same group, and a perfect match if they are the same class type. - Infinite uses
**Night Waltz (Night)** - Removes the cool-down on the Mastermind&#39;s Convert the next time they successfully convert a player. - One use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Mastermind [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Special [/color]**
**Can&amp;rsquo;t Touch This (Passive)** - Immune to death at night, occupation and target changing. Players who attempt to occupy you or change your target will believe it succeeded. Additionally, you will know who you would&amp;rsquo;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.
**Lurking Presence (Passive)** - If you die, then the starting Assassin will take your place. You appear as Hand of Byzantium to faction checks.
**Shadowy Presence (Day)** - Selects what class type you will be shown as to investigators and whether you have Royal Blood or not. Can be used alongside Foresight. - Infinite uses
**Foresight (Day)** - Determine a player&amp;rsquo;s converted class by the end of the day if they can be converted. - 4 uses
**Convert (Night)** - Change target player into the Unseen version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown
**Dirty Work (Night)** - If there are no more Unseen members left, you can become The Assassin and you will use Assassinate on your target. - 1 use
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Minstrel [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Support [/color]**
**Silvertongue (Passive)** - The Minstrel will appear as Hand of Byzantium for faction checks.
**Pure Wits (Day)** - In the coming night you will be immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. - 3 uses
**Ballad (Night)** - Select an Unseen player and for this night and they will be shown as Hand of Byzantium for faction checks. - Infinite uses
**Crescendo (Night)** - If your target is redirecting, occupying, or attacking, then their night actions will be guaranteed to succeed this night. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple] The Page [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Support [/color]**
**Innocent Youth (Passive)** - Causes you to appear as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks until they remember a class.
**Ascending Villain (Night)** - Allows you to select a Hand of Byzantium-aligned class from the Graveyard. The Page in turn will become their Unseen equivalent by the end of the night. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Plague Doctor [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Support [/color]**
&gt;**Self-Aid (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
**Hemophilia (Day)** - Causes a player to be unable to receive healing for the rest of the match. - One use
**Herbal Medicine (Night)** - Heals a player, preventing them from dying tonight, and curing any poison and bleeding they were suffering from. - Infinite uses
**Quarantine (Night)** -  Permantly causes an Unseen-aligned player to be seen as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Sibyl [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
**Arithmancy (Day)** - Informs you the precise number of Neutrals, Unseen, and Hand of Byzantium-aligned players are still alive by the beginning of the coming night. Does not take the Emperor&#39;s alignment into account. - 2 uses
**Fated Deck (Night)** - Grants an additional charge of Major Arcana. - Infinite uses
**Major Arcana (Night)** - Select three players. By the end of the night you will learn all of their class types. - 0 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]The Stalker [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
&gt;**Tracking (Day)** - You will learn if your target left their room last night. - 2 uses
&gt;**Eavesdrop (Day)** - You will learn who is invited to the Imperial Chat at the start of the night. - 2 uses
&gt;**Vigilant Stalking (Night)** - You will learn who your target visits along with who visits them this night. - Infinite uses
&gt;**Pinpoint (Night)** - You will learn who visits the Arbiter and who will be visited by them tonight. - 2 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Taxman [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Investigative [/color]**
**Precise Details (Passive)** - At the beginning of the night, you will be told how many day abilities and which abilities were used.
**Avarice (Day)** - Selects a player during the day. You will be notified if they have used any Day abilities this day and which abilities were used. - 3 uses
**Inventory (Night)** - Selects a player and you will be informed of the total number of uses they have for both their night abilities combined. Abilities with unlimited usage count as zero. - Infinite uses
**Confiscate (Night)** - If the target has any abilities with finite usage, then you will remove one usage from each of their abilities. - 3 uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = purple]  The Torturer [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Offensive[/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice.
&gt;**Solitary Confinement (Day)** - Prevents your target from using Day Abilities. - Infinite uses
**Incarcerate (Night)** - Prevents your target from visiting tomorrow while also preventing visits to them. - Infinite uses
**Enhanced Interrogation (Night)** - Removes all limited-use abilities charges from your target and they will bleed in the middle of the coming day. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*


&gt;# [color = purple]  The Undertaker [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]  Unseen Social [/color]**
**Embalm (Day)** - If a player is executed, then they will flip a class of your choosing. Usable during trials. - One use.
**Desecrate (Night)** - If the targeted player dies at night, then they will flip a class of your choosing. - Infinite uses
**Grave Robbing (Night)** - If the targeted player dies at night, then their logs will appear blank. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/details]


[details=&quot;Cult and Converts&quot;]

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Acolyte[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;[color=darkred] **Cult Killer**[/color]
**Spirit of Mithras (Passive)**  - Starting with the second use of the Cult Leader’s Blood of Mithras, if you would be sacrificed, the first time you will not die.
**Curse of Mithras (Night)**  - If the target is bled tomorrow, they will die in 1 night instead of 2 nights. - 1 us
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any Neutrals that oppose you.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Apostle[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;[color=darkred] **Cult Social**[/color]
&gt; **Eminence of Mithras (Day)**  - At the end of the day, you will learn who voted for whom during today’s king election. - 2 uses
&gt; **Influence of Corax (Night)**  - In the coming day your target will require one less vote to be executed. - 2 uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Cult Leader[/color]  :crossed_swords: :shield: 
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Special**[/color]
&gt; **Train (Passive)**  - At any point before the start of the first night, you may message the GM and choose the Cult alts that the Cult class that spawned with you will receive, based on a non-unique class they can be converted from. If you do not choose the Cult alts, they will receive a random valid set.
&gt; **Fanaticism (Passive)**  - You are immune to death at night until you successfully convert a player, where upon this passive is disabled. (Starting Cult Leader only)
&gt; **Disguise (Day)**  - If the target player dies tonight, they will appear as a class of your choice. - 3 uses
&gt; **Rupture (Day)**  - Cause a player to bleed. They will bleed and die in two nights if not healed. - 3 uses (shared)
&gt; **Brainwash (Night)**  - Change target player into the Cult version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown
&gt; **Blood of Mithras (Night)**  - Kill a Cult player and a non-Cult player. The first two uses of this will not kill the cult player. - Infinite uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Invoker[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Offensive**[/color]
&gt; **Fanatic (Passive)**  - Immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt; **Bewilder (Day)**  - Target player uses a day ability on themselves. - 1 use
&gt; **Strings of Corax (Night)**  - Control a player into targeting another. - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Ritualist[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Support**[/color]
&gt; **Will of Mithras (Day)**  - Make a Cult Member appear as selected BD class to investigations. - 1 use
&gt; **Strength Of Corax (Night)**  - The Cult Leader’s Blood of Mithras will bypass night immunity tonight. - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # [color=darkred]The Seeker[/color]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Investigative**[/color]
&gt; **Expose (Day)**  - Reveal who the Arbiter entrusted at the start of the night. - 1 use
&gt; **Gaze (Night)**  - Learn a player’s class type. - 2 uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/details]
[details=Neutrals]
&gt; # [color = &quot;plum&quot;] The Begrudged [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Social [/color]** 
**Hellbent (Passive)** - You cannot be killed by players who are not members of the Hand of Byzantium.
**Unyielding Vengence (Passive)** - All your abilities are locked and will only be usable if you are executed for treason.
**Whispers of the Damned (Day)** - Sends a message to a player, they will know you sent it and they can answer back. - Infinite uses 
**Influence of the Damned (Day)** - You will be able to vote while dead for the day. - Two uses
**Spiteful Hex (Night)** - Permanently frames a player who voted for your execution. - Two uses
**Eye for an Eye (Night)** - Puts a curse on one of the players who voted for your execution, they will need two less votes to be executed. - One use
*See the Hand of Byzantium defeated at any cost.* 

&gt; # [color = &quot;sienna&quot;] The Crone [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Social [/color]** 
**Reclusive (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night and to bleeding.
**Malicious (Passive)** - You can use both day abilities at once. You are immune to occupation and redirection.
**Evil Intentions (Day)** - Causes a player to silently require one less vote to be executed. - Three uses
**Grudge (Day)** - Marks a player as a target and learns their class type. Does not work if the target is not aligned with the Hand of Byzantium. - Infinite uses
**Haunting Presence (Night)** - Frames a player, making them show up as Unseen or Cult to faction checks or Killer to class type checks. - Infinite uses 
**Nightmare (Night)** - Mind warps a player, giving them incorrect feedback for the night. - Two uses
*See two of your marked targets publicly executed.* 

&gt; # [color = &quot;darkkhaki&quot;] The Headhunter [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Investigative [/color]** 
**Hunter&#39;s Will (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night until the third night from non-Hand of Byzantium classes. You will be given a class for your target. The class will be aligned with the Hand of Byzantium and cannot be the Arbiter. If all players of that class are nightkilled or executed during the day, you will commit suicide.
**Respite (Passive)** - Upon fulfilling your win condition, you will leave the match.
**Snipe (Day)** - Kills a player in broad daylight. - One use
**Camouflage (Day)** - Prevents all players who are your target of being visited the coming night. - Three uses
**Probing Mind (Night)** - Learns your target&#39;s class type and faction. - Infinite uses
**Stalking the Prey (Night)** - Learns who visited your target and who they visited. - Infinite uses
*Use Snipe to kill a player whose class started out as your target.* 

&gt; # [color = &quot;mediumvioletred&quot;] The Insurgent [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Offensive [/color]** 
**Adversity (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night and bleeding while the starting Emperor is alive.
**Rebellion (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
**Sabotage (Day)** - Prevents the starting Emperor&#39;s ability from taking effect tonight. - Two uses. 
**Decoy (Night)** - Occupies a player for the night. - Infinite uses 
**Barricade (Night)** - Prevents all visits on your target tonight. - 2 uses 
*See that the starting Emperor loses.* 

&gt; # [color = &quot;lightcoral&quot;] The Missionary [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Social [/color]** 
**Hopeful (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night for the first three nights.
**Visionary (Passive)** - If a second Hand of Byzantium member is executed, you will commit suicide the following night.
**Nonviolent Decree (Day)** - If a member of the Hand of Byzantium is executed today then you will take their stead. - Two uses
**Enlightenment (Night)** - Allows your target to bypass framing. - Infinite uses
**Vow of Innocence (Night)** - Prevents your target from being voted tomorrow. - Two uses
*Make sure no more than one Hand of Byzantium member is wrongfully executed.* 

&gt; # [color = &quot;black&quot;] The Necromancer [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Offensive [/color]** 
**Stench of Death (Passive)** - Any player visiting you will be shown as a Killer type for the current and following nights.
**Corpse Shield (Passive)** - Your are night immune for the first three nights against non-Hand of Byzantium classes.
**Raise Dead (Day)** - Selects a dead player and the target&amp;rsquo;s primary ability will be Unleash Ghoul&amp;rsquo;s effect for tonight. Can only use a corpse once before it decays. - Infinite uses. 
**Embalming (Day)** - Allows you to reuse the corpse that was used in the previous day. - 2 uses. 
**Unleash Ghoul (Night)** - Uses the ability that you have obtained via Raise Dead. - Infinite uses 
**Wall of Corpses (Night)** - Prevents all visits on you tonight. - 2 uses 
*See the Hand of Byzantium defeated at any cost.* 

&gt; # [color = &quot;forestgreen&quot;] The Senex [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Support [/color]** 
**Mentorship (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night and will have a 50-50 chance of starting aligned with the Hand of Byzantium or against them. If the Senex is aligned with the Hand of Byzantium, then he will lose his night immunity after the second night.
**Beloved Mentor (Passive)** - If you win with the Hand of Byzantium, your attributes will be:
&gt;* If you are executed on trial, then all Hand of Byzantium-aligned players who voted for your execution will be occupied in the coming night, will not be able to be protected from death if they are attacked, and will have their immunity to occupation bypassed.
&gt;* If you are killed by a Hand of Byzantium-aligned killing role, then they will die of guilt.
&gt;
&gt;**Teachings (Day)** - Reveals the user as the Senex - One use 
**Mind Reader (Day)** - Learns the target player’s alignment. If they are not aligned with the Hand of Byzantium then you learn their exact class. Can only be used if you are against the Hand of Byzantium and can be used in the same day along Teachings. - Infinite uses 
**Traditional Herbs (Night)** - Heals a player, preventing them from dying to night and cures poison and bleeding. The target player will also be seen as a member of the Hand of Byzantium to faction checks. Cannot be used on the same player two nights in a row and can be used on the user. - Infinite uses 
**Ancient Tonic (Night)** - Causes the targeted player to be night and occupy immune for the current night allows them to bypass healing, night immunity, occupation immunity, and redirection immunities. - 1 use 
*Has a random goal of either A) See that the Hand of Byzantium win or B) See that the Hand of Byzantium is defeated.*

&gt; # [color = &quot;Firebrick&quot;] The Strigoi [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Offensive [/color]** 
**Blood Sucker (Passive)** - If you are using Vampiric Bite then you will heal yourself if you would be nightkilled. You will always be under the effect of Vampirism and you will know all living players who are Bitten.
**No Pulse (Passive)** - You are immune to redirection and occupation.
**Mist Form (Day)** - All visits to you will be prevented this coming night - 2 uses 
**Blood Frenzy (Day)** - All players under the effect of Vampirism will receive the benefits of No Pulse and the healing from Blood Sucker if you successfully use Vampiric Bite. - One use 
**Vampiric Bite (Night)** - Bites a player, infecting them with Vampirism, preventing healing, and occupying them. Players infected with Vampirism will be shown as a Neutral and a Killer for investigative abilities and will have their visits hidden. - Infinite uses 
*Make sure at least half of the living remainder of the Court is infected with Vampirism by the end of the game.* 

&gt; # [color = &quot;blanchedalmond&quot;] The Viscount [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Offensive [/color]** 
**Megalomaniac (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count twice. You will crown into the Decadent Emperor.
**Green-Eyed Monster (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night against non-Hand of Byzantium classes. You will know who will be invited to the Imperial Chat at the end of the night.
**Interlopers (Day)** - Learns the class of a selected player. - Infinite uses 
**Misdirect (Day)** - Causes your first target to target your second one the coming night. - Infinite uses 
**Slander (Night)** - Removes Royal Blood from a player. - Infinite uses
**Death Writ (Night)** - Kills the Emperor&#39;s target tonight, bypassing protections. Cannot be used until the third night. - One use
*Live to become Emperor for at least a day.*
[/details]



[details=&quot;Neutral Killers&quot;]
&gt; # [color =  darkorchid] The Archduke [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Megalomaniac (Passive)** - Your votes for Emperor will count three times. Becomes the Tyrannous Emperor instead of the Psychopathic Emperor.
**Paranoia (Passive)** - Grants immunity against death at night and bleeding. The first player to accuse you of treason during the day will have their class revealed to the Archduke during the night.
**Tyrant&#39;s Orders (Day)** - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - 2 uses
**Tyrant&#39;s Decree (Day)** - To hit majority all players need one less vote. - One use
**Political Murder (Night)** - Kills a player without counting as a visit, but has a one-day cooldown period after every two uses and cannot target the King. - Infinite uses
**Coup d&amp;rsquo;Etat (Night)** - Kills the Emperor while bypassing healing and immunity. Can only be used in the third night or later. - One use
&gt;
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


&gt;# [color = olive] The Basilisk [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color =gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Scaled Armor (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night, immune to occupation or redirection, nor can you be bled.
**Drake&#39;s Senses (Passive)** - You will be alerted of every player who visited you during the night and will learn of their classes.
**Petrifying Glare (Day)** - Once the next day begins you will stone a player temporarily for the remainder of that day, in the next day they will recover from being stoned. - 3 uses.
**Gargoyle Form (Day)** - Stones yourself in the beginning of the next day. - Infinite uses
**Stone Gaze (Night)** - Turns a player to stone. Does not bypass death immunity but bypasses healing. Players who are turned to stone will be announced at the start of the day and they will be dead, but can still be targeted or voted up. Stoned players are not counted when factoring in the amount of votes to put a player on trial. - Infinite uses
**Gorgon Stance (Night)** - Uses Stone Gaze on every player that visits you at night while also bypassing their immunities. - 3 uses
&gt;
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*

&gt;# [color = Crimson] The Berserker [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Untamed (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation, target changing, and death at night, including against attacks that normally bypass death immunity. If you are attacked , then you will automatically use Bloody Swings on your attackers. If you are attacked, you will gain two charges of Rampage and empowers Bloody Swings for the next night.
**Unchained (Passive)** - If a player attempts and fails to occupy or redirect you or tries to bleed you, then you will gain a charge of Rampage.
**Quarrelsome Banter (Day)** - In the coming night, you will redirect any night actions used by the target onto yourself. - 3 uses
**Wild Leeches (Day)** - If you are bleeding then you can transfer the condition to another player during the day. - 3 uses
**Bloody Swings (Night)** - Kills a player. If Bloody Swings is empowered then it bypasses Night Immunity and healing. - Infinite uses
**Rampage (Night)** - Kills the target. If another player visited the target and you have more than one charge, then Rampage will chain to the next player until a player has not been visited or the Berserker runs out of Rampage charges. - 0 uses
&gt;
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


&gt; # [color = silver] The Doppelgänger [/color] :shield:
&gt;**[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Sadism (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation, target changing, and have self-healing for the first two nights. You will gain an additional three nights of self-healing for every Hand of Byzantium-aligned player executed during the day.
**Sociopathy (Day)** - Adds two silent votes towards a player&#39;s lynch during the first three days and one for the remainder. - Infinite uses
**Scapegoat (Day)** - If a player is voted to be executed in the day, including you, then they will swap their position with another chosen player. The Emperor cannot be the target and this ability is locked if there are 5 or less players remaining. - 1 use
**Impersonate (Night)** - Takes the form of one player and kills another one. Any investigative results a player will have on you will instead reflect on the player they impersonated. If the impersonated target has Royal Blood, then you shall also have Royal Blood for the next day. If you attack a player who is being followed, then the feedback will show the impersonated player being the visitor. The impersonated player will be framed for the night. - Infinite uses
**Crushing Guilt (Night)** - If a Hand of Byzantium-aligned player was executed the previous day, then you can select two players who&amp;rsquo;ve voted to execute and cause them to commit suicide by guilt, bypassing healing, night immunity, and not counting as visits. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


&gt;# [color = darkred] The Ifrit [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt; **[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Djinn Form (Passive)** - Grants you immunity to occupation, redirection, bleeding, and death at night.
**Burning Transformation (Day)** - Upon killing a target, you will cause them to flip a class of your choice. If you successfully kills a player this night, you will be able to see their true class. - 2 uses
**Heat Wave (Day)** - Occupies all targets who try to visit you the coming night. Bypasses immunity to occupation. - 3 uses
**Incinerate (Night)** - Kills a player by burning them alive. Players that have been incinerated will have their logs erased. Only you will see the player&amp;rsquo;s original logs. - Infinite uses
**Fires of Jahannam (Night)** - Prevents all visits to the target player and attacks them, erasing their logs if they die. - 3 uses
&gt;
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


&gt; # [color = slateblue] The Lich [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
**Phylactery (Passive)**  - During Day One, you shall specify two players to be our Phylactery Holders. If you fail to do so before the end of the day, they are randomized. They can not choose The Emperor to be their holder, nor can The Emperor be a randomized Holder. You will know their starting classes, and will be night immune while at least one of them lives. If both of them die, you will die the following night. Investigations against the Phylactery Holders will also yield the additional message “You feel a chill surrounding the target player. They are a Phylactery Holder for The Lich.” If your Phylactery Holders die, this fact that they are one will be included with their class information.
**Undeath (Passive)**  - As long as the Phylactery Holders are alive, at the start of every night you will automatically revive yourself if you are dead, regardless of how you died.
**Spectral Mist (Day)**  - A target Phylactery Holder is healed tonight. - 3 uses
**Black Fog (Day)**  - Attempts to investigate either of the Phylactery Holders will fail tonight. - 3 uses
**Finger of Decay (Night)**  - Kill a player. If you were revived at the start of the night, then this attack bypasses night immunity and healing. - Infinite uses
**Death’s Curtains (Night)**  - Kill one of your Phylactery holders (bypasses night immunity and healing), and two other targets. - Infinite uses, but only usable while you have two Phylactery Holders alive
*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


&gt;# [color = brown] The Occultist [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt; **[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Corrupting Energy (Passive)** - Any player that visits you will be corrupted. For each player that is alive and corrupted, your Corruption Rating increases by 3.5% per night and caps at 100%. You will known your corruption rating at the start of each night and your gains at the end of it.
**Shield of Corruption (Passive)** - Provides you with defensive bonuses depending on your Corruption Rating.
&gt;* 5%+: You will be immune to death at night.
&gt;* 15%+: You will be immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt;* 25%+: You will be immune to Bleeding.
&gt;* 65%+: You will automatically kill all incoming attackers.
&gt;* 90%+: You will be immune to attacks bypassing death immunity.
&gt;
&gt;**Mental Corruption (Day)** - If the target uses an ability the coming night, they will receive incorrect feedback. Only usable if your Corruption Rating is at 40% or higher. Able to use it against two players at once if your Corruption Rating is at 75% or higher. Gains an additional charge per 30% corruption. - 1 use
**Dreadful Omen (Day)** - Skips the day and goes straight into the night. Can only be used when the Occultist&amp;rsquo;s Corruption Rating is at 90% or higher. - One use
**Burst of Corruption (Night)** - Only usable your Corruption Rating is at 5% rating or higher. Kills a player. Gains the following bonuses depending on your Corruption Rating: -
&gt;* 20%+: The first attack does not count as a visit.
&gt;* 35%+: The first attack bypasses night immunity and healing.
&gt;* 55%+: The Occultist is able to select a second target.
&gt;* 65%+: The second attack does not count as a visit.
&gt;* 70%+: The second attack bypasses night immunity and healing.
&gt;* 75%+: The first attack kills all players who visits the first target.
&gt;* 85%+: The second attack kills all players who visit the second target.
&gt;- Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt;**Beacon of Corruption (Night)** - Increases your Corruption Rating by 5% and causes Corrupting Energy to trigger against anyone visiting the your target along with the target themselves. Allows selecting two targets if your Corruption Rating is at 50% or higher. - Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


&gt;# [color = orchid] The Succubus [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt;**[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Dependency (Passive)** - If you die during the night or you are executed, all drained players will also die with you the following night.
**Transfer Life (Day)** - Allows you to kill a drained player overnight, provided they are not healed or night immune, during the coming night and transfer their remaining life in turns to another drained player. This will also heal the latter player. If you transfers to yourself, then you will gain a charge of Love&amp;rsquo;s Malady instead. If the first player is healed then the ability will still function but without the first player dying. - Infinite uses
**Infatuation (Day)** - When this ability is activated, all drained players will have their votes locked to a target for the remainder of the day. - 2 uses
**Vital Drain (Night)** - Learns the target player&amp;rsquo;s class type and will drain them to death over the next two nights. While there is at least one player being drained then you will heal yourself if you are attacked or bleeding. If a drained player is healed then their timer until they are drained to death will not lower for the night but neither the healer nor the player will be notified. Does not count as an attack. - Infinite uses
**Love&#39;s Malady (Night)** - Makes the user immune to occupation and redirection for the night and instantly kills a player while bypassing Night Immunity, healing, and does not count as visiting. - 0 uses
&gt;
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


&gt; # [color = forestgreen] The Werewolf [/color] :shield:
&gt;
&gt; **[color = gray] Neutral Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Lycanthropy (Passive)** - You are also randomly assigned a Hand of Byzantium-aligned pseudo-class at the start of the game. The pseudo-class must be able to exist on its own, such as you cannot have a Surgeon pseudo-class if three Surgeons already exist or a Magistrate pseudo-class when a Magistrate is already in the match. This pseudo-class decides your first day and first night ability along with giving you all of the pseudo-class&amp;rsquo; passives and having bonus attributes depending on the current day or night.
&gt;
&gt;~Attributes until the fourth day.
&gt; * You will be seen as your pseudo-class to investigative abilities.
&gt; * If you are executed or die in any way, you will flip as your pseudo-class.
&gt;
&gt;~Attributes from the fourth day onwards.
&gt; * You are immune to Poison and Bleeding.
&gt; * You are immune to redirection and occupation.
&gt; 
&gt;**Lunacy (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night and also can use both night abilities starting the fourth night.
**??? (Day)** - The same primary day ability as of your pseudo-class. - ? uses
**Eclipse (Day)** - Allows you to switch back to the attribute set for the first three nights for this night and the following day, but you can still use Maul and Chow. - 1 use
**??? (Night)** - The same primary night ability as of your pseudo-class. - ? uses
**Maul and Chow (Night)** - Kills the target player, but this ability cannot be used in the first or second nights. Can be used alongside your pseudo-class primary ability. - Infinite uses
&gt;
&gt;*Your objective is to defeat the Hand of Byzantium, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*
[/details]
# Rolelist

**[color = grey]The Emperor[/color] (65% [color = goldenrod]Righteous[/color]/35% [color = purple]Corrupt[/color] or [color = darkred]Devout[/color]**)
**[color = purple]The Mastermind[/color]**/**[color = darkred]The Cult Leader[/color]**
**[color = purple]The Assassin[/color]**/**[color = darkred]Random Cultist[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]The Arbiter[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**
**[color = goldenrod]Random Hand of Byzantium[/color]**/**[color = grey]Random Neutral[/color]**
**[color = grey]Random Neutral[/color]**
**[color = grey]Neutral Killer[/color]**
# Players (4/16)

1. ~~MathBladee~~ - Killed N6 - [color=darkred]**The Devout Emperor**[/color]
2. DatBird
3. ~~HTM~~ - Killed N2 - [color=goldenrod]**The Governor**[/color]
4. ~~Maxwell~~ Executed D6 - [color=darkred]**The Cult Leader**[/color]
5. ~~Sulit~~ - Killed N2 - [color=darkkhaki]**The Headhunter**[/color]
6. ~~JakeTheWolfie~~ - Killed N4 - [color=goldenrod]**The Arbiter**[/color]
7. Lymphoma
8. ~~WazzaAzza~~ - Killed N3 - [color=darkred]**The Cult Leader**[/color]
9. Possessed
10. ~~Andrej~~ - Executeed D5 - [color=goldenrod]**The Druid**[/color]
11. ~~AreteSlashStars~~ - Executed D3 - [color=darkred]**The Cult Leader**[/color]
12. BlueStorm
13. ~~PokemonKidRyan~~ - Killed N6 - [color=orchid]**The Succubus**[/color]
14. ~~Kai_5~~ - Killed N5 - [color=goldenrod]**The Bard**[/color]
15. ~~Magnus~~ - Killed N6 - [color=goldenrod]**The Warden**[/color]
16. ~~Cheeki~~ - Executed D2 - [color=goldenrod]**The Eccentric**[/color]

# Backup</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum of Lies</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>( <a class="mention" href="/u/lymphoma">@Lymphoma</a> don’t worry I have also been there )</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3472">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3472</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3472</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this is from my setup. let’s talk there; i posted in here by mistake<br>
in my setup the unseen are town</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3471">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3471</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 23:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3471</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxwell" data-post="3469" data-topic="77327">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/maxwell/40/20105_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxwell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Hero’s Immunity (Night)</strong> - Permanently makes a player be seen as a member of the Unseen to faction checks. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3470">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3470</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 23:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3470</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1><font color="goldenrod"> The Purified King <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> </font></h1>
<p><font color="goldenrod"> <strong>Hand of Byzantium Special</strong> </font><br>
<font color="goldenrod"> <strong>Dynastic Cycle (Passive)</strong> </font> - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King.<br>
<font color="goldenrod"> <strong>Head of State (Passive)</strong> </font> - Your vote for treason counts as two.<br>
<font color="goldenrod"> <strong>Sword of Damocles (Day)</strong> </font> - If nobody hits majority by the end of the day, then the player with the most votes will be executed. - One use<br>
<font color="goldenrod"> <strong>Champion’s Council (Night)</strong> </font> - Sends a champion (An assistant champion, different than the real champion, does not affect the current champion’s actions) to a player. This attack does not count as a visit and cannot be stopped. Can only be used on the second night or after that you are crowned. - One use<br>
<font color="goldenrod"> <strong>Hero’s Immunity (Night)</strong> </font> - Permanently makes a player be seen as a member of the Unseen to faction checks. - 2 uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Unseen and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
<p>Crowned from:</p>
<ul>
<li>Any member of the Hand of Byzantum.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3469">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3469</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 22:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3469</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you have a concern, you can either flag a post or contact a moderator privately. Emphasis on privately.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3468">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3468</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 21:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3468</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure if this thread is the best place to litigate this, but then again I’m not super familiar with forum norms on how to go about collecting evidence of this sort of thing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3466">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3466</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3466</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/search?context=topic&amp;context_id=51835&amp;q=%40Lymphoma%20order%3Alatest_topic&amp;skip_context=false" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/search?context=topic&amp;context_id=51835&amp;q=%40Lymphoma%20order%3Alatest_topic&amp;skip_context=false</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3464">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3464</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3464</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is actually cool</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3463">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3463</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3463</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>WAIT</p>
<p>WE CAN LITERALLY POST THIS in the starting post of every game to give people a quick way to iso someone</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3462">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3462</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3462</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/search?context=topic&amp;context_id=57064&amp;q=%40Lymphoma%20order%3Alatest_topic&amp;skip_context=false" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/search?context=topic&amp;context_id=57064&amp;q=%40Lymphoma%20order%3Alatest_topic&amp;skip_context=false</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3461">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3461</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3461</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Going to find more</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3460">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3460</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3460</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/search?context=topic&amp;context_id=58833&amp;q=%40Lymphoma%20&amp;skip_context=false" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/search?context=topic&amp;context_id=58833&amp;q=%40Lymphoma%20&amp;skip_context=false</a></p>
<p>One game I found</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3459">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3459</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3459</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess that makes sense. I’m looking for the games now, however the last time I saw him play was when I wasn’t very good at forum mafia. I thought a lot of players were fantastic at the game till I realize once I got considered “good” that a lot of people aren’t good at mafia. One of the people I thought was good was lymphoma so I’m hoping I can find those games to see if I was mistaken or not</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3458">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3458</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3458</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Time to go hunting wabbits</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3455">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3455</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3455</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="firekitten" data-post="3451" data-topic="77327">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/firekitten/40/24106_2.png" class="avatar"> firekitten:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>purposefully</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m reluctant to make the determination myself that it’s <em>deliberate</em>, that’s a question I’d rather leave for the mods.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3454">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3454</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3454</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can link countless games on here he participated in and was much better then this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3452">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3452</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 19:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3452</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Possessed" data-post="3449" data-topic="77327">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/possessed/40/24344_2.png" class="avatar"> Possessed:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>m trying to be as nice and reflective as possible because I would love to see you improve, but right now a town Lymphoma in your game is like an extra convert/Evil Neutral…and it shouldn’t be like that. Id suggest talking to some of the veterans to see how they can help you improve your town game. I’m no expert at all, but I don’t want to have to struggle reading my actual town teammates.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no</p>
<p>stop being nice to him when he’s purposefully trolling the forums</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3451">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3451</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 19:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3451</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Possessed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It doesn’t hurt sometimes to say nothing rather than saying something if you feel your information would look suspicious . In all honesty, if you said NOTHING last day and just voted Blue for lying about you visiting Magnus I wouldn’t have even considered you were NK. I already had you confirmed as Duelist with PKR dead and there was 1 vote left on Blue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3450">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3450</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 18:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3450</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Possessed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It doesn’t hurt to reflect on what you could have done better to achieve your wincon. If you just say things like, " I suck cuz I didn’t lie", you are sarcastically trying to shrug off responsibility in this situation.</p>
<p>The MAIN issue I had wasn’t even your incorrect night actions; it was your overall lack of effort during day Chat…like you didn’t want to figure out who was scum. This is usually a telltale sign of BEING scum, and late game with 4 people left…you want to make ZERO DOUBT that you are town.</p>
<p>Im trying to be as nice and reflective as possible because I would love to see you improve, but right now a town Lymphoma in your game is like an extra convert/Evil Neutral…and it shouldn’t be like that. Id suggest talking to some of the veterans to see how they can help you improve your town game. I’m no expert at all, but I don’t want to have to struggle reading my actual town teammates.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3449">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3449</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 18:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3449</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not saying that you suck.</p>
<p>I do think that given the sheer frequency of you getting misexe’d, and the general perception that your actions suggest a lack of effort, it may be worth reconsidering your playstyle and experimenting with something else.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3448">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3448</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 17:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3448</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lymphoma" data-post="3446" data-topic="77327">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/lymphoma/40/15826_2.png" class="avatar"> Lymphoma:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I suck</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Correct</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3447">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3447</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 17:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3447</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lymphoma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I suck cuz i didnt lie</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3446">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3446</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 17:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3446</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MathBlade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I believed him NK. Didn’t think town would play like that. But if he was town I didn’t care</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3445">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3445</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 17:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3445</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, it was theoretically possible that one of us would convert him just because it wasn’t the sort of thing you’d expect.</p>
<p>We did in fact try to kill him at some point, on the admittedly-flawed theory that if his abilities weren’t locked first he’d probably manage to hit a Cultist at some point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3444">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3444</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 17:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3444</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Possessed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you believe him to be NK or town? I flipped back and forth all game with it. I knew he wasn’t converted but him being NK was always a high possibility.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3443">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327/3443</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 16:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-77327-3443</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/sfol-sfol-51-hand-of-byzantium-iii-3-16-completed/77327.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 51: Hand of Byzantium III - (3/16) - Completed</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
