<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bug with MM&#39;s become assassin ability</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bug-with-mms-become-assassin-ability/8903</link>
    <description>#### What happened?
As the MM I was the only unseen left. there were 2 BD and an alchemist left. First day of solo MM I spammed convert to assasin ability but due to the execution accusations, someone was put up on trial. They were executed and my ability was grayed out and I couldn&#39;t use it to become assassin. I couldn&#39;t convert anyone that night because the the king can&#39;t be convered, the preist&#39;s revive target can&#39;t be converted, and the alch can&#39;t be converted. The next day i convince them that 15 the alchemist came back as special/investigative because i KNEW i would be outted soon. After typing that I started spamming my convert to assasin ability becuase now i know the game is int he bag once i kill king. 15 gets put up and executed and again my ability was grayed out for the day. Next day since it&#39;s just king, revived target, and myself, I get put up and executed.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?
I was suppose to be able to convert to assasin even though someone was executed. 

#### Steps to reproduce:

#### Comments:
Please fix this as it was a huge inconvenience. I easily should have won that game after killing the king. It was d11 or 12 and I know he was out of guards because he kept guarding me &quot;the princess.&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 19:54:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bug-with-mms-become-assassin-ability/8903.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bug with MM&#39;s become assassin ability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>As the MM I was the only unseen left. there were 2 BD and an alchemist left. First day of solo MM I spammed convert to assasin ability but due to the execution accusations, someone was put up on trial. They were executed and my ability was grayed out and I couldn’t use it to become assassin. I couldn’t convert anyone that night because the the king can’t be convered, the preist’s revive target can’t be converted, and the alch can’t be converted. The next day i convince them that 15 the alchemist came back as special/investigative because i KNEW i would be outted soon. After typing that I started spamming my convert to assasin ability becuase now i know the game is int he bag once i kill king. 15 gets put up and executed and again my ability was grayed out for the day. Next day since it’s just king, revived target, and myself, I get put up and executed.</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>I was suppose to be able to convert to assasin even though someone was executed.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>Please fix this as it was a huge inconvenience. I easily should have won that game after killing the king. It was d11 or 12 and I know he was out of guards because he kept guarding me “the princess.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bug-with-mms-become-assassin-ability/8903/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bug-with-mms-become-assassin-ability/8903/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 19:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8903-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/bug-with-mms-become-assassin-ability/8903.rss">Bug with MM&#39;s become assassin ability</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
