<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806</link>
    <description>Mostly I&#39;m suggesting this as another way to make it hard for people to confirm, but it would also be an interesting buff to the Possessor, who seems like he could do all right with one.

Give the Possessor a Day ability, &quot;mimic&quot;.  It is only available after you&#39;ve possessed someone successfully.  When you activate it, your Day and Night abilities switch to those of the class of the person you&#39;re currently possessing until the end of the next night.  Your normal Possessor abilities are replaced.  You can use another Day ability after using Mimic (ie. one of the ones from the class you&#39;re copying.)

I&#39;m unsure how many charges it would have (possibly as few as 1, although I think it could be cool to give it more, possibly even unlimited if we want to take risks.)

Obviously, some abilities would be off-limits; we&#39;d have to discuss which ones.  (Probably no King or Prince abilities...  although Prince is an amusing thought.  Maybe jail but not execute?  Hm.  If it&#39;s just one mimic charge, even jail + execute might be all right.)

But remember that using Mimic replaces the Possessor&#39;s normal night abilities for that night (and the Possessor has one of the best killing abilities in the game natively), so a lot of things that might seem unbalanced at first glance are actually fine.  Eg. using a butler&#39;s poison on the king might seem powerful, but you&#39;re giving up your kill that night to do it, [i]and[/i] the king may get healed, [i]and[/i] if anyone knew who the Butler was you could get outed, jailed, and executed or even lynched immediately.

A few abilities might function differently (I&#39;d suggest that abilities like CS and Sacrifice don&#39;t cost the Possessor their life - remember, again, using one would replace your normal kill for the night!  So it&#39;d be fine for a Possessor using a knight&#39;s CS to kill regardless of the target&#39;s faction, since that would still be weaker than the Possessor&#39;s native [i]Puppet Strings[/i], which they gave up for the night to use CS instead.)

Basically, the idea is to add a way for almost any ability to be theoretically mimicked by at least one evil.  I don&#39;t think it would be hugely overpowered - Possessors often end up getting caught by process of elimination, when their last jump gets blocked, etc, and this wouldn&#39;t make them immune to any of that.  The Possessor endgame would still be tough (unless they mimicked someone with just the right ability, which would require planning and could get them caught if someone anticipates that they&#39;ll go for an obvious target.)

But it would allow for more interesting Possessor strategies and would increase paranoia when a Possessor is potentially in play, making it harder for people to auto-confirm themselves.   Especially given that Possessors also have Facelift, so even with a dead NK people could potentially argue that someone who would otherwise have used their abilities to confirm could be a Possessor.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:44:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, yes.  But those don’t matter since they’ll never be around for Possessors to mimic.  Compared to most of the ones available to non-NK roles, the Possessor is generally superior, so eg. copying a knight and using CS is generally a downgrade.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44806-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806.rss">Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="1" data-topic="44806">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and the Possessor has one of the best killing abilities in the game natively</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually the Possessor’s killing Ability’s are not any better than the other NK’s. If anything the one NK’s are better due to Sorcs Ability to multikill and the Reapers bypass.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 11:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44806-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806.rss">Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[techwolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually thats pretty good since if you jump king you can prove your still the king</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 06:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44806-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806.rss">Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mostly I’m suggesting this as another way to make it hard for people to confirm, but it would also be an interesting buff to the Possessor, who seems like he could do all right with one.</p>
<p>Give the Possessor a Day ability, “mimic”.  It is only available after you’ve possessed someone successfully.  When you activate it, your Day and Night abilities switch to those of the class of the person you’re currently possessing until the end of the next night.  Your normal Possessor abilities are replaced.  You can use another Day ability after using Mimic (ie. one of the ones from the class you’re copying.)</p>
<p>I’m unsure how many charges it would have (possibly as few as 1, although I think it could be cool to give it more, possibly even unlimited if we want to take risks.)</p>
<p>Obviously, some abilities would be off-limits; we’d have to discuss which ones.  (Probably no King or Prince abilities…  although Prince is an amusing thought.  Maybe jail but not execute?  Hm.  If it’s just one mimic charge, even jail + execute might be all right.)</p>
<p>But remember that using Mimic replaces the Possessor’s normal night abilities for that night (and the Possessor has one of the best killing abilities in the game natively), so a lot of things that might seem unbalanced at first glance are actually fine.  Eg. using a butler’s poison on the king might seem powerful, but you’re giving up your kill that night to do it, <span class="bbcode-i">and</span> the king may get healed, <span class="bbcode-i">and</span> if anyone knew who the Butler was you could get outed, jailed, and executed or even lynched immediately.</p>
<p>A few abilities might function differently (I’d suggest that abilities like CS and Sacrifice don’t cost the Possessor their life - remember, again, using one would replace your normal kill for the night!  So it’d be fine for a Possessor using a knight’s CS to kill regardless of the target’s faction, since that would still be weaker than the Possessor’s native <span class="bbcode-i">Puppet Strings</span>, which they gave up for the night to use CS instead.)</p>
<p>Basically, the idea is to add a way for almost any ability to be theoretically mimicked by at least one evil.  I don’t think it would be hugely overpowered - Possessors often end up getting caught by process of elimination, when their last jump gets blocked, etc, and this wouldn’t make them immune to any of that.  The Possessor endgame would still be tough (unless they mimicked someone with just the right ability, which would require planning and could get them caught if someone anticipates that they’ll go for an obvious target.)</p>
<p>But it would allow for more interesting Possessor strategies and would increase paranoia when a Possessor is potentially in play, making it harder for people to auto-confirm themselves.   Especially given that Possessors also have Facelift, so even with a dead NK people could potentially argue that someone who would otherwise have used their abilities to confirm could be a Possessor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 06:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-44806-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/allow-possessors-to-mimic-some-abilities-of-the-role-theyre-possessing/44806.rss">Allow Possessors to mimic some abilities of the role they&#39;re possessing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
