<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Bug of No Exiting</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bug-of-no-exiting/9759</link>
    <description>#### What happened? Uh herm, this has already been reported before, but I need to rebump this, you can&#39;t press X on the game or else the program freezes.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen? The program should close when you press X, it shouldn&#39;t freeze.

#### Steps to reproduce: Press X while at the main menu, or literally anywhere else.

#### Comments: It&#39;s getting to be a pain in my rearend having to open Task Manager to close ToL.

_edit:_ This bug has been here since I remember, in pre-alpha even, but now it&#39;s really starting to become intolerable, for a while it was just a kick in the butt, but now that foot is stuck in the butt if you know what I mean. :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 20:03:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bug-of-no-exiting/9759.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Bug of No Exiting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened? Uh herm, this has already been reported before, but I need to rebump this, you can’t press X on the game or else the program freezes.</h4>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen? The program should close when you press X, it shouldn’t freeze.</h4>
<h4>Steps to reproduce: Press X while at the main menu, or literally anywhere else.</h4>
<h4>Comments: It’s getting to be a pain in my rearend having to open Task Manager to close ToL.</h4>
<p><em>edit:</em> This bug has been here since I remember, in pre-alpha even, but now it’s really starting to become intolerable, for a while it was just a kick in the butt, but now that foot is stuck in the butt if you know what I mean. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bug-of-no-exiting/9759/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bug-of-no-exiting/9759/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 20:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9759-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bug-of-no-exiting/9759.rss">The Bug of No Exiting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
