<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A few bug reports</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-few-bug-reports/80194</link>
    <description>#### Decide Fate disabled, Cult Leader bleed randomly disabled, the victim of Hunter&#39;s Mark got the feedback that they were attacked, but not the feedback that they were occupied

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?

Regarding Hunter&#39;s Mark I was Alchemist with Stoneskin and attacked Inquisitor.  I got, &quot;You attacked X last night&quot; feedback, and &quot;You were attacked but immune&quot; feedback.  I was hit by Hunter&#39;s Mark so the feedback I should have gotten &quot;You were occupied&quot; instead of &quot;You attacked X last night&quot;.

&quot;You attacked X last night&quot; wasn&#39;t true since I was occupied, and also Inquisitor is death immune anyway so I would have gotten a death immune message.

#### Steps to reproduce:

Attack someone as Alch when you get hit by Hunter&#39;s Mark.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 08:11:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-few-bug-reports/80194.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A few bug reports</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>Decide Fate disabled, Cult Leader bleed randomly disabled, the victim of Hunter’s Mark got the feedback that they were attacked, but not the feedback that they were occupied</h4>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>Regarding Hunter’s Mark I was Alchemist with Stoneskin and attacked Inquisitor.  I got, “You attacked X last night” feedback, and “You were attacked but immune” feedback.  I was hit by Hunter’s Mark so the feedback I should have gotten “You were occupied” instead of “You attacked X last night”.</p>
<p>“You attacked X last night” wasn’t true since I was occupied, and also Inquisitor is death immune anyway so I would have gotten a death immune message.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<p>Attack someone as Alch when you get hit by Hunter’s Mark.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-few-bug-reports/80194/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-few-bug-reports/80194/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 08:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80194-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-few-bug-reports/80194.rss">A few bug reports</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
