<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Seeker</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-seeker/523</link>
    <description>Lore link: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Seeker

Lore Subject: Blood seeks blood

Lore: As with every pact a sacrifice must be made. The Cultists follow the example of their cult master most specifically the seeker will sacrifice his human eyes to gain the omnipotent belial gaze of Mithras. It is unclear just how much this new sight gives the seeker but we can determine that it allows the seeker to see the strength of a person&#39;s blood. This is not new to us we have long understood that royal blood holds certain properties of interest to the cultists but never did we imagine that blood would play such a part in the selection of the cultists members or victims. We believe that his abilities can even sense when a person&#39;s blood is boiling sensing when those around him have hostile intentions. We have to admit that if this is one of the gifts that Mithras bestows that perhaps this supposed god has every intention of searching us out and destroying us.

Comments: Went into detail on abilities. Didn&#39;t think motivation was that important being that the cult leader is the only one with any form of individuality. Borrowed a premise from Death note except that the seeker doesn&#39;t see lifespan but strength of person&#39;s blood.

Will probably expand on this in the future as I haven&#39;t talked about his headband or the use of his human eyes outside of himself yet.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 12:05:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-seeker/523.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Seeker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore link: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Seeker" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Seeker</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: Blood seeks blood</p>
<p>Lore: As with every pact a sacrifice must be made. The Cultists follow the example of their cult master most specifically the seeker will sacrifice his human eyes to gain the omnipotent belial gaze of Mithras. It is unclear just how much this new sight gives the seeker but we can determine that it allows the seeker to see the strength of a person’s blood. This is not new to us we have long understood that royal blood holds certain properties of interest to the cultists but never did we imagine that blood would play such a part in the selection of the cultists members or victims. We believe that his abilities can even sense when a person’s blood is boiling sensing when those around him have hostile intentions. We have to admit that if this is one of the gifts that Mithras bestows that perhaps this supposed god has every intention of searching us out and destroying us.</p>
<p>Comments: Went into detail on abilities. Didn’t think motivation was that important being that the cult leader is the only one with any form of individuality. Borrowed a premise from Death note except that the seeker doesn’t see lifespan but strength of person’s blood.</p>
<p>Will probably expand on this in the future as I haven’t talked about his headband or the use of his human eyes outside of himself yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-seeker/523/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-seeker/523/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 12:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-523-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-seeker/523.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Seeker</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
