<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bussing interface for unseen/cult</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941</link>
    <description>As there&#39;s been quite a few discusions on the topic of bussing, and I fully get the dev/mod&#39;s stances, and examples they&#39;ve given. I get how they handle it on case by case basis etc... but at least IMO I prefer more concrete dem&#39;s the rules, remove all subjectivity on it options. I&#39;m not doubting the dev&#39;s ability to judge these on a case by case basis and do it right, but I think for both the dev&#39;s and the players sake, a concrete no need for interpretation rule that can be pointed to and respond with &quot;This is how it is, you can disagree with the rule&#39;s existance, but you can&#39;t deny that&#39;s what the rule says&quot;.

The official statement is more or less, get concent etc... but of course there&#39;s exceptions to that, say someone gets jailed, you may fear they might get perma jailed, or you called someone out the day before you were converted etc...

What I&#39;m thinking, is a day interface for cult/unseen, with a list of the current cult/unseen members, in which they can click on a fellow unseen cult member, to request permission to bus them. Upon clicking them it pops a &quot;X has requested permission to call you out for the good of the side, do you accept?&quot;, Clicking on yourself sends a message of &quot;X is willing to die for the cause&quot;.

A system like that takes away the subjectivity. The worse case scenario, is someone that&#39;s in an impossible place refusing it, but that most likely would be done by the sort of people that create this debate to begin with (IE the ones who say OMG Gamethrower, when put up by a teammate, this lessens the damage in such a scenario).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 14:08:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bussing interface for unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Most players in my experience tell the person why they want to bus them exactly. There are times when they are about to be accused they bus someone, being the MM ofc, to get off the stand and live to convert. No-one has time in that situation to check a button or even ask that person but it needs to be done to win. Those are the moments I am defending.</p>
<p>I have never once been mad at anyone for bussing me if they at MM or CL. He’ll I don’t mind if I have used all my abilities and an herbalist wants to live and use his. I can die and play another game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 14:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20941-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941.rss">Bussing interface for unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bussing interface for unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>and you might… I’m more than sure there will be a decent amount of players with your stance. There are many players that do prefer the satisfaction of making their side win even at the cost of dying. I myself will more likely be using the “willing to die” button. So many times I’ve been occupied etc… and hoped a fellow unseen would beat the butler to the punch at calling me out, and I myself absolutely prefer watching my side win from the graveyard in part from actions I performed, than being alive in the court knowing I’m playing for a doomed side.</p>
<p>But an interface like that allows the team to know whether they have someone like me, or someone like you, and lets them adjust their tactics accordingly.</p>
<p>Hypothetically if you and I were in the same game, say you were the assasain, I was the first convert, this would allow say a scenerio where</p>
<p>N2.<br>
MM: I think it would help if I bussed you on day 3<br>
bbiaglla: No I want to live as long as I can<br>
MM: OK</p>
<p>Day 3.<br>
Vandalay has been initiated into the unseen<br>
Vandalay is willing to die for the cause<br>
MM: Vandalay is unseen!</p>
<p>Mastermind was given the chance and ability to know both players willingness, You got what you wanted in being able to not be bussed, MM gets what he wants in being able to know which of his 2 subjects was OK with going down, and was able to chose that subject to keep his own name fairly cleared, and I get what I want, in being on a side that hopefully just got a better chance of winning due to my choice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20941-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941.rss">Bussing interface for unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bussing interface for unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In before everyone always selects no because no-one likes sitting dead chat and winning doesnt mean shit in the game anyways.</p>
<p>Seriously…stay alive and lose or die and win For an extra 30 gold which is pointless anyways? I choose alive all day.</p>
<p>Edit ___</p>
<p>I will say I don’t mind dying to win most times. The only times I want to be alive is when my team of evil is trash and I am carrying us to victory and the dumb MM wants to bus me for him to stay alive. That happens alot actually. Also sometimes I want to bus someone to get a better, smarter, player or a better class. Say there is a sheriff and I’m tapped. Bus my assasin and grab that sheriff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20941-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941.rss">Bussing interface for unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bussing interface for unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah. this does really seem like a good idea</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20941-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941.rss">Bussing interface for unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bussing interface for unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While kind of a clunky workaround to not being dumb, I like the idea. All for it, personally.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 12:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20941-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941.rss">Bussing interface for unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bussing interface for unseen/cult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As there’s been quite a few discusions on the topic of bussing, and I fully get the dev/mod’s stances, and examples they’ve given. I get how they handle it on case by case basis etc… but at least IMO I prefer more concrete dem’s the rules, remove all subjectivity on it options. I’m not doubting the dev’s ability to judge these on a case by case basis and do it right, but I think for both the dev’s and the players sake, a concrete no need for interpretation rule that can be pointed to and respond with “This is how it is, you can disagree with the rule’s existance, but you can’t deny that’s what the rule says”.</p>
<p>The official statement is more or less, get concent etc… but of course there’s exceptions to that, say someone gets jailed, you may fear they might get perma jailed, or you called someone out the day before you were converted etc…</p>
<p>What I’m thinking, is a day interface for cult/unseen, with a list of the current cult/unseen members, in which they can click on a fellow unseen cult member, to request permission to bus them. Upon clicking them it pops a “X has requested permission to call you out for the good of the side, do you accept?”, Clicking on yourself sends a message of “X is willing to die for the cause”.</p>
<p>A system like that takes away the subjectivity. The worse case scenario, is someone that’s in an impossible place refusing it, but that most likely would be done by the sort of people that create this debate to begin with (IE the ones who say OMG Gamethrower, when put up by a teammate, this lessens the damage in such a scenario).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 12:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20941-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bussing-interface-for-unseen-cult/20941.rss">Bussing interface for unseen/cult</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
