<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Sheriff</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-sheriff/32848</link>
    <description>Lore Link: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Sheriff

Lore Subject: The light in the darkness, a badge.

Lore:
Ever since he was a child, his parents told him the stories of The Unseen. He has heard the troubling rumors of the Unseen. People who kill at night and who stay silent on the day... At one night, he spotted one, a dark figure, who walked into a room... and after that, he saw blood spilling... darkness oozed from that room ever since...from that day onwards, he decided that &quot;No more.... No more Unseen, they&#39;re a plague on us, who feed on us day by day, night by night.&quot; With that he studied the arts of the Unseen and found that there&#39;s a common link connecting every member. With that, he wandered the world searching for The Unseen, and ended up visiting Castle Adiart one day, and he saw exactly what he studied, oozes of darkness... blood spilling.... He decided to use his knowledge to his advantage, to save Castle Adiart... to get rid of the awful rumors, once and for all.

Comments:
I want to see Sheriff as a person who has already seen what the faction has done, and has made his life&#39;s goal to get rid of them, forever.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:42:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-sheriff/32848.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Monkke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore Link: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Sheriff" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Sheriff</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: The light in the darkness, a badge.</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
Ever since he was a child, his parents told him the stories of The Unseen. He has heard the troubling rumors of the Unseen. People who kill at night and who stay silent on the day… At one night, he spotted one, a dark figure, who walked into a room… and after that, he saw blood spilling… darkness oozed from that room ever since…from that day onwards, he decided that “No more… No more Unseen, they’re a plague on us, who feed on us day by day, night by night.” With that he studied the arts of the Unseen and found that there’s a common link connecting every member. With that, he wandered the world searching for The Unseen, and ended up visiting Castle Adiart one day, and he saw exactly what he studied, oozes of darkness… blood spilling… He decided to use his knowledge to his advantage, to save Castle Adiart… to get rid of the awful rumors, once and for all.</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
I want to see Sheriff as a person who has already seen what the faction has done, and has made his life’s goal to get rid of them, forever.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-sheriff/32848/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-sheriff/32848/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 22:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32848-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-sheriff/32848.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Sheriff</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
