<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Observer Advice</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059</link>
    <description># Observer Advice

Recently, I played a Cult Game where I watched a player repeatedly to see when he was converted and another Observer found a Cult Leader sacrificing another Cult member, thus, allowing me to put 2+2 to get 4, and revealing a couple Cult members. So here&#39;s some advice from me, about how Observer can catch evils.

* **Cult Leader visits their Sacrifice** 
If the person that you watch happens to have been a Cult member who has just died, followed by another death, then the person you saw visit is likely to have been a Cult Leader who used Blood of Mithras. 
If there were more than one visit, whisper to one of them and find out what you can. Ask them for their Class and/or check other Journals for potential information.

* **You can see Mastermind/Cult Leader convert**
In some instances, you may be able to catch a conversion in progress. Let&#39;s suggest you saw somebody was visited, and later on, the visitor is found dead and was a Faction Leader, that would mean the person you watched before was likely converted, if they weren&#39;t immune to conversion.

* **Finding Neutral Killers**
For in-experienced players, Possessor and Reaper are sometimes hard to detect. 
**Possessor** uses other players to beat down another player, so the if the Observer is watching the victim being killed, they will see the Possessed player, rather than the Possessor committing the kill. However, if the Observer is watching the Possessed player, they will see the Possessor in action, thus, it&#39;s important to announce if you were Possessed.
**Reaper** is a little different, since instead of the player falling dead straight away, they stay active for 1 day. Thus, an Observer may be tricked by a Reaper visit, and may miss it when the player eventually falls dead. If a player isn&#39;t talking during the day and falls dead the next day, and an Observer saw that player visited one night before, chances are you&#39;ve found your Reaper.


# This is my advice to Observers for future games. I hope it has been useful, I may work on other posts for other Classes. If anyone wants to add anything in the replies, by all means, any advice is appreciated</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 15:05:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Observer Advice</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The other important thing is not claiming observer unless you need to, especially in a cult game. Wait as long as possible, and try to claim privately through whispers to confirmed players. I recently played as an observer in a cult game. I was converted, died the next day due to lynching and players thinking I was converted, and then the blue dragon won the next day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 15:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2059-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059.rss">Observer Advice</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Observer Advice</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>FIRST!!. Also good advice</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 22:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2059-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059.rss">Observer Advice</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Observer Advice</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Observer Advice</h1>
<p>Recently, I played a Cult Game where I watched a player repeatedly to see when he was converted and another Observer found a Cult Leader sacrificing another Cult member, thus, allowing me to put 2+2 to get 4, and revealing a couple Cult members. So here’s some advice from me, about how Observer can catch evils.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Cult Leader visits their Sacrifice</strong><br>
If the person that you watch happens to have been a Cult member who has just died, followed by another death, then the person you saw visit is likely to have been a Cult Leader who used Blood of Mithras.<br>
If there were more than one visit, whisper to one of them and find out what you can. Ask them for their Class and/or check other Journals for potential information.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>You can see Mastermind/Cult Leader convert</strong><br>
In some instances, you may be able to catch a conversion in progress. Let’s suggest you saw somebody was visited, and later on, the visitor is found dead and was a Faction Leader, that would mean the person you watched before was likely converted, if they weren’t immune to conversion.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Finding Neutral Killers</strong><br>
For in-experienced players, Possessor and Reaper are sometimes hard to detect.<br>
<strong>Possessor</strong> uses other players to beat down another player, so the if the Observer is watching the victim being killed, they will see the Possessed player, rather than the Possessor committing the kill. However, if the Observer is watching the Possessed player, they will see the Possessor in action, thus, it’s important to announce if you were Possessed.<br>
<strong>Reaper</strong> is a little different, since instead of the player falling dead straight away, they stay active for 1 day. Thus, an Observer may be tricked by a Reaper visit, and may miss it when the player eventually falls dead. If a player isn’t talking during the day and falls dead the next day, and an Observer saw that player visited one night before, chances are you’ve found your Reaper.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>This is my advice to Observers for future games. I hope it has been useful, I may work on other posts for other Classes. If anyone wants to add anything in the replies, by all means, any advice is appreciated</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2059-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/observer-advice/2059.rss">Observer Advice</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
