<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cult Inprovement Ideas</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cult-inprovement-ideas/209</link>
    <description>Just before you read all the ideas I have just make sure you know they were my ideas(that&#39;s why.......Suck)

1)the cult will lose many members from death very quickly. you could just give a normal cult member the power to kill but that will only make it look like a reskinned assassin so the cult won&#39;t be unique anymore.
I suggest that when you kill someone with the cult leaders power the cult member is not killed the 1st time but the 2nd. so each cult member can kill 2 people before they die

2)I also suggest that you make it that the cult leader be able to choose who he will kill with, sometimes it&#39;s simply a better move not to kill the newest member

3)(this idea may suck the most) I believe I heard that the cult members powers will be weaker than their counterparts so depending on how powerful you could also let the cult members use their powers beyond the grave so being dead is not the most pointless thing in the game. would also give dark words some meaning because right now it has little to no purpose.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 07:13:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cult-inprovement-ideas/209.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cult Inprovement Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just before you read all the ideas I have just make sure you know they were my ideas(that’s why…Suck)</p>
<p>1)the cult will lose many members from death very quickly. you could just give a normal cult member the power to kill but that will only make it look like a reskinned assassin so the cult won’t be unique anymore.<br>
I suggest that when you kill someone with the cult leaders power the cult member is not killed the 1st time but the 2nd. so each cult member can kill 2 people before they die</p>
<p>2)I also suggest that you make it that the cult leader be able to choose who he will kill with, sometimes it’s simply a better move not to kill the newest member</p>
<p>3)(this idea may suck the most) I believe I heard that the cult members powers will be weaker than their counterparts so depending on how powerful you could also let the cult members use their powers beyond the grave so being dead is not the most pointless thing in the game. would also give dark words some meaning because right now it has little to no purpose.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cult-inprovement-ideas/209/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cult-inprovement-ideas/209/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 07:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-209-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cult-inprovement-ideas/209.rss">Cult Inprovement Ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
