<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128</link>
    <description>Alignment: Neutral Killing
Type: Killing

**Corax&#39;s Cloak** (passive) Immune to death at night
**Hematophagy** (night, infinite uses) Suck out the target&#39;s blood, killing them; if successful, gain one use of shape shift.
**Shape-shift** (Day, 0 uses) You will be seen as the target&#39;s class to investigators the following night
**Hypnotic gaze** (Day, 2 uses) Target will be unable to accuse anyone of treason or vote &quot;execute&quot; for any trials for the remainder of the day


Lore: While scholars know some about the cult, a book about what they did not know of them would be much longer than their current scrolls on the matter. However, scholars know **even** less about the vampire; only the mystics can provide us with any information.

Scholars are still learning about when Mithras and Corax worked together to create the cult. Eventually, they will stumble across a more mysterious fact: Mithras and Corax worked together **before**, and created the vampire.

It was a failed attempt at over-riding the kingdom of Adiart. Had it been successful, everyone would either have been killed by a vampire or turned to vampires and then starved to death because everyone else was ALSO a vampire. But it failed,because Vampires can only ever create one or **maybe** 2 offspring before they are caught and burned to death, or staked through the heart.

Eventually, all but one of the vampires died; This lats one had mutated the ability to shape-shift into his victims. Hopefully, investigators will figure it out and put an end to the vampire blood line.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 21:32:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ besides this one, of course.</p>
<p>Also I just changed it, I addressed your complaints in the revision.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 21:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThePlex" data-post="6" data-topic="2128">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/theplex/40/2519_2.png" class="avatar"> ThePlex:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You have some weird obsession with taking over the targets name</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When have I ever suggested a class in which player’s have their name get taken over?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 21:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>Hematophagy (night, infinite uses) Suck out the target’s blood, killing them; if successful, gain one use of shape shift.<br>
Shape-shift (Day, 0) If your target dies the following night, players will instead see your body die, and you will take over the target’s name, skin, and number</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>You have some weird obsession with taking over the targets name. That honestly just seems way outside an actual Vampire anyway and thus, I disagree with it. Plus, by the way people are typing and acting in game- the sudden change in personality would make you suspicious. Also, if the person that killed your target notices someone else die, you would instantly be found out IE: Prince, Knight, Alchemist, Mercenary - they would all out you.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>Hypnotic gaze (Day, 2 uses) Target will vote the same as you (execute/pardon) in the next trial today</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Suddenly this guy’s voting two people. Instantly outted.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>This is way too weak and can be quickly be rid of by people paying attention.</p>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 18:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just changed it, because I realized how weak it was. Also, it is better to post a class if you can’t think any more ideas for it and take feedback from other people.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This seems very weak, I’m assuming you mean for it to be night immune, because if you don’t this is absolutely godawful, but it still doesn’t have much going for it</p>
<p>Corax’s cloak is close to useless, as an Observer may not even be present<br>
Shape-shift is incredibly weak as it requires you not to kill just on the off-chance that a Princess or Phsychic(neither of which may appear in the game at all) might perhaps visit you on that night, maybe, also you run the risk of framing yourself as Unseen/Cult to Sheriff/Paladin or even a Psychic<br>
Hypnotic Gaze isn’t very useful either, as very few trials come down to a single vote, and even if they did the target may end up dead anyway</p>
<p>Compare this to the Reaper, who makes his victims appear alive, can silence a player AND can pierce night immunity, or the Possessor, who is immune to being occupied AND occupies another player, and you’ll see it is incredibly weak</p>
<p>Here’s some advice to you personally, stop trying to flood the forums with your ideas, I’m sure you have lots of great thoughts floating around in your head but next time you’re about to post a class, stop, take a good hard look at it and break down all of it’s flaws in your head, this should lead to a much better level of quality suggestions</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 16:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the Hypnotic Gaze day ability. I think 2 uses is a good amount.</p>
<p>I don’t see much value in Shapeshifting when you could be killing that night instead. You are immune to Sheriff and Paladin, so this only really applies to the Princess’ flirt or the Psychic’s vision. As it stands, I would never Shapeshift with this class and instead take the very small risk in exchange for killing somebody.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 16:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Corax Cloak sounds useless.</p>
<p>What if there isn’t an Observer?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Vampire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alignment: Neutral Killing<br>
Type: Killing</p>
<p><strong>Corax’s Cloak</strong> (passive) Immune to death at night<br>
<strong>Hematophagy</strong> (night, infinite uses) Suck out the target’s blood, killing them; if successful, gain one use of shape shift.<br>
<strong>Shape-shift</strong> (Day, 0 uses) You will be seen as the target’s class to investigators the following night<br>
<strong>Hypnotic gaze</strong> (Day, 2 uses) Target will be unable to accuse anyone of treason or vote “execute” for any trials for the remainder of the day</p>
<p>Lore: While scholars know some about the cult, a book about what they did not know of them would be much longer than their current scrolls on the matter. However, scholars know <strong>even</strong> less about the vampire; only the mystics can provide us with any information.</p>
<p>Scholars are still learning about when Mithras and Corax worked together to create the cult. Eventually, they will stumble across a more mysterious fact: Mithras and Corax worked together <strong>before</strong>, and created the vampire.</p>
<p>It was a failed attempt at over-riding the kingdom of Adiart. Had it been successful, everyone would either have been killed by a vampire or turned to vampires and then starved to death because everyone else was ALSO a vampire. But it failed,because Vampires can only ever create one or <strong>maybe</strong> 2 offspring before they are caught and burned to death, or staked through the heart.</p>
<p>Eventually, all but one of the vampires died; This lats one had mutated the ability to shape-shift into his victims. Hopefully, investigators will figure it out and put an end to the vampire blood line.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 16:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2128-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-vampire/2128.rss">[Class suggestion] Vampire</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
