<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Director/The Strategist (BD/UNS Offensive)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-director-the-strategist-bd-uns-offensive/30365</link>
    <description>My attempt at a sort of Offensive-Social hybrid class, and it&#39;s converted form.
&gt;## [color=steblue]The Director[/color]
&gt;[color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Offensive**[/color]
**Body Check (Day)** - The target player will be occupied tonight if they attempt to use an ability that can kill, with the exception of the Prince&#39;s Execute (Bypasses Occupy Immunity). You will know whether or not they were occupied. - 1 use
**Invitation (Night)** - Invite a target player to a social gathering tonight. They can accept or deny, and if they accept they will be occupied (If the player doesn&#39;t choose an option by the end of the night, they will deny the invitation). You will know what they chose. - Infinite uses
**Preventative Measures (Night)** - Occupy the target player. - 3 uses, can only be used on targets that have denied an Invitation
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;## [color=purple]The Strategist[/color]
&gt;[color=purple]**Unseen Offensive**[/color]
**Scheduled Interception (Day)** - The target player will be occupied tonight (Bypasses Occupy Immunity). - 1 use
**False Invitation (Night)** - Give a target player a false invitation to a social gathering. They can accept or deny, but you choose if you want to occupy them regardless of what they choose (If the player doesn&#39;t choose an option by the end of the night, they will deny the invitation). - Infinite uses
**Direct The Blade (Night)** - Choose a target. If the Assassin would be attacked by a Knight guarding their target, would be unable to kill or visit their target, or would receive a negative status effect from visiting their target they will instead attack your chosen target. - 1 use, only consumed if you successfully direct the Assassin&#39;s blade
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:25:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-director-the-strategist-bd-uns-offensive/30365.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Director/The Strategist (BD/UNS Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My attempt at a sort of Offensive-Social hybrid class, and it’s converted form.</p>
<blockquote>
<h2><font color="steblue">The Director</font></h2>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Blue Dragon Offensive</strong></font><br>
<strong>Body Check (Day)</strong> - The target player will be occupied tonight if they attempt to use an ability that can kill, with the exception of the Prince’s Execute (Bypasses Occupy Immunity). You will know whether or not they were occupied. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Invitation (Night)</strong> - Invite a target player to a social gathering tonight. They can accept or deny, and if they accept they will be occupied (If the player doesn’t choose an option by the end of the night, they will deny the invitation). You will know what they chose. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Preventative Measures (Night)</strong> - Occupy the target player. - 3 uses, can only be used on targets that have denied an Invitation<br>
<em>Defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><font color="purple">The Strategist</font></h2>
<p><font color="purple"><strong>Unseen Offensive</strong></font><br>
<strong>Scheduled Interception (Day)</strong> - The target player will be occupied tonight (Bypasses Occupy Immunity). - 1 use<br>
<strong>False Invitation (Night)</strong> - Give a target player a false invitation to a social gathering. They can accept or deny, but you choose if you want to occupy them regardless of what they choose (If the player doesn’t choose an option by the end of the night, they will deny the invitation). - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Direct The Blade (Night)</strong> - Choose a target. If the Assassin would be attacked by a Knight guarding their target, would be unable to kill or visit their target, or would receive a negative status effect from visiting their target they will instead attack your chosen target. - 1 use, only consumed if you successfully direct the Assassin’s blade<br>
<em>Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-director-the-strategist-bd-uns-offensive/30365/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-director-the-strategist-bd-uns-offensive/30365/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30365-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-director-the-strategist-bd-uns-offensive/30365.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Director/The Strategist (BD/UNS Offensive)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
