<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677</link>
    <description>## General:
* PRIEST HAS BEEN REMOVED.

&gt; #### Developer Notes
&gt; Most players didn&#39;t find the Priest very fun and most just waited for the Prince to die before reviving anyone. The Priest heavily affected balance. When it wasn&#39;t a guaranteed spawn and was convertable, games could be easily swing in one factions favor depending on if the Priest spawned or was converted. The BD had a low winrate, around 30%, before the Priest was buff, at which point it shot up to roughly 60%. There was no real in between where you could make the games not swing heavily because of the Priest and having the class not be overpowered. So the class was removed and other classes have taken over the utilities the Priest provided.

## Alchemist:
* Now had 4 uses of Stoneskin Potion

## Court Wizard:
* Magical Barrier Removed.
* Ice Ward now has infinite uses, but can only be used on each player two times.
* New night ability Recharge. Grant a player another use of all their limited use abilities. 1 use. Does not work on Physician or a Prince who executed a Blue Dragon.

&gt; #### Developer Notes
&gt; The Court Wizard was an extremely powerful class and could make it really difficult for the Cult/Unseen to convert players. Many people also didn&#39;t have much fun playing the class as they felt useless playing the most powerful class in the game. So the Court Wizard&#39;s Ice Ward receive infinite uses, but since it is a powerful ability, it needed the downside of not being usable on the same person twice. The Recharge ability was given so the class would have a powerful support ability that you have strategically decide when and who to use it on.

## Drunk &amp; Alcoholic:
* New passive I Am the Liquor - Immune to occupation at night.
* Debauchery now forcing all players targeting your target to target you instead. You will be immune to any attacks or conversions you redirected.

## Fool:
* Removed Surprise Mojo.
* Added new night ability Hide. No one will be able to visit you tonight while you hide. 2 uses.

&gt; #### Developer Notes
&gt; Too many Butlers pretending to be Fools and then getting executed by the Prince, so Surprise Mojo was removed. The ability also didn&#39;t provide much utility to the Fool. Hide can be used to protect the Fool from death and may have some other uses if you&#39;re creative enough. *wink* *wink*


## Herbalist:
* Drug no longer causes the player to believe their bleeding or poison was cured.

## King:
* Evil and Neutral King both now discover a player&#39;s faction.
* Good King still only discovers allies.

## Mastermind: 
* Now appears as occupied when a player tries to occupy them.

## Noble &amp; Aristocrat:
* Removed Spy Maid.
* Removed Private Matter.
* Added new day ability Political Pressure - Force a player to accuse another player of treason and block further voting from them. 2 uses.
* Added new day ability Noble Twin - Your vote for execution or pardon will count twice. 2 uses.
* Added new night ability Royal Decree - Make a player immune to treason accusations the next day. Infinite uses.

&gt; #### Developer Notes
&gt; The Noble was kind of all over the place with his Social ability themes. He will now be focused on vote manipulation, which is more fitting for a Noble.

## Psychic:
* Removed Misdirect
* New passive Call the Dead. Communicate with the dead at night.
* Added Private Matter as a day ability. Whispers to and from you will be hidden from the public. 2 uses.
* Link Minds now only targets 1 player but allows them to speak to you and the dead at night.
* Dead messages will appear in the Psychic chat tab.

&gt; #### Developer Notes
&gt; The Psychic gains the Priest&#39;s ability to talk to the dead, so no information is lost just because a player dies. They will have the ability to reveal information from the dead without revealing themselves. 

## Illusionist:
* Removed Misdirect
* Added Private Matter as a day ability. Whispers to and from you will be hidden from the public. 2 uses.

## Physician:
* Removed Exhume.
* Added Reanimate. Reanimate a dead Blue Dragon player as a Death Knight. They will die in 3 nights. 1 use.

&gt; #### Developer Notes
&gt; Too many people just wanted to wait for the Prince to die to revive them. Reanimate avoids this by making the revived player a special class. This way you can revive any class without having to worry that you wasted it.

## Death Knight:
* Passive Undead - Immune to occupation, conversion, and death at night. Immune to Nightshade and bleeding. Immune to Reap and Possess.
* Passive Rotting - Dies 3 nights after being revived.
* Night Ability Sacrifice - Protect a player, killing anyone attempting to attack them. 2 uses.
* Night Ability Cold Steel - Kill a player. If they&#39;re an ally you will take your own life instead. 1 use.

## Bug Fixes:
* Trollbox messages can now be highlighted.
* Fixed bug with Mastermind dying before day 4 causing dead players to appear alive.
* Fixed Merc not committing suicide.
* Fixed bug with Dirty Work where your abilities wouldn&#39;t appear the first night you&#39;re Assassin.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:55:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Official Announcements</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/120</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 15:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-120</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>nah not a flaw just hard at moment as physi not bringing him into play</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/119</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-119</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So? That isn’t a flaw really. Especially when you consider the fact that the death night is so powerful.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/118</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-118</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m still seeing physi die turn 6 with no death knight on the board</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/117</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 07:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-117</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That would also work well. <strong>/support</strong> until somebody points out some hidden flaw.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/116</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 19:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-116</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My problem with the ability is with how it confirms the phys. How about simply giving a dead player the Ability’s of the death night with no message to anyone else?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/115</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 19:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-115</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Easy - Death Knights can’t vote.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/114</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 19:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-114</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not so much that as it’s an extra untouchable BD member for a vote at the end that makes a big deal</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/113</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 18:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-113</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They are limited to use Cold Steel once.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/112</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-112</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>after playing a couple of games not seen a physi at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/111</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 18:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-111</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After playing a few games, Death Knights should probably get 2 days instead of 3.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/110</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-110</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Strangle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So it’s not exactly undead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/109</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 11:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-109</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Strangle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But in a way it’s possesed by a disease which is still alive hence killing a undead body with a living organism in it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/108</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 11:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-108</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can kill a zombie by removing the head, or destroying the brain</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/107</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 11:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-107</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Strangle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can you kill a thing which is already dead to more dead?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/106</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 11:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-106</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think dead knight should be night immune Imo</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/105</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 10:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-105</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Reanimate means Alch can’t claim Phys anymore, since it’s easy enough to confirm.  Maybe not a huge deal, I feel like the healer changes are designed to encourage BD to not just blindly execute Alchs, so maybe Alchs can just claim Alch.  Problem is, Alch is the only claim that <em>might</em> save you if King calls you non-ally, so you pretty much have to exec Alch claims off King Allies’ since they’re <em>always</em> going to claim Alch no matter they are.  This is all highly dependent on how the meta develops though, so it’s hard to predict.</p>
<p>Bigger issue though: Reanimate seems incredibly strong, but specifically against unseen in a way it isn’t against cult.  I think it’s clever changing the revived person to a new class to get around the ‘never revive anyone but the prince’ problem, but I think adding this onto a non-unique class that can heal is going to be incredibly strong.</p>
<p>Before we get into cult versus unseen, let me mention that Death Knights can bring all the info they gained while dead back into the game, just like an actual Priest revive. So, possessor is kind of screwed, they now have to kill a Psychic and possibly up to 2 physicians before they can safely jump, whereas before the Priest was the single point of failure. I think possessor is going to need some help here.  On the plus side, it encourages being active even while dead more, which I like.</p>
<p>Back to the cult versus unseen problem: The Death Knight is death immune so you can’t touch them. The Phys can easily self-confirm via their revive just like Priest could, so the DK can just guard the Physician. The normal tool for breaking protective chains, bleed/poison specifically doesn’t work on either the DK nor the Physician.  Yes, this only lasts 3 nights but for those 3 nights it’s going to be very hard on unseen.  But again, this is specifically a problem for unseen.  Cult can empowered Eradicate to get around it.  Unseen can only break it if they get lucky and convert a class that let’s them.</p>
<p>On the last night, the Knight has no reason not to yolo cold steel someone because he’s going to die anyway.  Put who you’re cold steeling in your will an you’ll either kill an unseen or confirm a BD as you go.  So all told, the Physician gets: 2 nights of immunity for himself or someone else with the added bonus of potentially killing a bad guy,  Auto-confirm for the Physician. Either 1 dead bad guy or 1 confirmed BD. 1 Extra vote for 3 days.</p>
<p>And Physician is not a unique class, so potentially double all the power listed above. Is this gamebreaking?  Probably not.  But it’s a pretty massive buff from Exhume, which was highly situational and barely useful.</p>
<p>My initial thoughts are it’s a bit strong.  Obviously I haven’t played it so I’m not saying it definitely is, but damn, I don’t even know how I’d start to deal with that as unseen.  Cult has it a bit easier with empower eradicate as I mentioned but still.</p>
<p>I’m curious though, couldn’t the solution to make the revived player into a unique class have been used while leaving the Priest mostly otherwise as is?  You could balance the new class however it needs to be balanced to help with the swing issue, making it stronger or weaker as needed.  That seems like a better call and would be less disruptive to other classes, especially the Possessor.</p>
<p>If things are to remain as they are, perhaps Physician could be made into a Unique role, and Alchemist could become a guaranteed role. This would encourage not mindlessly executing Alchs since you might need them, while keeping the Physican somewhat in check.</p>
<p>Could you clarify how Ice Ward works now? The bullet point states it can be used on each player two times, but the developer notes state it is not usable on the same person twice, which suggests you can only use it on each player once.  Honestly, I’m not a huge fan of this change, as a protective you generally want to read the room and guess who is likely to be attacked, or in the CW’d case, converted.  This is often the same person for several days in a row.  So not only will you need to use deduction but you’ll have to be fairly lucky to protect someone.  I think CW just needed more feedback on their abilities.  Let them know if someone attempted to occupy/convert/whatever their barrier’d target, and let the barrier’d target know as well, similar to how heals work.  CW doesn’t feel fun because even when you stop a convert attempt, you have no way of knowing you did.  It’s possible for a CW to completely shut down the cult/unseen by blocking the conversion of 2 high value targets, but the problem is even if the CW successfully does this, he and the targets will never know it.  Hell, even the CL/MM won’t know it was a CW.  Without feedback that you actually made an impact, the class isn’t fun to play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/104</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 09:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-104</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s a good change IMO. It makes whispers very useful as you can reliably pass info around secretly, but it’s seen as rather suspicious. Overall I think these changes are for the better, since I think ya’ll underestimate the power of Recharge.</p>
<p>Also you can still do the Private Matter + Claim to be everyone’s Merc as Psychic, so that’s all good then.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/103</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 09:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-103</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JanoRis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Noble was in a fun place to play. I think this update will make noble worthless in early game and really powerful in late game. Anyway if i see this right no BD class will be able to listen to whispers now</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/102</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 09:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-102</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Holy flip, this is really interesting.<br>
I’m looking forward to playing this and seeing how it all goes.</p>
<p>Also the fact that Physician has reanimate, I think it fits better almost.<br>
It’ll make things interesting and give an idea of whether this should stay or if Priest was better but should be reworked.</p>
<p>As usual an amazing patch.<br>
Great job Bos and the i42 team!<br>
You’re so dedicated to this game, surely everyone can recognise that. ^.^</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/101</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 09:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-101</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floofyboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally i think the problem is the Neutral killers. They create too much RNG. Critical BD roles dying to them n1 is big, just like a cult member dying to it N1 is huge.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/100</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 06:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-100</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m very interested in seeing how it plays out.</p>
<p>The early Prince RNG death might be a pain to deal with, but honestly I’ve seen more games where a MM get’s randomly murdered on day 3 I think.</p>
<p>If it comes to it, giving the Prince immunity like the Priest had wouldn’t be a terrible idea, even if it’s only for the first couple days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/99</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 06:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-99</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Impaleification]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, true. Since the Priest skewed win results so much, with it removed it should be easier to rebalance everything.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 06:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-98</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[slappy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Impaleification" data-post="96" data-topic="9677">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/impaleification/40/2231_2.png" class="avatar"> Impaleification:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>is there any chance of a reworked return of a Priest class?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My guess is most definitely, but I think this will be a good chance to test the meta without a Priest. <em>Priest was my fav</em> when I first started playing and I always claimed <strong>she was the best</strong>/ strongest role!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/97</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 06:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-97</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1.0.8 Patch Notes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Impaleification]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like these changes; they all are very good choices.</p>
<p>Though…is there any chance of a reworked return of a Priest class?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677/96</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 06:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9677-96</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/1-0-8-patch-notes/9677.rss">1.0.8 Patch Notes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
