<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376</link>
    <description>Background:
This scenario has happened many times to myself and everyone I know that has played the game more than just a few starting games. This is not about one or any match in particular, but rather addressing the issue of why is this type of situation even allowed to happen? Let me give an example
-Start off BD
-Call out multiple unseen and NK
-Its about to go to Night 11, there&#39;s only 1 Unseen left who is MM. You announce that MM is definitely him and BD agree with you and you guys plan to up him next day.
-he converts you and next morning is lynched himself due to how much you were calling him out before.
-You are left a lone assassin against confirmed BDs/Prince with a healer and the chance of winning is 0%.
This kind of situation plainly should not be allowed to happen. my example seeks to outline the flaw of how one can be heavily responsible for destroying the team that you at the very end get converted into and inevitably lose with.

**MY SUGGESTION (Maybe only for unseen games but could be added to all games)**

Create/implement a BD-Unique ability which will become available after lets say, NIGHT SIX, that makes it so that if the Mafia faction (Cult / unseen) attempts to convert you this night, you will instead commit suicide by immolation. As a result, you will die but your logs will be burnt and not shown to the castle. If you are being HEALED or GUARDED, you will still suicide because your suicide is in reaction to the convert. Additionally, your body will only die after 1 day delay (same as reaping)


This ensures unseen gets similar value from using the &#39;convert&#39; ability on someone who chooses suicide compared to getting a convert off successfully, as it will kill someone and destroy their logs and goes through healimg and guarding and also throws off BD by having him appear alive for one more day.
The goal is that it ensures that a BD who has made it that far (N6+) doesn&#39;t get screwed out of a potential win that maybe he/she heavily influenced when the game is potentially not winnable for the other faction that this player is about to get converted into.

if you missed it, I repeat that this button I&#39;m suggesting is only to appear after Night SIX. Unseen is free to convert people early on.

the reason I propose the suicide to be so loaded (Destroy logs, go through heal/guard, and 1 day delay in body dying) is because a normal conversion gives the same advantage to the mafia faction as killing 2 BD because it removes 1 BD and adds 1 Mafia member.
therefore, if a BD chooses to suicide to stay loyal to his faction, there must be trade offs.

[color=red](Edited out the spammy **bold** that covered 50%+ of this post. Rejoice! --Xblade)[/color]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 18:12:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also you aren’t being converted to a loss if there is a known Mastermind and a Prince. That MM is being jailed</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/64</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 18:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It isn’t. Situations where the MM is known but it is night start require a successful conversion for the MM to have any chance of winning if the King is alive and Good</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/63</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 18:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KronosZenom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>he goes for convert on guy who checked suicide.<br>
this guy now gets killed regardless of King guard or any heals and doesn’t drop log book.<br>
his corpse also doesn’t drop for one day same as being reaped.<br>
I think the value you get here is similar to getting the convert off.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/62</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 18:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also this post forgets that a lone assassin is fully capable of winning many endgames</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/61</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 14:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KronosZenom" data-post="58" data-topic="71376">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kronoszenom/40/6524_2.png" class="avatar"> KronosZenom:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>look past the specific example and notice that this is an aids situation in general that should not happen</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree, but also look at the situations that we would break with your proposed solution. Have you never seen a game where a known MM was able to prevent a loss at the last second via last second conversion that brought the vote to even numbers? If those turn to auto losses we’re likely looking at an off the charts swing in BDs favor and against unseen</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/60</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 12:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As I’ve already said, it has no repercussions, so it doesn’t matter if it happens occasionally. Until ranked is implemented, this issue isn’t even an issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/59</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KronosZenom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>that works in 1 specific scenario where you call out MM being most likely (a particular guy)</p>
<p>what if MM is not known for sure that night, but then is outed immediately next day?</p>
<p>same result, stuck lone assassin</p>
<p>look past the specific example and notice that this is an aids situation in general that should not happen</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/58</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KronosZenom" data-post="1" data-topic="71376">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kronoszenom/40/6524_2.png" class="avatar"> KronosZenom:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>-You are left a lone assassin against confirmed BDs/Prince with a healer and the chance of winning is 0%.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Prince could just jail MM.</p>
<p>No way he’d have jailed him 3 times.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/57</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KronosZenom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this entire feature is mainly targeted at unwinnable late-convert-into-<strong>unseen</strong> situations.<br>
I’m fine with cult being the way it is honestly cause even if you’re the last cult on night X, you can stall until you convert more people and its technically possible to recover fully because last cult will always be CL</p>
<p>when you’re the converted into the last lone assassin though against several BD, it’s not possible. 98% of the time too you will not have eradicate because unseen has already used it before.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/56</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 05:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like this idea, making MM permanently invisible to Unseen checks but I think to balance that his class would never transfer when he’s killed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/55</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 13:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>first off I do have to say we seriously need some tone control here. The guy is pointing out a legitimate issue.</p>
<p>Though the problem is the issue is with conversion in general, of which the game is kind of 100% built on.  IE some wins and losses will always be undeserved. IE people who failed their team miserably will get pulled to the winning side at the last second, and people who helped their team massively will get pulled over at the last second.</p>
<p>However with that as the primary ability for the minority factions… destroying the ability to convert, also completely crushes their ability to turn games around, which is literally the point of conversion in a game, is to keep the ending on their toes.</p>
<p>Maybe a fairer concept to actually address this complaint, without completely crashing the game (in particularly nerfing a side that’s already at a slight disadvantage), could be some redefining of win/loss…</p>
<p>Maybe being converted in the last 2 days could put you as a seperate category in a win/loss.</p>
<p>Semi-win<br>
semi-lose</p>
<p>or some better title could be given.</p>
<p>with win as 100%, lose as 50% reward as our baselines. Semi-Lose would award 70% gold, semi-win would award 85% gold, and the 2 could also be added as seperate categories in stat tracking etc…</p>
<p>Semi results only count if you are explicitly converted from the side that wins, to the side that loses or vice versa (IE if you are converted from BD to cult, then the possesor wins, it’s just a normal lose).</p>
<p>This could allow the issue to be addressed at least slightly, without effecting the balance at all,</p>
<p>also I would point out, there’s a reason why on the whole i oppose a ranked in this game to begin with, and preffer the concept of a veterans mode, for the exact same reasons that this topic is about. conversion and true competitive stats… are nearly incompatible things, and chance + team factors will massively outpower anything you can do to control your rank (and rank will likely effect that, meaning if you are unlucky early on, you will be swept into bad games, which will cause more losses, and worse teams ad infinium).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/54</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Temmeh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>keep in mind the other team loses too, yes it sucks but its the core mechanic of the game. some players will take this and scream in chat the next day OH NO I WAS CONVERTED INTO LOSS OML KILL ME STUPID MM, and others will turn around the course of the game into unseen’s favor. your saying that everyone is focusing on the specific situation, but theres so many situations where people turn around the game and pull through. you seem like the kind of person that screams in chat about getting “converted into loss”, when there is almost always a way to pull through. unseen has to do their best in this situation and if it means converting you, or anyone else, then thats not their fault or your fault. this isnt really a good idea. sure, sometimes it feels like you’ve been converted into loss, but hey its happened to literally everyone and it doesnt do anything but affect your stats. if you played well you still played well, if you were a giant ass and fucked around all game then your still a giant ass. just because you end up dying near the end of the game because the opposite faction trying to prevent you from winning so they can win converts you doesn’t make the game worse.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/53</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 02:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Temmeh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i think thats called the mvp system</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/52</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 02:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can guarantee that I have played ToL wayyyy longer than you. So shut the fuck up, your suggestion sucks, stop having a hissy fit and acting like a tough guy online.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/51</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 02:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, stop the saltposting you two and let’s get back to the original discussion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/50</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 02:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, It’s confirmed. You are braindead.</p>
<p>I was replying to Marcus’ suggestion. In your own words ‘learn how the forums work before posting.’</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/49</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 02:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KronosZenom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>say that when ranked comes out and threads pop up daily about how they lost MMR after carrying BD because they got converted on N9 or something by a dying unseen.</p>
<p>you and several others here need to look at the issue itself, the abstract idea being brought up that this is a situation that is unfair and shouldn’t happen, and not “oh I think you’re just salty about your personal experience, we’ve all had it” I’m sure you have, but that doesn’t make it right just because everyone’s been screwed by the current way of things a couple times</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/48</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 02:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean it’s not so bad if people want to get competitive</p>
<p>but in regards to the OP, conversion is one of the core mechanics of ToL. If you out people or are being active you had better ask for protection or hope the King SFs you</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not a troll post, you are attacking people for disagreeing with you. The only punishment for losing in this game is losing 30GP, so why would you care? Ranked isn’t even implemented yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/46</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Take this site for example. We actually have a forum version of throne of lies. They used to have all the feedback currently present for the steam game, but have since reduced it so only investigative classes receive feedback, and even that is limited so they have no idea if they were redirected.</p>
<p>The reason? Forum of lies was EXTREMELY BD sided with all the feedback in place, the game is unbalanced, the reason people can get away with it is time is very short and thus you can’t exactly go back and examine stuff. So the people who put forward the most convincing arguments, no matter how silly, are often the people who win.</p>
<p>Also <a class="mention" href="/u/nuclearburrito">@NuclearBurrito</a> I want to discuss that endgame scenario with you on Discord at some point</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/45</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The game is designed around conversion. It would be nice if they implemented a system that could detect how well you played and rewarded you appropriately, but it ain’t gonna happen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d8009a76a618607459083cbd22de9038e72ccc50.gif" alt="small%20sun" data-base62-sha1="uOQqqQaUgNhA7UiDDZWueeogHss" width="240" height="132"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/43</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KronosZenom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I guess it’s really up to the devs what they want the game to be, but traditionally in other mafia-type games, this kind of thing would never happen. ToL can still retain its uniqueness of having so many classes with so many abilities, without the cheesiness of the potential aids situation I describe in my original post</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/42</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KronosZenom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wasn’t planning to respond to your troll post, but when has this ever been about GP or rewards?</p>
<p>this is regarding the stability and balance of the game, Id still be making this topic if you got more gold for losing</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/41</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KronosZenom" data-post="35" data-topic="71376">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kronoszenom/40/6524_2.png" class="avatar"> KronosZenom:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>when you relentlessly trash a suggestion that increases the stability of the game</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When the game revolves around conversion, you have to expect an amount of instability, no? Some people are going to be more obvious when they’re converted than others. People will have a range of different reactions.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KronosZenom" data-post="35" data-topic="71376">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kronoszenom/40/6524_2.png" class="avatar"> KronosZenom:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>your win condition as BD is you do what you need to do to benefit your faction</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Correct</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KronosZenom" data-post="35" data-topic="71376">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kronoszenom/40/6524_2.png" class="avatar"> KronosZenom:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but then the last unseen facing certain defeat can decide to take away what you’ve been playing for (BD win) by making you not BD, that’s flawed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Say you’re against prince and GK and you and the game isn’t over, sure, life sucks. However, if there is even an <em>ounce</em> of unconfirmability, you need to go hammer and tong to do everything to benefit your NEW faction.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71376-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/add-a-n6-bd-ability-to-solve-being-late-game-converted-into-loss/71376.rss">Add a N6+ BD ability to solve being late game converted into loss</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
