<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277</link>
    <description>There once was A King in the Kingdom of Adiart. It was at the time of Darkness, Wind Blowing into the Trees surrounding the castle. Inside of the Castle Torches Burned with the Sound of Embers scraping against a Piece of Chalk. The King Sat happily on his thrown thinking about what the kingdom should do. Hes Butler slowly walked up to him, his feet slowly clomping against the hard grey. The King eyed the butler in a eerie style, almost as if he was staring into the butler&#39;s soul. The Butler, whose hand was out carrying a Silver Tray, slowly approached the king. The tray had a Silver Top to it, as if it was dissembling something that was inside of the object. The Butler opened his mouth and began to speak, &quot;Our Researchers have found something that was recovered in the Indies. It Resembles some sort of _Monkey&#39;s Paw_. 
The king eyed the butler in a way that was so distinct, he gazed at the butler&#39;s eyes straight. The King then stated, &quot;Why did you bring a monkey&#39;s Paw Here?&quot;. The Butler in fear of the king promptly responded, &quot;My Liege, this Paw has Magically abilities!&quot;. The King Laughed, as more of a Chuckle, in the face of the butler. The Butler Opened the Tray to reveal the paw of a Monkey, it looked like it was of a mummy&#39;s. The King swiftly grabbed the paw and stated, &quot;What kind of magical abilities does it have?&#39;. The king looked at the Butler again, but not in a sinister look but more in a, &quot;You get this Wrong im Going to Smite you!&quot; Look. The Butler parched his lips and began to open his mouth, &quot;The Paw has the ability to grant 3 wishes between 3 people.&quot;. The King Looked at the Butler, More interred, he responded to the butler&#39;s statement, &quot;Have there been any wishes granted?&quot;. The Butler Responded, &quot;2.... There have been 2.&quot;. The King looked at the Butler like he was going to kill him, he was ferrous that this information didn&#39;t immediately get to him. The King Stated, &quot;And Who were those two?&quot;. The Butler then told the king, &quot;I knew the man who had the first wishes, his last wish was for Death.&quot;. The Butler Began to Say the Next Line of his Phrase but he was Interrupted.  The King then said, &quot;I wish for a Cult to Arise Within the Kingdom.&quot;. The Butler looked at the king in shock, he realized that the king&#39;s finger twisted back, in the same way as the monkey&#39;s paw. The king yelled, &quot;GUARDS, THIS MAN HAS COMMITTED TREASON THROW HIM IN THE DUNGEON!&quot;. Promptly, 3 guards grabbed the butler, he was swiftly dragged away. In a last cry for help, the butler stated &quot;THE.. THE KING IS&quot;, he was stopped, for the knights gagged him. The king then wished for another, &quot;I wish for my son to realize the same views that I have, I wish for him to be evil.&quot;. The paw twisted it&#39;s hand back, and with it the hand of the king twisted back. Hours Past, the Butler was In the Dungeons of the Prince. The Prince approached the Butler, he spoke &quot;You have committed Treason against the Kingdom!&quot; The Prince turns, he spits. The Prince then began to state, &quot;Your obviously a trustworthy person, I have known you for years!&quot;. The Butler swiftly responded to the Prince in Excitement, &quot;THANK YOU! I KNEW I COULD TRUST YO~&quot;. The Butler was Interrupted by the Prince, &quot;And that Is why I shall have your Head.&quot;. The Butler Gulped, he was afraid of what will happen next, for he was surprised by this. The Day Began again, and the King had his final wish. He then spoke aloud in his chambers, while the sun was rising. &quot;I wish for you death.&quot;. Time paused....................................................</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 22:05:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://americanliterature.com/author/w-w-jacobs/short-story/the-monkeys-paw" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://americanliterature.com/author/w-w-jacobs/short-story/the-monkeys-paw</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 22:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8277-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277.rss">The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Never heard of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8277-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277.rss">The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Its a parody on “The Monkey’s Paw”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 11:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8277-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277.rss">The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m both confused as to where this fits in existing lore, and why the King manages to view himself as evil. Nobody does that, so it’s almost jarringly unrealistic to have him wish that his son is “evil like him”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 02:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8277-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277.rss">The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There once was A King in the Kingdom of Adiart. It was at the time of Darkness, Wind Blowing into the Trees surrounding the castle. Inside of the Castle Torches Burned with the Sound of Embers scraping against a Piece of Chalk. The King Sat happily on his thrown thinking about what the kingdom should do. Hes Butler slowly walked up to him, his feet slowly clomping against the hard grey. The King eyed the butler in a eerie style, almost as if he was staring into the butler’s soul. The Butler, whose hand was out carrying a Silver Tray, slowly approached the king. The tray had a Silver Top to it, as if it was dissembling something that was inside of the object. The Butler opened his mouth and began to speak, "Our Researchers have found something that was recovered in the Indies. It Resembles some sort of <em>Monkey’s Paw</em>.<br>
The king eyed the butler in a way that was so distinct, he gazed at the butler’s eyes straight. The King then stated, “Why did you bring a monkey’s Paw Here?”. The Butler in fear of the king promptly responded, “My Liege, this Paw has Magically abilities!”. The King Laughed, as more of a Chuckle, in the face of the butler. The Butler Opened the Tray to reveal the paw of a Monkey, it looked like it was of a mummy’s. The King swiftly grabbed the paw and stated, "What kind of magical abilities does it have?’. The king looked at the Butler again, but not in a sinister look but more in a, “You get this Wrong im Going to Smite you!” Look. The Butler parched his lips and began to open his mouth, “The Paw has the ability to grant 3 wishes between 3 people.”. The King Looked at the Butler, More interred, he responded to the butler’s statement, “Have there been any wishes granted?”. The Butler Responded, “2… There have been 2.”. The King looked at the Butler like he was going to kill him, he was ferrous that this information didn’t immediately get to him. The King Stated, “And Who were those two?”. The Butler then told the king, “I knew the man who had the first wishes, his last wish was for Death.”. The Butler Began to Say the Next Line of his Phrase but he was Interrupted.  The King then said, “I wish for a Cult to Arise Within the Kingdom.”. The Butler looked at the king in shock, he realized that the king’s finger twisted back, in the same way as the monkey’s paw. The king yelled, “GUARDS, THIS MAN HAS COMMITTED TREASON THROW HIM IN THE DUNGEON!”. Promptly, 3 guards grabbed the butler, he was swiftly dragged away. In a last cry for help, the butler stated “THE… THE KING IS”, he was stopped, for the knights gagged him. The king then wished for another, “I wish for my son to realize the same views that I have, I wish for him to be evil.”. The paw twisted it’s hand back, and with it the hand of the king twisted back. Hours Past, the Butler was In the Dungeons of the Prince. The Prince approached the Butler, he spoke “You have committed Treason against the Kingdom!” The Prince turns, he spits. The Prince then began to state, “Your obviously a trustworthy person, I have known you for years!”. The Butler swiftly responded to the Prince in Excitement, “THANK YOU! I KNEW I COULD TRUST YO~”. The Butler was Interrupted by the Prince, “And that Is why I shall have your Head.”. The Butler Gulped, he was afraid of what will happen next, for he was surprised by this. The Day Began again, and the King had his final wish. He then spoke aloud in his chambers, while the sun was rising. “I wish for you death.”. Time paused…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 23:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8277-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-kingdoms-paw/8277.rss">The Kingdom&#39;s Paw</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
