<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Class Cards for SFoL: Regicide</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-cards-for-sfol-regicide/1323</link>
    <description>&gt;# Butler
&gt;You&#39;ve been working at this castle since you were seven, and you make sure that everyone knows it. Using your position as a servant to your advantage, may convince two guests to swap rooms for the night. However, people will get angry with you if you do this too often.
&gt;**Twice per game you may swap two players at night, causing all actions against one to target the other and vice-versa.**
---
&gt;# Court Wizard
&gt;You may be frail and sickly, but your years spent working as a librarian have paid off in more ways than you expected. As you are in possession of a magical tome, you may place an ice ward on a player&#39;s room each night. This completely freezes them, keeping them from harm but also preventing them from moving.
&gt;**Each night you may freeze one player, roleblocking them but also protecting them from death.**
---
&gt;# Knight
&gt;Years of combat experience and protecting the King have steeled you to killing. Therefore, what better way to solve your current crisis than do what you do best — guarding others with extreme prejudice.
&gt;**Twice per game you may protect a player&#39;s room, killing any who attempt to enter.**
---
&gt;# Noble
&gt;You know you&#39;re not much of a man. You&#39;ve had a silver spoon in your mouth since the day you were born. This position - it&#39;s not suited for a meek gentleman like yourself. But you&#39;ll be damned if you tuck your tail between your legs at the first sight of peril. Therefore, you wander the halls at night and try to catch glimpses of anybody doing anything out of the ordinary.
&gt;**You will be informed if and where: the Knight is standing guard, the Butler is switching guests&#39; rooms, the Court Wizard is freezing somebody, the Paladin is attacking somebody, or the Physician is checking up on somebody passively every night.**
---
&gt;# Observer
&gt;As the Castle&#39;s only passable astronomer, you have spent years gazing at the stars. In the current crisis, however, you are determined to gaze into the hearts of your fellow men. Or, barring that, their rooms.
&gt;**Every night, you may watch a player&#39;s room, seing all who visit.**
---
&gt;# Paladin
&gt;You&#39;ve spent years of your life murdering others in the name of religion. The King&#39;s death gives you the perfect opportunity to continue doing just that. However, doing so will almost certainly see your weapons confiscated.
&gt;**Once per game, you may kill any player at night.**
---
&gt;# Physician
&gt;You feel like a total failure. The King died on your watch, and there was nothing you could do to stop the poison coursing through his veins. You wildly start mixing potions and remedies of every sort, but in your despair accidentially knock your entire supply onto the ground. You were only able to save two vials of the resulting mixture, and while you can&#39;t guarantee its effects, it&#39;s all you have.
&gt;**Twice per game, you may check up on a player at night and slip them a vial of your potion, allowing them to move before everybody else that night and making them immune to death.**
---
&gt;# Priest
&gt;Long years of your life have been spent attending to the religious duties of the castle and its inhabitants. Your spiritual endevors have led Photine to grant you minor control over the souls of the dead, and as such you have been planning funerals since the late King&#39;s father sat on the throne. In this crisis, your power might be the only way to determine whether the dead are allied with or against you.
&gt;**You will be informed of the alignment of each player on their death. Once per game, you may spend a night meditating, allowing you to send and receive one 100-character message from any dead player of your choice.**
--- 
&gt;# Prince
&gt;Your father may be dead, but you still have a job to do. You must lead your people through this struggle and emerge as the victorious faction, so you may claim the throne and continue to rule. 
&gt;**As next in line to the throne, your vote counts as double that of any other citizen during the day.**
---
&gt;# Princess
&gt;You&#39;ve spent your entire life waiting to be married off for the good of the family, so you understandably feel quite lost in the current calamity. However, you are determined to find some way to help avenge your father&#39;s death - you just need to start studying.
&gt;**Once per game, you make take the class of a deceased player.**
---
&gt;# Psychic
&gt;You&#39;ve always had a strong affinity for the occult. So strong, in fact, that you&#39;ve let magic come to you rather than study it like so many others. And while some may claim that this is taking the easy road through life, you don&#39;t care - they&#39;ll never be as talented as you with magic anyways. If only you&#39;d spent enough time to learn more than one spell, that is.
&gt;**Each night, you may focus your spirit and link minds with another player, allowing you to communicate with them for the duration of the night.**
---
&gt;# Sheriff
&gt;As the man in charge of enforcing the laws, you&#39;ve picked up a couple tricks on snooping around. Given the situation, you decide to use your intimate knowledge of the castle&#39;s security to sneak around and see if anybody seems to be working together.
&gt;**Each night you may check a player, comparing their alignment to the last player you checked.**</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 02:40:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum of Lies</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-cards-for-sfol-regicide/1323.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Class Cards for SFoL: Regicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>Butler</h1>
<p>You’ve been working at this castle since you were seven, and you make sure that everyone knows it. Using your position as a servant to your advantage, may convince two guests to swap rooms for the night. However, people will get angry with you if you do this too often.<br>
<strong>Twice per game you may swap two players at night, causing all actions against one to target the other and vice-versa.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Court Wizard</h1>
<p>You may be frail and sickly, but your years spent working as a librarian have paid off in more ways than you expected. As you are in possession of a magical tome, you may place an ice ward on a player’s room each night. This completely freezes them, keeping them from harm but also preventing them from moving.<br>
<strong>Each night you may freeze one player, roleblocking them but also protecting them from death.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Knight</h1>
<p>Years of combat experience and protecting the King have steeled you to killing. Therefore, what better way to solve your current crisis than do what you do best — guarding others with extreme prejudice.<br>
<strong>Twice per game you may protect a player’s room, killing any who attempt to enter.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Noble</h1>
<p>You know you’re not much of a man. You’ve had a silver spoon in your mouth since the day you were born. This position - it’s not suited for a meek gentleman like yourself. But you’ll be damned if you tuck your tail between your legs at the first sight of peril. Therefore, you wander the halls at night and try to catch glimpses of anybody doing anything out of the ordinary.<br>
<strong>You will be informed if and where: the Knight is standing guard, the Butler is switching guests’ rooms, the Court Wizard is freezing somebody, the Paladin is attacking somebody, or the Physician is checking up on somebody passively every night.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Observer</h1>
<p>As the Castle’s only passable astronomer, you have spent years gazing at the stars. In the current crisis, however, you are determined to gaze into the hearts of your fellow men. Or, barring that, their rooms.<br>
<strong>Every night, you may watch a player’s room, seing all who visit.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Paladin</h1>
<p>You’ve spent years of your life murdering others in the name of religion. The King’s death gives you the perfect opportunity to continue doing just that. However, doing so will almost certainly see your weapons confiscated.<br>
<strong>Once per game, you may kill any player at night.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Physician</h1>
<p>You feel like a total failure. The King died on your watch, and there was nothing you could do to stop the poison coursing through his veins. You wildly start mixing potions and remedies of every sort, but in your despair accidentially knock your entire supply onto the ground. You were only able to save two vials of the resulting mixture, and while you can’t guarantee its effects, it’s all you have.<br>
<strong>Twice per game, you may check up on a player at night and slip them a vial of your potion, allowing them to move before everybody else that night and making them immune to death.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Priest</h1>
<p>Long years of your life have been spent attending to the religious duties of the castle and its inhabitants. Your spiritual endevors have led Photine to grant you minor control over the souls of the dead, and as such you have been planning funerals since the late King’s father sat on the throne. In this crisis, your power might be the only way to determine whether the dead are allied with or against you.<br>
<strong>You will be informed of the alignment of each player on their death. Once per game, you may spend a night meditating, allowing you to send and receive one 100-character message from any dead player of your choice.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Prince</h1>
<p>Your father may be dead, but you still have a job to do. You must lead your people through this struggle and emerge as the victorious faction, so you may claim the throne and continue to rule.<br>
<strong>As next in line to the throne, your vote counts as double that of any other citizen during the day.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Princess</h1>
<p>You’ve spent your entire life waiting to be married off for the good of the family, so you understandably feel quite lost in the current calamity. However, you are determined to find some way to help avenge your father’s death - you just need to start studying.<br>
<strong>Once per game, you make take the class of a deceased player.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Psychic</h1>
<p>You’ve always had a strong affinity for the occult. So strong, in fact, that you’ve let magic come to you rather than study it like so many others. And while some may claim that this is taking the easy road through life, you don’t care - they’ll never be as talented as you with magic anyways. If only you’d spent enough time to learn more than one spell, that is.<br>
<strong>Each night, you may focus your spirit and link minds with another player, allowing you to communicate with them for the duration of the night.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Sheriff</h1>
<p>As the man in charge of enforcing the laws, you’ve picked up a couple tricks on snooping around. Given the situation, you decide to use your intimate knowledge of the castle’s security to sneak around and see if anybody seems to be working together.<br>
<strong>Each night you may check a player, comparing their alignment to the last player you checked.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-cards-for-sfol-regicide/1323/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-cards-for-sfol-regicide/1323/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 10:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1323-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-cards-for-sfol-regicide/1323.rss">Class Cards for SFoL: Regicide</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
