<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551</link>
    <description>==========================

**PROLOGUE**

===================================
Ones speak of boslof in the mist, none truly know her origins. Today, me, Braixen will try to uncover the secret history of the legendary boslof. 

The furthest back or researches can find of the legendary Boslof, we have found out that the first post she ever posted on the discord, Throne of Lies server was a picture of a man putting his face in a cake. This came to surprise our researchers, seeing as though the nature of the cake and the man appear to be mysterious. And, it came more to our surprise that the post was in #Off-top-not-tol, which is one of the places she hand picks people for her _fan club_, all of our researchers names will not be told in fear of assassins coming for them. In these 5 chapters, with the start of reign of boslof, the conquering of the land and recruiting her army, to the climax of her rule of a thousand slaves. To how she decided to not rule the world, to what we think will come next. Follow this 5 chapter lore, and discover the secrets of Boslof.

================================

**CHAPTER 1, THE RISE TO POWER**

================================

Boslof first started her rise to power and fame with her first post on 12/23/2016, we have uncovered scrolls of this, but they were burnt due to the power of black magic. The scrap of paper that was left was the date 12/23/2016. This is happened to be 17 days before the launch of the kick-starter campaign of Throne of Lies. This campaign dates back to January, 9th 2017. This is a powerful record of the legendary boslof, none of our other records manage to date back further. But, after this post her campaign for power started. Where he began to get millions of supports to stand by her side, where her rise to power began.

=====================================================

**CHAPTER 2, THE ARMY OF MILLIONS**

====================================================

We have seen many inscriptions around these a ages, many and many. But the inscription that we all find the most interesting and chocking is Boslof&#39;s first slave. If you are asking, who must be the first slave of boslof, it must be someone truly loyal to them, and the answer might shock you. The first slave of boslof was, flaggy. This is surprising to most people seeing as though boslof no longer has him as a loyal slave. &quot;This is the start to a enormous army in which she will rule the world with a iron fist with. The legendary boslof has recruited many to become part of her army and this will be the start of the campaign to rule the world. She will be crowned king of the world with her slaves by her side for none to oppose her, for she is the legendary boslof.&quot; ~ The prophecy, this prophecy was foretold, we have found records of a meeting that took place, in order for boslof to take over the world. Unfortunately we are risking the lives of our writers in the process of reading this, so we will not read this scroll on the meeting of the Boslof and her slave court.

=========================


**Chapter 3: Rule of the master and A thousand slaves**


=================================

After the destruction of many of her foes, the master known has Boslof had carried her slaves all threw the land. Some tried to betray them, but no matter boslof took care of their rebelliun not by killing them but by sacrificing them to lord Mithras. This allowed her to not only keep the support of her slaves from the dead, but also allowed her to gain more power to rule the land with. she and her slaves crossed the land kindly with no burning houses or Killing the Innocent. but being kind to everyone that there was. This is what are researches have uncovered about the reign of the legendary boslof, or Boslof the Great. For she is the true ruler of the land and bringer of peace. This is according to the writings in the medieval age. These facts are passed down from generation to generation, each tale different from the last.

=============================================

**Chapter 4: The end of her rule**

================================

While boslof&#39;s rule will truly never end. The &quot;end&quot; of her rule over the kingdom and her slaves, is a simple yet kind one. When she freed her slaves from their willing captivity, and creating a &quot;fan club&quot; inviting many people, but her slaves that stayed loyal to her side all this time, they were invited immediately into this fan club. This surprised most people seeing as though more were welcome to joining this &quot;Fan club&quot; then becoming a slave to the mighty boslof. Some think that this &quot;Fan club&quot; is actually a cult in which they sacrifice their members to the lord Mithras in order to give boslof their power. 
Although these stories are frequent, I have searched for accurate proof of these happening and nothing seems to points to this being fact. In the case that it is fact, I would not object seeing as though I would even willingly sacrifice my self for the legendary boslof. But that leaves the question as to how as no one figured it out yet, and why is this not proven fact yet. Well some say, that whenever a person tries to escape the grasp of boslof, she will sacrifice them, although I believe this to not be true, seeing as though the legendary boslof or boslof the great is very kind. She even gives her club members treats to eat. So, in my opinion this isn&#39;t really the fall of boslof but instead the rise of a new age of boslof one that she wins via kindness rather then control (although he did it already). 
 
============================

**Chapter 5: The End**

=====================

This seems to be the end of our story uncovering the facts and myths of boslof the great, each second we spend here, the more we uncover about boslof. She turned out to not be a evil and cold heart-ed man but a generous and kind one. Although~ &quot;Sir!&quot; 
Braixen: Yes?
?: We have found something that contradicts all of this.
Braixen: What?
?: We have found the lair of boslof&#39;s slaves
Braixen: But this cant be a bad thing, we will learn more about her, let us go
?: No but sir
Braixen: Yes
?: The liar is, is, is 
Braixen: Spit it out
?: The liar is made out of~

_The page ends here_</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 17:20:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off-Topic (Thronepass)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>*Fan club</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 17:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Must be Boslof’s slave.</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#SaveTheSlave</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 17:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is just the kind of quality suggestion this forum was made for.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 07:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This. This is the lore we needed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 01:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Braixen" data-post="1" data-topic="2551">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/braixen/40/26209_2.png" class="avatar"> Braixen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>?: The liar is made out of~ JOHN CENAA!!!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The John Cena part is faked</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 01:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 01:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TryphonX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You spent all this time… to write a Lore for Boslof? <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/+1.png?v=9" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 01:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Boslof</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>==========================</p>
<p><strong>PROLOGUE</strong></p>
<p>===================================<br>
Ones speak of boslof in the mist, none truly know her origins. Today, me, Braixen will try to uncover the secret history of the legendary boslof.</p>
<p>The furthest back or researches can find of the legendary Boslof, we have found out that the first post she ever posted on the discord, Throne of Lies server was a picture of a man putting his face in a cake. This came to surprise our researchers, seeing as though the nature of the cake and the man appear to be mysterious. And, it came more to our surprise that the post was in <span class="hashtag">#Off-top-not-tol</span>, which is one of the places she hand picks people for her <em>fan club</em>, all of our researchers names will not be told in fear of assassins coming for them. In these 5 chapters, with the start of reign of boslof, the conquering of the land and recruiting her army, to the climax of her rule of a thousand slaves. To how she decided to not rule the world, to what we think will come next. Follow this 5 chapter lore, and discover the secrets of Boslof.</p>
<p>================================</p>
<p><strong>CHAPTER 1, THE RISE TO POWER</strong></p>
<p>================================</p>
<p>Boslof first started her rise to power and fame with her first post on 12/23/2016, we have uncovered scrolls of this, but they were burnt due to the power of black magic. The scrap of paper that was left was the date 12/23/2016. This is happened to be 17 days before the launch of the kick-starter campaign of Throne of Lies. This campaign dates back to January, 9th 2017. This is a powerful record of the legendary boslof, none of our other records manage to date back further. But, after this post her campaign for power started. Where he began to get millions of supports to stand by her side, where her rise to power began.</p>
<p>=====================================================</p>
<p><strong>CHAPTER 2, THE ARMY OF MILLIONS</strong></p>
<p>====================================================</p>
<p>We have seen many inscriptions around these a ages, many and many. But the inscription that we all find the most interesting and chocking is Boslof’s first slave. If you are asking, who must be the first slave of boslof, it must be someone truly loyal to them, and the answer might shock you. The first slave of boslof was, flaggy. This is surprising to most people seeing as though boslof no longer has him as a loyal slave. “This is the start to a enormous army in which she will rule the world with a iron fist with. The legendary boslof has recruited many to become part of her army and this will be the start of the campaign to rule the world. She will be crowned king of the world with her slaves by her side for none to oppose her, for she is the legendary boslof.” ~ The prophecy, this prophecy was foretold, we have found records of a meeting that took place, in order for boslof to take over the world. Unfortunately we are risking the lives of our writers in the process of reading this, so we will not read this scroll on the meeting of the Boslof and her slave court.</p>
<p>=========================</p>
<p><strong>Chapter 3: Rule of the master and A thousand slaves</strong></p>
<p>=================================</p>
<p>After the destruction of many of her foes, the master known has Boslof had carried her slaves all threw the land. Some tried to betray them, but no matter boslof took care of their rebelliun not by killing them but by sacrificing them to lord Mithras. This allowed her to not only keep the support of her slaves from the dead, but also allowed her to gain more power to rule the land with. she and her slaves crossed the land kindly with no burning houses or Killing the Innocent. but being kind to everyone that there was. This is what are researches have uncovered about the reign of the legendary boslof, or Boslof the Great. For she is the true ruler of the land and bringer of peace. This is according to the writings in the medieval age. These facts are passed down from generation to generation, each tale different from the last.</p>
<p>=============================================</p>
<p><strong>Chapter 4: The end of her rule</strong></p>
<p>================================</p>
<p>While boslof’s rule will truly never end. The “end” of her rule over the kingdom and her slaves, is a simple yet kind one. When she freed her slaves from their willing captivity, and creating a “fan club” inviting many people, but her slaves that stayed loyal to her side all this time, they were invited immediately into this fan club. This surprised most people seeing as though more were welcome to joining this “Fan club” then becoming a slave to the mighty boslof. Some think that this “Fan club” is actually a cult in which they sacrifice their members to the lord Mithras in order to give boslof their power.<br>
Although these stories are frequent, I have searched for accurate proof of these happening and nothing seems to points to this being fact. In the case that it is fact, I would not object seeing as though I would even willingly sacrifice my self for the legendary boslof. But that leaves the question as to how as no one figured it out yet, and why is this not proven fact yet. Well some say, that whenever a person tries to escape the grasp of boslof, she will sacrifice them, although I believe this to not be true, seeing as though the legendary boslof or boslof the great is very kind. She even gives her club members treats to eat. So, in my opinion this isn’t really the fall of boslof but instead the rise of a new age of boslof one that she wins via kindness rather then control (although he did it already).</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><strong>Chapter 5: The End</strong></p>
<p>=====================</p>
<p>This seems to be the end of our story uncovering the facts and myths of boslof the great, each second we spend here, the more we uncover about boslof. She turned out to not be a evil and cold heart-ed man but a generous and kind one. Although~ “Sir!”<br>
Braixen: Yes?<br>
?: We have found something that contradicts all of this.<br>
Braixen: What?<br>
?: We have found the lair of boslof’s slaves<br>
Braixen: But this cant be a bad thing, we will learn more about her, let us go<br>
?: No but sir<br>
Braixen: Yes<br>
?: The liar is, is, is<br>
Braixen: Spit it out<br>
?: The liar is made out of~</p>
<p><em>The page ends here</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 00:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2551-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-boslof/2551.rss">[Lore suggestion] Boslof</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
