<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612</link>
    <description>I&#39;m gonna be honest right from the get go, guys -- fool and scorned are my favorite classes by a mile. I love the idea of using chaos to disrupt the flow of the game. 

However, the day ability of both the fool and scorned, trollbox, is utterly useless. 

In the current meta, trollbox is easily dismissed. It has one use, and once you use it, the recipient of its effect is immediately able to dismiss the message by stating that it was a &quot;tb&quot;. If you&#39;re REALLY lucky, maybe your victim doesn&#39;t see the trollbox, but when others call them out on it, it&#39;s almost certain that they will. 

Most people who use trollbox use it to say pointless things, which is trolling, but at a meta level, which defeats the purpose of it in the first place. 

I propose this:

Trollbox should silence its target for 10 seconds and only have two uses. This removes both problems with trollbox -- spamming pointless messages won&#39;t be able to occur under limited usage, and a ten second silence will allow a well-timed trollbox to cause some much desired chaos in the game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 05:44:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Trollbox is fine as-is.  People absolutely do not ask for every single line to be repeated twice; they only ask for surprising or suspicious things to get repeated twice.  This forces Scorned and Fools to use the TB creatively, which is a good thing - if you could just TB the Sheriff to say “X is Unseen!”, it would be silly and boring.</p>
<p>You’re supposed to use it to stealthily insert innocuous-seeming lines into a conversation that will help accomplish your goal, not to use it as a blunt weapon.  The fact that you have to prevent anyone from suspecting a TB for it to work is a feature, not a bug.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 05:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Trollbox is fine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 05:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Basically don’t make someone accuse. Instead make a small statement like “Poisoned” or “Btw I’m alch. Don’t mind me” or something else that no one would think twice about and thus wouldn’t ask for a repeat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually use TB to make the target say little things that no one would think twice about right up until the point where he starts contradicting himself.</p>
<p>That or I make someone say exe when someone is on the stand (usually king) to encourage others to exe.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[methomps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the 10-second silence would actually be a mini-nerf to TB unless you are proposing that the target is not informed they are silenced.  10 seconds just isn’t very long.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Littlefinger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with you that you CAN make good plays with your words, but ultimately, that’s true of any class, and the difference is, the win conditions for fool and scorned are more difficult to achieve solely with words. Frame is a good night ability, but it really is reliant on pure luck and can actually out you as fool or scorned in some cases.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The thing is that Scorned/Fool don’t need any powers. You can make good plays with just your words, and they don’t really need any abilities. If you make Trollbox useful, then it will be too easy for them.</p>
<p>Especially when they also have Frame.</p>
<p>And it does have its uses, especially towards the end of the day or on trial when. There is little time to check for a Trollbox.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Littlefinger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree that Scorned and Fool’s words are powerful, but they aren’t really any more powerful than the words of any other classes that ultimately have much better day abilities that they can use. Scorned and Fool have to try extremely hard to win in some cases, because good BD can typically out a Scorned and Fool really easily, and have the prince execute them.</p>
<p>Infinite use hardly matters when it’s always the same thing:</p>
<p>(insert trollbox here)<br>
“I was TBed”<br>
“oh ok”</p>
<p>It’s not just weak at this point, it’s useless.</p>
<p>Edit: Thanks for the reply, by the way!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t really think how weak it is is bad.</p>
<p>Scorned and Fool’s own words are very powerful. While Trollbox is a neat ability and does have a little utility, I think it’s better as infinite use and weak.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tweaking Trollbox</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Littlefinger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m gonna be honest right from the get go, guys – fool and scorned are my favorite classes by a mile. I love the idea of using chaos to disrupt the flow of the game.</p>
<p>However, the day ability of both the fool and scorned, trollbox, is utterly useless.</p>
<p>In the current meta, trollbox is easily dismissed. It has one use, and once you use it, the recipient of its effect is immediately able to dismiss the message by stating that it was a “tb”. If you’re REALLY lucky, maybe your victim doesn’t see the trollbox, but when others call them out on it, it’s almost certain that they will.</p>
<p>Most people who use trollbox use it to say pointless things, which is trolling, but at a meta level, which defeats the purpose of it in the first place.</p>
<p>I propose this:</p>
<p>Trollbox should silence its target for 10 seconds and only have two uses. This removes both problems with trollbox – spamming pointless messages won’t be able to occur under limited usage, and a ten second silence will allow a well-timed trollbox to cause some much desired chaos in the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53612-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tweaking-trollbox/53612.rss">Tweaking Trollbox</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
