<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>As a poss inside a king, lost 1v1 vs prince</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478</link>
    <description>#### What happened?
I was possessor inside the body of king. At the end of the last day phase, only I and prince remained alive. BD won and I lost right then automatically

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?

Well if the game actually played out, I think I would have won. At night, prince wouldn&#39;t be able to jail me since I was &quot;king&quot; (I was possessor, not really king, but still, I think prince cannot jail me if I have the &quot;King&quot; tag). So I would attack prince at night and kill him.

#### Steps to reproduce:

1.Be a possessor
2.Jump into king
3.Make sure only you and prince survive the last day phase

#### Comments:

To be honest, I am not sure how various 1v1 situations in the endgame resolve (who wins among kings, killers, princes) so I could just be misunderstanding something.
 
Just some additional details, in case they matter.
1.On the last night, I jumped from my original body into bd king. I am mentioning this in case it&#39;s a bug that doesn&#39;t register possessor win if he jumps on the last night. For example, I have seen a bug where if a scorned gets his target executed on the very last day, the game doesn&#39;t register it as a win.

2.On the last day phase, 4 people remained: A) me, a poss inside a king&#39;s body, B)a resurrected prince, C)a hunter, D)a random bd (can&#39;t remember what role).  We voted and executed the hunter and D died to the hunter passive. So only I and prince remained alive. Then the game just ended and bd won.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:41:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>As a poss inside a king, lost 1v1 vs prince</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is why I think the game should simply play out as meny situations as possible.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6478-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478.rss">As a poss inside a king, lost 1v1 vs prince</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>As a poss inside a king, lost 1v1 vs prince</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm. Seems like the code doesn’t recognize the Possessor as a “King” when it takes control of the body.</p>
<p>Would a Prince be able to imprison a Possessor King during the day? If his player number lights up during the day, that would be a huge issue and giveaway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6478-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478.rss">As a poss inside a king, lost 1v1 vs prince</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>As a poss inside a king, lost 1v1 vs prince</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TruthTeller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>I was possessor inside the body of king. At the end of the last day phase, only I and prince remained alive. BD won and I lost right then automatically</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>Well if the game actually played out, I think I would have won. At night, prince wouldn’t be able to jail me since I was “king” (I was possessor, not really king, but still, I think prince cannot jail me if I have the “King” tag). So I would attack prince at night and kill him.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<p>1.Be a possessor<br>
2.Jump into king<br>
3.Make sure only you and prince survive the last day phase</p>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>To be honest, I am not sure how various 1v1 situations in the endgame resolve (who wins among kings, killers, princes) so I could just be misunderstanding something.</p>
<p>Just some additional details, in case they matter.<br>
1.On the last night, I jumped from my original body into bd king. I am mentioning this in case it’s a bug that doesn’t register possessor win if he jumps on the last night. For example, I have seen a bug where if a scorned gets his target executed on the very last day, the game doesn’t register it as a win.</p>
<p>2.On the last day phase, 4 people remained: A) me, a poss inside a king’s body, B)a resurrected prince, C)a hunter, D)a random bd (can’t remember what role).  We voted and executed the hunter and D died to the hunter passive. So only I and prince remained alive. Then the game just ended and bd won.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6478-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/as-a-poss-inside-a-king-lost-1v1-vs-prince/6478.rss">As a poss inside a king, lost 1v1 vs prince</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
