<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Seeker</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-seeker/522</link>
    <description>[http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Seeker](http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Seeker)

**Seekers Path**

**Lore**
The Seeker once a loyal princess was approached by a cult leader who spoke tempting words even tho they went against her ideals Infact, they were twisted into evil intent, who knew the princess was so weak or was something else at work? no matter what went on that night she betrayed the blue dragon

The seeker was promised power but never told the price of it. her right eye was forcibly removed and imbued with magic letting her see as she never saw before. even since this she wore a blindfold with the symbol of Mithras covering her lost eye socket symbolizing his power

ever since this the seeker has used her newfound power obeying the leader as her fellow cult members die until the night she will also be killed in the name of Mithras

**Explanations**
I believe the short stories each class gets won&#39;t need in detail how their powers work only the way they got them. so I never focused on each of her powers only the general.

the Cult leader has the power brainwash making it easy to convert people to the cult. However, we don&#39;t know how he can do this is it natural talent or is one of the gods weakening her? does add some mystery 

I picked the princess because the seeker picture is a girl making princess the easy choice however if you don&#39;t wish to have cult roles come from a single class I can change this
speaking about the seeker&#39;s picture I took some things like the Mithras symbol on the blindfold covering the eye she lost and added meaning to it

if you are wondering about anything just ask</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 09:48:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-seeker/522.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Seeker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Seeker" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Seeker</a></p>
<p><strong>Seekers Path</strong></p>
<p><strong>Lore</strong><br>
The Seeker once a loyal princess was approached by a cult leader who spoke tempting words even tho they went against her ideals Infact, they were twisted into evil intent, who knew the princess was so weak or was something else at work? no matter what went on that night she betrayed the blue dragon</p>
<p>The seeker was promised power but never told the price of it. her right eye was forcibly removed and imbued with magic letting her see as she never saw before. even since this she wore a blindfold with the symbol of Mithras covering her lost eye socket symbolizing his power</p>
<p>ever since this the seeker has used her newfound power obeying the leader as her fellow cult members die until the night she will also be killed in the name of Mithras</p>
<p><strong>Explanations</strong><br>
I believe the short stories each class gets won’t need in detail how their powers work only the way they got them. so I never focused on each of her powers only the general.</p>
<p>the Cult leader has the power brainwash making it easy to convert people to the cult. However, we don’t know how he can do this is it natural talent or is one of the gods weakening her? does add some mystery</p>
<p>I picked the princess because the seeker picture is a girl making princess the easy choice however if you don’t wish to have cult roles come from a single class I can change this<br>
speaking about the seeker’s picture I took some things like the Mithras symbol on the blindfold covering the eye she lost and added meaning to it</p>
<p>if you are wondering about anything just ask</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-seeker/522/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-seeker/522/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 09:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-522-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-seeker/522.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Seeker</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
