<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011</link>
    <description>As the physician bustled about his chambers, he heaved a weary sigh. He hadn&#39;t chosen this profession, but his father before him had also been a healer, and so apprenticeship was the obvious choice. &quot;Potions go here, charms over there...&quot; he muttered to himself as he rearranged his shelves, but he gave a start when he heard a sharp knock at the door.

&quot;May I help you?&quot; he asked, inching the door open to peer cautiously at the visitor.
&quot;I&#39;m afraid I am in dire need of healing,&quot; replied the aging man. &quot;May I come in?&quot;
&quot;Of course,&quot; the physician beckoned, pulling the door open to allow his guest to enter. &quot;Seat yourself; I&#39;ll be there in a moment. Oh, and don&#39;t mind the cadaver on the table...&quot;

The visitor hobbled over to a chair to sit. &quot;Always good to have a court physician,&quot; he remarked gratefully. &quot;You have my gratitude!&quot;
&quot;Actually, I once dreamt of becoming a court wizard,&quot; the physician admitted with a chuckle. &quot;Thought I&#39;d learn the ways of the mages, but my father had other plans for me.&quot;
The wounded man eyed him curiously as he worked. &quot;A wizard, you say? Well, that sounds rather fun.&quot;
A wistful smile played at the healer&#39;s lips. &quot;Indeed,&quot; he agreed, &quot;but it&#39;s too late for that now.&quot;
Leaning in closer, the old man lowered his voice as he spoke. &quot;It&#39;s never too late to become a wizard, my friend. I believe I can help you...&quot;

The night passed quickly with good conversation, and by the dawn, the physician found himself uttering the names of the gods who promised him a glorious existence beyond a lost childhood dream. At the break of day, his visitor stood to leave. &quot;Farewell, my ritualist. We&#39;ll meet again under the cover of darkness.&quot;
The converted physician returned a grin. &quot;You have my eternal gratitude, sir. May the blessings of Corax and Mithras be with you!&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:50:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>rip corn</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was the CL, and a princess flirted them as S/S immediately after they claimed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>oh right</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="mention">@corn</span> thought that it would be a good idea to claim butler as rit :wowee:</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean… “CW claim? This is rit, exe this” in every cult game ever</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like how this points out how ritualist and CW are similar.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 20:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know I already shared this a while ago on the discord but I’m posting it here for consistency xD</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 20:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Ritualist [Lore]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As the physician bustled about his chambers, he heaved a weary sigh. He hadn’t chosen this profession, but his father before him had also been a healer, and so apprenticeship was the obvious choice. “Potions go here, charms over there…” he muttered to himself as he rearranged his shelves, but he gave a start when he heard a sharp knock at the door.</p>
<p>“May I help you?” he asked, inching the door open to peer cautiously at the visitor.<br>
“I’m afraid I am in dire need of healing,” replied the aging man. “May I come in?”<br>
“Of course,” the physician beckoned, pulling the door open to allow his guest to enter. “Seat yourself; I’ll be there in a moment. Oh, and don’t mind the cadaver on the table…”</p>
<p>The visitor hobbled over to a chair to sit. “Always good to have a court physician,” he remarked gratefully. “You have my gratitude!”<br>
“Actually, I once dreamt of becoming a court wizard,” the physician admitted with a chuckle. “Thought I’d learn the ways of the mages, but my father had other plans for me.”<br>
The wounded man eyed him curiously as he worked. “A wizard, you say? Well, that sounds rather fun.”<br>
A wistful smile played at the healer’s lips. “Indeed,” he agreed, “but it’s too late for that now.”<br>
Leaning in closer, the old man lowered his voice as he spoke. “It’s never too late to become a wizard, my friend. I believe I can help you…”</p>
<p>The night passed quickly with good conversation, and by the dawn, the physician found himself uttering the names of the gods who promised him a glorious existence beyond a lost childhood dream. At the break of day, his visitor stood to leave. “Farewell, my ritualist. We’ll meet again under the cover of darkness.”<br>
The converted physician returned a grin. “You have my eternal gratitude, sir. May the blessings of Corax and Mithras be with you!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 20:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-85011-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-ritualist-lore/85011.rss">The Ritualist [Lore]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
