<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092</link>
    <description>Brutalist [Neutral_Killer]

Goal: Survive until one faction is destroyed.

Passive Ability:
Steel Skin; Death Immune Once

Day Ability 1:
Brutalize - Select a character to prevent from taking any action at night. Five uses. (Sort of like Imprisoning but no conversation will occur, does not stop immunity&#39;s)

Day Ability 2:
Spit Rage - Sort of like the king&#39;s &#39;Thumb&#39; but only adds 2 to your vote for Execution. Two uses.

Night Ability 1:
Bestial Rage - Kill a target during the night. Five Uses.

Night Ability 2:
Stone Wall - Sort of like the king&#39;s guard, except it occupies anyone attempting to visit your selected target, but also prevents your target from taking an action, can be used on self to defend. Three Uses. (Unusable against king)

Lore:
A character of ill repute, not interested in trifling matters of goodwill or blood cults, or even the arts of stealth, the Brutalist is a character that only wants one thing, to fight another day. He has a hardy hide and a ferocious anger towards most if not all of the world. Having made most of his life from fighting hard with nothing but his hands the Brutalist is a force to be reckoned with.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandy_Claws]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With the voting power you would be found out immediately as a target. Defiantly as you get towards to mid to late game and less people are voting. And having a 5 use kill button seems heavily overpowered even if it’s more favored to BD side.</p>
<p>And the stone wall how does that affect occupy immune targets? Also into of that it’s like the court wizards ice barrier but does not let the person leave. What would be the reason behind it when so many other classes block in some way. (Drunk butler need CW invoker etc.) There is nothing that is too crazy that stands out besides how strong this class is. Late game having 5 uses on stopping a nighttime use is broken which ever side you decide to go with has a crazy advantage even more soon late game when you have the same voting power as the king.</p>
<p>Maby 2 uses of these abilities and change spit rage around to somthing like taunting everyone to target you and your granted night immunity each use of it.<br>
You would use it as a day ability and it would lock you out of using the rest of your nighttime abilities and anything that happens that night is targeted on you. Your granted night immunity and you can end up saving cult or BD depending on the context of it’s use. Only ones it would not affect would be prince Hunter and butler MM. Which are occupy immune. But it could be really strong in a cult game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 23:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8092-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092.rss">[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It doesn’t have standerard NK Ability’s. It’s sort of like Hunter + Merc + Alch. Maybe the type should be changed?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 19:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8092-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092.rss">[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>NK that can win with BD is far too easy</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 10:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8092-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092.rss">[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solar_Silver]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Brutalist [Neutral_Killer]</p>
<p>Goal: Survive until one faction is destroyed.</p>
<p>Passive Ability:<br>
Steel Skin; Death Immune Once</p>
<p>Day Ability 1:<br>
Brutalize - Select a character to prevent from taking any action at night. Five uses. (Sort of like Imprisoning but no conversation will occur, does not stop immunity’s)</p>
<p>Day Ability 2:<br>
Spit Rage - Sort of like the king’s ‘Thumb’ but only adds 2 to your vote for Execution. Two uses.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
Bestial Rage - Kill a target during the night. Five Uses.</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
Stone Wall - Sort of like the king’s guard, except it occupies anyone attempting to visit your selected target, but also prevents your target from taking an action, can be used on self to defend. Three Uses. (Unusable against king)</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
A character of ill repute, not interested in trifling matters of goodwill or blood cults, or even the arts of stealth, the Brutalist is a character that only wants one thing, to fight another day. He has a hardy hide and a ferocious anger towards most if not all of the world. Having made most of his life from fighting hard with nothing but his hands the Brutalist is a force to be reckoned with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 08:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8092-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-brutalist/8092.rss">[Class Suggestion] Brutalist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
