<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New faction focusing on poison, whispers and limited conversion</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-faction-focusing-on-poison-whispers-and-limited-conversion/8193</link>
    <description>I attached a link to the Google doc because it&#39;s easier for me to format my ideas in there.

The Herald: a Druid/Nature clan that invaded the castle to reclaim it for nature. The flavor is nature-y with poison, vine and tree-ish skills. 

I wanted to create a faction that relied on very limited conversion, high KPN potential but with delayed poison kills and an emphasis on whispering and communication.

If the Emerald dies, either the Prognosticator or the Cerebrus may choose to become the Emerald at night. 

The Killer class (Emerald) is unique in the sense he has the Hunter&#39;s Wolf Companion (essentially) but can target two people each night to make up for the fact his attacks can be healed. He has a limited back-up standard kill if somebody needs to die sooner. The day ability Last Stand also discourages BD from VFR as it becomes dangerous for a Prince or Priest to claim during the day if the Emerald can kill him instantly.  (though sacrificing yourself would be a strategic choice for sure.)

The Social class (Prognosticator) is unique in the way they are almost solely focusing on whispering and can pretend to be a Psychic at night. This causes some doubt to fall on &quot;confirmed &quot; Psychics. The Prog also has Royal Blood which feels fitting for a Social class. Being able to link minds with neutrals or Treants can help find allies. Link with your own Herald member if you want them to listen in on the conversation. 

The Offensive class (Cerberus) has a one shot conversion ability that has a high variance to it. Choosing a target causes all other players visiting that target to become Treants, replacing their current abilities and changing their win condition to the Herald&#39;s. The problem is that they don&#39;t know who the Treants or Herald are, so even if 4 or 5 Treants were converted, it wouldn&#39;t mean an auto loss for BD. The Cerberus can also protect visits to targets affected by poison, blocking the physician or alch from saving their target and casting suspicion on them.

Tear it apart, pls thnx :smile:



https://docs.google.com/document/d/1DL0_EP37RPZTuMPDpJJKys9TsRPjr3bwKaPC6Dt3XTw/edit?usp=sharing</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 19:46:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-faction-focusing-on-poison-whispers-and-limited-conversion/8193.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New faction focusing on poison, whispers and limited conversion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I attached a link to the Google doc because it’s easier for me to format my ideas in there.</p>
<p>The Herald: a Druid/Nature clan that invaded the castle to reclaim it for nature. The flavor is nature-y with poison, vine and tree-ish skills.</p>
<p>I wanted to create a faction that relied on very limited conversion, high KPN potential but with delayed poison kills and an emphasis on whispering and communication.</p>
<p>If the Emerald dies, either the Prognosticator or the Cerebrus may choose to become the Emerald at night.</p>
<p>The Killer class (Emerald) is unique in the sense he has the Hunter’s Wolf Companion (essentially) but can target two people each night to make up for the fact his attacks can be healed. He has a limited back-up standard kill if somebody needs to die sooner. The day ability Last Stand also discourages BD from VFR as it becomes dangerous for a Prince or Priest to claim during the day if the Emerald can kill him instantly.  (though sacrificing yourself would be a strategic choice for sure.)</p>
<p>The Social class (Prognosticator) is unique in the way they are almost solely focusing on whispering and can pretend to be a Psychic at night. This causes some doubt to fall on "confirmed " Psychics. The Prog also has Royal Blood which feels fitting for a Social class. Being able to link minds with neutrals or Treants can help find allies. Link with your own Herald member if you want them to listen in on the conversation.</p>
<p>The Offensive class (Cerberus) has a one shot conversion ability that has a high variance to it. Choosing a target causes all other players visiting that target to become Treants, replacing their current abilities and changing their win condition to the Herald’s. The problem is that they don’t know who the Treants or Herald are, so even if 4 or 5 Treants were converted, it wouldn’t mean an auto loss for BD. The Cerberus can also protect visits to targets affected by poison, blocking the physician or alch from saving their target and casting suspicion on them.</p>
<p>Tear it apart, pls thnx <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smile.png?v=9" title=":smile:" class="emoji" alt=":smile:"></p>
<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1DL0_EP37RPZTuMPDpJJKys9TsRPjr3bwKaPC6Dt3XTw/edit?usp=sharing" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://docs.google.com/document/d/1DL0_EP37RPZTuMPDpJJKys9TsRPjr3bwKaPC6Dt3XTw/edit?usp=sharing</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-faction-focusing-on-poison-whispers-and-limited-conversion/8193/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-faction-focusing-on-poison-whispers-and-limited-conversion/8193/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 19:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8193-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-faction-focusing-on-poison-whispers-and-limited-conversion/8193.rss">New faction focusing on poison, whispers and limited conversion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
