<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215</link>
    <description>First of all, I want to state upfront the following belief:
Throne of Lies is a paid game. It costs money to enjoy the service, it is not provided freely.
If you pay to participate in the game, and are them deprived of your ability to play said game, you should be entitled to a full refund. If you are not refunded, you have been robbed.
In very plain terms, banning players is theft. I find it entirely unconscionable. You have taken their money and decided, for whatever reason, to stop providing the thing they paid for. If you do not compensate them for this, you are a thief.

This is my stance and it is quite hardline. I would also note that i have never been banned or warned in this game at all. I&#39;ve merely seen reports from others who have, and it doesn&#39;t sit well with me

Now, all of that said, i do understand that there is some value in maintaining a certain quality of experience. That certain players - especially those who refuse to play the game correctly - drag down the quality for everyone, and there must be some way of ensuring that quality for a majority.

My proposed solution then, is not banning, but tiered play. 
Allow two modes of play. The moderated and the unmoderated queue.
The moderated queue works as normal, it is what we have now.
The unmoderated queue is a wild west. No rules, no holds barred. Nobody is allowed to report anyone else in those games,whatever happens, happens. Total freedom. Anything said or done in those games will be ignored, no action taken against such players
Only in the moderated queue will reports be allowed and reviewed

Instead of a ban, someone would be forced to play in the unmoderated queue only, for X number of games, before they can then play in the moderated one. &quot;Play&quot; in this case means participating until they complete their objective or die, as per usual. Then they may leave and play another

This should be a wholesale replacement for banning. At no point ever, should anyone be banned from playing the game that they played for. Only restricted in exactly who they can play with.
The unmoderated pool will be populated not only by those being punished, but also by those who, for whatever reason, can&#39;t tolerate rules and oversight. Racist names will be common, fools will spam their websites, gamethrowing will be commonplace, people will experiment with unusual and probably poorly advised tactics without fear of reprisal, some people will play it just to learn, without any worry about failure.

Whatever happens in the unmoderated pool stays there. It will act as a containment zone for all the most chaotic players and behaviours, leaving the normal moderated pool as a quality-assured experience of fair play</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 18:15:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TryphonX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 18:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TryphonX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Throne of Lies is a paid game. It costs money to enjoy the service, it is not provided freely.<br>
If you pay to participate in the game, and are them deprived of your ability to play said game, you should be entitled to a full refund. If you are not refunded, you have been robbed.<br>
In very plain terms, banning players is theft. I find it entirely unconscionable. You have taken their money and decided, for whatever reason, to stop providing the thing they paid for. If you do not compensate them for this, you are a thief.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This statement is <strong>false</strong>. When you open the game for the first time, you have to make an account. Meanwhile steam gives you 2 hours of playtime of any game to request a refund. When you are prompted to make an account you are asked to <strong>read</strong> and <strong>accept</strong> the <a href="https://www.throneoflies.com/legal/">Terms of Service</a>. In these terms you will find this:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“The scope of the Community Guidelines and determination of disciplinary action is solely up to the discretion of Imperium42®, LLC. Although Imperium42®, LLC can issue disciplinary action on your account, not limited to warnings, suspensions, and permanent bans for any reason, Imperium42®, LLC will generally only issue disciplinary action for extreme measures and generally will issue warnings or lower-level suspensions before higher-level suspensions/bans, although not always. <strong>If you disagree with these moderation practices or any part of the Community Guidelines or this document, do not play the game.</strong>”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This is explained in more detail below, I’m just not going to paste the whole thing here, I linked it above anyway, if you’re curious about what you were supposed to have read.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My proposed solution then, is not banning, but tiered play.<br>
Allow two modes of play. The moderated and the unmoderated queue.<br>
The moderated queue works as normal, it is what we have now.<br>
The unmoderated queue is a wild west. No rules, no holds barred. Nobody is allowed to report anyone else in those games,whatever happens, happens. Total freedom. Anything said or done in those games will be ignored, no action taken against such players<br>
Only in the moderated queue will reports be allowed and reviewed</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pretty sure this “Wild West” solution would not even be legally possible since the game is PG13. Even if it is however, you can already do a “no-rules” game, if you make a 16-player private lobby. We don’t enforce rules there, anything that happens in those games is the host’s fault. So if you really want something like this you could make a discord server for exclusively “Wild West” games and post it on our reddit for anyone else that might be interested.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This should be a wholesale replacement for banning. At no point ever, should anyone be banned from playing the game that they played for. Only restricted in exactly who they can play with.<br>
The unmoderated pool will be populated not only by those being punished, but also by those who, for whatever reason, can’t tolerate rules and oversight. Racist names will be common, fools will spam their websites, gamethrowing will be commonplace, people will experiment with unusual and probably poorly advised tactics without fear of reprisal, some people will play it just to learn, without any worry about failure.</p>
<p>Whatever happens in the unmoderated pool stays there. It will act as a containment zone for all the most chaotic players and behaviours, leaving the normal moderated pool as a quality-assured experience of fair play</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re literally describing every developer’s worst nightmare here. You can’t have a PG13 game and make this an official gamemode. As I said above, you can organize this on your own.</p>
<p>One more thing, having that unmoderated pool would not work because there won’t even be enough people for it 24/7.</p>
<p>I think I covered all your points, nothing more to discuss. If you wish to, you can just organize your own private games and even link the server mentioning it’s for wild west games on <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ThroneOfLiesGame/">reddit</a>. Cheers!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nanako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is a game, not an asylum. The goal isn’t to provide mental help, its to provide a game for people to play.</p>
<p>Seperating such players from the rest does solve the problem - because the problem is those people disrupting the main game.  You seem to be under the impression that the problem is the mere existence of those people.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 18:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Alice" data-post="23" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/alice/40/32176_2.png" class="avatar"> Alice:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>nor is it theft nor fraud as this was explicitly outlined in the ToS.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ToS = Town of Salem = Fraud</p>
<p>Get wrecked</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 17:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Throne of Lies is a paid game. It costs money to enjoy the service, it is not provided freely.<br>
If you pay to participate in the game, and are them deprived of your ability to play said game, you should be entitled to a full refund. If you are not refunded, you have been robbed.<br>
In very plain terms, banning players is theft. I find it entirely unconscionable. You have taken their money and decided, for whatever reason, to stop providing the thing they paid for. If you do not compensate them for this, you are a thief.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Christ on a cracker… Did you even read the terms of conditions you agreed to when you created the account? You are not buying the game per-se as the account still belongs to i42 and they’re allowing you to play on their servers and by the agreement it’s perfectly legal for them to remove your access for any reason whatsoever.</p>
<p>This is not robbery, as i42 is not holding you at gunpoint or anything like that, nor is it theft nor fraud as this was explicitly outlined in the ToS.</p>
<p>Every online game does this and this can be easily avoided by not being a toxic twat in-game. And frankly, looking by the <span class="hashtag">#justice</span> logs, if you somehow get banned, you deserve it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 12:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you feel you’ve/ someone else has been suspended/banned unfairly, talk to/get that person to talk a mod. They don’t bite (I think) and are very reasonable.<br>
However, an unmoderated queue is not the solution. This encourages <em>oh its ok ill just be moved somewhere else</em> and a repetition of bad behaviour.</p>
<p>What a suspension (<em>most people arent banned forever, that takes quite a bit of effort</em>) teaches it that the action that you have done is wrong. And that you shouldnt do it again.</p>
<p><em>Hobbles off becuase I make no senseeee :^)</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 11:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even if it was a crime (it isn’t) surely it’d be classed as Fraud not Robbery</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 11:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wolfy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s within the terms and conditions. And you know when they say you should read the fine print, you should as that may save your life in the future. The best thing is, the terms and conditions are clear cut and do not have a fine print.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>ou should be entitled to a full refund. If you are not refunded, you have been robbed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Unfortunetly, this is not how it works. I would say something about what I have learnt in Law and is currently the subject I’m revising for my exam on Monday, but in simple terms, no. It would not be robbery. If you want an explanation of it, dm me here and I can explain why it isn’t robbery.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 10:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and are them deprived of your ability to play said game, you should be entitled to a full refund. If you are not refunded, you have been robbed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>sips tea</em><br>
here we go.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 10:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When you purchase a game you are signing a contract with the game’s creators.</p>
<p>The contract says that you give money, and they give you the game.</p>
<p>Any rules the game may have are also part of the contract, if you fail to follow them you have broken your end of the deal, and so in return your game-playing privileges are revoked.</p>
<p>You have not been robbed, in the same way that being arrested is not being kidnapped.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 10:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you pay to participate in the game, and are them deprived of your ability to play said game, you should be entitled to a full refund. If you are not refunded, you have been robbed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>False</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 10:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Shit on Friday is still shit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 02:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eh, makes a good friday night movie.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 02:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That series is shit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 02:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No.</p>
<p>Just no</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 02:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or maybe we make it so that one day a year there are no rules and it’s no holds barred, survival of the fittest style throne of lies, to get out all that <em>salt</em>  we’ve accumulated and help make it a better community!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 02:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You realise that unmoderated pools have proven to not work in correcting toxic behaviour, right? Riot Games addressed that very system a few years back (<a href="https://nexus.leagueoflegends.com/en-us/2017/01/ask-riot-banished-to-prisoners-island/" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">here</a> and <a href="https://na.leagueoflegends.com/en/news/game-updates/player-behavior/player-behavior-design-values-punishment" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">here</a>), and they have actual specialists looking into their toxicity issues. These people have done their theses in online behaviour, so when they say that Prisoner’s Island systems do not work, I tend to take their expert opinion under advisement.</p>
<p>Toxic players have behavioral issues. These issues are <em>not</em> solved by separating them from the rest of the playerbase. If anything, they are exacerbated by placing them alongside others with similar issues.</p>
<p>But by all means, do some research of your own, see if you find studies/expert opinions to the contrary.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 02:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nanako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If they cheated through some technical means, then firstly the method they used should be patched, and then they should be sent to the unmoderated pool like anyone else. Their hacks would no longer work.</p>
<p>This is a sort of game which is easily authenticated serverside, hacking it would be pretty hard, and patching such things pretty easy</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you pay to participate in the game, and are them deprived of your ability to play said game, you should be entitled to a full refund. If you are not refunded, you have been robbed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually - They aren’t. They read the terms of service and accepted them. It is explicitly stated in the terms of service that you can be banned and deprived of your ability to play.</p>
<p>People aren’t just getting banned for no reason - If someone gets permanently banned, they have been banned and warned MULTIPLE times before, and refused to stop throwing/cheating/harassing people/being racist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>itd eb difficult and i have no idea how it would work. but it could happen</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nanako" data-post="1" data-topic="67215">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/sheriff-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Nanako:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This should be a wholesale replacement for banning. At no point ever, should anyone be banned from playing the game that they played for</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>what if they cheated<br>
like not stream sniping cheating. like actual hacking cheating.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If we manage to get a larger player-base, then yes, the idea could possibly work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This sort of system doesn’t work for games with smaller player bases. Not enough people to support a second que</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Typically, the person who was banned <strong>deserved</strong> to get banned.<br>
If they feel like they didn’t, they can bring it up with a mod.<br>
This idea isn’t <strong>horrible</strong>, just unnecessary.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to handle bans and toxic players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When you pay taxes to the government and commit a crime, are you entitled to a refund for the government services you were incapable of using due to being imprisoned?</p>
<p>If it helps you conceptualise the effect, consider it a fine for committing a misdemeanor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 01:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67215-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-handle-bans-and-toxic-players/67215.rss">How to handle bans and toxic players</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
