<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790</link>
    <description>
Welcome to the eighth annual Hunger Gam- wrong script. *Ahem*. Welcome to the eighth Blood on the Forums! Hosted by @KyoDaz and @Amelia! This is going to be a disaster.

[details=”Character List”]
This game is uPick. Players who sign up send us a submission in private. We will do our best to create a fun and entertaining character for you relevant to the submission you send us.

[/details]
[details=&quot;Town Composition&quot;]

This game is designed for a variable number of players, and thus the composition of the game is able to change depending on how many players join. The following list denotes the standard composition of the game at each possible player count.

Total Players: Townsfolk/Outsiders/Minions/Demons
5: 3/0/1/1
6: 3/1/1/1
7: 5/0/1/1
8: 5/1/1/1
9: 5/2/1/1
10: 7/0/2/1
11: 7/1/2/1
12: 7/2/2/1
13: 9/0/3/1
14: 9/1/3/1
15: 9/2/3/1

Every character in-game is unique in that more than one of the same character will never appear at the start of the game (there can never be two Clockmakers at the start, for example).

Certain characters may contain parts of their ability which modify the game setup; some add character types (and subtract others to compensate), while others change elements of the game entirely. Be sure to take notice of these.

[/details]
[details=&quot;Phase Length&quot;]

Each day phase will last for no longer than 48 hours.
24 hours: Nomination phase. Players who wish to nominate may do so at this time, and votes may *not* be pre-queued in this stage.
24 hours: Vote finalization. During this time, votes may be cast freely on any existing nomination, but no new nominations may be made. Once this time ends or all votes have been locked in, the day will resolve.

The night phase will last for no more than 24 hours. If all relevant actions have been submitted and processed, Storytellers reserve the right to begin the next day early. 
[/details]

[details=&quot;Storyteller&quot;]

The Storyteller is the key moderator for the game; All ability uses at night must be sent to the Storyteller via private message, and Storyteller will have the final say on any open-ended ability behaviors. Storyteller’s goal is to keep the game both fun and balanced, and they’ll often be trying to make it last as long as possible; however, the Storyteller may not alter any existing rules to accomplish this.
[/details]

[details=&quot;The Fabled&quot;]
The Fabled aren&#39;t really characters so much as special modifiers that the Storyteller can put in play to tweak the game. For example, the Angel can be put into play to help keep newer players from being targeted, or the Buddhist can be put into play to keep the more experienced players from dominating the discussion. Fabled will always be announced when they are in play, along with their effect upon gamestate. A breakdown of Fabled characters can be found below.

**Angel:** Something bad might happen to whomever is most responsible for the death of a new player.
**Buddhist:** Veteran players may not speak for the first six hours of the day phase.
**Doomsayer:** If more than four players live, each living player may publicly invoke the Doomsayer once per game to cause a player of their own alignment to die.
**Fiddler:** Once per game, at night, the Demon secretly chooses a player of an opposing alignment; All players then choose which of these two wins the game.
**Hell’s Librarian:** Something bad might happen to whomever speaks when the Storyteller calls for silence.
**Djinn:** The two specified characters cannot both be in play, however Evil knows which ones are. Or, the Djinn&#39;s special rule is in play instead, known as a &quot;jinx.&quot;
The following Fabled character must be added before the game begins; please speak to the Storyteller if you wish to see it added.
**Revolutionary:** Two neighboring players are known to be the same alignment. Once per game, one of them may register falsely.
[/details]
[details=&quot;Scum Info&quot;]

On the first night of the game, when relatively few characters act, the evil characters will all be woken to learn who one another are. Evil players will not be allowed to communicate at night. The Demon will be told who all of their Minions are, and the Minions will know who the Demon is and who all of the other Minions are. However, the Minions and the Demon will not learn which specific characters any of their fellow evils are. The Demon will additionally be told three characters that are not in play, to serve as safe claims. They may claim any of these, none of these, or simply hand the claims off to Minions; however they think they will be best served.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Malfunctions&quot;]

The primary source of interference with abilities in this game is the malfunction. A class that is malfunctioning is not told that they are malfunctioning; if the character is one that gathers information, then the information they receive that night is arbitrary (open-ended, Storyteller may resolve at their discretion), otherwise, the malfunctioning character’s ability simply does not have any effect.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Nominations and Voting&quot;]
Once the discussion phase has ended, the Storyteller will formally announce the opening of the nomination phase. Players must be nominated before they may be voted on that day. Each player may only be nominated once per day, and each player may only nominate once per day.
When a nomination is opened, the storyteller begins to track votes for that nomination. The players may precast votes, but the votes will lock in a clockhand format. Starting with the player below the nominee on the list, and working downwards, the votes will be locked if they are cast. As an example, take the following five players;
&gt; Alex
Brianna
Cameron
Derek
Ellen

Brianna is nominated. Cameron’s vote will be locked as soon as he places it, because he is the first person below Brianna on the list. Derek may cast his vote before Cameron, and may alter his vote if Cameron has not yet voted, but once Cameron has voted and had his vote locked, Derek’s vote will be the next to lock, and if it is placed when Cameron’s vote locks, then Derek’s vote will lock as the vote cast by Derek at that time.
Any votes that are not cast by EoD will be considered votes to pardon. If the count of votes to execute is equal to half of the living players (or more), and is the highest count of votes against any player that day, the accused will be considered “about to die”. At the end of the day or when all votes on all nominations have been cast, the player who is “about to die” will be executed. If there is a tie between two or more players for the highest count of votes, the day will end with no execution. The Storyteller may only declare an early end to voting if it is no longer possible to tie or exceed the highest nomination.

[/details]
[details=&quot;Whispers&quot;]

Players may whisper each other in-game through private messages. Whispers must, however, be publicly announced, typically by requesting permission to whisper (a standard format is /whisper [Player]). Whispers to your neighbors (those seated next to you) do not have to be announced. Once a whisper has been declared and accepted, the two players may whisper via private message until one of them speaks publicly in the game chat, at which point the whisper is considered over and the players must declare whispers again if they wish to whisper.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Death&quot;]

When a player dies, nothing is revealed about their character and they are allowed to stay in the game and speak. They may not nominate and they will have only one vote token (this will allow them to cast a vote to execute) for the entire game. Evil players who die may thus continue to help their allies by keeping up their claim and spreading misinformation, and good players may similarly help their allies by retaining relevant info that others may have forgotten in the heat of the game. Once a player dies, their ability stops working, which means that a player killed before they would perform their ability will not perform their ability, and any ability with a persistent effect will end upon the player’s death.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Victory&quot;]

Good wins by eliminating all Demons (Minions do not necessarily need to die for Good to win, but eliminating Minions can be helpful). Evil wins by reducing the game to two living players (irrespective of either player’s alignment). The Storyteller may also declare a victory for Evil if Good may no longer possibly win (for example, if only evil players are left alive and thus no one would nominate the Demon). Certain class abilities may present alternate routes to victory; these classes, if able to appear, will be made known on the class list. In the event of a tie (both teams would win simultaneously), Good wins.

[/details]


[details=&quot;Jinxes&quot;]
Due to the nature of uPicks, &#39;conflicting&#39; characters will not be introduced into the script and therefore there is no need for jinxes.
[/details]

The player list can be found below ;

1. EliThePsycho
2. Intensify
3. BlueStorm
4. 
5. 
6.
7.
8.
9.
10.

Backups 
1. CRichard564
2. WindwardAway
3.

Spectators :
1. 
2.
3.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 13:07:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Signups</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah.<br>
2/5s of possible signups were lost to blacklists. (Gorta’s forced removal from signups and yourself)<br>
Unfortunate but I understand it’s neccesary to enforce blacklists.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/38</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 13:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CRichard564]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wouldn’t have minded being a main player and being a traveller in this setup.<br>
Sigh.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/37</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 01:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/pokemonkidryan">@PokemonKidRyan</a> your invite has been sent</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/36</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>does this mean you want to join the discord i made for the express purpose of playing botc</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 18:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>nice</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 18:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My local furry con is doing a virtual conference and one of the games that will be played is BotC.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 18:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arctic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KyoDaz" data-post="28" data-topic="87790">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kyodaz/40/38564_2.png" class="avatar"> KyoDaz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this marks the end of BotF</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crab.png?v=9" title=":crab:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":crab:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 08:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Rip BoTF.</p>
<p>You will always be remembered for giving me brain meltdowns</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CRichard564]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just get Tan to host next time 4Head.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 23:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I blame the lack of Tan hosting it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><font color="00ffff">Canned due to lack of interest. Imo, this marks the end of BotF which VII suggested (the gargantuan, enormously large 7 signups) but we now have actual evidence for. </font></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 21:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DatBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/canned_food.png?v=9" title=":canned_food:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":canned_food:"><br>
</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 21:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>202∞: upick ur nose</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 16:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>2020: Upick<br>
2021: Upick the script<br>
2022: Upick the players<br>
2023: Upick the hosts</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 16:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>bump  </p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightingale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>/out</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 17:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightingale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Memo garment</p>
<p><strong>/in</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlueStorm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gamer moment</p>
<p><strong>/in</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 15:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Chip is goodest boy to have 2 people have him as his pfp.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 13:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CRichard564]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Imagine if someone else is using a Kyoko pfp.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 12:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the fact that you and Blitz have the same pfp for the second time already is beyond confusing to me</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 11:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/backup</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 10:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It makes the hosts cry</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So how does outsider modification work in this script?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 16:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/in</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 16:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87790-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/botf-viii-upick-the-script-signups-3-15/87790.rss">BotF VIII: uPick the Script - Signups (3/15)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
