<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558</link>
    <description># The Masterminds 
Currently, Unseen is at the point where it&#39;s practically at it&#39;s peak of brilliance. This thread is more to do with.. &quot;Where do we go from here?&quot; and of course, we can add more Classes to their arsenal or we could give them a new ability here and there but... what if... Mastermind got reworked?

Ruby had a post previously that had some interesting stuff for an Unseen change but, I wanna focus more on the Class that expands the ranks of Unseen.

Let&#39;s look at the current Mastermind:

&gt;#  [color=purple]The Mastermind[/color]
&gt;Passive: Can&#39;t Touch This - Immune to death at night.
&gt;Passive: In The Shadows - Does not appear as Unseen to all Investigative classes for the first 3 nights.
&gt;Night Ability: Convert - Attempt to convert a player to the Unseen faction. There can only be three members including yourself in the Unseen at a time. Unlimited uses, but 1-day cooldown.

Here are some ideas for if we wanted different kinds of Mastermind:

# **Note: Anything in _Italics_ will not show up in the grave.**

# [color=purple]The _Skilled_ Mastermind[/color]
**Passive: Tough Mind** - Immune to occupation and death at night.

**Passive: In The Crowd** - You will appear as a Social Type to Investigative classes for the first 3 nights.

**Night Ability: Re-Educate** - You will send your own personal messenger to attempt to Convert a player to the Unseen. You will not be seen as visiting the target. There can only be three members including yourself in the Unseen at a time. Unlimited uses, but 1-day cooldown.

**Day Ability: The List** - You will check your list. At the start of the Night, you will be told how many people are left that can be converted. 2 uses.

# [color=purple]The _Broken_ Mastermind[/color]
**Passive: Shattered Mind** - Immune to death at night once. Will kill the attacker that kills them.

**Passive: In The Cellars** - If an Investigative attempts to visit you, they will be told something prevented them from visiting.

**Night Ability: Proselytize** - You will attempt to convert a player into the Unseen. If they are immune, you will attempt to Occupy them instead. There can only be three members including yourself in the Unseen at a time. Unlimited uses, but 1-day cooldown.

**Night Ability: Supply Wine** - You will attempt to Occupy your target and be informed if they are able to be converted. - 2 uses. Usable only when on Cooldown.

# [color=purple]_-I have more, but right now I was hoping to get opinions on these two before I carry on-_[/color]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 15:29:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThePlex" data-post="1" data-topic="2558">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/theplex/40/2519_2.png" class="avatar"> ThePlex:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Skilled Mastermind</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Social isn’t that big a step up from special, as that just gives you 2 claims (atm).</p>
<p>Only problem I have is with his being immune to being occupied… maybe it should be that they are immuen to occupation nights 1-3?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThePlex" data-post="1" data-topic="2558">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/theplex/40/2519_2.png" class="avatar"> ThePlex:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Broken Mastermind</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I really like this one, because if a knight cold steels you, it will seem as though you were blue dragon (provided they kept a will).</p>
<p>The other abilities are also good. Only suggestion ius that “supply wine” is only usable if the unseen is not at it’s capacity.</p>
<p>My suggestion: the skilled mastermind is the first mastermind, and the broken master mind only comes on when the assassin becomes master mind (I think this is what you were thinking as well?)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 15:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2558-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558.rss">[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grizzfang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would certainly make MM more interesting to play, just the convert ability at night is a bit boring.<br>
Problem here is though that both of these are pretty OP. Especially the Broken MM seems way too powerful.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 13:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2558-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558.rss">[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Votes? It’s at Night</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2558-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558.rss">[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How does the killing bit of broken work with votes?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 13:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2558-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558.rss">[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>The Masterminds</h1>
<p>Currently, Unseen is at the point where it’s practically at it’s peak of brilliance. This thread is more to do with… “Where do we go from here?” and of course, we can add more Classes to their arsenal or we could give them a new ability here and there but… what if… Mastermind got reworked?</p>
<p>Ruby had a post previously that had some interesting stuff for an Unseen change but, I wanna focus more on the Class that expands the ranks of Unseen.</p>
<p>Let’s look at the current Mastermind:</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="purple">The Mastermind</font></h1>
<p>Passive: Can’t Touch This - Immune to death at night.<br>
Passive: In The Shadows - Does not appear as Unseen to all Investigative classes for the first 3 nights.<br>
Night Ability: Convert - Attempt to convert a player to the Unseen faction. There can only be three members including yourself in the Unseen at a time. Unlimited uses, but 1-day cooldown.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Here are some ideas for if we wanted different kinds of Mastermind:</p>
<h1><strong>Note: Anything in <em>Italics</em> will not show up in the grave.</strong></h1>
<h1><font color="purple">The <em>Skilled</em> Mastermind</font></h1>
<p><strong>Passive: Tough Mind</strong> - Immune to occupation and death at night.</p>
<p><strong>Passive: In The Crowd</strong> - You will appear as a Social Type to Investigative classes for the first 3 nights.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability: Re-Educate</strong> - You will send your own personal messenger to attempt to Convert a player to the Unseen. You will not be seen as visiting the target. There can only be three members including yourself in the Unseen at a time. Unlimited uses, but 1-day cooldown.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability: The List</strong> - You will check your list. At the start of the Night, you will be told how many people are left that can be converted. 2 uses.</p>
<h1><font color="purple">The <em>Broken</em> Mastermind</font></h1>
<p><strong>Passive: Shattered Mind</strong> - Immune to death at night once. Will kill the attacker that kills them.</p>
<p><strong>Passive: In The Cellars</strong> - If an Investigative attempts to visit you, they will be told something prevented them from visiting.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability: Proselytize</strong> - You will attempt to convert a player into the Unseen. If they are immune, you will attempt to Occupy them instead. There can only be three members including yourself in the Unseen at a time. Unlimited uses, but 1-day cooldown.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability: Supply Wine</strong> - You will attempt to Occupy your target and be informed if they are able to be converted. - 2 uses. Usable only when on Cooldown.</p>
<h1><font color="purple"><em>-I have more, but right now I was hoping to get opinions on these two before I carry on-</em></font></h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 12:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2558-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/unseen-suggestion-the-masterminds/2558.rss">[Unseen Suggestion] The Masterminds</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
