<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414</link>
    <description>Goal : Steal valuables from at least 3 people before you die.

The Highwayman is a neutral offensive role. At the beginning of the game, 5 people are marked randomly. The Highwayman is not aware of who has been marked.

[Passive ability] Cunning: You are occupy immune. Whoever occupied you is not informed that you are occupy immune.

[Night ability] Pillage: You occupy your target for the night and check them for valuables. If they have been marked, their valuables will be stolen and you will get a notification informing you of the fact. If the target is being guarded, you will die as if you attacked. Unlimited uses.
(Bypasses occupy immunity)

[Night ability] Blackmail: Your target cannot accuse the following day. 2 uses.

[Day ability] Disguise: For the next night only, upon investigation you will appear as the role of the person you select. 1 use.


Came up with the idea after looking and seeing there wasn&#39;t any neutral offensive role yet. 5 people are marked because I thought they might be screwed out of a win if one of their targets dies, in addition to making their win condition a bit easier. And I think a highwayman would be fun and fit thematically into the lore. Feedback is appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 02:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Xephi-Zero]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Based on the complaints I read here, on discord and Reddit about CW tornadoes, Most players really hate randomness. And having the entire objective built around getting lucky is too random (imo).</p>
<p>So I think avoiding luck dependency while designing the class is the way to go.</p>
<p>Best of luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 02:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32414-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414.rss">[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NeoDnyarri]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like these suggestions, some nice ideas. Thanks for the feedback my dude. Highwayman just has to get lucky, so I was thinking it would encourage them not to spam their occupy immunity bypassing occupy on a single person. They would probably suicide if 3 of their marks die as well, yes.</p>
<p>The “disables day abilities the following day” idea could be pretty cool as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 22:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32414-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414.rss">[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Xephi-Zero]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Instead of pillage occupying someone, how about it disable their abilities on the next day/night? I think that befits the ability name better and is a more unique ability.</p>
<p>Another idea, it only works if the target is visiting someone. The ability won’t work if the target stayed in his room.</p>
<p>A silly idea for the objective: “Every surviving player at the end of the match has been robbed” makes them aim for the long game and have to predict who would survive. And makes them less similar to scorned (Random targets).</p>
<p>I have some questions too.<br>
Is there anyway the highwayman can find his marks? or is it just hoping they get lucky? that just makes them pick targets at random without a clear planning.</p>
<p>What if more than 3 marks die before he finish the job? do they suicide like scorned and mercenary do? Doesn’t sound like something a highwayman would do.</p>
<p>Last note: I think someone else suggested a similar convertible class called thief/rogue? can’t remember. check it out for ideas ^^</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 08:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32414-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414.rss">[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NeoDnyarri]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Goal : Steal valuables from at least 3 people before you die.</p>
<p>The Highwayman is a neutral offensive role. At the beginning of the game, 5 people are marked randomly. The Highwayman is not aware of who has been marked.</p>
<p>[Passive ability] Cunning: You are occupy immune. Whoever occupied you is not informed that you are occupy immune.</p>
<p>[Night ability] Pillage: You occupy your target for the night and check them for valuables. If they have been marked, their valuables will be stolen and you will get a notification informing you of the fact. If the target is being guarded, you will die as if you attacked. Unlimited uses.<br>
(Bypasses occupy immunity)</p>
<p>[Night ability] Blackmail: Your target cannot accuse the following day. 2 uses.</p>
<p>[Day ability] Disguise: For the next night only, upon investigation you will appear as the role of the person you select. 1 use.</p>
<p>Came up with the idea after looking and seeing there wasn’t any neutral offensive role yet. 5 people are marked because I thought they might be screwed out of a win if one of their targets dies, in addition to making their win condition a bit easier. And I think a highwayman would be fun and fit thematically into the lore. Feedback is appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 02:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32414-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/role-suggestion-highwayman/32414.rss">[Role Suggestion] Highwayman</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
