<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Scorpion (Neutral Wildcard)/ Iudex (Unseen)/ Ritualist (Cult)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225</link>
    <description>Scorpion- (Neutral Wildcard)
_The lifelong poverty of the Scorpion&#39;s family have driven them to sell their own organs to the Cult for a quick buck. Therefore, she is the only person left to be the voice of reason in a land where the royalty grow richer and the poor are kicked around like dogs. She saw a glimpse of what was told to be &quot;Unseen propaganda&quot; before it was ripped down.  What she saw was an idea she could get behind. the Observer just took away the instruction manual._

Goal: Trick the group into executing your target, or see the Blue Dragon lose (even if dead)
Your target will always be Blue Dragon.
Your target is [Name], (Role)
You know your target&#39;s role.
Your target cannot be the King.
If your target is killed at night, you can still win as long as there are no Blue Dragon members alive.

Passive: Iron Skin
Immune to normal death at night. 
If you are attacked with an attack that pierces night immunity by the Unseen or Cult, you will survive and join them.
---If Blue Dragon is already dead, or if your target is executed publicly, the effects change up a bit-

**No more night immunity** (if you already won and nothing can change that, not even if your target was brought back to life)

Publicly Executed- Dead
Attacked by Neutral- Dead
Attacked by Unseen- Dead
Converted by Unseen- Immune (No cooldown)
Attacked by Cult- Dead
Converted by Cult - Immune (No cooldown)

Passive 2: Acquired Taste: You insert snake venom into your own drinks every morning. Without the fear of adverse effects, the venom serves to neutralize components in alcohol while increasing your body temperature.
Immune to occupation.
----------------------------------------------**Support Abilities**-------------------------------------






Night ability 1: Paralysis: fill your target&#39;s room with a temporary neurotoxin, occupying the player and preventing anyone from visiting them.

Night Ability 2: Stinger: Two uses: Anyone who visits you is stung by a pet scorpion, suffering from delusions. The player visits the person you target with your ability.

Day Ability 1: Black Tongue- Three uses
Poison a player&#39;s tongue with a vile substance from your pen, _The Stinger_, making them unable to speak for ten seconds. If done as they are explaining themselves on trial, they will remain unable to speak until after the trial.

Day Ability 2: Invisible Ink- Unlimited uses- Send anonymous letters to the Unseen/ Cult


____________________________________________________________________________________- 

Iudex- Unseen
_The Assassin, stepping on a tree branch, has botched the kill. He sees that he has met an ally, and helps The Scorpion  pack._

_The Mastermind informs her that her skills are needed, and in their new society, they will need a judge. Hatred of the Blue Dragon&#39;s corruption is good, but it simply won&#39;t do. She mustn&#39;t allow anarchists such as The Possessor to survive, but honest workers like the Alchemist might be of assistance._

_A Scorpion no longer, the young woman jots down her last note using the Stinger. It reads: &quot;I will be the law when I am needed. I will preserve order, and under my hand, the land will prosper&quot;._

Goal: Unseen win condition
________________________________**Support Abilities**________________
Passive:Cheater:  
+1 Innocent to the Unseen **This stays through death**

 Day Ability: Decide Fate: One: After the final vote, the Iudex can veto the votes and decide if the person defending themselves will get executed or not. If she decides to pardon the player on the stand, they can&#39;t be voted up again that day. **It appears as though the king made the decision** (Be careful using this ability because you could get an Unseen king in a pickle, but you could bring a Blue Dragon king down. **If this is used before the King can use this, the King cannot use this, but he will know you exist if he tries**

Day Ability: Judge: Two: Rig the vote to incriminate or pardon a player. **This generates a random set of guilty/innocent/abstain votes that result in the selected option, and switches some votes with said set to result in the selected option without causing too much suspicion. Players see their own original choice, but others see the randomized option for that player if it is changed. Example below for convenience.**
_
Iudex changes votes to guilty
votes are innocent, innocent, innocent, innocent, innocent, guilty, guilty
votes changed to guilty*, guilty*, guilty*, innocent, innocent, guilty, guilty
*= Votes changed, but the individual thinks they voted as they did

Night 1: Imprison: lock your target&#39;s doors and leave them under a trap door. They cannot visit or be visited.
______________________________________________________________________________________
Ritualist- Cult (Buffed) 
_Seeing that the Unseen are nowhere to be found, the Scorpion decides that it is better to bathe the Castle in blood and begin anew. Within hours, she becomes a true believer._

Passive: Timeline of Corax- One use- if Blood Redemption still has an ability use left, and  a Cult member is found guilty of treason  , that is revealed to be a paradox, and the member is put down and cannot be voted against again. That night , _Blood of Mithras_ is automatically used by The Cult Leader, and **the same player found guilty of treason  is sacrificed to kill a non-cult player. If no-one is selected, a random Blue Dragon member will die (if Blue Dragon no longer exists, a random non-cult player will be selected should the Cult Leader not select someone). This may be any cult member, including the Cult Leader and Yourself, as long as they were found guilty of treason and let down due to the ability.** (The Cult Leader may still attempt Brainwashing that night, but Blood of Mithras will not be able to be used on any living Cultists that night) (The Cult Leader may even attempt conversion if he is the one being sacrificed.)  **This bypasses night immunity**

Passive: Blood Redemption: One use:  If Timeline of Corax still has an ability use, and a Cult Member dies at night, The Cult Leader automatically uses _Blood of Mithras_ to kill a non-cult player (If No-one is selected, a random Blue Dragon player will be killed by this.), and the just-killed cultist&#39;s blood is sacrificed. (The Cult Leader may still attempt Brainwashing that night, but Blood of Mithras will not be able to be used on any living Cultists that night) **This bypass night immunity**

Curse: Day: 2: Place the Mark of Corax on your target&#39;s arm. If they attempt to perform a day ability, they will target themselves. If they do not perform a day ability, the use will be returned.

Brotherhood: Night: 1	Prevent any Cult members from being occupied tonight.

Trap: Night: Infinite: Trap your target inside the Cult&#39;s torture chamber. They will be occupied and nobody can visit them that night.

__
Curse taken from Bewilder, as Bewilder was a cult copy of the Knight&#39;s former power. The court wizard can perform a similar ability.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 14:34:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Scorpion (Neutral Wildcard)/ Iudex (Unseen)/ Ritualist (Cult)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Changed Invoker to Ritualist</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 14:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1225-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225.rss">Scorpion (Neutral Wildcard)/ Iudex (Unseen)/ Ritualist (Cult)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scorpion (Neutral Wildcard)/ Iudex (Unseen)/ Ritualist (Cult)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scorpion- (Neutral Wildcard)<br>
<em>The lifelong poverty of the Scorpion’s family have driven them to sell their own organs to the Cult for a quick buck. Therefore, she is the only person left to be the voice of reason in a land where the royalty grow richer and the poor are kicked around like dogs. She saw a glimpse of what was told to be “Unseen propaganda” before it was ripped down.  What she saw was an idea she could get behind. the Observer just took away the instruction manual.</em></p>
<p>Goal: Trick the group into executing your target, or see the Blue Dragon lose (even if dead)<br>
Your target will always be Blue Dragon.<br>
Your target is [Name], (Role)<br>
You know your target’s role.<br>
Your target cannot be the King.<br>
If your target is killed at night, you can still win as long as there are no Blue Dragon members alive.</p>
<p>Passive: Iron Skin<br>
Immune to normal death at night.<br>
If you are attacked with an attack that pierces night immunity by the Unseen or Cult, you will survive and join them.<br>
—If Blue Dragon is already dead, or if your target is executed publicly, the effects change up a bit-</p>
<p><strong>No more night immunity</strong> (if you already won and nothing can change that, not even if your target was brought back to life)</p>
<p>Publicly Executed- Dead<br>
Attacked by Neutral- Dead<br>
Attacked by Unseen- Dead<br>
Converted by Unseen- Immune (No cooldown)<br>
Attacked by Cult- Dead<br>
Converted by Cult - Immune (No cooldown)</p>
<p>Passive 2: Acquired Taste: You insert snake venom into your own drinks every morning. Without the fear of adverse effects, the venom serves to neutralize components in alcohol while increasing your body temperature.<br>
Immune to occupation.<br>
----------------------------------------------<strong>Support Abilities</strong>-------------------------------------</p>
<p>Night ability 1: Paralysis: fill your target’s room with a temporary neurotoxin, occupying the player and preventing anyone from visiting them.</p>
<p>Night Ability 2: Stinger: Two uses: Anyone who visits you is stung by a pet scorpion, suffering from delusions. The player visits the person you target with your ability.</p>
<p>Day Ability 1: Black Tongue- Three uses<br>
Poison a player’s tongue with a vile substance from your pen, <em>The Stinger</em>, making them unable to speak for ten seconds. If done as they are explaining themselves on trial, they will remain unable to speak until after the trial.</p>
<p>Day Ability 2: Invisible Ink- Unlimited uses- Send anonymous letters to the Unseen/ Cult</p>
<p>____________________________________________________________________________________-</p>
<p>Iudex- Unseen<br>
<em>The Assassin, stepping on a tree branch, has botched the kill. He sees that he has met an ally, and helps The Scorpion  pack.</em></p>
<p><em>The Mastermind informs her that her skills are needed, and in their new society, they will need a judge. Hatred of the Blue Dragon’s corruption is good, but it simply won’t do. She mustn’t allow anarchists such as The Possessor to survive, but honest workers like the Alchemist might be of assistance.</em></p>
<p><em>A Scorpion no longer, the young woman jots down her last note using the Stinger. It reads: “I will be the law when I am needed. I will preserve order, and under my hand, the land will prosper”.</em></p>
<p>Goal: Unseen win condition<br>
________________<strong><strong><strong><strong><strong><strong><strong><strong><strong>Support Abilities</strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong><br>
Passive:Cheater:<br>
+1 Innocent to the Unseen <strong>This stays through death</strong></p>
<p>Day Ability: Decide Fate: One: After the final vote, the Iudex can veto the votes and decide if the person defending themselves will get executed or not. If she decides to pardon the player on the stand, they can’t be voted up again that day. <strong>It appears as though the king made the decision</strong> (Be careful using this ability because you could get an Unseen king in a pickle, but you could bring a Blue Dragon king down. <strong>If this is used before the King can use this, the King cannot use this, but he will know you exist if he tries</strong></p>
<p>Day Ability: Judge: Two: Rig the vote to incriminate or pardon a player. <strong>This generates a random set of guilty/innocent/abstain votes that result in the selected option, and switches some votes with said set to result in the selected option without causing too much suspicion. Players see their own original choice, but others see the randomized option for that player if it is changed. Example below for convenience.</strong><br>
_<br>
Iudex changes votes to guilty<br>
votes are innocent, innocent, innocent, innocent, innocent, guilty, guilty<br>
votes changed to guilty*, guilty*, guilty*, innocent, innocent, guilty, guilty<br>
*= Votes changed, but the individual thinks they voted as they did</p>
<p>Night 1: Imprison: lock your target’s doors and leave them under a trap door. They cannot visit or be visited.</p>
<hr>
<p>Ritualist- Cult (Buffed)<br>
<em>Seeing that the Unseen are nowhere to be found, the Scorpion decides that it is better to bathe the Castle in blood and begin anew. Within hours, she becomes a true believer.</em></p>
<p>Passive: Timeline of Corax- One use- if Blood Redemption still has an ability use left, and  a Cult member is found guilty of treason  , that is revealed to be a paradox, and the member is put down and cannot be voted against again. That night , <em>Blood of Mithras</em> is automatically used by The Cult Leader, and <strong>the same player found guilty of treason  is sacrificed to kill a non-cult player. If no-one is selected, a random Blue Dragon member will die (if Blue Dragon no longer exists, a random non-cult player will be selected should the Cult Leader not select someone). This may be any cult member, including the Cult Leader and Yourself, as long as they were found guilty of treason and let down due to the ability.</strong> (The Cult Leader may still attempt Brainwashing that night, but Blood of Mithras will not be able to be used on any living Cultists that night) (The Cult Leader may even attempt conversion if he is the one being sacrificed.)  <strong>This bypasses night immunity</strong></p>
<p>Passive: Blood Redemption: One use:  If Timeline of Corax still has an ability use, and a Cult Member dies at night, The Cult Leader automatically uses <em>Blood of Mithras</em> to kill a non-cult player (If No-one is selected, a random Blue Dragon player will be killed by this.), and the just-killed cultist’s blood is sacrificed. (The Cult Leader may still attempt Brainwashing that night, but Blood of Mithras will not be able to be used on any living Cultists that night) <strong>This bypass night immunity</strong></p>
<p>Curse: Day: 2: Place the Mark of Corax on your target’s arm. If they attempt to perform a day ability, they will target themselves. If they do not perform a day ability, the use will be returned.</p>
<p>Brotherhood: Night: 1	Prevent any Cult members from being occupied tonight.</p>
<p>Trap: Night: Infinite: Trap your target inside the Cult’s torture chamber. They will be occupied and nobody can visit them that night.</p>
<p>__<br>
Curse taken from Bewilder, as Bewilder was a cult copy of the Knight’s former power. The court wizard can perform a similar ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1225-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/scorpion-neutral-wildcard-iudex-unseen-ritualist-cult/1225.rss">Scorpion (Neutral Wildcard)/ Iudex (Unseen)/ Ritualist (Cult)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
