<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>(Rework)The Possessor</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529</link>
    <description>**Passive 1:Blackened Shield:** Immune to death at night; occupy immune
**Passive 2:Mental Strength Dependancy:** The Scorned, Fool, Alchemist and the King will resist being controlled by Puppet Strings and if you try to possess them you will be unable to expel them from their body; in that case, they will get converted.
**Day Ability 1: Emergency Preparations(1 use)**:Select someone to reflexibly possess tonight if you get imprisoned. If The Prince imprisons you you will change bodies instead. This always consumes a usage of Possess(if you do not get imprisoned, you will not be able to change bodies!).
**Night Ability 1: Puppet Strings:(unlimited uses)** Control a player tonight and force them to attack another. You may control yourself. 
**Night Ability 2: Possess(1 use)**: Take over the body of someone, gaining access to their journal and previous class. Your old body will appear dead upon success. You may choose a fake class to appear as. 

This fixes some problems with The Possessor: You can defile yourself, so no one really knows that a possessor just jumped(unless you used your emergency preparations; then the Prince will know).
The King is no longer an invalid Possess target. Promotion into the King is no longer a safe bail out(you keep your wincondition). You can no longer control the King or the normal neutrals; you will be able to identify the real neutrals... 
On the flip side you will have a reduced kill capacity.

**Conversions:** Someone who survives Possess and shares a body with the Possessor gets their win condition. Control over the body will alternate; with Possessor having the first Day and Night.

The converted King will not have any change in their abilities. 
The converted Fool and Scorned will get a night kill instead of Frame/Self-Frame.
The converted Alchemist will gain 2 additional uses of Emerald Potion.
The Fool, Scorned and Alchemist will get Blackened Shield.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 19:51:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>(Rework)The Possessor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You do realize that the king already is a valid possession target. Just a dumb one. Also this just seems unnecessary complicated in its interaction with the Alch, Scorned Fool and king.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 19:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23529-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529.rss">(Rework)The Possessor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Rework)The Possessor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unknown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Passive 1:Blackened Shield:</strong> Immune to death at night; occupy immune<br>
<strong>Passive 2:Mental Strength Dependancy:</strong> The Scorned, Fool, Alchemist and the King will resist being controlled by Puppet Strings and if you try to possess them you will be unable to expel them from their body; in that case, they will get converted.<br>
<strong>Day Ability 1: Emergency Preparations(1 use)</strong>:Select someone to reflexibly possess tonight if you get imprisoned. If The Prince imprisons you you will change bodies instead. This always consumes a usage of Possess(if you do not get imprisoned, you will not be able to change bodies!).<br>
<strong>Night Ability 1: Puppet Strings:(unlimited uses)</strong> Control a player tonight and force them to attack another. You may control yourself.<br>
<strong>Night Ability 2: Possess(1 use)</strong>: Take over the body of someone, gaining access to their journal and previous class. Your old body will appear dead upon success. You may choose a fake class to appear as.</p>
<p>This fixes some problems with The Possessor: You can defile yourself, so no one really knows that a possessor just jumped(unless you used your emergency preparations; then the Prince will know).<br>
The King is no longer an invalid Possess target. Promotion into the King is no longer a safe bail out(you keep your wincondition). You can no longer control the King or the normal neutrals; you will be able to identify the real neutrals…<br>
On the flip side you will have a reduced kill capacity.</p>
<p><strong>Conversions:</strong> Someone who survives Possess and shares a body with the Possessor gets their win condition. Control over the body will alternate; with Possessor having the first Day and Night.</p>
<p>The converted King will not have any change in their abilities.<br>
The converted Fool and Scorned will get a night kill instead of Frame/Self-Frame.<br>
The converted Alchemist will gain 2 additional uses of Emerald Potion.<br>
The Fool, Scorned and Alchemist will get Blackened Shield.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 18:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23529-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/rework-the-possessor/23529.rss">(Rework)The Possessor</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
