<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320</link>
    <description>## Airlock
### Co-hosted by N.1 and eevee

I believe this game plays anywhere between 9 and 15 players or something. The best way I can describe it is Clocktower in Space with some other elements as well.

Let me know if you have any questions as to how this game works, and I&#39;ll try to help as best as I can. Thank you!

Roles (All roles except for members of the Parasite faction are Unique. Also, if the Sympathizer is in-play, the equivalent ship-aligned Crew role may not spawn):

:biohazard: = If the game progresses to the secret destination before ending, and this role is alive then, aliens win.

:radioactive: = If the game progresses to the secret destination before ending, and the player with this passive is alive, aliens win.

The :biohazard: passive is locked to particular roles, while the :radioactive: passive is locked to particular players.  

[details=&quot;Crew (Aligned with the Ship):&quot;]

[color = #3A5BFF]**Crew**[/color] (Aligned with the [color = blue]**Ship**[/color]):

[color = #3A5BFF]**Biologist**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Day Ability 1**: Choose a player. Draw blood from them to determine whether or not they are an alien.
**Day Ability 2**: Choose a player. Infect them, making them alien-aligned and giving them the :radioactive:  passive.
**Day Ability 3**: Choose a player. If they were infected by either you, the Queen, or the Reanimator, they will lose their :radioactive: passive and become Ship-aligned. 

[color = #3A5BFF]**Galley Officer**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Day Ability 1**: Choose a player. Give them food poisoning, preventing them from waking in the next warp phase.
**Day Ability 2**: Do nothing.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Science Officer**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Warp Ability 1**: Choose any alien role and learn whether or not it is in play.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Communications Officer**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Day Ability 1**: Visit the computer to overhear two pieces of information -- one is true and one is false *(If hacked, both may be true or both false)*.
**Day Ability 2 (One Use Only)**: Instead, ask the computer one true or false question. The computer will answer truthfully, unless you are hacked, in which case it may answer either truthfully or falsely.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Medical Officer**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Warp Ability 1**: Scan two players and see if at least one of them is an alien.
**Day Ability 1**: Forego your next scan to bring a player that died at the end of the previous day phase or later back to life.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Security**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 4)
**Day Ability 1**: Place a player in the brig, protecting them and stopping them from waking during the warp phase or using abilities until released. They will not learn that they have been placed in the brig.
**Warp Ability 1**: If the brig is empty, protect a player for a cycle or until the brig becomes occupied.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Engineer**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 4)
**Warp Ability 1**: Choose half of the ship&#39;s living players, rounded up. Learn if at least one of them is an alien.
**Warp Ability 2**: Sabotage the engine to stop the ship&#39;s movement and ensure that it does not move closer to the secret destination during this phase.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Navigator**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 5)
**Warp Ability 1**: Jump the ship twice as far (+2 Advance)
**Warp Ability 2**: Jump the ship backwards (-1 Advance)
**Warp Ability 3**: Do Nothing (+1 Advance)

[color = #3A5BFF]**Technician**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 5)
**Warp Ability 1**: Select a player to protect them from being hacked.
**Warp Ability 2**: Select a player to hack them.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Ensign**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Day Ability 1**: Select a player, annoying them and proventing them from acting in the next warp phase *(You may not annoy yourself)*.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Quartermaster**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 4)
**Passive 1**: Each warp phase you are alive, you learn the role that died via airlock the previous day.
**Passive 2**: If you die via murder or at night, you learn what role killed you.

[color = #3A5BFF]**Transporter Chief**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 5)
**Warp Ability 1**: Select two players and cause them to swap seats. Every aspect of a seat remains, except the player and their alignment, meaning their role and whether they are alive or dead can change, and their seating position definitely changes.
**Warp Ability 2**: Select two players and cause them to swap roles. Their alignment, life status, and seating position will remain the same, while their roles will change.
**Warp Ability 3**: Do nothing.

[/details]


[details=&quot;Passengers (Aligned with the Ship):&quot;]

[color = #CD00FF]**Passengers**[/color] (Aligned with the [color = blue]**Ship**[/color]):

[color = #CD00FF]**Guard**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 3)
**Warp Ability 1**: Select a player to protect them from all killing, offensive, and harmful effects for this warp phase *(You may no longer guard once dead)*.

[color = #CD00FF]**Stowaway**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 4)
**Passive 1**: If any player that is not the VIP (yes, anyone, this passive applies to all players, not just yourself) claims to be the Stowaway, they will be airlocked immediately. This can also apply postmortem to anyone. This passive will always be in-play, even if the Stowaway is not in the game.

[color = #CD00FF]**Hybrid**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 4)
**Passive 1**: You will be informed if you ever have at least one living alien neighbor.
**Passive 2**: You might register as one of the alien roles to investigative abilities.

[color = #CD00FF]**VIP**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Passive 1**: If you die, and are not revived by the next possible End of Day after you die (you have a full warp and day if you die via airlock, otherwise less than that), the Aliens win.
**Passive 2**: If the VIP is in the game, the Guard must also be in-play.

[color = #CD00FF]**Pet**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 2)
**Passive 1**: You will know how many of your living neighbors are aliens at all times while alive.
**Passive 2**: You cannot die via any method besides airlock.
**Passive 3**: You may only communicate via text-less, number-less emojis and text-less, number-less images and GIF&#39;s. You may not speak, use any text, numbers, or characters from any language or code. If you do, you will be airlocked immediately. This passive remains postmortem.
**Passive 4**: All of your votes will be ignored and not count. This passive remains postmortem.
**Passive 5**: You will register as some alien class and as alien alignment to all investigative checks.

[/details]


[details=&quot;Parasites (Aligned with the Aliens):&quot;]

[color = #21C600]**Parasites**[/color] (Aligned with the [color = red]**Aliens**[/color])

[color = #21C600]**Queen**[/color] :biohazard:  (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 4)
**Passive 1**: If the Parasite faction is in the game, you will be its only member at the start of the game.
**Warp Ability 1 (Once per game only)**: Select a player and infect them. They will retain their old role, but will now be alien-aligned. The player you infect with this ability now has the :radioactive: passive for good unless they are ever cured by the Biologist. This effect is the only thing that can be cured by the Biologist outside of the Reanimator&#39;s ability and the Biologist&#39;s own infections.
**Warp Ability 2 (Only usable when the ship chose not to execute anyone via airlock on the previous day)**: Choose a player. Their alignment will change to alien, if they are not already alien-aligned, and their role will change to one of the four Parasite roles.

[color = #21C600]**Hivemind**[/color] :biohazard:  (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Passive 1**: As long as you are alive, you will be consistently informed of all information the computer knows; i.e. all mechanical information that is possibly present in the game.

[color = #21C600]**Influencer**[/color] :biohazard:  (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Warp Ability 1**: Select a player. Nullify their vote for the next day phase.

[color = #21C600]**Reanimator**[/color] :biohazard:  (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Day Ability 1**: Choose a player that died at the end of the previous day phase or later. Revive them. They will be infected (and get the :radioactive: passive) at the start of the next warp phase, and will become alien-aligned if not already. This effect is the only thing that can be cured by the Biologist outside of the Queen&#39;s ability and the Biologist&#39;s own infections.

[/details]


[details=&quot;Warriors (Aligned with the Aliens):&quot;]

[color = #B25656]**Warriors**[/color] (Aligned with the [color = red]**Aliens**[/color])

[color = #B25656]**Predator**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 2)
**Passive 1**: If the warrior faction is in the game, the Predator must be in the game. However, there is no definition as to which of the other Warrior roles may be in the game at the start with the Predator, unlike with the Queen and Parasite faction.
**Warp Ability 1**: Select one player. Kill them.
**Warp Ability 2**: Select two players. Kill them.
**Warp Ability 3**: Do nothing.

[color = #B25656]**Contaminator**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Day Ability 1**: Select a player, making them sick and preventing them from waking up during the next warp phase.

[color = #B25656]**Hacker**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 6)
**Passive 1**: You do not register as an alien to the engineer.
**Warp Ability 1**: Hack a player&#39;s ability for one cycle, until the end of the next day phase.
**Warp Ability 2**: Sabotage the engine to stop the ship&#39;s movement for this phase.

[color = #B25656]**Informant**[/color] :biohazard:  (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 5)
**Passive 1**: You do not register as an alien to the biologist.
**Warp Ability 1 (One use only)**: When this ability is used, the countdown until the ship is attacked tomorrow will be some amount shorter than it otherwise would be.

[/details]


[details=&quot;Other Aliens (Aligned with the Aliens):&quot;]

[color = #D5C742]**Other Aliens**[/color] (Aligned with the [color = red]**Aliens**[/color])

[color = #D5C742]**Ambassador**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: 5)
**Passive 1**: If you are in the game, both the Parasite and Warrior factions may be in-play. Normally, only one of those two factions may be in-play if you are not in the game.
**Passive 2**: Replaces two members of the ship with one passenger and one alien at the start.

[color = #D5C742]**Sympathizer**[/color] (Difficulty Class on a D6 Murder Attempt: Whatever the DC for the Crew role you receive is)
**Passive 1**: You are a member of the crew, but aligned with the aliens. You are informed what ship role you are at the start.
**Passive 2**: You appear as that member of the crew that you are and as aligned with the ship to all investigative checks.
**Passive 3**: If you are ever role swapped or seat swapped by the Transporter Chief, the Crew role that you were will be left behind, while you will still be sympathizer, be alien-aligned but register as ship-aligned, and also register as and now instead have the powers of the new role you are swapped into, whatever that is.

[/details]

Here is the information about how the game ends:

[details=&quot;Win Conditions Information:&quot;]
Each team has two standard wincons.
**Ship Wincon 1:** Ensure both all alien roles and all alien-aligned players are dead before reaching the secret destination.
**Alien Wincon 1:** Ensure that all ship-aligned players possessing ship roles are dead before reaching the secret destination.

If neither of these win conditions are met before reaching the secret destination, but there are still players alive when arriving at the secret destination, then these other two wincons come into play.
**Ship Wincon 2:** Ensure that all roles with the :biohazard: passive and all players with the :radioactive: passive are dead when you reach the secret destination.
**Alien Wincon 2:** Ensure that there is at least one role with the :biohazard: passive and/or at least one player with the :radioactive: passive still alive when you reach the secret destination.

The Aliens also have a third wincon, which can come into play if no other wincon is satisfied, before arriving at the Secret Destination.
**Alien Wincon 3:** If the VIP is in-game, they die, and are not revived by the next possible End of Day after they die (they have a full warp and day if they die via airlock, otherwise less than that), you win.

If it somehow ends up the case that everyone is dead before reaching the secret destination and without satisfying the Ship Wincon 1, Alien Wincon 1, or Alien Wincon 3 first, that is canonically undefined; I currently have it set as a draw, but that might be changed depending on balance purposes.
[/details]

Here is some additional rules stuff for added clarity in addition to the rules PDF:


[details=&quot;Additional Rules Info&quot;]
You can attempt to murder someone while alive once per game. Your attack will trigger a D6 that will determine whether or not they die.

Each day will have a timer that players have until the ship is attacked. There must be 80% or more (This percentage was just made up and might change before the game starts) votes in favor out of everyone (alive and dead) to progress to the warp phase. If this happens, whoever is in the airlock dies, or no one does if no one got airlocked. If players do not progress to airlock before the ship is attacked, someone will die and the day will continue with a new timer that could cause a second attack on the same day, and so on.

At the start of every warp phase, every player that has abilities in the Warp Phase will be notified that they have woken up and can act that night, except for anyone who was targeted by the Galley Officer, Ensign, or Contaminator on the previous Day phase, who will instead be informed at the start of the warp phase that they have not woken up and will not be able to act that night. Players who do not have any abilities to use in the Warp phase will not be told this sort of information, however.

Only starting members of the alien team know their teammates for sure. Converted people will essentially be lost wolves. There is an alien leader who will get three bluffs. The alien leader must be either the Queen, Predator, Ambassador, or Sympathizer.

Like BotF, this game will also have a set seating arrangements and the same whisper rules as BotF (where you can whisper neighbors for free). Everyone will be informed if anyone&#39;s seating arrangement changes, like due to the Transporter Chief or something.
[/details]

Here is some information on mechanical information that players will not be privy to that they might otherwise be in other games such as Clocktower:


[details=&quot;Mechanical information players won&#39;t be privy to:&quot;]
Some of the mechanical information that players will not be privy to will be game composition (in terms of roles or alignments), how the starting distance to the secret destination and current day&#39;s attack timer were determined, the night priority sequence in terms of which roles act in what order, what you roll on murder attempts (those rolls will be made privately by the hosts and won&#39;t be viewable by any players until the game ends), and possibly more.
[/details]

The rest of the information can be found in the canonical PDF&#39;s below, but anything that conflicts with information from above should be ignored:

https://www.dropbox.com/s/h2rqnkwr3iviqbz/Airlock%20-%20Rules.pdf?dl=0

https://www.dropbox.com/s/1m42cpfdqbwkevx/Airlock%20-%20Characters.pdf?dl=0

Credit for the design of this game goes to C63 Industries and the Deduction Engine: http://press.c63.industries/
http://deduction.engine.games/
Currently, the only way this game is run officially is at large conventions across the U.S. using a proprietary A.I. software. The game is probably going to change more next year after they&#39;ve hosted more, but this is the most current version as it was run at DeceptaCon back in mid-February of this year which I attended, and that probably was the last time it will be run before 2021 (Since all major conventions in the U.S. for the remainder of this year have pretty much been cancelled), meaning this will be the most current version of the game for a pretty long while. eevee&#39;s in their discord, so contact him if you&#39;d like to join that to speak with any non-me ppl there who&#39;ve played this game officially.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 19:36:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I already got the co-host in eevee i think</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/159">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/159</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 19:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-159</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you have the patience to teach me, like everything (I haven’t even read the OP yet)<br>
I can try to help you host this</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/158">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/158</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 17:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-158</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We’ve yet to decide if stuff like that will be host determined or randomized</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/157">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/157</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-157</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh yeah there’s no set EoD</p>
<p>Each day just has a set timer<br>
If the day doesn’t end before the timer reaches zero, the ship gets attacked and someone dies<br>
Then there’s a new timer</p>
<p>So you could have the game end D1 if u wanted lul</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/156">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/156</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-156</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It makes sense that it’s slightly wtf.<br>
The game was designed to be run by a proprietary AI software that we dont have access to lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/155">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/155</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-155</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the reaction is trying to convey that it looks complicated and probably slightly wtf.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/154">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/154</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-154</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>im having trouble understanding what sort of reaction you’re trying to convey with this message</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/153">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/153</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-153</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah that uh</p>
<p>sure is something</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/152">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/152</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-152</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh yeah<br>
there’s also the pet</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/151">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/151</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-151</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Transporter Chief is like if you put Barber and Matron into one class</p>
<p>Looks chaotic <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/eyes.png?v=9" title=":eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/150">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/150</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-150</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s clocktower in space with more jank, because 1) setup philosophy is not public and is host decided, 2) secret destination mechanic, 3) conversion, and 4) transporter chief lul</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/149">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/149</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-149</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do not feel like I have the mental capacity to understand this especially when i’m already doing Fortified Tower</p>
<p>but</p>
<p>i’ll probably spec</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/148">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/148</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-148</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ya got one then</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/147">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/147</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-147</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just want a spot, as I don’t know when the sign ups will be up and how quick they would fill</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/146">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/146</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-146</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you’d like to be sure</p>
<p>I would allow mass pre-inning but im pretty sure allowing that is frowned upon by leadership here so u’ll probs be the only pre-in before i post signups.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/145">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/145</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-145</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Am I still pre-in’d?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/144">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/144</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-144</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This game is ready to go</p>
<p>Signups will open when BotF 3 ends, then they will close when both 1) at least 10 players have signed up and 2) it has been at least 9 days since signups opened, then the game will be dormant for a week while we balance and rand (since doing this game’s balance from the host side depends on knowing how many players are playing beforehand), and then the game will begin.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/143">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/143</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-143</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m back so I will co-host with you</p>
<p>We need to talk as there are elements that are host decided that contain information that players are not privy to but would be in other stuff like clocktower</p>
<p>I invited you to a PM about this game; will ping you there</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/142">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/142</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 21:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-142</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eevee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I will if you will.</p>
<p>I won’t solo host it if I don’t perfectly know the rules.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/141">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/141</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 21:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-141</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>still need a co-host for this thing</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/eevee">@eevee</a> do you still want to be a co-host or not? if so, we need to talk privately about stuffs</p>
<p>if not, i’d need someone else</p>
<p>if there’s no clear co-host determined within a week from now, im removing this from the queue for the time being.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/140">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/140</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 20:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-140</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s sad, but real life always comes first</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/139">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/139</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-139</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i dont think N is gonna host this anymore considering he’s leaving the forum permanently</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/138">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/138</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 10:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-138</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This would be a unbalanced mess if it got rushed</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/137">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/137</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 10:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-137</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>take as much time as you need</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/136">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/136</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 10:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-136</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this game probably should move down as it is clogging up the misc queue and preventing VLDR2 from posting signups. Also, even if / when I find the necessary co-hosts, it will probably take time to reach the necessary balance level via conversing. Since the role / alignment composition are not public and can be fluid, unlike clocktower, this game is tricker and will def take longer to ensure balance in setup than clocktower.</p>
<p>if you would be comfortable co-hosting, please ping me. I won’t consider being a part of it without at least 2 co-hosts that aren’t eevee and i’ll invite you to a PM to talk</p>
<p>Please note that since we’ll need to discuss things that will not be public to players regarding the setup of the game, if u agree to this, you will not be able to play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/135">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320/135</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 06:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82320-135</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-interest-check-airlock/82320.rss">[Misc] [Interest Check] Airlock</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
