<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[RESOLVED] Question on reporting</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969</link>
    <description>What happened: After 6 days of no info from a sheriff, we voted him up as we felt he was suspicious. The sheriff obviously claimed innocent and stated bad luck. I said &quot;If thats true, Im sorry, but you have to admit its suspicious&quot; (I was king). We exed him. The played then proceeded to call everyone retarded and dumbf***s over and over, and posted profanity and salt in his will.

I asked the players in the game to report the sheriff for toxicity and salt at the end of the game. I was then beholden to a bunch of players telling me to stop being a P**sy over and over again, and name calling and such about being &quot;soft&quot;. My understanding of the rules is that this type of behavior isnt allowed, nor to be encouraged. I went ahead and reported the sheriff in question, but thought Id ask here - Are we really supposed to report violations of the profanity and salt rules?

I get when people get upset about being exed when they are inno, but we have NO way of knowing if their protestations are true. In a game of suspicion and lies (Which is exactly what ToL is), you should have NO grounds for being pissed on getting exed unless you are obviously inno (Like a prince with no CCs, or a psychic in a Cult game).

Let me know if the report was appropriate. Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 21:53:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Question on reporting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 21:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8969-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969.rss">[RESOLVED] Question on reporting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Question on reporting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dealt with the Report, but we can’t disclose any actions taken. But we appreciate that you are helping keep Throne of Lies clean!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 21:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8969-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969.rss">[RESOLVED] Question on reporting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Question on reporting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sharvax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What happened: After 6 days of no info from a sheriff, we voted him up as we felt he was suspicious. The sheriff obviously claimed innocent and stated bad luck. I said “If thats true, Im sorry, but you have to admit its suspicious” (I was king). We exed him. The played then proceeded to call everyone retarded and dumbf***s over and over, and posted profanity and salt in his will.</p>
<p>I asked the players in the game to report the sheriff for toxicity and salt at the end of the game. I was then beholden to a bunch of players telling me to stop being a P**sy over and over again, and name calling and such about being “soft”. My understanding of the rules is that this type of behavior isnt allowed, nor to be encouraged. I went ahead and reported the sheriff in question, but thought Id ask here - Are we really supposed to report violations of the profanity and salt rules?</p>
<p>I get when people get upset about being exed when they are inno, but we have NO way of knowing if their protestations are true. In a game of suspicion and lies (Which is exactly what ToL is), you should have NO grounds for being pissed on getting exed unless you are obviously inno (Like a prince with no CCs, or a psychic in a Cult game).</p>
<p>Let me know if the report was appropriate. Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 21:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8969-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/resolved-question-on-reporting/8969.rss">[RESOLVED] Question on reporting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
