<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suggested changes to investigator class structure</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528</link>
    <description>Hi everyone, I&#39;m reposting this from reddit to hear more opinions. The last few patches have made some big changes to the game. Investigators in particular are becoming more powerful and more difficult to fake claim. I like that the devs are willing to make big changes and I think they are addressing important issues within the game. However, I also feel like making classes harder to fake, making them unique or guaranteed to spawn can be good for game balance but can limit the choices available to us during gameplay.

I think that a game which revolves around deceit/deduction/mind-fuckery should thrive on uncertainty. When you go into a game knowing that there will be exactly one nonconvertible sheriff, one nonconvertible prince, etc, there is less uncertainty and therefore less room to be creative in your playstyle. There is still obviously room to come up with awesome plays - but my point is that more immediately verified information at the start of the game results in less opportunities to deceive other players.

I&#39;m going to throw out some potential changes to investigators that I think would help add more uncertainty to the game. I am not a career gamer or game designer, so feel free to improve on my ideas or tell me why they suck.

The main change I&#39;d like to suggest would be to revert the recent sheriff changes and buff the princess up to a prince-tier investigator. I&#39;m not going to suggest specific ability changes but I am thinking something like buffing flirt to be more like allies, making wisp more like surveillance and perhaps giving her some socially oriented day abilities (secret whispers perhaps? no reason for psychic to get all the fun toys). The goal is to make the princess an alternative to the prince who is equally powerful, but focused more on social interaction and deduction than brute force.

Then make the princess unique/nonconvertible and give each game a 50/50% to spawn either prince or princess. This way BD would always have one really high powered investigator who specializes in either threat neutralization (prince) or social manipulation (princess). But we wouldn&#39;t know which spawns in a given game. More investigative classes could be reasonably claimable and we&#39;d have a ton of new opportunities to fuck with people&#39;s heads. We would also have more diverse games in general, instead of the guaranteed prince/sheriff, prince/paladin combo we can always anticipate now.

Let me know what you guys think. (ps I would also like to propose that each game should have a very small chance to spawn zero or two NKs instead of just one, based on the reasoning that more uncertainty = good. And it would just be fucking awesome.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 19:34:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Suggested changes to investigator class structure</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I still like my idea of making it so if a Prince dies before N4, a Princess can silently change their class to Prince.  (Only one Princess can do this per game.)</p>
<p>This would reduce the impact of the prince randomly dying in the first few nights, just like the Mastermind has a similar contingency.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 19:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41528-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528.rss">Suggested changes to investigator class structure</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggested changes to investigator class structure</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure about the princess changes you suggest, but I actually like the idea of getting a second really powerful BD class that can replace the prince. Not sure how it could work balance-wise but having a Prince in all games gets a bit stale (I mean, there is uncertainty even in other guaranteed stuff: King has a random faction, the evil faction is also random), so having an alternative could make the game more fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 06:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41528-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528.rss">Suggested changes to investigator class structure</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggested changes to investigator class structure</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrtriple6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi everyone, I’m reposting this from reddit to hear more opinions. The last few patches have made some big changes to the game. Investigators in particular are becoming more powerful and more difficult to fake claim. I like that the devs are willing to make big changes and I think they are addressing important issues within the game. However, I also feel like making classes harder to fake, making them unique or guaranteed to spawn can be good for game balance but can limit the choices available to us during gameplay.</p>
<p>I think that a game which revolves around deceit/deduction/mind-fuckery should thrive on uncertainty. When you go into a game knowing that there will be exactly one nonconvertible sheriff, one nonconvertible prince, etc, there is less uncertainty and therefore less room to be creative in your playstyle. There is still obviously room to come up with awesome plays - but my point is that more immediately verified information at the start of the game results in less opportunities to deceive other players.</p>
<p>I’m going to throw out some potential changes to investigators that I think would help add more uncertainty to the game. I am not a career gamer or game designer, so feel free to improve on my ideas or tell me why they suck.</p>
<p>The main change I’d like to suggest would be to revert the recent sheriff changes and buff the princess up to a prince-tier investigator. I’m not going to suggest specific ability changes but I am thinking something like buffing flirt to be more like allies, making wisp more like surveillance and perhaps giving her some socially oriented day abilities (secret whispers perhaps? no reason for psychic to get all the fun toys). The goal is to make the princess an alternative to the prince who is equally powerful, but focused more on social interaction and deduction than brute force.</p>
<p>Then make the princess unique/nonconvertible and give each game a 50/50% to spawn either prince or princess. This way BD would always have one really high powered investigator who specializes in either threat neutralization (prince) or social manipulation (princess). But we wouldn’t know which spawns in a given game. More investigative classes could be reasonably claimable and we’d have a ton of new opportunities to fuck with people’s heads. We would also have more diverse games in general, instead of the guaranteed prince/sheriff, prince/paladin combo we can always anticipate now.</p>
<p>Let me know what you guys think. (ps I would also like to propose that each game should have a very small chance to spawn zero or two NKs instead of just one, based on the reasoning that more uncertainty = good. And it would just be fucking awesome.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41528-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggested-changes-to-investigator-class-structure/41528.rss">Suggested changes to investigator class structure</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
