<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Merchant</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-merchant/73112</link>
    <description>This class is supposed to bring more action in the game.

_**Flavor text:**_ Products of exceptional quality and good customer service made the Merchant famous and influential person. However, no one knew all the secrets of his work. Enlisting the help of his only friend, the Alchemist, he provided a large selection of poisons, weapons, forbidden books, and runestones that contain tremendous power — he sold anything to anyone.

**Fraction:** Neutral
**Class type:** Special

_**Passives:**_
**Have some rest:** can&#39;t appear in the same game with the Alchemist.
**High security:** occupy immunity, all attacking visits will be prevented.

_**Day abilities (all 1 use limited):**_
**Deliver Dagger:** if your target is Support or Investigative(BD) give them additional Night abilities.
For Support: you will kill all your attackers tonight, but will die anyway.
For Investigative (only BD classes, doesn&#39;t work with Maid): kill your target if they will appear suspicious.
_Notes:_ all abilities the Merchant provides can(must) be used in addition to your base Night Abilities. For Investigative, new ability must combine with Peek, W-o-W, Test, Investigation and Surveillance.

**Deliver Acid:** if your target is Killer or Offensive give them additional Night abilities.
For Killer (won&#39;t work on Prince): if you killed a player tonight, his logs will be erased (not just empty, court must know about Acid usage) and exhume of his body will provide no results.
For Offensive (and Prince): your target (jailed player) will be poisoned at the start of the next day. 

**Deliver Runestone:** if your target is Social or Investigative(Evil) give them additional Night abilities.
For Social: you will be death immune tonight.
For Investigative (only Evil classes AND Maid): you will be occupy immune tonight.

_**More notes:**_ 
1) Merchant will know if his good was delivered only at the start of next day, if good was delivered, one charge of used ability will be spend.
2) You can&#39;t deliver your items to Neutrals, except for NK.
3) Delivered items can be used any time later, the Merchant won&#39;t know if item is used.
4) Target player will recieve notification &quot;The Merchant have delivered some goods for you&quot; during the day

_**Night abilities:**_
**The dead don&#39;t need it (1 use):** send your assistant to search for your goods in dead player&#39;s house. Can target only dead players to whom you have previously successfully delivered the goods. If item wasn&#39;t used, you will regain 1 use of your Day Ability.

_**Win Condition:**_ You must survive untill the end of the game, you must successfully deliver all your goods, at least 2 of your goods must be used.

_Will appreciate all feedback._
**P.S.** English isn&#39;t my mother tongue, so I&#39;m sorry for mistakes.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 09:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-merchant/73112.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PressFtoPayRespects]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This class is supposed to bring more action in the game.</p>
<p><em><strong>Flavor text:</strong></em> Products of exceptional quality and good customer service made the Merchant famous and influential person. However, no one knew all the secrets of his work. Enlisting the help of his only friend, the Alchemist, he provided a large selection of poisons, weapons, forbidden books, and runestones that contain tremendous power — he sold anything to anyone.</p>
<p><strong>Fraction:</strong> Neutral<br>
<strong>Class type:</strong> Special</p>
<p><em><strong>Passives:</strong></em><br>
<strong>Have some rest:</strong> can’t appear in the same game with the Alchemist.<br>
<strong>High security:</strong> occupy immunity, all attacking visits will be prevented.</p>
<p><em><strong>Day abilities (all 1 use limited):</strong></em><br>
<strong>Deliver Dagger:</strong> if your target is Support or Investigative(BD) give them additional Night abilities.<br>
For Support: you will kill all your attackers tonight, but will die anyway.<br>
For Investigative (only BD classes, doesn’t work with Maid): kill your target if they will appear suspicious.<br>
<em>Notes:</em> all abilities the Merchant provides can(must) be used in addition to your base Night Abilities. For Investigative, new ability must combine with Peek, W-o-W, Test, Investigation and Surveillance.</p>
<p><strong>Deliver Acid:</strong> if your target is Killer or Offensive give them additional Night abilities.<br>
For Killer (won’t work on Prince): if you killed a player tonight, his logs will be erased (not just empty, court must know about Acid usage) and exhume of his body will provide no results.<br>
For Offensive (and Prince): your target (jailed player) will be poisoned at the start of the next day.</p>
<p><strong>Deliver Runestone:</strong> if your target is Social or Investigative(Evil) give them additional Night abilities.<br>
For Social: you will be death immune tonight.<br>
For Investigative (only Evil classes AND Maid): you will be occupy immune tonight.</p>
<p><em><strong>More notes:</strong></em></p>
<ol>
<li>Merchant will know if his good was delivered only at the start of next day, if good was delivered, one charge of used ability will be spend.</li>
<li>You can’t deliver your items to Neutrals, except for NK.</li>
<li>Delivered items can be used any time later, the Merchant won’t know if item is used.</li>
<li>Target player will recieve notification “The Merchant have delivered some goods for you” during the day</li>
</ol>
<p><em><strong>Night abilities:</strong></em><br>
<strong>The dead don’t need it (1 use):</strong> send your assistant to search for your goods in dead player’s house. Can target only dead players to whom you have previously successfully delivered the goods. If item wasn’t used, you will regain 1 use of your Day Ability.</p>
<p><em><strong>Win Condition:</strong></em> You must survive untill the end of the game, you must successfully deliver all your goods, at least 2 of your goods must be used.</p>
<p><em>Will appreciate all feedback.</em><br>
<strong>P.S.</strong> English isn’t my mother tongue, so I’m sorry for mistakes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-merchant/73112/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-merchant/73112/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 08:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73112-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-merchant/73112.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Merchant</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
