<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717</link>
    <description># One Piece Roleplay - Hosted by Jgoesgaming.

Wealth, fame, power.
The world had it all won by one man:
The Former Pirate King, Jane D. Patrick.

On this day, Nordin D. Allaert shocked the world by defeating the deemed undefeatable former Pirate King Jane D. Patrick in *The War For Everything* and becoming the new Pirate King.

Now, thousands of aspiring pirates&#39; dreams are reawakened, and they set sail towards the Grand Line with the aim to one day become a great pirate.

The golden age of piracy has now truly begun!

[details=&quot;Devil Fruits&quot;]

**Devil Fruits**  are mystical and mysterious fruits found throughout the Grand Line that, when consumed, provide the eater a special super-human power, at the cost of the eater&#39;s ability to swim.

A Devil Fruit can grant the user an immense variety of powers that can be used in many ways, from mundane utilities to powerful attacks. They are extremely valuable on the market, and many of the world&#39;s most powerful combatants, especially those among the Three Great Powers have consumed them.

You only need to take a single bite of a Devil Fruit for it to take effect, and other Devil Fruits will no longer affect you if you&#39;ve eaten one.

If the user of a Devil Fruit dies, the fruit reincarnates into the nearest fruit that its shape was based upon.

## Paramecia

The most common and most diverse of the three types, some Paramecia-type Devil Fruits grant their user superhuman powers or alter features of the user&#39;s body. Others allow the user to modify the people, objects, and environment around them. Finally, there are some that grant the user the power to generate and manipulate substances.

## Zoan

The users of Zoan-type Devil Fruits gain the ability to transform into an animal. The user can also transform into a hybrid form of their own species and the species the fruit allows them to transform into. A recently discovered science allows Zoan Fruits to be integrated into objects, bringing the object to life and granting it the standard Zoan transformations. Carnivorous animal Zoan&#39;s are better suited for combat.

## Logia

Logia-type Devil Fruits allow their users to create, control, and transform themselves into a naturally occurring substance, whether it be a solid element, a liquid element, a gaseous element or energy. The elemental transformation effectively makes the user intangible, as well as allowing the user to remain in control of their body, even when it is broken into pieces. They also gain every ability related to that substance.

## Ancient Zoan

A variation of Zoan Fruits that is rarer than Logia Devil Fruits that allows the user to transform into an extinct species, such as dinosaurs. Ancient Zoans appear to be stronger than regular Zoans.

## Mythical Zoan 

Zoan Fruits that allow the user to transform into a mythological creature, such as a dragon or a phoenix. Mythical Zoan animals tend to have special powers and are the rarest type of Devil Fruit.

There may or may not be more Devil Fruit types than these.

## Awakening

Devil Fruit powers can, in rare instances, be &quot;awakened&quot;, greatly increasing the abilities of the user. The details of how a Devil Fruit can be awakened are currently unknown, but the increased abilities have been seen to allow significantly more power, more refined control, new abilities that would otherwise not be possible. The effects of the awakening depend on the type of the Devil Fruit.

For Zoan-type powers, awakening grants far greater strength, speed, and durability than unawakened Zoan powers. This also includes faster recovery time, which functions involuntarily, even when the user is unconscious.

Because Paramecia-type Devil fruits are so diverse, the effects of awakening depend on the Devil Fruit. However, awakening generally allows the user to use their Devil Fruits at a new level of strength and in different manners than they originally could.

An awakened Logia allows the user to spread their power beyond their own body and transform inorganic material around them to match the nature of their Fruit. As well as manipulate the transformed material in any way they desire. The transformation effect can be spread over a very wide area.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Haki&quot;]

Haki is dormant in every living person, but it&#39;s rare for most people to ever awaken that ability. Becoming very powerful can awaken it, as can extreme shock,

# Kenboshuki Haki

## Basic Techniques

#### Presence Sensing

This type of Haki allows the user to see another person through the aura, be it behind buildings, strategically hidden, or camouflaged.

#### Strength Sensing

This application of Haki allows the user to measure the strength of the people whose presence they sense.

#### Emotion Sensing

This variation of Kenbunshoku allows the user to sense and empathize with the emotions and nature of others.

#### Intention Sensing

Another variant of Kenbunshoku Haki allows its user to sense another person&#39;s intent to act in the immediate future (especially through bloodlust/killing intent within combat), allowing them to predict what someone is going to do, usually seconds prior, in what resembles a pseudo-form of precognition.

## Advanced Techniques

#### Precognition

If trained enough, users of advanced Kenbunshoku Haki can see a short period into the future Instead of just sensing what would happen by intuition, the user of this advanced level of Kenbunshoku Haki can literally see a precise mental image of what will happen in the immediate future.

If I don&#39;t know what someone is planning, I&#39;ll just give the actions they are most likely to take.

# Busoshoku Haki

## Basic Techniques

#### Enhancement

This type of Haki also can bypass the powers of a Devil Fruit) user whose body has been altered by their fruit in any way, touching the &quot;substantial body&quot; beneath whatever protection the fruit provides.
By the same effect, this Haki can also be used as a higher level of offensive power, more so than just bypassing a foe&#39;s Devil Fruit powers.

#### Hardening

An evolved step of the Enhancement technique. A heavy concentration of this Haki can harden the body of the user, granting the user a greater increase in power and endurance that surpasses the mere Enhancement application.

It is the most distinctive and recognizable Haki, as it turns the user&#39;s body shining black. In some cases, the skin-blackening effect of Hardening takes on a flame-like pattern; the reason for this is currently unknown.

#### Imbuement

Another evolved step of the Enhancement technique. By touching an object, the user can imbue it with their own Haki to greatly increase its power and endurance.

## Advanced Techniques

#### Emission 

With this technique, the user can project their Haki flow from their body without a medium. This method allows the user to damage the target without making contact, but most people cannot use it from a distance greater than a few inches.

#### Internal Destruction

A higher grade of the Emission technique. The emitted Haki flows inside a target and destroys it from the inside-out.

# Haoshoku Haki

## Basic Techniques

#### Domination

Haoshoku Haki can be used to temporarily dominate the psyche of other people or animals, intimidating them to point where they are frozen with fear and/or forcing them to obey the user&#39;s commands for a short time. Depending on the will of the victim(s), they could even suffer a panic attack.

#### Incapacitation

An ability that allows the user to release their own will in the form of a strong burst, allowing them to incapacitate others. Instead of just intimidating or subjugating others, these bursts of Haki are so powerful, they render those with a weak will unconscious. Those with greater willpower will simply feel very uncomfortable and could stumble if they try to move.

#### Pressure

Users with an extremely high Haoshoku Haki can use it to exert their will over objects, resulting in said objects breaking.

There may or may not be more Haki techniques than these.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Occupations&quot;]

## Pirate

Start your own Pirate Crew or join another and embark on your adventure through the Grand Line!
Aim to become a Shichibukai, a Yonko or even the Pirate King!

## Marine

Become a Marine, enact law and order throughout the world and impose the will and might of the World Government as you rise through its ranks.

## Bounty Hunter

Become a Bounty Hunter, and hunt pirates that have made enough of a name for themselves that a body has been placed on their head.

## Devil Fruit Hunter

Become a Devil Fruit Hunter, and go in search of unknown Devil Fruits, or Reincarnated Devil Fruits that got lost. You can also try to take back devil fruits either eaten by or in possession of other individuals. All for a price, of course.

## Scientist

Become a scientist, and develop new technologies for whoever you work for, be that The Marines, a Pirate Crew, Bounty Hunters, Revolutionaries or Devil Fruit Hunters. While it may not be the most exciting occupation, you can still have a great impact on the world.

## Revolutionary

Become a Revolutionary and join the Revolutionary Army in their war against the Marines.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Races&quot;]

You can only be a human, but you can recruit or ally yourselves with people from other races.

## Dwarves

Dwarves are an extremely small sentient race.
They are mostly human in appearance, and often have pointed noses.

## Fish-Men

Fish-men are a combination between a man and a fish or other aquatic creature, however, they still have legs. They also have gills between their shoulders and necks, sometimes covered by their clothing, as well as often having webbed hands. Depending on species, they may have multiple limbs (mainly extra arms).

## Merfolk

Like the mermaids and mermen of folklore, their upper half is that of a human while the lower half is that of a fish or other undersea creature. While the males, referred to as mermen, keep their tails intact their whole lives, the females&#39;, referred to as mermaids, tails split when they turn 30, allowing them to walk on land more easily.

## Giants

Being giants, they are literally giant in appearance, although many giants seen have been noted as having more exaggerated proportions and features than most humans. They are so large that when they cry, their tears can cause large areas on the ground to appear flooded.

## Minks

Minks are humanoids with animal features. Similar to fish-men, each individual takes after a specific animal. So far, the animalistic traits of the minks have all been fur-covered mammalian. As such, fur, which they also refer to as &quot;mink&quot;, covers most of their bodies and is considered their pride and joy. Females tend to look more like humans while males tend to look more bestial. They possess humanoid hands and feet, but those based on animals with paws will also possess paw pads on their palm and up to their first knuckle.

There are more races than these, but these are the only you know of.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Technology&quot;]

## Dance Powder

Dance Powder is a green powder that is used to make artificial rain.
The powder, unfortunately, causes long periods of drought in other countries. The process in which the artificial rain is created nurtures clouds that aren&#39;t ready to rain yet. When this happens, all of the water contained within these clouds would all be used up. Because of this, other countries and locations, who would naturally benefit from rainfall when these clouds would naturally mature, would be greatly deprived.

The controversy that this powder brought whenever it was used started a war. The number of lives lost in this war was so great that the prohibited the manufacturing and possession of Dance Powder worldwide.

## Coating

Coating is a process in which a ship is coated with special resin from the Yarukiman Mangroves, enabling it to survive the crushing depths of the ocean.

## Cyborgs

A cyborg is a human or another life form that has been modified with machinery and metal for better functioning. These mechanical enhancements can include cybernetic replacements for missing organs or body parts, metal skin for extra protection, and weapons installed somewhere in the body.

## Vivre Cards

A Vivre Card is made from part of a person’s fingernail which is then made into paper. It is completely water and fireproof but can be torn and given to a cared person that one would be separated from.

The torn pieces will point to and move towards each other no matter where they are in the world, allowing one to always be able to tell in which direction the other person is.

True to the name &quot;paper of life&quot;, Vivre Cards also display the life force of their owner. If the life force of the person who gave the Vivre Card is disappearing, the card will begin to burn. It will grow back to its original size if the person recovers, but disappears completely if the person dies.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Creatures&quot;]

Species in the One Piece world are classified as:

* Type A Creatures: Big Friendly
* Type B Creatures: Small Friendly
* Type C Creatures: Big Savage
* Type D Creatures: Small Savage

## Sea Kings

Sea Kings are fearsome sea creatures that are generally much larger than normal sea creatures. They are found in great numbers along the Calm Belt around the Grand Line, although on rare occasions they can be found in other places throughout the world.

## News Coo

News Coo are medium-sized gulls that deliver newspapers and wanted posters around the world. They wear hats to signify their employment and carry bags over their shoulders, just like a paperboy and a small bag that hangs on the neck to collect money from anyone that purchased the newspaper. They are the main source of news and information for people across the globe. News Coo normally perch around the ship&#39;s mast or fly through until they are called to deliver the news. They do not deliver newspapers to the Calm Belt. It&#39;s also possible to deliver private letters through them, but that requires prior negotiation first.

Naturally, there are many more creatures, but these are the only you know of.

[/details]


[details=&quot;Den Den Mushi&quot;]

## Baby Den Den Mushi

A Baby Den Den Mushi is small enough to fit in a palm or even be worn like a wristwatch and is favored by many for portable communication. However, its signal is weaker than that of a full-grown specimen, and cannot be used for inter-island calls. They can also be used as speakers, to broadcast the user&#39;s voice throughout the area.

## Black Den Den Mushi

The Black Den Den Mushi is a species of Den Den Mushi that remains small for its entire lifespan and enjoys &quot;eavesdropping&quot; on the signals of the standard variety rather than openly communicating. It can also memorize anything it intercepts, to be repeated at a later time.

## White Den den Mushi

The White Den Den Mushi can produce signals that neutralize the Black Den Den Mushi&#39;s eavesdropping abilities; as such, they can be attached to any standard Den Den Mushi to encrypt the user&#39;s calls.

However, this breed of Den Den Mushi is extremely rare.

## Horned Den Den Mushi

The Horned Den Den Mushi can jam radio transmissions. The range and period of a transmission jamming caused by this type are unknown.

## Visual Den Den Mushi

The Visual Den Den Mushi can receive, project and broadcast what it sees onto a bigger video screen.

[/details]

[details=&quot;Grand Line &amp; Log Poses&quot;]

Chains of islands surrounded on both sides by the Calm Belt, a part of the sea where there are no wind nor waves, making it nearly impossible to enter the Grand Line that way.

Because of how wild the sea in the Grand Line is, a Log Pose (basically a compass) is required to navigate from island to island.

[/details]

It&#39;ll probably start like next week or something since there are still some things I have to flesh out.

If you have any questions, feel free to ask me.

To join, post **/In** or **/Join**.

# Playerlist

1. Emilia
2. Magnus
3. Shurian
4. Boss110
5.
6.
7.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 17:07:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Roleplaying</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eating did not take away my stomachache so I’m taking a break.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 17:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t really been ‘into’ rps on this forum<br>
So probably not</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 18:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wasn’t sure you wanted to join tbh.</p>
<p>Do you?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 18:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Realizing that I can’t micspam a pbp rp has left my day immeasurable and my ruined disappointment</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 18:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eh, I’m just going to let you create characters now, people can still join later if they want to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is anyone else going to join?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 12:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GamerPoke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/thinking about it</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 04:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure, you can micspam.</p>
<p>Partly because I’m curious how you will do this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 22:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 22:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 22:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How are you going to micspam in a text-base game?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 21:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DirectorHail]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No I’m alright, thanks for the offer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 21:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if I can micspam, I’ll join</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 21:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/in</strong></p>
<p>yeah this looks too good to pass up</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You haven’t done anything evil until endgames though, in any games.<br>
Except for that game where your wincon was to kill.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 20:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boss110]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/Join.</strong><br>
Please don’t mind my previous question which is totally not me planned something evil at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 14:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can do secret stuff here too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 13:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boss110]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You know, in Magnus misc he just spam DM so I can do <em>secret</em> stuff and plans out <em>secret</em> plan.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can if you want to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 13:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boss110]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is this like Magnus misc where I can murder people in cold blood.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 13:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/simon">@Simon</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/boss110">@Boss110</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/directorhail">@DirectorHail</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/ami">@Ami</a></p>
<p>Do any of you want to join this?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 13:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/in</strong></p>
<p>Please take care of me!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Welcome to the game, Shuri.<br>
<em>Evil grin.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 02:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/3X/0/7/07d92165dbfb7a24e95733d74fb751df877a7d83.png" alt="20200315_231446" data-base62-sha1="17qxC3JLi97HN9c7hfgxZvjMXJx" width="623" height="500"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 02:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DatBird" data-post="8" data-topic="80717">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/datbird/40/32705_2.png" class="avatar"> DatBird:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Like Simon, Boss, Magnus, Hail, Ami, Shuri</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is a good idea tbh<br>
<strong>/in</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 20:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80717-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/one-piece-rp-signups-4-7/80717.rss">One Piece RP - Signups [4/7+]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
