<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544</link>
    <description>I joined ToL not so long ago, and TBH the steam reviews had me worried. A lot.
Fortunately the &quot;get trolled into oblivion as a newbie&quot; part turned out to be false (for me at least).
My respects and congratulations on this. Both to the community and to the ones moderating it.
You guys beat ToS in this by a mile.
Unfortunately a hell of a lot of other complaints were spot on.
My apologies in advance if the amount of ToS comparison in this thread upsets you. But that&#39;s &quot;where I&#39;m from&quot; and, more importantly, it&#39;s a very similar game with similar concepts in play.

I&#39;m going to start from talking about the prince a little bit. Do you know why his ToS counterpart is so damn strong? It&#39;s his ability to secretly gather information from his faction without putting any of them at risk of exposure and while having their complete trust. Sure, being able to both protect and kill adds to that, but the real source of his power is the above factor. He IS, after all, notably stronger than just a killer + a healer combined.

Why am I bringing that up though? Wait for it... [drumbeat] ... it&#39;s about the whisper king meta.
See, it&#39;s not the prince that&#39;s the problem, it&#39;s the king. In your game prince is NOT the main carry. You went well over the limit of the &quot;most OP&quot; class in ToS. (Yes that&#39;s a lame term, but it DOES show the extent of power shift doesn&#39;t it?) And made him barely more than an afterthought. Who cares if he can gather info at night from select players. The king has it ALL and more, and get&#39;s updated every bloody day in real time. 

But more importantly than just breaking the prince&#39;s main feature, you broke strategy in the process.

ToS, before the DLC anyway, was a strategic masterpiece. Time to analyse the right parts of your competition&#39;s effort and learn from it.

I&#39;ve already discussed one peak of power - the jailer.
Let&#39;s add two more before we get to the real business.

First is the retributionist. Not the player himself though, the one he brings back is the cornerstone of power here. Why? Because he&#39;s a 100% proven character who you can whisper to. Next comes the whisper meta and the end. Why am I bringing this one up? (no pun intended) To show the extent to which the whisper meta is limited in ToS. I doesn&#39;t start until the ret does his thing, and ret is not a guaranteed class, and then even if it does, the cornerstone of whisper meta is fragile.

And last but not least - the mayor.
A class that excels at being proven and leading the public execution.
Note his two limits - he cannot be whispered to after revealing, nor can he be healed.

But we are not quite there yet. Before we get to the king&#39;s affairs I&#39;m going to bring up a few more points.

Please note how the roles are usually distributed. A normal class usually excels at one of the &quot;areas&quot;.

Protection. Those classes decide who gets to live longer, but they have to stay hidden to live themselves and as such are the LEAST informed of ALL the classes.

Killing. Those classes decide who gets to live shorter, can count of support of protectors to an extent and need the help of investigators to work.

And investigators. The guys who know who should live longer or shorter, but can&#39;t DO anything about it without receiving support from others.

And all of them, generally, need to earn their allies trust and put themselves at risk via public exposure in order to get anything done.

There. Done. Now let&#39;s take a look at the monstrosity that you call king. He:
-Has statistical trust of the BD from the get-go. (more likely to be good than evil)
-Is able to be the cornerstone of whisper meta.
-Is able to influence public executions both through his position AND his abilities.
-Is able to protect both others and himself.
-Is able to take justice into his own hands and kill without public&#39;s consent.

WHAT THE F dev team? What were you thinking. You threw away ALL the possible limitations (and caution) with this guy.
Unsurprisingly you ended up with the most strategically shallow meta-game possible.

ONE player ends up gathering all the intel there is to gather, gets to lead the game during the day, gets to protect the important roles without even revealing them, gets to kill the bad guys without even saying who or how found them out and he gets to stay alive through all of that because he&#39;s so well protected most killers don&#39;t even **consider** going for the king&#39;s throat.

If you want your game to be fun for anyone other than the king this has to end. And the sooner the better.
There are several paths you can choose here, so let&#39;s get to them.

**1st - the &quot;Mayor&quot; path**
Plain and simple - no whispers to and from the king. EVER. Make the game social again, and stop &quot;the throne of whispered lies&quot; nonsense. Wanna accuse someone, or to defend your innocence (real or otherwise)? Step out into the public eye and plead your case to the WHOLE court, not to one uberman. Let the good know who&#39;s badmouthing them, let the evil know who found them out and how, let the good protectors and killers scratch their head thinking who to trust and who to distrust. MAKE THIS A GAME OF **PUBLIC** DECEPTION AND DEDUCTION.

**2nd - the &quot;powerless king&quot; path**
Also rather simple - remove the kings ability to act on his own. No more ordered executions, no more fingers, no more decide fate, heck, no more VOTING for him either. Force the king to SHARE the intel to get **anything** at all done. This is a weaker path than the first, obviously, but at least it gets SOME social component back into the game. Would probably be a good idea to make his guard ability infinite on this path.

**3rd - the &quot;isolated king&quot; path**
Again rather simple - remove the kings ability to SHARE intel. COMPLETELY. No whispering from the king, no chating from the king, no logs from the king. And again, no VOTES from the king either. Make him socially an observer (not the class kind of observer). Depending on how it goes with balance up the number of his night executions. Definitely decrease the number of his guards. Preferably spread the number of his guards between the kings. Basically we&#39;re making him an empowered vigilante (again, not a class reference). He get&#39;s more info than anyone else on account of statistical trust and whisper TO the king still being enabled, and can do things about it. That&#39;s more than the other players get anyway. The important part here is that it allows people to mislead a king, and then get rid of him to get away with it. The rest of the court can still opt to stay hidden and act with the king as their proxy, but since it&#39;s no longer (near) impossible to mislead the king and get away with it the rest of the court gets a harder time earning his trust.

**4th - the &quot;gambling king&quot; path**
You guessed it..., it&#39;s simple, it&#39;s also boring and weak, but still better than what we currently have. Just remove the statistical trust from the king. Make him EXACTLY as likely to be evil as he is likely to be good. Do something to strongly weaken the subsequent kings. Maybe just force them to take the one of the 3 other paths.

And before I forget, on all of those paths you&#39;ll want to make prince be unguardable by the good and neutral kings. Or else the whisper meta will just jump to him as the new cornerstone.

And for fun&#39;s sake, take a good long inquisitive look at how the pre-dlc ToS plays out. It may be limited in term of class abilities, but it&#39;s a strategic masterpiece as a result of those carefully crafted limits.

Most actions that have a good reason to be taken have a similarly good reason to NOT be taken. You often have to wonder what is the evil doing, how would they react to this situation, and whether or not you&#39;re playing into their hands right now. This both supports social deception and is born from social deception.

How can it work in your game when most classes are provable? Princess, WoW the king. The &quot;princess&quot; gets exed first thing the next morning. Noble, make me vote 10. The &quot;noble&quot; get&#39;s exe-d within seconds. I could continue, but do I have to? WHERE is deception in your game? It&#39;s ok to have provable classes. But you have to have UNpovable classes, and that&#39;s how the **majority** of them has to be.

I get it that &quot;more power to the classes&quot; is your moto, and I&#39;m not saying that you have to get rid of that. But you have to handle that extra power with a LOT more care than that.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 03:48:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Before the king meta I once fooled the cult into thinking I was alch because I outed myself as alch to the court. The cult were saying stop throwing pls and Im like Lel.</p>
<p>I led a Good King+Phys a win against 4 cult. (Rip other phys who got converted.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/92</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-92</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly and let’s RIOT about Cupcakes not being in the gam… what were we talking about?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/91</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 22:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-91</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve seen Sheriffs and Paladins work as fine leaders under the right circumstances.</p>
<p>The assertion that they can’t lead is simply false.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/90</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 22:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-90</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>People said I was cheating… no it was RNG and the fact that I was very execited.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/89</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-89</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I remember being a sheriff. Day two found nothing. But on that day I noticed who was in number 1. I said get him up Hes a bad guy. People didn’t agree but we got him up. He was the possessor. Next day didn’t find anyone. I voted somone up was<br>
A bad guy. Next day got somone up who was a sheriff who didn’t claim. His refusal to claim made me think he was innocent so I sad pardon he’s bad enough to be innocent. I was right but they still executed. Soon we got all the  bad guy</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/88</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-88</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice fancy list. But what I was saying that 2/3 criteria are complete bs. The only thing that matters is if you are confirmable. You do not need to have your own protectives as if you are confirmed protectives will be on you. You do not need to have leverage as if you are confirmed you can lead town and the lynches and use lynching people as leverage.</p>
<p>You literally only need to be confirmed. The real list of best BD leaders would simply be</p>
<p>1: Any Confirmed and Nonconvertible Class<br>
2: Any Confirmed Class</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/87</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-87</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Leverage is the lynch. Nothing else is needed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/86</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-86</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sheriff/Paladin and princess have none of the 3 needed traits.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/85</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-85</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just to list it out btw from best leader classes to worst leader classes:</p>
<p>King: Auto confirmed. Guards for defense (6 shot).  OE and decide fate for leverage.</p>
<p>Hunter: Unique and Wolf is confirmable. Bear for a defense that counter attacks (3 shot). Wolf for leverage in a way that is particularly good at being leverage.</p>
<p>Prince: Unique and guaranteed. Execute for leverage</p>
<p>Psychic: Telepathy and link for confirming. Private matters synergies well with leader status.</p>
<p>Physician: Heal for confirming, First aid and remedy study for defense.</p>
<p>Noble: Spy and PP for confirming</p>
<p>Butler: Wine for confirming, Party for defence</p>
<p>Knight: CS for leverage (Note: Its rare but whenever a knight does lead it is godlike)</p>
<p>Observer: Follow for confirming</p>
<p>Drunk: Debauch for confirming</p>
<p>CW: Tornado for defence</p>
<p>Remember I said you need AT LEAST 1 of the traits in order to lead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/84</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-84</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Aren’t we are killers cause we are lynching the bad guys. We are a DEMOCRATIC killer</p>
<p>We have to atleast Vote on who dies Jeez. You think we are monsters?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/83</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-83</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A. I bet I can fake claim prince and get away with it</p>
<p>Totally possible</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/82</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-82</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am here just to</p>
<ol>
<li>Make  people  laugh</li>
<li>To argue cause I really love to</li>
<li>Cause chaos</li>
</ol>
<p>People love me</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/81</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-81</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly anyone can lead. Being a good leader has nothing to do with being a Killing class.</p>
<p>I agree that leaders need to be confirmed, which is like I said why Prince, and to a lesser extent Hunter, can be powerful. But lot’s of other classes have that and that’s not related to them being Killers at all.</p>
<p>Your idea that you have to have your own defense to be a leader is bs. To start you are contradicting yourself as Prince has no defense whatsoever. If you are a good enough leader you will clearly be protected.</p>
<p>To answer C, if you are leading BD you will always have leverage during the day to get claims whatever class you are. That leverage is called Lynching! And that kind of Leverage is far more likely to have an impact to get claims or push people as it can be proved and commenced there and then. If a random guy says “oi I’m hunter gimme you’re class” you have to be a moron to give it to him. Even if he is Hunter now he can be converted.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="59" data-topic="53544">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh and the job of a BD Killer is to lead</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>tl;dr This is not true in anyway. It happens that 2/3 BD Killers are easily confirmable so can lead well, which has probably led you to this conclusion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/80</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-80</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh god we are losing bad I am cold steeling 14</p>
<p>Tried attacking BD</p>
<p>Day 4 and 7 BD are dead</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/79</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-79</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Told you</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/78</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-78</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>See! It works!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/77</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-77</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh god here have it LEAVE ME ALONE<br>
<img src="/images/emoji/twitter/popcorn.png?v=9" title=":popcorn:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":popcorn:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/76</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-76</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gimme your popcorn or I will wolf you in the face.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/75</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-75</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t guard 7 this night he died<br>
Sad</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/74</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-74</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>-whispers fight fight fight softly in your ears- HEY guys I Have popcorn</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/73</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-73</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As long as whispers exist anyone can get claims. Leading should never be exclusive to one class as taking the role of leader is half the fun of the game (for me anyways). To properly lead you need at least 1 of 3 things:</p>
<p>A: Confirmability</p>
<p>B: Defense</p>
<p>C: Leverage</p>
<p>The Hunter and King are the only classes which have lots of all 3. And having a phys on you for example doesn’t count. This is about what you can do on your own.</p>
<p>Right now the only BD classes that have none of all 3 of these are Sheriff/Pally and Princess.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/72</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-72</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Playing as knight right now guard 7 always. When you don’t guard him he dies</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/71</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-71</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Um mate a social class can have a anti social person playing it</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/70</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-70</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Social classes are better placed to lead as everyone can listen to them easier and they are easier to confirm during the day when everyone is listening AND invest classes are meant to lead as they have all the info so everyone can just sheep them.</p>
<p>Killers are the worst placed to lead honestly. They can try make threats to people during the day but I have never once given someone my class who was threatening me because I do it all the time as scum lol.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/69</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-69</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am sorry but any person who can type can lead.</p>
<p>Whether for the better or worst</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544/68</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53544-68</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/get-your-ship-togather-my-wall-of-feedback/53544.rss">Get your ship togather - My wall of feedback</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
