<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Ifrit (NK)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525</link>
    <description>&gt; # [color = &quot;darkred&quot;] The Ifrit [/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Killer [/color]** 
**Djinn Form (Passive)** - Grants the Ifrit immunity to occupation, redirection, bleeding, poison, and death at night.
**Burning Transformation (Day)** - Upon killing a target, the Ifrit will cause them to flip a class of the Ifrit’s choice. If the Ifrit successfully kills a player this night, they will be able to see their true class. - 3 uses 
**Heat Wave (Day)** - Occupies all targets who try to visit the Ifrit the coming night. Bypasses immunity to occupation. - 3 uses 
**Incinerate (Night)** - Kills a player by burning them alive. Players that have been incinerated will have their logs erased. Only the Ifrit will see the player’s original logs. - Infinite uses 
**Fires of Jahannam (Night)** - Prevents all visits to the target player and attacks them, erasing their logs if they die. - 3 uses 
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*


Theme: A neutral killer with a focus on causing preventions and misdirection via defiles.
Survivability: Natural immunity via Djinn Form and can pretty much avoid Knights, Observers, and Physicians via Fires of Jahannam.
Late-game: Has no trouble killing priority BD targets with Fires of Jahannam and can semi-reliably fake Butler via Heat Wave and the preventions caused by Fires of Jahannam.

Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Ifrit (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wouldn’t it be more consistent and unique to have a log-erasing and class-erasing ability, instead of log-erasing and class-changing?</p>
<p>Since we already have Possessor that can change logs and classes…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70525-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Ifrit (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Ifrit (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="darkred"> The Ifrit </font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Djinn Form (Passive)</strong> - Grants the Ifrit immunity to occupation, redirection, bleeding, poison, and death at night.<br>
<strong>Burning Transformation (Day)</strong> - Upon killing a target, the Ifrit will cause them to flip a class of the Ifrit’s choice. If the Ifrit successfully kills a player this night, they will be able to see their true class. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Heat Wave (Day)</strong> - Occupies all targets who try to visit the Ifrit the coming night. Bypasses immunity to occupation. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Incinerate (Night)</strong> - Kills a player by burning them alive. Players that have been incinerated will have their logs erased. Only the Ifrit will see the player’s original logs. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Fires of Jahannam (Night)</strong> - Prevents all visits to the target player and attacks them, erasing their logs if they die. - 3 uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Theme: A neutral killer with a focus on causing preventions and misdirection via defiles.<br>
Survivability: Natural immunity via Djinn Form and can pretty much avoid Knights, Observers, and Physicians via Fires of Jahannam.<br>
Late-game: Has no trouble killing priority BD targets with Fires of Jahannam and can semi-reliably fake Butler via Heat Wave and the preventions caused by Fires of Jahannam.</p>
<p>Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70525-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-ifrit-nk/70525.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Ifrit (NK)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
