<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Necromancer (neutral royal) -The Exiled Prince +Lore</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/necromancer-neutral-royal-the-exiled-prince-lore/204</link>
    <description>Before starting to explain this class is really needs some talking skills and decision making and also a good understanding of the game to play properly basiclly its like an &quot;extravaganza class&quot; that has enough style to have his own game mode. lets get into it
there are 4 classes that includes and is needed for the necromancer listed below:
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Name: The Necromancer

Faction: Neutral

Goal: Create a kingdom of undead  (Basicly turning everyone undead or killing them)



Day Abilities:

1) Cold Touch: If the target player dies that night he will turn into a &quot;Zombie&quot; instead. (cant use it on an undead)
Uses: once per day

2) Sense Prey: Tonight you will kidnap a random &quot;Non-Royal&quot; Blue Dragon, occupying them for the night and at the end of the night turning them into an &quot;Abomination&quot;
Uses: 1

3)Royal Blood: (Only usable upon the death of a King) Can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.
Uses: ∞



Passive abilities:

-You can comminucate with the Zombies and the Abomination at ANY time but ZOMBIES CAN&#39;T RESPOND to you in the &quot;undead chat&quot; !

-You will have an extra chat for the undead army of yours called &quot;undead chat&quot; no one can see your messages at the undead chat other than the undeads

-When choosen to be the king he will become &quot;The Undead King&quot;

-Immune to convert and poison




---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Class: Zombie

Faction: Neutral

Goal: Help your MASTER to create the  kingdom of undead



Day Abilities : 

1) Smell target: smell the target player identifying thier &quot;role&quot;
Uses: 3 (once per day)


Night Abilities:

1) Fake Dead: You will fake death protecting you from the incoming attacks.
Uses: 1

2) Warn Master: notify the necromancer with the latest &quot;Smell target&quot;s result. 
Uses: 1


Passive abilities:

-You can READ the undead chat.

-Immune to convert


------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------


Class: Abomination

Faction: Neutral

Goal: Help your MASTER to create the  kingdom of undead



Night Abilities:




1)Obliteration: Unreveal your true form and attack a target killing ANYONE who visits them. Killed players will be known to be &quot;torn into pieces by an unnatural being&quot; (which will reveal the necromancers existance)
Uses: 1

2) Protect Minion: Watch a zombie learning the &quot;names&quot; of the visiters.
Uses: once per night

3) Protect MASTER: guard the necromancer making him immune to death.
Uses: 1

4) Animal Senses: you are immune to death at night.



Passive Abilities:

-Can CHAT with the necromancer from the &quot;undead chat&quot; at ANYTIME.

-Immune to convert

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------


Class: The King (necromancer)

Faction: Neutral

Goal: Clear the living and make Adiart great again! (basicly the same goal of turning everyone undead or killing them)


Abilities:

(these are kings normal abilities can be found in the wikia)
1)Pass the Torch

2)The Royal Finger

3)Decide Fate

4)Guard!

5)Brotherhood

and the main necromancer ability

6) Cold Touch: If the target player dies that night he will turn into a &quot;Zombie&quot; instead. (cant use it on an undead)
Uses: once per day

7)Passive:&quot;undead chat.&quot;

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------


Lore : 

As Crazad grown to be untalented at fighting, unlike his brother, he became enyvious of power with an ambition to suprass his brother. he started to secretly study on dark arts. after a few months he resurrected his first corpse keeping him hidden in the celler secretly feeding him. But this didnt take long for the buttler to discover the creature and tell it to his father......the king. The unlike child Crazad has always been, his father exiled him to never return and gave one of his best guards to protect him on his journey to east. The kng thought that would keep him away from the cursed magic but that wasnt the case.... Crazadd dint stop studing the dark arts, he used his loyal guard and turned him into an Abomination, traveling the oldest temples mastering his magic, to one day come back and take over what he desirved !</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 15:54:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/necromancer-neutral-royal-the-exiled-prince-lore/204.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Necromancer (neutral royal) -The Exiled Prince +Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ozdeger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Before starting to explain this class is really needs some talking skills and decision making and also a good understanding of the game to play properly basiclly its like an “extravaganza class” that has enough style to have his own game mode. lets get into it<br>
there are 4 classes that includes and is needed for the necromancer listed below:</h2>
<p>Name: The Necromancer</p>
<p>Faction: Neutral</p>
<p>Goal: Create a kingdom of undead  (Basicly turning everyone undead or killing them)</p>
<p>Day Abilities:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Cold Touch: If the target player dies that night he will turn into a “Zombie” instead. (cant use it on an undead)<br>
Uses: once per day</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Sense Prey: Tonight you will kidnap a random “Non-Royal” Blue Dragon, occupying them for the night and at the end of the night turning them into an “Abomination”<br>
Uses: 1</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>3)Royal Blood: (Only usable upon the death of a King) Can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.<br>
Uses: ∞</p>
<p>Passive abilities:</p>
<p>-You can comminucate with the Zombies and the Abomination at ANY time but ZOMBIES CAN’T RESPOND to you in the “undead chat” !</p>
<p>-You will have an extra chat for the undead army of yours called “undead chat” no one can see your messages at the undead chat other than the undeads</p>
<p>-When choosen to be the king he will become “The Undead King”</p>
<p>-Immune to convert and poison</p>
<hr>
<p>Class: Zombie</p>
<p>Faction: Neutral</p>
<p>Goal: Help your MASTER to create the  kingdom of undead</p>
<p>Day Abilities :</p>
<ol>
<li>Smell target: smell the target player identifying thier “role”<br>
Uses: 3 (once per day)</li>
</ol>
<p>Night Abilities:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Fake Dead: You will fake death protecting you from the incoming attacks.<br>
Uses: 1</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Warn Master: notify the necromancer with the latest "Smell target"s result.<br>
Uses: 1</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Passive abilities:</p>
<p>-You can READ the undead chat.</p>
<p>-Immune to convert</p>
<hr>
<p>Class: Abomination</p>
<p>Faction: Neutral</p>
<p>Goal: Help your MASTER to create the  kingdom of undead</p>
<p>Night Abilities:</p>
<p>1)Obliteration: Unreveal your true form and attack a target killing ANYONE who visits them. Killed players will be known to be “torn into pieces by an unnatural being” (which will reveal the necromancers existance)<br>
Uses: 1</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>Protect Minion: Watch a zombie learning the “names” of the visiters.<br>
Uses: once per night</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Protect MASTER: guard the necromancer making him immune to death.<br>
Uses: 1</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Animal Senses: you are immune to death at night.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Passive Abilities:</p>
<p>-Can CHAT with the necromancer from the “undead chat” at ANYTIME.</p>
<p>-Immune to convert</p>
<hr>
<p>Class: The King (necromancer)</p>
<p>Faction: Neutral</p>
<p>Goal: Clear the living and make Adiart great again! (basicly the same goal of turning everyone undead or killing them)</p>
<p>Abilities:</p>
<p>(these are kings normal abilities can be found in the wikia)<br>
1)Pass the Torch</p>
<p>2)The Royal Finger</p>
<p>3)Decide Fate</p>
<p>4)Guard!</p>
<p>5)Brotherhood</p>
<p>and the main necromancer ability</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>Cold Touch: If the target player dies that night he will turn into a “Zombie” instead. (cant use it on an undead)<br>
Uses: once per day</li>
</ol>
<p>7)Passive:“undead chat.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Lore :</p>
<p>As Crazad grown to be untalented at fighting, unlike his brother, he became enyvious of power with an ambition to suprass his brother. he started to secretly study on dark arts. after a few months he resurrected his first corpse keeping him hidden in the celler secretly feeding him. But this didnt take long for the buttler to discover the creature and tell it to his father…the king. The unlike child Crazad has always been, his father exiled him to never return and gave one of his best guards to protect him on his journey to east. The kng thought that would keep him away from the cursed magic but that wasnt the case… Crazadd dint stop studing the dark arts, he used his loyal guard and turned him into an Abomination, traveling the oldest temples mastering his magic, to one day come back and take over what he desirved !</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/necromancer-neutral-royal-the-exiled-prince-lore/204/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/necromancer-neutral-royal-the-exiled-prince-lore/204/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 12:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-204-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/necromancer-neutral-royal-the-exiled-prince-lore/204.rss">Necromancer (neutral royal) -The Exiled Prince +Lore</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
