<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;ve been watching the development for quite some time and am really excited, I can totally see differences from this and other games that are inspired by Werewolf &amp; Mafia, I think the one thing I&#39;m disappointing in is the lack of VoIP to communicate, I enjoy Town of Salem but it&#39;s 2016 and to be honest games without VoIP implemented annoy me,

Werewolves Within is being developed on Unity, the two major factors to play that over games like Town of Salem are VR and VoIP and I know from personal experience that implementing VoIP in Unity is... Well, it&#39;s not that difficult like in the past, I beg you! **I BEG YOU!** Please think or re-think on the VoIP matter.

You could easily implement it with permissions, The King may allow someone to speak at the table or give it a timed system like Werewolves Within, Not everyone can afford nor does everyone want VR and even though I will be buying Werewolves Within I still see a reason to play Throne of Lies, but I will be disappointing if yet ANOTHER Werewolf/Mafia game gets released without VoIP access.

Other then that, me and my friends are excited, I am still contemplating the Kickstarter, the VoIP hurts me... But who knows, it&#39;s only $10 for the base and it is still well worth it if you guys can actually deliver what you&#39;re promising.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 10:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>More like<br>
New class<br>
Spambot</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 10:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>New role</p>
<p>Necromancer</p>
<p>/s</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 10:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What are you talking about? Aftermath was fun until it was removed. A little bland obviously but that’s not VoIP’s fault!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="23" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is after alpha. Does this work as a reminder? Cuz I would love to see a game mode designed for small groups of people with VoIP.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We had this in beta - it was awful (Aftermath). It also eliminates the use of many abilities that use chat (troll box)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It should possibly be invite-only?</p>
<p>So only premade groups can do it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="10" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We definitely have the tech/knowledge to do something with VoIP, btw <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> remind us after alpha. Who knows~</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is after alpha. Does this work as a reminder? Cuz I would love to see a game mode designed for small groups of people with VoIP.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They tried it with an alternative gamemode, it didn’t last</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 12:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hasnae_El_Idrissi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I enjoy this kind of games too. hope that developpers will add <a href="https://www.bravotelecom.com/en-CA/duo-telephone-internet-residential.php" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">VoIP</a> technology as a feature !</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 08:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Turbo123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="17" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>especially threatening not to back us because of VoIP</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am totally fine with you not adding it, I thought I made myself clear. As the developers you have the design that you want. I am not threatening a thing. I buy a lot of games, if there is something I want not in the game I won’t purchase it. It’s not personal lmao.</p>
<p>Also my post was not to insult the developers. However if what I posted did insult you/them I apologize, I am excited to see what the game has and how you plan to expand on your ideas… But that doesn’t mean I am “in” even for $10 without a feature I feel is so crucial in today’s social mafia games.</p>
<p>I speak in a Teamspeak with 15 people, heck I have joined random Teamspeaks and spoken with 30 people in the same channel… I have had fantastic conversations. There are many systems  you can implement to stop trolls and it’s not nearly as bad as you keep referencing it being… Honestly you act like VoIP is a scary wolf and your players are sheep…</p>
<p>I know it can work and just wanted to give you guys a suggestion. I again as I have stated multiple times wish you guys much luck. I want to see the game succeed and hope to see this feature especially.</p>
<p>P.S. Voice-to-text is a bad idea don’t even say it in jest… Moonbase Alpha…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 17:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-username="JammySplodge" data-post="18" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 JammySplodge:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>"William is Black Rose!"system types “Billy and his sack glows”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>heheh… I think it would be funny – I never said it would be <strong>good</strong>, but optional for those with a good Microphone and for complaining old men that hate to type in video games ;D we can’t satisfy everyone, so the best we can do is offer compromises in some situations. Which may not always be the best solution <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>Realistically I can’t see the voice-to-text coming to life, as this would only be for 1 person, at the moment, that probably won’t play our game <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> but this did make me realize that I should open a “features voting” section one day or throw some polls out later when we have to choose where to focus our resources.</p>
<p>During Alpha we’re just focusing on the core game, but Beta we can bring in some cool stuff.</p>
<p><strong>But back to topic:</strong> So far, our best bet is to have a special game type with VoIP in the future that disables the social type classes until we can find out how to fill the hole. It would also be experimental and could explode <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> This would likely be implemented after release once we get experimental on alternate game modes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Voice to text doesn’t sound like the best idea</p>
<p>“William is Black Rose!”<br>
<em>system types “Billy and his sack glows”</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 11:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Turbo123" data-post="6" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Turbo123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also I’m an old man and hate typing in video games. <span class="hashtag">#GIVEOURFINGERSAREST</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is why I thought of the voice-to-text. For this comment.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Turbo123" data-post="16" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Turbo123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Honestly, you act like it’s 1972 and game design takes years to make something as simple as Pong. Students in college can make it in 15 minutes using the exact engine you’re using</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not only is this insulting to my entire team, but it’s not even that we <em>can’t</em> do it – it’s that we <em>won’t</em> do it – especially threatening not to back us because of VoIP.</p>
<p>This game is simply not meant for 15 players to talk over each other, since there’s already a very limited time to discuss. Not to mention many abilities are tied with social interruptions which simply wouldn’t work. In fact, we have “social” types solely based on chat manipulation and tactics – which would render them all moot and pointless.</p>
<p>Werewolves Within is <strong>designed</strong> for VoIP and has significantly less people per-game – so much that they don’t even have chat. Despite being 2017 and chat being around for years, they won’t add it because, simply, the game was not designed for it: Much like the opposite of our situation.</p>
<p>We already mentioned we would likely later allow it between friends that queue up together. It may even be fun for a sub-faction such as black rose or cult since there would only be a few members talking over each other. However, our team is working hard to satisfy everyone – Want a new feature to be added? It’s not going to be added by speaking ill about the devs. Good luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 11:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Turbo123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I spend hundreds easily on games each year, it isn’t anything to me to drop $60 on a game. My game accounts are filled with fluff that I will never play but once and throw it out with little thought of it… I have been play-testing at EA Tiburon for years now and have found myself in love with the idea of online gaming since 1999…</p>
<p>I know a small bit about every major engine in existence today and have dabbled in them as well, I know for a fact what it takes to implement a VoIP system into a game especially on Unity. I know there are two routes.</p>
<ol>
<li>Make it yourself… YUDODIS?</li>
<li>Use an architecture within the Unity Asset store… Work a week on getting their framework to fit within your net/game code! TADAH!!!</li>
</ol>
<p>A few of the developers make tutorials on their products and how to merge your product with their framework. I know some can work in as little as 15 minutes. (maybe not the most in-depth system or optimized) but a week…</p>
<p>I have heard rumors that the asset Master Server Framework is adding Mumble into their system… Honestly, you act like it’s 1972 and game design takes years to make something as simple as Pong. Students in college can make it in 15 minutes using the exact engine you’re using, I’ve been a huge game dev fan for years and am not asking for the world right now. Just a feature that in my opinion in 2017 is vital for team communication! I am all about indie development and think I have backed enough indie games to be at least a little informed in how you guys can easily make money off of people who thrive to support games just like this one…</p>
<p>But don’t take my indie loyalty for a weakness, I call it as I see it. &amp; there are just too many mafia styled games with not enough 2017 features. It’s honestly sickening to see, it’s like they release a new Call of Duty and NOTHING NEW! EACH TIME! Indie Developers can easily be just as bad as Activision at times… &amp; I am to old not to notice.</p>
<p>Again, I wish you guys well and I really do hope you guys make the Kickstarter. I will definitely check out the game when/if you guys add VoIP as a feature!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 10:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Turbo123" data-post="13" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Turbo123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>VoIP</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hmm I just had a Eureka moment. What about voice to text? That may be a compromise other than a game type standalone.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Turbo123" data-post="13" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Turbo123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but without the 2017 features to back it… It’s kind of lacking in my opinion.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We’re an indie dev seeking only $20k in funding (40% is gone after taxes and fees) asking for only 10 bucks which includes 2 game keys ($5 for the game). We’re not necessarily asking for much <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 06:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Turbo123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Already planning on grabbing Werewolves within as I went into detail on it’s use of Unity and VoIP interaction in my first post. I have followed Throne of Lies for some time now and know exactly what it is about. But just like many other games that are inspired from various other platforms it is unique, but without the 2017 features to back it… It’s kind of lacking in my opinion. I wish you guys well and hope it turns out successful.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Turbo123" data-post="11" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Turbo123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m just trying to show you the game is different but not different enough from other games for many</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree. Realistically, I don’t believe this is the game for you if this is the main thing that’s stopping you:</p>
<p>I encourage you to check out “Werewolves Within” that has the features you desire while being completely different – more different than we personally want to be. We do not plan to implement VoIP until meta-release, if at all.</p>
<p>If that game doesn’t end up being what you are looking for, I encourage you to look again at our <a href="https://tol.wikia.com">Wikia</a> – it’s more different than you may have initially anticipated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 14:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Turbo123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You limiting the game on the statement “99% of the games that support VoIP people don’t use it.” is a problem because I play games ALL the time and most of them support VoIP Comms and oddly enough people use the VoIP a lot. I agree with external applications but lol…</p>
<p>Also B? Really? External programs will allow anyone to cheat without even the slightest bit of risk… People will of course use external apps to cheat, but it’s fine to limit your player-base. I’m just trying to show you the game is different but not different enough from other games for many. It’s the developers choice in the end. glhf</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 01:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Turbo123" data-post="6" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Turbo123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I mean 99% of the games I play today have some form of VoIP… It’s 2017</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>99% the games that support VoIP people don’t even use the in-game integration: usually Discord, Vent, Teamspeak, etc unless on a FPS.</p>
<p>If we had a game of 5 people, sure – but 15 people speaking at once? If we did something like this, it would either</p>
<p>A) Have to be a special game mode</p>
<p>B) Have to be friends chat only – and they’d have to check a box declaring if they cheat they will be punished.</p>
<p>If you <strong>really</strong> want to voice chat during alpha, feel free to setup a game in Discord. I’ll make more voice channels when the time comes.</p>
<p><strong>EDIT:</strong> We definitely have the tech/knowledge to do something with VoIP, btw <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> remind us after alpha. Who knows~</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 12:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Queen_Alfa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And I totally agree with that c:</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 13:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is why a voice-enabled gamemode makes sense.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 23:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Queen_Alfa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What if I do not want to talk? Doesn’t that put me at a disadvantage? While the people voice chatting can chat about stuff quickly I’m stuck typing just because I don’t want others to hear my voice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 23:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Turbo123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You know I’ve been using VoIP’s for well over a decade now and most of the games I play with it implemented the “talking over everyone” thing doesn’t really apply. Believe me, I’ve done my trolling and a simple “Mute” will suffice. I know a lot of people would think, “OH THE AMOUNT OF MIC SPAM AND TROLLING THIS WOULD ALLOW”… Let’s be honest the amount of game throwing that happens in Town of Salem and backstage VoIP uses to try and spoil the game for other people is a rampant issue.</p>
<p>Throne of Lies is unique, but is it unique enough to allow it to survive long enough? I know a lot of games that had something special and failed. I would hate to see the thing that holds this back a possible great feature of the game and a feature that I feel is necessary in many social games be that a Mafia styled game or a tabletop game. I mean 99% of the games I play today have some form of VoIP… It’s 2017. It’s time and arguing that people would talk over each other or everyone would troll… That is as the kids say “So 2007”</p>
<p>Also I’m an old man and hate typing in video games. <span class="hashtag">#GIVEOURFINGERSAREST</span></p>
<p>I’m also excited for the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 20:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Queen_Alfa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="4" data-topic="177">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>voice-enabled gamemode would be a better idea</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with this, maybe a smaller game so everyone isn’t talking over everyone as well cause if you’ve ever been in a friend game of Tos with skype ohhh lordy XD</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 18:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel like a voice-enabled gamemode would be a better idea than having it standard. I would be completely behind this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Voice/VoIP implementation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TeaHacker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for being interested in Throne of Lies! If we hit a high stretch goal on Kickstarter, we can begin development on VR. If we do VR, it might make sense to look into VOIP. I’ll let the devs know about your ideas!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 04:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-177-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/voice-voip-implementation/177.rss">Voice/VoIP implementation</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
