<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921</link>
    <description>This is my third offical version of the PK, it takes some suggestions from @ShadowKnight and @Alice also, so this isn&#39;t all mine. This class has to do with bounding to a target and helping them fulfill their goal. You can also bound with other players to see what they are claiming and to see if they could help you out in anyway

  
&gt;**Ashen Communion (Passive) -** At the start of the game, you will know the identity of all non-NK neutral players. If the NK remains the last neutral alive while you have still not won, then their identity will be revealed to you. 
&gt;
&gt;**Grim Determination (Passive) -** On days where no one die, you gain death immunity that night. You are  immune to occupation, redirection and target changing
&gt;
&gt;**Peace Bond (Day) -**  [Unavailable on Day 1] You will bind yourself to a target player. While bound to that player, you can hear all whispers to and from them. If they are neutral then all whispers will be hidden from the public. You may only be bound to one player at a time and you will only be unbounded on their death or if you change to a new target.- [Infinite uses]
&gt;
&gt;**Peace treaty (Day) -** Give your bounded target an extra use of all of their abilities, this includes day abilities. If they are a _[color=Grey ]Mercanary [/color]_ or a _[color=grey]Sellsword[/color]_ they will gain night immunity for the night. - [2 uses]
&gt;
&gt;**Showing your true colors (night) -** Visit a player. If they are Neutral, they will be healed and protected from negative effects. If your target is immune for this night, then the ability cost is refunded. - [4 uses]
&gt;
&gt;**Conspire (Night) -**  [Unavailable before Night 2]. Create a group chat between yourself and a bonded player. - [Infinite uses]
&gt;
&gt;**Win Conditions -**  help _2_ other neutral players complete their goals or win with the NK

&gt;**Bonus gold** - If you achieved your goal by helping 2 neutral players win then any other neutral player you help achieve their goal, you will gain 25 gold at the end of the game.


Questions that you could answer for this class:

1 - will this be a good class to play along with in the game?
2 - will you have fun playing this class?
3 - do you think this class is too overpowered or too underpowered?
4 - do you think this class will change the game in a positive or negative way?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 17:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>changed win con to help PK win more</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 17:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NosduhYons]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I see more what you mean now, of having neutrals win at their goals. Sorry I took it the wrong way, I was just confused with the term helping. If this is not what you mean, please clarify as I don’t want to take it the wrong way.</p>
<p>As for creating a post for a class suggestion, I may create a version of this with my ideas, I just don’t know if it would be different enough. It would mainly be just a change in the way you have a different win con and you get charges of the abilities from the class you chose. As I think about it more though, on its current state, it would need heavy changes to fit in a place in the game. That may make it different enough I want to make a separate post about. I may just do it anyways because it is a good exercise to see why certain things are on certain classes. Thank you very much for the suggestion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 21:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NosduhYons" data-post="5" data-topic="72921">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nosduhyons/40/4443_2.png" class="avatar"> NosduhYons:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I like the idea of having a person protect neutrals, but the goal of helping neutral players complete their goal can’t really be determined,</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with everything else you said except this. If a fool is executed then the game recognizes that a neutral has completed their goal. If 4 people are executed then the scorn wins along with the PK. But i want to hear your version of the PK. Could you make a new post about it with your idea for abilities and win con because i would like to see your version too</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 14:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NosduhYons]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right now since it itself takes up a neutral slot, there can be 2-3 other neutrals, 1 being NK. If one dies early, you either have a hard game getting the remaining ones or it is completely impossible to win. It would also be very hard to define helping a neutral achieve their goal, does that mean just voting execute on a fool? How could you help scorned if their goal is to kill people on the stand? I like the idea of having a person protect neutrals, but the goal of helping neutral players complete their goal can’t really be determined, especially for some neutrals, like scorned. I saw in earlier drafts that you had neutrals accepting your goal, but what if it was the other way around? What if in the very beginning you chose from the neutrals in the game and adopted their goal instead (Probably not including the NK.) You would get a certain amount of uses of all of their abilities (Day and night) and the game could track your progress together. For example, if you adopted the Fool’s goal, as soon as one of you was executed, you would win. Instead of choosing to bond with someone, the person’s goal you chose would be the one you were bonded with. You would still have peace treaty and conspire, with less charges of Showing your true colors or none at all. Then though, it isn’t really a peacekeeper anymore, maybe just a follower or something. No matter if you take my changes into consideration, right now it is just too hard to win as and doesn’t really have a defined objective. You also need to keep in mind that one of the main reasons Mercenary was changed was that it was too amplifying to NK or Cult/Unseen because it was basically just another number in their forces. It was unfun to play against and made mercenaries too powerful to evils and most of the time underwhelming to BDs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 02:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Planterror]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="72921">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Win Conditions -</strong> help <em>2</em> other neutral players complete their goals</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>TMW there’s only 2 neut spawns</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>People take brakes for a bit</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 23:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whatever happened to shadow he disappeared</p>
<p>He hasn’t been online since July</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 23:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is my third offical version of the PK, it takes some suggestions from <a class="mention" href="/u/shadowknight">@ShadowKnight</a> and <a class="mention" href="/u/alice">@Alice</a> also, so this isn’t all mine. This class has to do with bounding to a target and helping them fulfill their goal. You can also bound with other players to see what they are claiming and to see if they could help you out in anyway</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Ashen Communion (Passive) -</strong> At the start of the game, you will know the identity of all non-NK neutral players. If the NK remains the last neutral alive while you have still not won, then their identity will be revealed to you.</p>
<p><strong>Grim Determination (Passive) -</strong> On days where no one die, you gain death immunity that night. You are  immune to occupation, redirection and target changing</p>
<p><strong>Peace Bond (Day) -</strong>  [Unavailable on Day 1] You will bind yourself to a target player. While bound to that player, you can hear all whispers to and from them. If they are neutral then all whispers will be hidden from the public. You may only be bound to one player at a time and you will only be unbounded on their death or if you change to a new target.- [Infinite uses]</p>
<p><strong>Peace treaty (Day) -</strong> Give your bounded target an extra use of all of their abilities, this includes day abilities. If they are a <em><font color="Grey">Mercanary </font></em> or a <em><font color="grey">Sellsword</font></em> they will gain night immunity for the night. - [2 uses]</p>
<p><strong>Showing your true colors (night) -</strong> Visit a player. If they are Neutral, they will be healed and protected from negative effects. If your target is immune for this night, then the ability cost is refunded. - [4 uses]</p>
<p><strong>Conspire (Night) -</strong>  [Unavailable before Night 2]. Create a group chat between yourself and a bonded player. - [Infinite uses]</p>
<p><strong>Win Conditions -</strong>  help <em>2</em> other neutral players complete their goals or win with the NK</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Bonus gold</strong> - If you achieved your goal by helping 2 neutral players win then any other neutral player you help achieve their goal, you will gain 25 gold at the end of the game.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Questions that you could answer for this class:</p>
<p>1 - will this be a good class to play along with in the game?<br>
2 - will you have fun playing this class?<br>
3 - do you think this class is too overpowered or too underpowered?<br>
4 - do you think this class will change the game in a positive or negative way?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 23:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72921-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-peace-keeper-v-3/72921.rss">[Class suggestion] Peace Keeper V.3</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
