<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348</link>
    <description>I come from Epic mafia, where the way the game work is different. Its instead pre determined setups where you know exactly all roles in the game. In that game, pro players often post an optimal strategy for each setups. It is often based on finding 1 person who is &quot;clear&quot;, and getting everyone to claim to him.

I decided to attempt to post what i believe is the best strategy for blue dragon in this game. Of course, i&#39;m not saying to go out there and try this out in real games. I believe right now, most players are too new for this to ever work. But here it is:

Day1:
Priest claims. If there is a counter claim, King is charged with investigating one of the 2 claims. He should be able to tell who is fake (and quite honneslty, even as fool, counter claiming the priest is a terrible strategy, i don&#39;t expect people to counter claim).

Night 1:

Knights defend King. Physicians/alch defend priest.

Day 2:

Once the priest is uncced, everyone claims to him, with full logs. This part is difficult for priest because with only 90 seconds it might be hard for him to fully build his whole log. But believe with full day 2 and night 2, he should have a pretty clear picture of whats going on.

He most likely can clear 1 person with Prince. 1 Person with king&#39;s report. 1-2 person with investigative class. MAybe have 3 claims of the same role, etc.

Ideally, the priest should lynch whoever he thinks is the most suspicious. For example, someone that refused to claim. he can also ask Prince to jail someone. He should also order all investigative class including king on who to investigate so they dont investigate clear people, or the same people.

All of this is quite hard to do in a single day, and i fullly expect priest to make some mistakes. Its ok not to execute on day 2 and focus on building a solid information base. Priest also has the full night to continue doing this

Day 3:

By now, the priest should have a really clear picture of who initial cult/unseen were. From there, he should pretty much use the execution every single day. With the large information he has, it should be easy to execute with at least 50% chance not to exe a BD member. If we take a look at possible fake claims:

Drunk: Absolutly suicidal to fake claim this. Priest will eventually be able to easily tell you are fake.

Princess: Priest knows all classes. You are bound to make a mistake eventually.

Noble: Worst fake claim ever. Priest can easily verify if your real or not.

Butler: Similar to drunk, really hard to fake since priest get every reports every days.

Court Wizard: Decent claim, but since priest has all reports, might get caught.

Essentially, the 2 best claims are physician and Knight, but not everyone can claim this!


Overall, i think this strategy is great for the following reasons:

1: It makes sure investigative roles dont waste investigation on the same people, or on already cleared people

2: It makes sure the person with the info isn&#39;t a neutral king or an evil king. You almost negate evil king from doing anything. You know the dude handling the info is blue dragon.

3: Priest cannot be converted and will be really hard to kill.

4: You make full use of the BD&#39;s greatest strenght: Executing. I see too often indecisive blue dragons with no real leader do nothing several days in a row until too many people are converted. Here, we know priest is able to do good executions every single day. Its better to execute one of the few unclear blue dragons and be wrong than wait forever and have to face 4 cult members.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 19:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floofyboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I did it again and actually found a plot hole. There was a merc in the game, so he outted me. Some of them understood i was noble, but a lot of people accused me of “fool”. Then i died to a reaper…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 19:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floofyboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Decent point NuclearBurrito, but i feel like the % of the games where the baddies have access to an aristocrat isn’t that high. And the drawback isn’t that insane either.</p>
<p>“The empowered cult wouldn’t kill a priest if the phys is on him. Or is this comment outdated?”</p>
<p>Good question</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 19:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I find that thi biggest weakness that this strategy has is the aristocrat. The noble is probably smart enough to spy the Priest and build his own similar logs, the only difference is that the Noble is convertible so he can out everyone’s roles to the unseen/cult and knows what everyone does as long as the priest is alive. From there you have a huge advantage as the unseen can now claim any invest classes and the aristocrat can reveal what he finds in real time with private matter to support the unseen/cults fake claims.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The empowered cult wouldn’t kill a priest if the phys is on him. Or is this comment outdated?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floofyboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re unfortunatly right. I didn’t think of those holes. This means the game is better designed than i thought <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 07:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Really interesting and all but what about the Reaper’s Icy Touch that can stop the priest from hearing anything for two full days? Or an empowered cult or reaper attack? This strategy still has a lot of weaknesses.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 05:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floofyboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>lol damn. true xD</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 05:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cult empower kill Priest night one.GG</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 04:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floofyboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I come from Epic mafia, where the way the game work is different. Its instead pre determined setups where you know exactly all roles in the game. In that game, pro players often post an optimal strategy for each setups. It is often based on finding 1 person who is “clear”, and getting everyone to claim to him.</p>
<p>I decided to attempt to post what i believe is the best strategy for blue dragon in this game. Of course, i’m not saying to go out there and try this out in real games. I believe right now, most players are too new for this to ever work. But here it is:</p>
<p>Day1:<br>
Priest claims. If there is a counter claim, King is charged with investigating one of the 2 claims. He should be able to tell who is fake (and quite honneslty, even as fool, counter claiming the priest is a terrible strategy, i don’t expect people to counter claim).</p>
<p>Night 1:</p>
<p>Knights defend King. Physicians/alch defend priest.</p>
<p>Day 2:</p>
<p>Once the priest is uncced, everyone claims to him, with full logs. This part is difficult for priest because with only 90 seconds it might be hard for him to fully build his whole log. But believe with full day 2 and night 2, he should have a pretty clear picture of whats going on.</p>
<p>He most likely can clear 1 person with Prince. 1 Person with king’s report. 1-2 person with investigative class. MAybe have 3 claims of the same role, etc.</p>
<p>Ideally, the priest should lynch whoever he thinks is the most suspicious. For example, someone that refused to claim. he can also ask Prince to jail someone. He should also order all investigative class including king on who to investigate so they dont investigate clear people, or the same people.</p>
<p>All of this is quite hard to do in a single day, and i fullly expect priest to make some mistakes. Its ok not to execute on day 2 and focus on building a solid information base. Priest also has the full night to continue doing this</p>
<p>Day 3:</p>
<p>By now, the priest should have a really clear picture of who initial cult/unseen were. From there, he should pretty much use the execution every single day. With the large information he has, it should be easy to execute with at least 50% chance not to exe a BD member. If we take a look at possible fake claims:</p>
<p>Drunk: Absolutly suicidal to fake claim this. Priest will eventually be able to easily tell you are fake.</p>
<p>Princess: Priest knows all classes. You are bound to make a mistake eventually.</p>
<p>Noble: Worst fake claim ever. Priest can easily verify if your real or not.</p>
<p>Butler: Similar to drunk, really hard to fake since priest get every reports every days.</p>
<p>Court Wizard: Decent claim, but since priest has all reports, might get caught.</p>
<p>Essentially, the 2 best claims are physician and Knight, but not everyone can claim this!</p>
<p>Overall, i think this strategy is great for the following reasons:</p>
<p>1: It makes sure investigative roles dont waste investigation on the same people, or on already cleared people</p>
<p>2: It makes sure the person with the info isn’t a neutral king or an evil king. You almost negate evil king from doing anything. You know the dude handling the info is blue dragon.</p>
<p>3: Priest cannot be converted and will be really hard to kill.</p>
<p>4: You make full use of the BD’s greatest strenght: Executing. I see too often indecisive blue dragons with no real leader do nothing several days in a row until too many people are converted. Here, we know priest is able to do good executions every single day. Its better to execute one of the few unclear blue dragons and be wrong than wait forever and have to face 4 cult members.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 03:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8348-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/optimal-blue-dragon-strategy/8348.rss">Optimal Blue dragon Strategy</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
