<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404</link>
    <description>**Trader** (Neutral Social) - A kingdom-hopping peddler of assorted goods... and evils?

Passive 1:
**The Customer is Always Right** - You will win with anyone you have successfully sold to using your &quot;Vigor&quot; ability. _(In other words, if you sell to someone in Cult AND someone in BD, you will win with either one - but if Neutral Killing wins, you lose. Similarly, if you sell to Neutral Killing and no one else, you can ONLY win with the Neutral Killer. And so on.)_

Day Ability:
**Blacklist** - Selected player will be &#39;prevented&#39; from visiting you on any future night. (2 uses.)

Night Ability 1:
**Vigor** - Offer to sell someone a VERY potent elixir, giving them multiple immunities for that night only. The moment you choose to offer it to a player, they will receive a popup asking if they want to purchase it. This simply allows them to accept/decline your offer, no real transfer of any &quot;payment&quot; occurs. You can sell to the same person multiple times. (4 uses.)

Effects of Vigor if accepted:
- Gives block immunity.
- Gives target swap immunity.
- Gives murder immunity.
_This is very powerful on purpose._

Night Ability 2:
**Snake Oil** - Offer to sell someone a fake elixir with multiple negative effects for that night only. Works the same as &quot;Vigor&quot; in terms of accept/decline popup. Needless to say, target isn&#39;t told which one you&#39;re offering, just that they have the offer. (2 uses.)

Effects of Snake Oil if accepted:
- Remove any block immunity.
- Remove any target swap immunity.
- Remove any murder immunity.
_This is obnoxious on purpose. XD_

----

**Comments:** I know people will likely hate this, but... you know. I like it, so I figured it was worth a shot. Trader would ideally sell to someone, and then try to help that person win. Ideally, he should cover his bases and sell to as many factions as he can find, however... ;)

Reasons to accept the Trader&#39;s offer:
- The immunities, duh.
- He may sell to you again if you accept.
- You get Trader on your side.

Reason to decline the Trader&#39;s offer:
- You might lose your class&#39; immunity.
- He may have made an agreement with a previous buyer to betray you.

If absolutely necessary, the popup could be removed and the Trader could just force-sell to people. I like the interactive aspect, though.

Alternate name: Merchant?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 21:55:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also, I now realize (a day late) “Cure-All” sounds like it would cure poison/bleeding, which may confuse players. Maybe a better name would be “Vigor Elixir” or something equally open-ended.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 21:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39404-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404.rss">[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Class doesn’t have to survive to win, has to sell to the faction that wins. (Sell to a BD, Cult, Unseen, NK, etc. Whichever one ends up winning. Needs to cover his bases.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 21:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39404-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404.rss">[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Reasons to sell Snake Oil:<br>
1.) Someone is “Neuts Out” and you don’t want them finding and killing you.<br>
2.) Someone is specifically trying to vote you. (Not believing you or whatever reason.)<br>
3.) Someone isn’t accepting your Cure-All and you’re worried they’re not part of your factions.<br>
4.) Someone finds out you’re Trader and demands you do it for them. (Sucks, but a reason.)<br>
5.) Someone finds out you’re Trader immediately and says “sell all Cure-Alls to ME or die.”<br>
6.) You’re out of sales and believe/know the target isn’t part of your factions.<br>
7.) You’re out of sales, and want to fool someone into thinking you sold them a Cure-All so they think you’re on their side.</p>
<p>(Naturally, you’d likely be telling someone you sold to that you’re clearing they way for them to do something to your Snake Oil target. Alternately, in endgame, you’d reasonably know they’d have a high chance of being attacked/blocked/etc. that night.)</p>
<p>I could come up with more reasons if pressed to, but those would be the most realistic and the rest would be more “out there”. XD</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 21:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39404-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404.rss">[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Does this class have to survive to the end to win? If so he’ll need more survive-ability in my opinion. Possibly be able to use Cure-All on himself and give it more uses? Do the people that have been sold Cure-All have to survive until the end?</p>
<p>Does Blacklist work on king? Does Cure-All/Snake Oil work on king?</p>
<p>It looks way more like a support type than a social type in my opinion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 11:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39404-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404.rss">[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why would the trader use snake oil when giving a cure all to every faction means he wins?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39404-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404.rss">[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Trader</strong> (Neutral Social) - A kingdom-hopping peddler of assorted goods… and evils?</p>
<p>Passive 1:<br>
<strong>The Customer is Always Right</strong> - You will win with anyone you have successfully sold to using your “Vigor” ability. <em>(In other words, if you sell to someone in Cult AND someone in BD, you will win with either one - but if Neutral Killing wins, you lose. Similarly, if you sell to Neutral Killing and no one else, you can ONLY win with the Neutral Killer. And so on.)</em></p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Blacklist</strong> - Selected player will be ‘prevented’ from visiting you on any future night. (2 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Vigor</strong> - Offer to sell someone a VERY potent elixir, giving them multiple immunities for that night only. The moment you choose to offer it to a player, they will receive a popup asking if they want to purchase it. This simply allows them to accept/decline your offer, no real transfer of any “payment” occurs. You can sell to the same person multiple times. (4 uses.)</p>
<p>Effects of Vigor if accepted:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gives block immunity.</li>
<li>Gives target swap immunity.</li>
<li>Gives murder immunity.<br>
<em>This is very powerful on purpose.</em>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Snake Oil</strong> - Offer to sell someone a fake elixir with multiple negative effects for that night only. Works the same as “Vigor” in terms of accept/decline popup. Needless to say, target isn’t told which one you’re offering, just that they have the offer. (2 uses.)</p>
<p>Effects of Snake Oil if accepted:</p>
<ul>
<li>Remove any block immunity.</li>
<li>Remove any target swap immunity.</li>
<li>Remove any murder immunity.<br>
<em>This is obnoxious on purpose. XD</em>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong> I know people will likely hate this, but… you know. I like it, so I figured it was worth a shot. Trader would ideally sell to someone, and then try to help that person win. Ideally, he should cover his bases and sell to as many factions as he can find, however… <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Reasons to accept the Trader’s offer:</p>
<ul>
<li>The immunities, duh.</li>
<li>He may sell to you again if you accept.</li>
<li>You get Trader on your side.</li>
</ul>
<p>Reason to decline the Trader’s offer:</p>
<ul>
<li>You might lose your class’ immunity.</li>
<li>He may have made an agreement with a previous buyer to betray you.</li>
</ul>
<p>If absolutely necessary, the popup could be removed and the Trader could just force-sell to people. I like the interactive aspect, though.</p>
<p>Alternate name: Merchant?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 06:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39404-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-trader-neutral-social/39404.rss">[Class Suggestion] Trader (Neutral Social)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
