<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>In game player profiles</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482</link>
    <description>it would be nice for everybody to have a player profile, that you can access in game. First of all customizing a player profile is always fun. Secondly here are the benefits viewing a player&#39;s profile in game would be helpful:

1. See their amount of games played. This is the biggest reason I want this. Claiming new player shouldn&#39;t be a &quot;tactic&quot; for evil king etc. and if somebody appears to be making bad decisions or throwing, being able to see their games played and seeing that they ARE new would prompt you to help them learn instead of getting upset. It&#39;s just nice info to know for sure. 

2. Customizable &quot;play style&quot; option. Looking for friends to play with that are talkative? quiet and serious? Other play styles that might be similar to yours? Choose your play style or personality or whatever for your profile and check others and find friends that will click with you. (I explained that awful but the idea is nice)

3. If you could get medals from getting positive feedback for being nice or helpful or team oriented etc that would decorate your profile, that is a huge incentive for people to behave nicely in game. Yes that idea was inspired by LoL&#39;s positive feedback system but I feel it does work. Or at least doesn&#39;t hurt. 

Can&#39;t think of other things that an in game viewable profile would be good for right this second but i guarantee if you&#39;re reading this you can think of some and should comment with your ideas. My big thing is being able to see games played for the reasons I listed.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 19:55:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>In game player profiles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or for knight/phys they’d be the person to protect!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 19:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8482-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482.rss">In game player profiles</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In game player profiles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>parts of me like the idea of playing with similar players to myself but I do wonder if in the end only playing with certain types of players would take the shine of the game .<br>
I can do without the idiot game throwers but most other player types are interesting to play with</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 19:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8482-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482.rss">In game player profiles</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In game player profiles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seeing how many hours ppl have in game would result in all the players with lots of hours being killed first every time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 18:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8482-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482.rss">In game player profiles</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In game player profiles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Id worry about stepping away from the evil king claiming newb defence and heading towards the . Listen to me I’ve got 1000 games meta .</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8482-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482.rss">In game player profiles</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In game player profiles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would assume this is the type of stuff coming as they continue to iterate on the game.</p>
<p>The social stuff is rather bare bones as the company continues to build on the game.</p>
<p>In the future, I’d be interested in knowing my win rate, win rate with certain factions, certain classes. Etc.</p>
<p>Leaderboards would be cool too.</p>
<p>Who’s the best fool, etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 21:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8482-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482.rss">In game player profiles</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In game player profiles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it would be nice for everybody to have a player profile, that you can access in game. First of all customizing a player profile is always fun. Secondly here are the benefits viewing a player’s profile in game would be helpful:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>See their amount of games played. This is the biggest reason I want this. Claiming new player shouldn’t be a “tactic” for evil king etc. and if somebody appears to be making bad decisions or throwing, being able to see their games played and seeing that they ARE new would prompt you to help them learn instead of getting upset. It’s just nice info to know for sure.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Customizable “play style” option. Looking for friends to play with that are talkative? quiet and serious? Other play styles that might be similar to yours? Choose your play style or personality or whatever for your profile and check others and find friends that will click with you. (I explained that awful but the idea is nice)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If you could get medals from getting positive feedback for being nice or helpful or team oriented etc that would decorate your profile, that is a huge incentive for people to behave nicely in game. Yes that idea was inspired by LoL’s positive feedback system but I feel it does work. Or at least doesn’t hurt.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Can’t think of other things that an in game viewable profile would be good for right this second but i guarantee if you’re reading this you can think of some and should comment with your ideas. My big thing is being able to see games played for the reasons I listed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 16:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-8482-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/in-game-player-profiles/8482.rss">In game player profiles</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
