<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460</link>
    <description>I used Paint.. And apparently there is this thing called Paint 3d aswell..
Anyway, to the point ! 

Everything stays pretty much the same as it is right now. The only difference is, we get more info from the start. We know who&#39;s cult/unseen, we know the DK and so on so. The reason to knowing this is : We want to see what abilities they are planning to use.. And where. I&#39;ve made a small example, I realise later on that I probably should have use the graveyard as a background but it&#39;s just the idea that I want to be posted. 
https://imgur.com/a/DcLc2

Also, for us spectators, we want to read the logbooks. Have them available for us all the time!

If the spectator mode should be something to use in game or not who knows. But it should (could) be used in tournaments. Where casters wouldn&#39;t have to be in the game but spectating from the sideline.

Should this be top priority? Absolutely not. But I think it&#39;d be great if we got something like it in the future. 

Thanks for taking your time trying to read through my horribly written suggestion!
/tiny</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 18:34:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tinyneut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yea, it’d be mainly for custom games and tournaments. Public games, maybe not…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 18:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I believe their intention for the “private spectator”. in closed matches, is that he’s an all seeing eye. IE he see’s everything. The intent of it is for say tournaments etc… to which the “private spectator” serves as the announcer etc… most likely recording the game for the purpose of uploading it to be watched and reviewed by others later.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 16:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What would private spectators be able to do?</p>
<p>I would suggest that spectators should be able to see from the perspective of the person that invited them (unless specified otherwise in the invite)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally I’d be in favor of 2 spectator modes. 1 usable only in closed private tournaments etc…</p>
<p>and one mode for public games and live streamers. availible to pop into any games, both by invites (again for streamers who wish to snipe proof their games) as well as just whim (IE you hit spectate random game, and it just pops you into whatever game is about to start as a spectator only).</p>
<p>Public spectator mode – This mode shows no classes. Nothing that isn’t visible to every player in the game… Camera fades to an empty court room in the night phase, and of course shows none of the night chats at all.</p>
<p>Public spectator mode would be good for people who say want to work on their scumreading skills… but aren’t sure if they have the time for a full game etc…</p>
<p>As well as streamers, as they can set up their stream to show the game in spectator mode on a different computer (or monitor if the dev’s rig it to do that).</p>
<p>Again I’d emphasize that public spectators, would get absolutely NO information that everyone else at the table doesn’t have in front of them… They see the same public journals etc… (I do suppose the one area of cheating that would be unavoidable, is that through spectator mode, someone could see a trollboxed message from themselves, as obviously the spectator would err more on the side of one of the 15 players noting it’s absense, rather than the 1 player happening to know.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Custom games only, invite only would be my requirements for a spectator mode.</p>
<p><strong>/support</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 14:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Spectator should only spectate after the game has ended.</p>
<p>It is just a cheat harmony for those cheater.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 13:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This should only be for custom games though - it could be used to cheat on live games.</p>
<p>As long as that is met, <strong>/support</strong>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 11:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spectator mode suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tinyneut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I used Paint… And apparently there is this thing called Paint 3d aswell…<br>
Anyway, to the point !</p>
<p>Everything stays pretty much the same as it is right now. The only difference is, we get more info from the start. We know who’s cult/unseen, we know the DK and so on so. The reason to knowing this is : We want to see what abilities they are planning to use… And where. I’ve made a small example, I realise later on that I probably should have use the graveyard as a background but it’s just the idea that I want to be posted.<br>
<a href="https://imgur.com/a/DcLc2" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://imgur.com/a/DcLc2</a></p>
<p>Also, for us spectators, we want to read the logbooks. Have them available for us all the time!</p>
<p>If the spectator mode should be something to use in game or not who knows. But it should (could) be used in tournaments. Where casters wouldn’t have to be in the game but spectating from the sideline.</p>
<p>Should this be top priority? Absolutely not. But I think it’d be great if we got something like it in the future.</p>
<p>Thanks for taking your time trying to read through my horribly written suggestion!<br>
/tiny</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 10:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39460-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/spectator-mode-suggestion/39460.rss">Spectator mode suggestion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
