<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Discussion - Forum of Lies</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/c/forum-matches/fol-discussion/16</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Discussion&#39; category </description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:51:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/c/forum-matches/fol-discussion/16.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>BotC / BotF Discussion</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>  </p>
            <p><small>178 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botc-botf-discussion/88754">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botc-botf-discussion/88754</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88754</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/botc-botf-discussion/88754.rss">BotC / BotF Discussion</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Interest Check: Life of the Party</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would people join a misc with 3d inspection mechanics and like actual distance consideration for things like throwing and also hopefully lighting mechanics additionally on the inspection mechanics so when the lights are off the actual image is dimmed too<br>
I’ve designed two rooms so far and just want to see what people think before I actually commit to making a mansion in 3d<br>
They’re definitely not pretty and the main hall is subject to change but meh w/e it’s just a preview<br>
Current plan is to have “heretics” run around the mansion with secret passages and other players (the partygoers) to try and find a way out or otherwise defeat the heretics in some way</p>
<p>                    <a href="https://i.imgur.com/ZRQZXNv.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://i.imgur.com/ZRQZXNv.png" width="690" height="381">
          </a>

</p>
<p>If the player closer inspects the bookshelves:</p>
<p>                    <a href="https://i.imgur.com/ovTfPsP.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://i.imgur.com/ovTfPsP.png" width="690" height="381">
          </a>

</p>
            <p><small>37 posts - 16 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-life-of-the-party/88737">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-life-of-the-party/88737</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 18:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88737</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-life-of-the-party/88737.rss">Interest Check: Life of the Party</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Murder Mystery Smalltown</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>
<a name="after-the-tepid-reception-of-big-town-mash-i-have-decided-to-experiment-with-the-formula-a-bit-this-is-the-result-1" class="anchor" href="#after-the-tepid-reception-of-big-town-mash-i-have-decided-to-experiment-with-the-formula-a-bit-this-is-the-result-1"></a>after the tepid reception of big town mash I have decided to experiment with the formula a bit, this is the result</h4>
<p>Two teams</p>
<p>Guilty (informed minority, included Accomplices and the Culprit)</p>
<p>Innocent (Uninformed Majority)</p>
<p>There is a <strong>Culprit</strong>: The host decides how they are determined, and it is announced at the start of the game.</p>
<p>α: Culprit is picked by the Accomplices at pre-game, and they do not join scum chat</p>
<p>β: The host randomly picks the culprit along with the Accomplices, the culprit joins scum chat.</p>
<p>γ: 3 accomplices are randed, they decide amongst themselves which of them they would like to be the Culprit</p>
<p>Guilty Players win if they reach parity with the Innocents with the Culprit alive</p>
<p>Innocent players win if the Culprit dies</p>
<p><strong>Roles:</strong></p>
<p>2 Neighbours</p>
<p>1-Shot Reviver (a revived player will not have their alignment learned by the Coroner the night they died, the game will not end if an accomplice Reviver still has a use of their ability)</p>
<p>Strongman Ninja Doctor</p>
<p>Alien</p>
<p>2-shot commuter</p>
<p>Redirector</p>
<p>Coroner</p>
<p>Even-Night Bus Driver</p>
<p>Roleblocker</p>
<p>Tree Stump</p>
<p>Universal Backup (will inherit all shots of abilities)</p>
<p><strong>Events:</strong></p>
<p>Events are similar to mash events, at least one will happen in a game. No events will cause deaths (no B O A T S sorry for the disappointment )</p>
<p>Event prizes will be one shot of one of these possible abilities:</p>
<p>Watch</p>
<p>Track</p>
<p>Vigilante</p>
<p>Cop</p>
<p>Ninja</p>
<p>Strongman Vigilante</p>
<p>Bus Drive</p>
<p>Redirect</p>
<p>Roleblock</p>
<p>Poison (can be healed by doctor)</p>
<p>Doctor</p>
<p>Jailkeep</p>
<p>Commute</p>
<p>Events and event prizes are predetermined at the start of the game. Events will be announced either at End of Day or at the Start of Day, events can be submitted doing whatever is necessary to enter in your class card.</p>
            <p><small>42 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/murder-mystery-smalltown/88482">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/murder-mystery-smalltown/88482</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 02:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88482</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/murder-mystery-smalltown/88482.rss">Murder Mystery Smalltown</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Bigtown mash discussion oh god oh fuck</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Roleblocker</p>
<p>Jailkeeper</p>
<p>Tracker</p>
<p>Watcher</p>
<p>Doctor</p>
<p>Beholder</p>
<p>Alien</p>
<p>Neighbourizer</p>
<p>Arsonist</p>
<p>Redirector</p>
<p>^ these roles get an odd and even cycle copy each</p>
<p>1-shot vigilante</p>
<p>universal backup</p>
<p>Bus Driver</p>
<p>Coroner</p>
<p>Death Vanillizer (if you die you publicly vanillize a player)</p>
<p>^ these are all ungated roles, there’s only one of each</p>
<p>I want to make a big town mash, these roles all kinds suck. I want some feedback</p>
            <p><small>17 posts - 9 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bigtown-mash-discussion-oh-god-oh-fuck/88462">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bigtown-mash-discussion-oh-god-oh-fuck/88462</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 16:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88462</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bigtown-mash-discussion-oh-god-oh-fuck/88462.rss">Bigtown mash discussion oh god oh fuck</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Trying (and failing) to fix d6 mafia</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <div align="center">
<h1>
<a name="setup-design-is-my-passion-1" class="anchor" href="#setup-design-is-my-passion-1"></a>Setup Design is My Passion</h1>
</div>
<hr>
<p><strong>Why are you trying to do this?</strong></p>
<p>20% Spite<br>
80% Tangent</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Introduction to the Problems that are D6 Mafia</strong></p>
<div align="center">
<img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/669045121555103760/865135626679222292/c0e98e26214a1b0998f6e66a1906e433b4e95372.png" width="690" height="229">
<img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/8/3/830e50b75a611ec26e957b84072a4d813e08de6c.png" width="212" height="268">
</div>
<p>This is often run as a Light or Newbie setup, which means that roughly optimal numbers will be a tad bit more townsided than setups looking for pure balance.</p>
<p>Premises:</p>
<ul>
<li>3 PR rands are significantly stronger for town when compared to 2 (or 1) PR rands.</li>
<li>Mafia rands where they have 1+ of Roleblocker/Jailkeeper are disproportionately stronger than rands where they do not. This is especially so in 3 PR rands.</li>
</ul>
<p>A potential justification for statement 1 could be that an additional claimable role is often worth significantly more than the slight power increase roles get (which is not properly counterbalanced by the additional scum PR in 3 PR rands). It gives an additional clear and some form of utility, however minimal.</p>
<p>A potential justification for statement 2 would be in terms of action economy. The factional killl does not render most PRs useless for the night, except for those in the investigative column (assuming the kill actually goes through). As a result, scum without a roleblocker/jailkeeper have little counterplay for any attempts by the villagers to make night plans or FtC strategies. Even if villagers do not make specific plans, a lack of counterplay means that openly being a PR without a scum roleblocker/jailkeeper often will not impact your mechanical relevance.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Methodology to Improve the Setup:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Improve some rands that are guaranteed to be 2 (or 1) PR setups to be slightly stronger.*</li>
<li>Rework scum PR system.</li>
</ol>
<p>*- Outside of specific instances such as Role Cop being significantly stronger than contemporaries in most situations potentially justifying a nerf, nerfing the lower value town roles may prove to be volatile to the setup due to how many interactions they would have with the overall setup.</p>
<p>Guaranteed 2 (or 1) PR setups:<br>
5I (+ 1P or 1K)<br>
6I<br>
6P<br>
6K</p>
<ul>
<li>5I (Tracker) is at a strange impasse where it either has significant power or is nearly useless. It cannot get standard greenpeeks on players until there is only one remaining member of the scumteam alive, and even at that point its previous checks mean very little unless it hit a member of the scumteam either doing the factional or their PR performing an action. This, alongside the fact that the scum PR can choose to holster, puts this role on a similar power level to Role Cop overall. Role Cop has an even higher scaling potential due to its previous checks being useful if scum PR(s) are the only scum alive. I’d compare it to JOAT^2, but in that setup scum aren’t nearly as guaranteed to have counterplay as they do here.</li>
<li>6I is horribly weak. Scum know what PR is in game when it rands. To be better than the base power level of a 3 PR rand, not counting potential utility offered by the various PRs, the PC needs to live until D4. That’s kind of ridiculous.</li>
<li>6P is around the same power level of 5P while not having the additional PR that 5P gets. The best case scenario is both PRs living to the point where there is only one scum left alive and the scum PR is either dead or an investigative (wow investigative scum kind of suck here, who would have thought).</li>
<li>6K is only marginally better than 5K at a strict power comparison and also doesn’t have the additional PR.</li>
</ul>
<p>Potential solutions:</p>
<ul>
<li>6I is pretty simple. We can either go the route of making the role a normal Cop (with or without N0), or we can make 6I two different investigative roles. It could be Voyeur/Inno  Child + Tracker. It could be Voyeur/Inno Child + Role Cop. It could even be MoDet + MoDet (which is a little silly). We could even use roles outside of the current setup.</li>
<li>Making 6P into Jailkeeper + Doctor seems to be the natural move. The doctor could have some form of gating, but since scum are getting a PR regardless there’s the possibility that it might be ~fine as is.</li>
<li>6K is a weird one given that, since the setup is automated, it needs to be roles that work via modbot. As a result, I’m going to take a risk and say Vigilante + Vengeful. Vengeful is an extremely strong role. While it is a bit unfun to play against, it may just be worth it to go through with it.</li>
<li>5I is weird and I don’t have an exact fix. It might just be worth it to have the role break step with the rest of the setup by being a JOAT, or do the dumb thing and make the role a weaker cop-like role.</li>
</ul>
<p>Scum Changes:</p>
<p>For scum, I might want to change how randing works. In setups where there are 3 PRs, scum will be guaranteed a scum manipulative (either roleblocker or jailkeeper) by rolling from a specialized wheel for their first PR. The randing for the second PR will operate as normal (I’m a bit uncertain on this one).</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Why is this a thread?:</strong></p>
<p>Mainly due to not being sure which options should be taken for the 2 PR setups and the scum randing. Thus, I wanted to open up discussion for that.</p>
            <p><small>26 posts - 8 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/trying-and-failing-to-fix-d6-mafia/88343">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/trying-and-failing-to-fix-d6-mafia/88343</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 22:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88343</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/trying-and-failing-to-fix-d6-mafia/88343.rss">Trying (and failing) to fix d6 mafia</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Alice Alignment Push Test</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So while playing a game with <a class="mention" href="/u/arete">@Arete</a> they brought up my meta when it comes to pushes and I decided to check out a few past games where I mislynched/tried to mislynch villagers as both alignments. Here are posts from each day where I pushed lynches on villas, by mistake as V and intentionally as W.</p>
<p>Here’s a challenge for ya, read each of these statements and try to guess whether they come from V!Me who mistakenly wolfread villager X or W!Me who’s trying to push villager X for a mislynch.</p>
<hr>
<ol>
<li>
<p>“Hmmm, looks like she’s at the point where she can make genuine-sounding reads as a wolf but can’t fake a progression on them.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“Can we just yeet X today? I seen no reason why not do it today since nobody has any idea for an alternative lynch.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“On one hand at least both your claims look to be corroborating each other so I don’t think either of you are faking it. On the other…”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“I’m basically full on the X lynch as his perspective has repeatedly shown that he does have TMI in this case.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>X/Y have basically been useless, tbh. Would go X&gt;Y being that X just keeps posting excuses why he hasn’t made any analysis while Y’s first inquiry into Z felt kind of villagery.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“I frankly want to lynch X rn being that he looks extremely detached from the game considering that he’s just floating around at an EoD when we’re at XYLO-1.“</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“I meant I was hesitating earlier on her because on this site villas do dumb shit like write LAMIST clusterfucks or try to negate town reads for no reason. I just don’t think her read on W/Y/Z is ever genuine.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“X looks frozen as hell. Kind of wanting Y/X wagons as Z actually dealt with pressure relatively well.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“Actually, X wolf/Y village makes the most sense in respect to the gamestate with Z taking his vote off Y. She should be the day’s lynch unless she claims [PR].”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“X’s read on me distancing from Y was tbh pretty bad and artificial. I was repeatedly townreading Y and she doesn’t further elaborate than this. Also of course I’m going to have bland posts at the SoD as I have trouble creating content from nothing.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“Thinking it may be just X by now being that there really isn’t any reason not to clear Y here unless they want to do it solely to expand the PoE.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“It should be obvious that this post is ridiculously performative.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>“…that’s follow-up. The point is that I’m suspecting x as he hasn’t really done anything read-wise and spent much of the time theorizing about classes and trying to role-fish. Him making these odd deductions on Y is basically just another reason why I’m suspicious of him.”</p>
</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>430 posts - 29 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alice-alignment-push-test/88317">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alice-alignment-push-test/88317</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 01:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88317</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alice-alignment-push-test/88317.rss">The Alice Alignment Push Test</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Are Replacements on FoL Alignment-Indicative? An Analysis</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="are-replacements-on-fol-alignment-indicative-an-analysis-1" class="anchor" href="#are-replacements-on-fol-alignment-indicative-an-analysis-1"></a>Are Replacements on FoL Alignment-Indicative? An Analysis.</h1>
<p><strong>Introduction</strong></p>
<p>A common belief among forum mafia players is that replacements are alignment-indicative, and in particular indicative that that player is more likely to be Mafia. Terms such as “RWSTFO” (“rand wolf, sub the fuck out”) are often applied to argue that there is a pattern of Mafia replacing out for solely alignment related reasons. While there are certainly some replacements that are alignment-indicative, I was curious if the trend was true overall, so I decided to investigate. I don’t know if anyone else actually cares, but if you don’t care, you can just skip the post.</p>
<p><strong>Methodology</strong></p>
<p>I analyzed completed forum mafia games from 2021, going based off of the <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/list-of-completed-fm-games-2021/87188">list of completed games</a> in 2021. (As the 2020 list is not fully updated, I didn’t want to risk missing some games from 2020 if I included 2020 games in the sample). I excluded Quantum Mafia due to the fact that most players did not know their alignment until roughly day 4, and the fact that player actions could very directly influence alignment; this left me with 22 completed games. I counted the number of scum, town, and third party replacements, and calculated the proportion of each faction that replaced out over the course of all games in the sample.</p>
<p>One complicating factor was the presence of conversion in many FoL and SFoL setups. For the purposes of this analysis, I counted converted players as scum. (No one in the sample replaced out in a converted slot, either before or after conversion, so the only thing this affects is the total number of scum and town).</p>
<p>In cases where multiple players replaced out of a slot, I counted each rotation separately. Pre-game subs were excluded from the analysis entirely (including one potentially-alignment-indicative case in which a player subbed out due to having outed in the signup thread, but possibly after receiving a rolecard).</p>
<p><strong>Results</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p>FoL Annual Mash - 4 subs (3 wolf, 1 town) [overall playercomposition was 33/12/2]<br>
Ninjas and Guns - 3 subs (0 wolf, 3 town) [player composition was 13/4]<br>
RWBY FM - 6 subs (0 wolf, 6 town) [13/4]<br>
Catgirl Bomb Nightless 0 subs (0 wolf, 0 town) [9/3]<br>
NFoL 5 - 1 sub (0 wolf, 1 town) [9/4/3]<br>
DitF FM - 6 subs (1 wolf, 5 town) [15/6]<br>
Sonic the Hedgehog FM - 4 subs (0 wolf, 3 town) [10/3]<br>
SFoL 66 - 3 subs (0 wolf, 2 town, 1 3p) [11/3/2]<br>
Return of the Darkness UPick - 6 subs (3 wolf, 3 town) [13/4]<br>
NUF FM 2 - 0 subs afaict (0 wolf, 0 town) [11/3/1]<br>
Golden Wind Smalltown - 1 sub (0 wolf, 1 town) [10/3]<br>
Catgrill Night Jesterless - 0 subs (0 wolf, 0 town) [5/2]<br>
Modified Thing Game - 2 subs (0 wolf, 2 town) [13/4]<br>
Vig10 - 0 subs (0 wolf, 0 town) [8/2]<br>
Umineko FM 2 - 0 subs (0 wolf, 0 town) [14/4]<br>
Quantum Mafia: I am explicitly discounting this one because most players didn’t know their alignment until D3-D4. all the subs were town though.<br>
SFoL 65 - 3 subs (1 wolf, 2 town) [10/5/2]<br>
Shortnite 2 - 4 subs (0 wolf, 2 town) [12/3]<br>
EFoL 4 - 3 subs (1 wolf, 2 town) [11/2/3]<br>
Clown Fiesta 2 - 1 sub (0 wolf, 1 town) [16/5/1]<br>
Morphogenetic Mafia - 2 subs (0 wolf, 2 town) [14/4]<br>
Gay Mafia - 1 sub (0 wolf, 1 town) [6/2]<br>
JoaTJoaTJoaT13 - 0 subs (0 wolf, 0 town) [10/3]</p>
</details>
<p><em>Disclaimer: It is possible that I erred in some way while counting subs, as many OPs were only partially updated. I welcome any corrections to this data.</em></p>
<p>Overall, there were 9 wolf subs, 37 town subs, 1 3p sub. There were 85 total wolf slots in the sample, 248 village slots, and 14 3p slots, for a 10.6% wolf sub rate, a 14.9% village sub rate, and a 7.1% 3p sub rate.</p>
<p>Additionally, I performed a 2-proportion z-test with a two-tailed hypothesis (basically, a <a href="https://www.statisticshowto.com/probability-and-statistics/hypothesis-testing/z-test/">statistical test</a> used to compare the proportion of something in two populations), and got a p-value of .31732, which is not generally considered statistically significant. (In plain English, that means that if wolves and town are equally likely to sub out, the odds of a difference this extreme in either direction happening by pure random chance are roughly 31.7 percent). I didn’t do any statistical tests with third party sub rates due to the very low sample size.</p>
<p><strong>Caveats</strong></p>
<p>There are a few factors that may make this result less reliable.</p>
<ul>
<li>I was specifically looking at games from FoL. Other sites may have more alignment-indicative sub rates.</li>
<li>While this result fails to support the conclusion that substitutions are alignment-indicative in the aggregate, they are still sometimes AI in individual circumstances – there are a few subs in this sample that I know to have been influenced by the player’s alignment. Similarly, it doesn’t account for the possibility that <em>individual</em> subs are consistently alignment indicative, but <em>collectively</em> happen in proportion to the ratio of scum and town.</li>
<li>Some of these were force-replacements. I didn’t have data on which subs were force-replacements and which weren’t, so I couldn’t exclude forced subs from the sample, and forced subs are more likely to happen to villagers for game integrity reasons.</li>
<li>In a couple of cases, a player attempted to sub out, but was killed or executed before they could actually be replaced. I didn’t count those because I couldn’t confidently be aware of all cases when it had happened.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusions</strong></p>
<p>Overall, the data does not support the conclusion that substitutions on FoL  are alignment-indicative, and especially does not support the conclusion that substitutions are Mafia-indicative. Although attempting to use substitutions to argue that a player is a particular alignment is considered angleshooting anyway, the evidence does not support the conclusion that it would even be accurate angleshooting.</p>
            <p><small>19 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/are-replacements-on-fol-alignment-indicative-an-analysis/88279">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/are-replacements-on-fol-alignment-indicative-an-analysis/88279</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 23:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88279</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/are-replacements-on-fol-alignment-indicative-an-analysis/88279.rss">Are Replacements on FoL Alignment-Indicative? An Analysis</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>BASTARD SWORD - Interest Check</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Title. I’m making a thread here so I’d get feedback on what people want/do not want in the upcoming bastard game as I want to make it a fun bastard game rather than one where everyone just pulls their hair out trying to understand what’s happening.</p>
<p>I’m still refining the game, so I’d like some feedback. From the get-go here are some of the things I’m gonna do.</p>
<ul>
<li>No conversions. Should be obvious, but people in general just dislike conversions and they don’t really add much to the game to compensate.</li>
<li>No multiball. Only one wolfteam should suffice. I want the game to be bastard, not annoying. Plus, literally every time that a multiball game gets hosted on this site one of the wolf factions just straight up doesn’t bother to play at all.</li>
<li>No lying in the OP or about role card. Being a bastard game, the host will lie from time to time. Though the OP and the role card, though not the entire private thread itself, will be free from lies.</li>
<li>Limited flip tampering. I don’t think anyone on this site would want to play a game that becomes almost flipless after CFM2.</li>
<li>Limited shitposting. Personally I feel that Geyde went overdrive when it came to shitposting in CF2. The entire goal of this game is to be a game similar to Eevee’s CFM2 or Anime uPick, not a shitpost in game form.</li>
</ul>
<p>What’s still on the table.</p>
<ul>
<li>Serial Killers, or 3p roles that are basically an entire faction by themselves. Some people dislike them, but I don’t feel like the amount of dislike they receive on this site is enough to completely rule them out. Plus, SKs on this site generally die before late-game so they don’t impact the game by much.</li>
<li>Jesters. I get that some people hate them <em>cough</em>IciandOrange<em>cough</em>, but except game-ending jesters they don’t warp the game too much unlike multiball or conversions.</li>
<li>Dead interaction. Honestly, I feel like the only reason DI is disliked on this site was because of Geyde solving Drakengard from beyond the grave with Boss’ help.</li>
<li>Lost Wolves. Like, I don’t think I’ve ever seen a FM here that used LWs, so I’m still keeping it.</li>
<li>Millers, Godfathers, Tailors, and Framers. Duh.</li>
</ul>
<p>What’s unlikely, but still not completely off the table.</p>
<ul>
<li>Survivors. Come the fuck on, you know very well that I can make more creative and fun 3p roles than this.</li>
<li>Cop sanities. Feels like a lazy way to fuck with cop checks.</li>
</ul>
            <p><small>127 posts - 20 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bastard-sword-interest-check/88217">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bastard-sword-interest-check/88217</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 22:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88217</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bastard-sword-interest-check/88217.rss">BASTARD SWORD - Interest Check</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Community FM 3 Polls</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chloe]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>
<a name="important-details-1" class="anchor" href="#important-details-1"></a>Important Details</h1>
<p>CFM3 is a large game for our site. We expect 21+ people to join, and there is no limit to the amount of people who can play. (For reference, last year had 31 players!)</p>
<p>This game will have In-Thread-Attacks (ITAs) with a base accuracy of 10%. There may or may not be other forms of day killpower. There will also be events. It’ll be pretty mash-like. (Longer days can get exhausting)</p>
<p>We will not be doing any phase lengths other than the options listed. Sorry if you wanted something else ):</p>
<p>The game will begin mid-June.</p>
<p>The following polls’ results <em>are not public.</em> Voting just to see the results won’t work. Please vote seriously.</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-close="2021-05-30T07:00:00.000Z" data-poll-name="poll3" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="staff_only" data-poll-charttype="bar" data-poll-type="regular">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<div class="poll-title">Do you plan on playing in CFM3?</div>
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="277962ea3b8227e06ed3eb378fbdba0d">Yes</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="720aa6324194f0ccd395b3cd0ed76f0e">No</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="c689d17b8138e679e43895d95f372cda">Maybe</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-close="2021-05-30T07:00:00.000Z" data-poll-max="2" data-poll-min="1" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="staff_only" data-poll-charttype="bar" data-poll-type="multiple" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<div class="poll-title">Which phase length do you prefer?</div>
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="938bb569ee675eaebcc88fd4a0a3b429">24/24</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="7e20e6745226ba22f6980ecbb5952c20">36/12</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Please vote in the following polls <em>regardless</em> of your choice(s) in the last poll. Keep in mind that 36/12 will have a different SoD and EoD time (12h apart):</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-close="2021-05-30T07:00:00.000Z" data-poll-max="16" data-poll-min="1" data-poll-name="poll2" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="staff_only" data-poll-charttype="bar" data-poll-type="multiple">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<div class="poll-title">Which SoD/EoD times do you prefer for 24/24? (PDT is UTC -7)</div>
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="3b9dce58cd6fd366845d1a5780c9716a">9am PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="027de6d3f36027105295e8edec2cd5e3">10am PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="e7f558d97a6210efa09eca492c7c36ff">11am PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="9bde1c0ab8d9928721b46bac178e0613">12pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="af1e515077edecb0e8c2b2987fab308e">1pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="e77b4b7f3b59981a48916680fb49be65">2pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="5126d579172a9de0e56b55af650e9232">3pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="a2d2f005a178fbc1cfa82c294e0ec3e6">4pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="8461428a0f08eb451aed91fd552220e2">5pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="88f40dbc977e8ad103a178bdda71fe98">6pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="a11ca6510476969d864f4eafce6ec994">7pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="36a196c383ae19018f40e7b83a3d52d8">8pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="e0138a0c7f3bd8d2641def193485a26d">9pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="2b6c9a56356ab0b900971d398ccc2763">10pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="b85034974ea148d130650b82af553669">11pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="7c23e1a5ec56cd9935c911a8f260830c">12am PDT</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-max="8" data-poll-min="1" data-poll-name="poll4" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="staff_only" data-poll-charttype="bar" data-poll-type="multiple">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<div class="poll-title">Which SoD time do you prefer for 36/12? (PDT is UTC-7)</div>
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="3b9dce58cd6fd366845d1a5780c9716a">9am PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="027de6d3f36027105295e8edec2cd5e3">10am PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="e7f558d97a6210efa09eca492c7c36ff">11am PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="9bde1c0ab8d9928721b46bac178e0613">12pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="e0138a0c7f3bd8d2641def193485a26d">9pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="2b6c9a56356ab0b900971d398ccc2763">10pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="b85034974ea148d130650b82af553669">11pm PDT</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="7c23e1a5ec56cd9935c911a8f260830c">12am PDT</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<h3>
<a name="thread-is-closed-because-were-bad-people-3-2" class="anchor" href="#thread-is-closed-because-were-bad-people-3-2"></a>Thread is closed because we’re bad people &lt;3</h3>
<p>DM us with any questions you may have (<a class="mention" href="/u/chloe">@Chloe</a>, <a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a>, <a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a>)</p>
            <p><small>4 posts - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/community-fm-3-polls/87920">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/community-fm-3-polls/87920</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 03:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87920</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/community-fm-3-polls/87920.rss">Community FM 3 Polls</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Just thought of a terrible setup (feel free to post your own)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>caltrop mafia</p>
<p>14er</p>
<p>2 mafia goons, one mafia PR</p>
<p>10 vanilla town, 1 town PR</p>
<p>(1) 1-shot vig</p>
<p>(2) Jail keeper</p>
<p>(3) Joat (1-shot poison, 1-shot heal)</p>
<p>(4) Roleblocker</p>
<p>roll 2 d4s</p>
<p>the first roll corresponds to the town power role, the second to the mafia power role</p>
<p>any critiques</p>
<p>want to run a modbot supported open setup soon ish so I’ll take suggestions for any bad setups</p>
            <p><small>94 posts - 16 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-thought-of-a-terrible-setup-feel-free-to-post-your-own/87795">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-thought-of-a-terrible-setup-feel-free-to-post-your-own/87795</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87795</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/just-thought-of-a-terrible-setup-feel-free-to-post-your-own/87795.rss">Just thought of a terrible setup (feel free to post your own)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Game mechanics discussion thread</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mech ideas you find cool/interesting? Class concepts you just thought of? Post it here so a setup designer may steal it or other players develop it.</p>
<p>Particularly I’ve always liked the idea of those setups that empower or debuff users depending on their positions on readslists submitted at night. There should be a name for this but idk what it is.</p>
            <p><small>60 posts - 17 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-mechanics-discussion-thread/87769">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-mechanics-discussion-thread/87769</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 07:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87769</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/game-mechanics-discussion-thread/87769.rss">Game mechanics discussion thread</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Help katze make their champs bio</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="81673">
  <div class="title">
    <div class="quote-controls"></div>
    <img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/eevee/40/37897_2.png" class="avatar">
    <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mafia-championship-bio-creation/81673">Mafia championship bio creation</a> <a class="badge-wrapper  bullet" href="/c/forum-matches/11"><span class="badge-category-bg" style="background-color: #BF1E2E;"></span><span style="" data-drop-close="true" class="badge-category clear-badge" title="Forum Mafia/Werewolf. Organize @ https://discord.gg/tol &gt;&gt; Looking for #forum-matches:forum-of-lies ?">Forum Matches</span></a>
  </div>
  <blockquote>
    Okay guys. I need a bio for mafia championship. 
They said it’s okay to enlist some of my communities for help, so here you go, add whatever you want into it. As trolly as you want too. 
This post is a wiki btw. 
TO EDIT:

And lastly, I need a bio from you. 
Please fill out the below form and then send it to me via PM on your home site or on Discord. 
NATIONALITY: […] 
STARTED PLAYING MAFIA (YEAR): […] 
HAVE PLAYED MAFIA ON THE FOLLOWING SITES: […] 
BIO: 
Quotes: 

Eevee is the kind of person wh…
  </blockquote>
</aside>

<p>im kind of just copying eevee. im not gonna use everything here, probably? since i don’t think ill be fully copying how eevee did it or anything, but i  do want to mostly crowdsource it because i think it fits me well and is funny</p>
<p>im not gonna make the OP a wiki and will instead probably just cherrypick replies (so try to keep the replies relatively on topic?)</p>
<p>so y’know. roast me. make fun of me. compliment me. post cat pictures. describe my playstyle… i don’t know for sure what i want my bio to look like, so just do what feels right!</p>
<p>or do nothing that’d be pretty funny too</p>
            <p><small>90 posts - 24 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/help-katze-make-their-champs-bio/87702">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/help-katze-make-their-champs-bio/87702</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87702</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/help-katze-make-their-champs-bio/87702.rss">Help katze make their champs bio</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mafia Championship Season 8 - RESULTS ARE IN! (post 464)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ahoy there! <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I’m very excited to invite your community to participate in Season 8 of the Mafia Championship.</p>
<p>The Mafia Championship is an annual forum-based tournament series that pits representatives from various online Mafia (aka Werewolf) communities against one another as they compete to determine the Internet’s greatest forum Mafia player. Each participating community democratically elects one person to represent them and be their “Champion”.</p>
<p>The tournament first started back in 2013. Since then, 320+ different communities and 50+ different nationalities have been represented.</p>
<p>It’s a super fun event that has created many new friendships and close bonds between communities. I hope that you would be interested in taking part yet again <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<h3><strong>1) DO YOU ACCEPT THE INVITATION?</strong></h3>
<p>If your community wishes to participate, please confirm your participation to Lissa as soon as you can to ensure yourselves a spot. Currently, the plan is to accommodate 150 communities this season. If there is further interest, additional communities may sign up as substitutes; generally there are some replacements needed both before and during games.</p>
<p>If your community agrees to participate, the deadline for selecting your representative is <strong>May 7th</strong>, but the sooner the better.</p>
<p>The games will take place on Mafia Universe.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><strong>Important notes</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>You may decide yourselves how you want to elect your representative, but we highly recommend some sort of democratic process (public nominations followed by a poll usually works out well).</li>
<li>In addition to electing a representative, you should also name an alternate (a back-up) who will be asked to step in if the first choice needs to back out.</li>
<li>Your representative should be prepared for having to read <strong>upwards of 500-600 posts per 24 hours</strong> during the early stages of the game. Additionally, there’s a requirement that each player must make at least 10 posts per Game Day. Only active players should apply/participate. <strong>I repeat: Your chosen player needs to be able to promise a good amount of activity on a daily basis!</strong>
</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>2) SEASON 8 FORMAT</strong></h3>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><strong>The Tournament Structure</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>150 communities</strong> will participate, each sending one representative.</li>
<li>
<strong>QUALIFIERS:</strong> 10 Qualifier Games will be played, consisting of 15 players each. I.e. every representative plays in one Qualifier Game. The players themselves vote post-game to determine who is deserving of advancement. 1st and 2nd place will advance to the Semifinal Games.</li>
<li>
<strong>SEMIFINALS:</strong> A Jury consisting of finalists from Season 7 (presumably including our own <a class="mention" href="/u/arete">@Arete</a>) will select 25 additional players to advance to the three Semifinal Games. From each game, five players will advance to the Finale Game based on a post-game player vote, just like in the qualifying phase.</li>
<li>
<strong>THE FINALE:</strong> The Finale Game is played. Once it has completed, the players vote to determine who shall receive the title of Season 8 Champion and a winner’s certificate signed by Dmitry Davidoff, the creator of mafia.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><strong>This year’s setup: Gold Rush 15er</strong></span></p>
<p><strong><font color="red">2x Mafia Goons</font></strong></p>
<p><strong><font color="red">1x Mafia Roleblocker</font></strong></p>
<p><strong><font color="green">1x Town Motion Detector</font></strong></p>
<p><strong><font color="green">1x 1-Shot Town Vigilante (n2+)</font></strong></p>
<p><strong><font color="green">1x Town Doctor</font></strong></p>
<p><strong><font color="green">9x Vanilla Townie</font></strong></p>
<p>Flips are alignment only.</p>
<p><strong><span class="bbcode-u">Relevant Mechanics</span></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Day start.</li>
<li>Majority elimination is enabled Day 2+, but majority is not required at any point for the elimination.</li>
<li>Tied votes will result in a player being eliminated at random from among the tied players.</li>
<li>No outside communication. I.e. you may not contact the other players outside of the thread (unless you are Mafia and wish to speak with your teammates).</li>
<li>Phase Lengths and Deadlines will be up to the players themselves (I’ll organize your representative into a game with deadlines that suit their preferences).</li>
<li>Thread is locked during Night Phases.</li>
<li>Votes are automatically locked in at LYLO.</li>
<li>Mafia factional kills are <span class="bbcode-u">assigned</span>. They can be tracked, watched, roleblocked, etc. (In this setup, that means they display as an action to the Motion Detector action.)</li>
<li>Mafia share a factional Night Kill, which is a single standard shot for their faction. <strong>The mafia factional kill is mandatory.</strong>
</li>
<li>Mafia may communicate at any time.</li>
<li>Each individual player may make a maximum of 150 posts per day phase (this restriction is lifted 2 hours before day end).</li>
<li>The game will have a host to oversee everything and make sure everyone’s following the code of conduct, but otherwise the game is completely automated (automatic votecounts, thread locks and reveals alignments automatically, the bot receives and processes actions, etc.).</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>3) SEASON 8 TIMELINE</strong></h3>
<p>There will be 10 Qualifier Games, and your representative plays in just one of these. They will have start dates ranging from mid-May to early July. So in other words, as long as your representative can play sometime during that period, they should be good and I’ll make sure they get scheduled into a game that suits their schedule well. I.e. if your rep is busy until June, that isn’t a problem.</p>
<p>The Semifinal Games will be played in July/August, and the Finale Game sometime in August/September (whenever we can work out something that suits everyone).</p>
<p>If you want to get in contact with an organizer ASAP, you can reach out to Lissa on Discord (Lissa#8083).</p>
<p>Kind regards,</p>
<p>orangeandblack5</p>
<hr>
<h1>Please nominate anyone you think would make a good representative below.</h1>
<h2>They must have played at least one game in the past year.</h2>
<h2>They can choose to accept or decline their nomination.</h2>
<h3>Acceptances:</h3>
<ul>
<li>SirDerpsAlot</li>
<li>Chloe</li>
<li>Katze</li>
<li>Marluxion</li>
<li>sulit</li>
<li>astand</li>
<li>orangeandblack5</li>
</ul>
<h3>Nominations:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Hippolytus</li>
</ul>
<h3>Declined Nomination:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Marshal</li>
<li>Icibalus</li>
<li>Geyde</li>
<li>Whysper</li>
<li>WindwardAway</li>
<li>Centuries</li>
</ul>
<h1>Voting round 2 is open, check <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mafia-championship-season-8-final-vote-go-to-post-366/87580/366">here</a> for details</h1>
            <p><small>511 posts - 38 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mafia-championship-season-8-results-are-in-post-464/87580">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mafia-championship-season-8-results-are-in-post-464/87580</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 18:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87580</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mafia-championship-season-8-results-are-in-post-464/87580.rss">Mafia Championship Season 8 - RESULTS ARE IN! (post 464)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>DR6 Disinterest Check</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Good day. This is a disinterest check. In this thread, you will express how disinterested you are in these ideas, such that I don’t feel guilty about not hosting a DR game for a good year for the sake of my own health. With that said, positive feedback will be tolerated. Somewhat. You’re on thin ice.</strong></p>
<hr>
<p>So, Dangling Grandpas. The old DR. In the post-game of DR5, several problems with the overall formula were brought up, mostly by eevee, in particular about several problems with the game, which I will summarise in three points:</p>
<ol>
<li>The Mastermind is pointless, and feels either too involved or too disconnected from the rest of the game.</li>
<li>The fact that as there are less and less people there is more and more content makes the game become less active as it goes on due to having less itneractions.</li>
<li>In a simmilar vein, players who are more likely to do outlandish things (usually leading to murder), or in other words the most active players, are more likely to leave the game earlier, exaccerbating the issue.</li>
</ol>
<p>The problem with the second two can be fixed, but the first problem is quite thorny. The game needs to have some sort of underlying tension; if it just Stops Happening once five murders have taken place the finale becomes a major anticlimax, but it’s fairly clear that the current syestem of Masterminds just simply isn’t working.</p>
<p>How exactly do we solve all these issues? Well, Ladies, Gentlemen, Gentlefolk and other distinct entities of the forum of lies forum mafia forums, I have created an innovative solution.</p>
<p>Introducing <strong>TRUE ENDINGS</strong>.</p>
<p>Instead of the usual thing of having one singular wincon (usually “You win if you escape and you lose if you die”), players will have a set of three  conditions, like such:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><font color="red"><strong>BAD ENDING</strong></font> - Die or fail to escape.<br>
<font color="green"><strong>GOOD ENDING</strong></font> - Escape at any cost.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font> - [Redacted]</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Here’s how the game would function. All players will start the game knowing only their bad and good ending conditions, which will usually be identical to the  Participant wincon. However, all players will also have a condition on their classcard, such as this condition:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Unbridled Rage</strong> - If [player] dies, you will learn your <font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font> once you discover of their death.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Upon one of these conditions being fulfilled, players may gain new abilities, but most pertinently their wincons will update to include a <font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font>. Let’s see what would happen if this hypothetical card learned their true ending:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><font color="red"><strong>BAD ENDING</strong></font> - Die or fail to escape.<br>
<font color="green"><strong>GOOD ENDING</strong></font> - Escape at any cost.<br>
<font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font> - Escape after destroying a room on the map.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Now, if you notice, the player has  a chance of winning a <font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font> by going against the rest of the players and performing something that has a very real chance of getting someone killed. Players will have an incentive, upon learning their full win condition, to go out of their way to do shocking and potentially dangerous things to potentially get the bragging rights of acheiving a true ending.</p>
<p>What are the benefits of this system? Well:</p>
<ul>
<li>All players are now potentially incentivised to do odd and provocative things <em>other than</em> simply murdering people, making the game overall more exciting as more Things™ happen every phase. You might have to go out of your way to do something dangerous to <em>get</em> your <font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font> condition revealed to you.</li>
<li>The problem with the game getting less exciting as it goes on is mitigated by the fact that as the game goes on, more and more players will learn their Wilcard-like conditions for their <font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font>, making the later phases of the game more eventful as it goes on.</li>
<li>The tension of the Mastermind (that the seemingly helpful people near you could secretly be working against you) is replicated by the fact that players, driven to extremes by the circumstances, could begin to have more and more selfish motivations to potentially win the game as a <font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font> instead of merely cooperating to get a <font color="green"><strong>GOOD ENDING</strong></font>.</li>
<li>Lore! The game’s lore will become more important despite the lack of a Mastermind, because conditions based around lore could be used to determine a character’s motivations, and how those would lead to their <font color="gold"><strong>TRUE ENDING</strong></font>, keeping the incentive to explore the game’s lore.</li>
<li>Instead of players becoming Wildcards due to the rand, they become Wildcards due to their own choices, increasing player freedom and agency in the way the game’s story will occur.</li>
</ul>
<p>The problem with the map size is still extant, of course, but I have certain ideas for fixing that, although I will not publicisie them as I will this system.</p>
<p>So, what are your thoughts? Is there some critical flaw that I’m missing? What is love? Would you play in a game with this sytem (that I will not host until I’m less of a hot mess as a person)?</p>
<p>Please, scream your thoughts into the void in the ceaseless abyss of the thread below! I look forward to hearing your ideas</p>
            <p><small>417 posts - 32 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/dr6-disinterest-check/87360">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/dr6-disinterest-check/87360</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 13:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87360</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/dr6-disinterest-check/87360.rss">DR6 Disinterest Check</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Small_Tank has exploded. They were</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Small_Tank]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I gave up.<br>
Truth to be said, I wanted to just go away.<br>
But considering the number of problems, it would create to people… I think I need to explain this and inform you.</p>
<p>eevee account is blocked (authorization keys deleted).<br>
eevee_bot had all API keys removed.<br>
And this account will go to Derps, as they wanted it.<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/sirderpsalot">@SirDerpsAlot</a> password from discord.</p>
<p>Altho I guess tank is also an issue for moderation to handle, as it’s no longer needed to test eevee bot.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/datbird">@DatBird</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a> - I edited queue to remove myself and put you in charge of certain games as per previous discussions.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Chapter 1 - small tank engine failure</strong></p>
<p>Why?<br>
Well forum… you killed me once.<br>
Look, this tank is not afraid of death. It should stopped working 4 times by now. And by that I mean I was in situation where medically I had 15% or below chance to survive unscratched.</p>
<p>Some of you know I had a stroke last year.<br>
Altho I never gave exact date to not associate it with certain person or event.</p>
<p>Truth to be told night before I was working on raport comparing data from NATO long range bioparticles radars from eastern US and eastern EU, requested by counter bio-terrorism unit leader.<br>
Which is obviously stupid, cause if Covid was bioterrorism, it would start from China and not someone spraying virus in EU and US.</p>
<p>So having some time before delivering the report, I decided to relax on forum for a moment… and was involved in a big drama.<br>
Stressed, tired, with high blood pressure due to drama… you can see where it’s going.<br>
So I fainted in front of a military hospital.</p>
<p>I mean… it’s covid fault.<br>
Working overtime to make sure everything is working was definitely not healthy.<br>
But if I found relax I was searching for on this forum, maybe I wouldn’t fall.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Chapter 2 - patching up the tank</strong></p>
<p>Tank is not an easy thing to fix, right?<br>
So… I staied in the hospital for few weeks.<br>
Hey, I even got a postcard from orange, who wished me to get back to health.</p>
<p>But I also thought about what happened and… I realized that forum is just not as fun as it was.</p>
<p>Don’t misunderstand me, I play mafia for 12 years, both in professional club and over the internet.<br>
I organized events, plaied in international tournaments and tried teaching people. Both irl and over the internet. I did NOT get bored.</p>
<p>But back in the days biggest drama was privatization between Chubby and PKR or Jammy’s rebellious attitude. (Which actually cause big drama).<br>
But like… issues were rate in between and handled.</p>
<p>Now everyone game has few of ad-hominem attacks.<br>
And while most of them are pretty weak… they still hurt people and make worse atmosphere.</p>
<p>It might be me noticing it, as I went through high-end cultural education… which despite being obsolete and mostly non-used and me using an “everyday culture” level… it just put my borders a bit higher when it comes to what is acceptable.</p>
<p>So I did what every other tankist would do.<br>
<s>Chosing different route and not enter forum which nearly killed me</s><br>
Tried to defuse the mines.</p>
<p>Started small, tried to help people, teach them how to scumread and convince others without need for direct attacks. How to acusse someone’s arguments and actions, not person. And… showing them what’s going on on the forum.</p>
<p>But things got worse.<br>
Someone was adding the powder to mines to give more and more strong explosions.<br>
Murder threats, telling others to kill themself, dramas based on cultural / ethcnical / religious / political differences… you know. Big stuff.</p>
<p>I also hopped actual sapper squad, armed with banhammers will come and defuse the mines.<br>
That happened… rarely.<br>
And you know, there is a polish saying “Don’t touch shit or it will start smelling”.</p>
<p>Somewhere along the way I learnt that reviewers deny certain games, just so theirs favorite can happen faster. That GMs and mods straightforward say they don’t care about rule breaks at games/forum they look after.<br>
That tank is now stuck in middle of minefield and no help or rescue is gonna come.</p>
<p>Many times talk with people, mods, reviewers etc. happened, trying to figure out what to do to help the situation of more and more people just… quitting the site due to toxicity.<br>
Like for example event together with MC where people form MC decided to never play on this site again.<br>
See the problem?</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Chapter 3 - Don’t fix tanks if you don’t know how</strong></p>
<p>Well, due to lack of help… I went further and started to make drama out of drama.<br>
More than once placing mods in position where they HAVE TO react.</p>
<p>To be fair, I don’t hold much respect to current moderation, considering corruption around the queue and reviews and decisions.<br>
But it’s about them doing nothing, or doing stuff directly hurtful to community and our reputation, not them personally.</p>
<p>But hearby I would like to apologize for all the dramas caused by me recently.<br>
Altho more than once I was told that no action would be performed otherwise.<br>
More than once no action was performed regardless and it led to weird consequences. Which people apologized that they didn’t react when I asked for it, but… if you cared earlier, it would just not end up catastrophic.</p>
<p>I think our main issue right now is not caring.<br>
Not caring about reviews, games, other people, site etc.</p>
<p>It got to a point where people prefer to gamethrow hammer themselves to get themselfs out of game, even if there are very strong possibilities they wouldn’t die otherwise.<br>
Yeah, I’m talking about NUF.<br>
I won’t be here after this pots, so it doesn’t even matter.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Chapter 4 - Tank explodes</strong></p>
<p>So I gave up.<br>
That’s it.</p>
<p>I gave up with trying to fix this site.<br>
And tbh I gave up somewhere around chapter 3 of this post, with explaining all the things happening along the way, like SFoL 65 and many, many other situations.</p>
<p>I tried.<br>
I failed.</p>
<p>And I leave as this forum is not safe for my health anymore.</p>
<p>Like… I’m tired and I got bigger headache than I had on stroke day due to today’s drama.<br>
But I will be fine, I’m on double dose of emergency pills.</p>
<p>But tank… tank has finally exploded.<br>
And it’s last wish is not to completely stop all the arguments, it’s natural to be angry.<br>
But at least try to target persons decisions and not themself / theirs religion / culture / LGBT stuff.</p>
<p>Bye forum, I loved you. And I put a lot of effort to make sure you keep running.<br>
But we usually love stuff we can’t have, right?<br>
Sigh.</p>
<h3>Small_Tank has exploded. They were…</h3>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
</details>
            <p><small>165 posts - 27 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/small-tank-has-exploded-they-were/87324">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/small-tank-has-exploded-they-were/87324</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87324</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/small-tank-has-exploded-they-were/87324.rss">Small_Tank has exploded. They were</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>(Interest check)SCP fm</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Emilia]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would anyone be interested in playing large clown fiesta-like SCP fm?</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="always" data-poll-charttype="bar" data-poll-type="regular" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<div class="poll-title">interest check</div>
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="277962ea3b8227e06ed3eb378fbdba0d">Yes</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="a79f78e32a82ea2f4648c89cf4372525">likely</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="c29d26fc13e544433bfb4076af7c56bc">unlikely</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="720aa6324194f0ccd395b3cd0ed76f0e">No</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            <p><small>29 posts - 14 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-scp-fm/87278">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-scp-fm/87278</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87278</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/interest-check-scp-fm/87278.rss">(Interest check)SCP fm</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>FoL Awards 2021 - Nominations Thread</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is the thread for awards nominations! Please be sure to include (1) who you are nominating, (2) what award you are nominating them for, and (3) a short description of why you are nominating them.</p>
<p>Please ensure that all discussion is strictly <em>on-topic</em>.</p>
<p>Credit to <a href="https://www.mafiauniverse.com/forums/threads/29730-Mafia-Universe-Awards-2021-Nominations">the Mafia Universe mods</a> for creating the system that I’ve modelled these awards off of.</p>
<h1>
<a name="rules-1" class="anchor" href="#rules-1"></a>Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>Anyone who has played at least one game on FoL can nominate another member for an award. Anyone who has played or hosted at least one game on FoL is eligible to receive an award.</li>
<li>All nominations must have a <strong>nomination</strong> and a <strong>second</strong> to be valid. You cannot nominate yourself, nor can you nominate a team that you were part of (for example, if you were scum in FoL 99, you can’t nominate the FoL 99 scumteam for a group award; however, you could nominate a teammate for an individual award).</li>
<li>A minimum of 3 days must pass between a game ending and any nominations for that game.</li>
<li>All games that occurred at least in part in 2021 are eligible for awards. For this year only, there is also a “legacy” category, for games prior to 2021.</li>
<li>The deadline for nominations is one week after the last game that began in 2021 ends.</li>
<li>Once the nominations period is over, all relevant awards will be eligible for voting. Voting will be done via forum poll (the results will not be visible to anyone except forum moderators).</li>
</ul>
<h1>
<a name="awards-2" class="anchor" href="#awards-2"></a>Awards</h1>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Individual Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Town Perfomance - Single Player (small game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as town in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance - Single Player (large game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as town in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Perfomance - Single Player (small game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as scum  in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance - Single Player (large game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as scum in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Neutral/Third Party Performance:</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as a neutral role, in a game of any size.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc Performance:</strong> <em>For good performance in a Misc game. In extraordinary circumstances, a team may be nominated for this award.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Use of a Power Role:</strong> <em>For a player who displayed skill in using their Power Role (PR). This may be any PR, even a very weak one.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Mechanical/Strategical Player:</strong> <em>For a player who consistently displays good knowledge of mechanics and uses them effectively, as either alignment.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Replacement Player:</strong> <em>For a player who consistently replaces into games, and plays solidly after doing so.</em></p>
<p><strong>Rookie-of-the-Year:</strong> <em>For a player whose first game was in 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Most Improved Player:</strong> <em>For a player whose first game was PRIOR to 2021, but who improved significantly in 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Most Dedicated/Enjoyable/Enthusiastic Player:</strong> <em>For a player who is dedicated, enthusiastic, and enjoyable to play with, even when the game is going poorly.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Team Player:</strong> <em>For a player who does a good job at working with their teammates, regardless of their alignment.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc Player:</strong> <em>For a player who consistently does well in Misc games.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Player:</strong> <em>For the best overall town player.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Player:</strong> <em>For the best overall scum player.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best All-Around Player:</strong> <em>For a player who is “good at everything.”</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Team Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance, Group (Small Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as town, in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance, Group (Large Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as town, in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance, Group (Small Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as scum, in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance, Group (Large Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as scum, in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Hosting Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Host:</strong> <em>For a host who consistently hosts well-designed and enjoyable games.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Flavor:</strong> <em>For a host who writes good flavor.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Setup:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed setup.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed Misc.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Role/Mechanic:</strong> <em>For a role or mechanic that was both interesting and well-designed.</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Fun Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Funniest Moment:</strong> <em>For the funniest moment.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Fakeclaim:</strong> <em>For the most effective fakeclaim.</em></p>
<p><strong>Community MVP:</strong> <em>For the community member most willing to help out the community and make it a good place to be. Mods are not eligible.</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Legacy Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance (Individual):</strong> <em>For the best individual performance as town, in a game (of any size)  prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum/Neutral Performance (Individual):</strong> <em>For the best individual performance as scum or neutral, in a game (of any size)  prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance (Group):</strong> <em>For the best collective performance as town, in a game (of any size) prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance (Group):</strong> <em>For the best collective performance as scum, in a game (of any size) prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Setup:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed setup, prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed Misc, prior to 2021.</em></p>
</details>
            <p><small>383 posts - 41 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fol-awards-2021-nominations-thread/87187">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fol-awards-2021-nominations-thread/87187</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 01:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87187</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fol-awards-2021-nominations-thread/87187.rss">FoL Awards 2021 - Nominations Thread</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Discussion] Introducing the Forum of Lies Awards!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi everyone!</p>
<p>As we mentioned earlier this week, we’re planning on shifting to an annual awards system. This thread is going to go through the current draft of the rules, as well as the awards categories. This isn’t set in stone yet – one of the things we’re hoping to do here is get feedback on the rules, as well as on categories you’d like to see added or removed.</p>
<p><s>In particular, one thing we’d like feedback on is whether you’d prefer <em>annual</em> awards or a <em>semiannual</em> (every six months) awards. The rules we have right now assume the former, but it would be fairly easy to rewrite them.</s> Awards will be held annually!</p>
<p>Feel free to use this thread to discuss nominations!</p>
<p><strong>Updated Awards System:</strong></p>
<p>Credit to <a href="https://www.mafiauniverse.com/forums/threads/29730-Mafia-Universe-Awards-2021-Nominations">the Mafia Universe mods</a> for creating the system that I’ve modelled these awards off of.</p>
<h1>Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>Anyone who has played at least one game on FoL can nominate another member for an award. Anyone who has played or hosted at least one game on FoL is eligible to receive an award.</li>
<li>All nominations must have a <strong>nomination</strong> and a <strong>second</strong> to be valid. You cannot nominate yourself, nor can you nominate a team that you were part of (for example, if you were scum in FoL 99, you can’t nominate the FoL 99 scumteam for a group award; however, you could nominate a teammate for an individual award).</li>
<li>A minimum of 3 days must pass between a game ending and any nominations for that game.</li>
<li>All games that occurred at least in part in 2021 are eligible for awards. For this year only, there is also a “legacy” category, for games prior to 2021.</li>
<li>The deadline for nominations is one week after the last game that began in 2021 ends.</li>
<li>Once the nominations period is over, all relevant awards will be eligible for voting. Voting will be done via forum poll (the results will not be visible to anyone except forum moderators).</li>
</ul>
<h1>Awards</h1>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Individual Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Town Perfomance - Single Player (small game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as town in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance - Single Player (large game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as town in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Perfomance - Single Player (small game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as scum  in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance - Single Player (large game):</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as scum in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Neutral/Third Party Performance:</strong> <em>For a good individual performance as a neutral role, in a game of any size.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc Performance:</strong> <em>For good performance in a Misc game. In extraordinary circumstances, a team may be nominated for this award.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Use of a Power Role:</strong> <em>For a player who displayed skill in using their Power Role (PR). This may be any PR, even a very weak one.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Mechanical/Strategical Player:</strong> <em>For a player who consistently displays good knowledge of mechanics and uses them effectively, as either alignment.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Replacement Player:</strong> <em>For a player who consistently replaces into games, and plays solidly after doing so.</em></p>
<p><strong>Rookie-of-the-Year:</strong> <em>For a player whose first game was in 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Most Improved Player:</strong> <em>For a player whose first game was PRIOR to 2021, but who improved significantly in 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Most Dedicated/Enjoyable/Enthusiastic Player:</strong> <em>For a player who is dedicated, enthusiastic, and enjoyable to play with, even when the game is going poorly.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Team Player:</strong> <em>For a player who does a good job at working with their teammates, regardless of their alignment.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc Player:</strong> <em>For a player who consistently does well in Misc games.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Player:</strong> <em>For the best overall town player.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Player:</strong> <em>For the best overall scum player.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best All-Around Player:</strong> <em>For a player who is “good at everything.”</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Team Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance, Group (Small Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as town, in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance, Group (Large Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as town, in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance, Group (Small Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as scum, in a game with 15 or fewer players.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance, Group (Large Game):</strong> <em>For collective excellence as scum, in a game with 16 or more players.</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Hosting Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Host:</strong> <em>For a host who consistently hosts well-designed and enjoyable games.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Flavor:</strong> <em>For a host who writes good flavor.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Setup:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed setup.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed Misc.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Role/Mechanic:</strong> <em>For a role or mechanic that was both interesting and well-designed.</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Fun Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Funniest Moment:</strong> <em>For the funniest moment.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Fakeclaim:</strong> <em>For the most effective fakeclaim.</em></p>
<p><strong>Community MVP:</strong> <em>For the community member most willing to help out the community and make it a good place to be. Mods are not eligible.</em></p>
</details>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Legacy Awards</font></strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance (Individual):</strong> <em>For the best individual performance as town, in a game (of any size)  prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum/Neutral Performance (Individual):</strong> <em>For the best individual performance as scum or neutral, in a game (of any size)  prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Town Performance (Group):</strong> <em>For the best collective performance as town, in a game (of any size) prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Scum Performance (Group):</strong> <em>For the best collective performance as scum, in a game (of any size) prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Setup:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed setup, prior to 2021.</em></p>
<p><strong>Best Misc:</strong> <em>For an interesting, enjoyable, and well-designed Misc, prior to 2021.</em></p>
</details>
            <p><small>221 posts - 29 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/discussion-introducing-the-forum-of-lies-awards/87059">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/discussion-introducing-the-forum-of-lies-awards/87059</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87059</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/discussion-introducing-the-forum-of-lies-awards/87059.rss">[Discussion] Introducing the Forum of Lies Awards!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Weekly Monday Discussion #7 - Moderation</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1><font color="orange">Welcome to the Weekly* Monday Discussion!</font></h1>
<p><small>* <strong>Disclaimer: Not actually weekly</strong></small></p>
<p><strong><font color="orange">katze</font>:</strong> Not only is it <em>actually</em> on a Monday this time, you’re <s>stuck</s> here with your favorite discussion host, katze!<br>
<strong>Audience Member:</strong> You’re a mod?<br>
<strong><font color="orange">katze</font>:</strong> Somehow! Even better, that’s surprisingly close to what I’m here for! I’m <em>actually</em> here for a few reasons, so let me speak for <em>us</em> – The Moderation Team. We know we’re not flawless. Look at <em>us</em>, they sent <em>me</em> to host this! Surely this is a sign of our fallibleness as mods! (At least the <em>other</em> mods. I’m perfect.)<br>
<strong>Audience Member:</strong> shut up katze<br>
<strong><font color="orange">katze</font>:</strong> Point taken. Anyway, we’d first like to discuss <em>us</em>. We know we’re flawed. We’d like to better ourselves for you, and we have ideas on how to improve already, but we’d like <em>your</em> feedback. Yes, even <em>you</em>, the reader!</p>
<hr>
<p>In order let people give feedback anonymously, we created a form with some questions. At the end you may optionally leave your username if you’d like it to <em>not</em> be anonymous feedback. <strong>You may still answer them in this thread, if you’d like!</strong></p>
<aside class="onebox googledocs">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScLd1C-HmeQzWCO0QFludpdP-la78WNQQkfXc0WCs2g4_0s3A/viewform?usp=sf_link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">docs.google.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScLd1C-HmeQzWCO0QFludpdP-la78WNQQkfXc0WCs2g4_0s3A/viewform?usp=sf_link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="googledocs-onebox-logo g-forms-logo"></span></a>

<h3><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScLd1C-HmeQzWCO0QFludpdP-la78WNQQkfXc0WCs2g4_0s3A/viewform?usp=sf_link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Weekly Discussion #7</a></h3>

<p>Hi! We're looking to receive some feedback on ourselves, as moderators. Please be as honest as you can be!</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<details>
<summary>
If you'd like to answer in thread, here are the questions!</summary>
<ul>
<li>Do you think we are too lenient/strict regarding punishment lengths?</li>
<li>Do you think the <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/official-forum-mafia-and-forum-of-lies-rules/78926">Forum Mafia rules</a> are in need of changing? If so, what would you change?</li>
<li>What is your biggest issue with the moderation system currently?</li>
<li>Do you have anything else you’d like to say, that the prior questions did not quite reach?</li>
</ul>
</details>
<hr>
<p>Additionally, we’ve recently run into problems with the Team Player MVP Awards, one where categorizing Third Parties/Neutrals is… inconsistent and awkward, to say the least.</p>
<p>We’ve thought of a few ideas internally, but would like to instead ask the people how they think this should be handled in the future! Even if that suggestion is “lol just delete the team awards stupid mods”, we’d like to hear it!</p>
<hr>
<h1>Due to the nature of this discussion, please remember to keep it constructive and civil!</h1>
            <p><small>258 posts - 30 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/weekly-monday-discussion-7-moderation/86580">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/weekly-monday-discussion-7-moderation/86580</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 20:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86580</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/weekly-monday-discussion-7-moderation/86580.rss">Weekly Monday Discussion #7 - Moderation</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Video Mafia</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m thinking of hosting a Video Mafia this Saturday.<br>
Is anyone interested In joining?</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-video-mafia/86415">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-video-mafia/86415</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 19:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86415</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-video-mafia/86415.rss">The Video Mafia</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Step 2 - Make a public game review</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[eevee]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Step number one, create a poll:</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="always" data-poll-charttype="bar" data-poll-type="regular" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<div class="poll-title">Do you want to play mountainous 20er?</div>
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="277962ea3b8227e06ed3eb378fbdba0d">Yes</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="720aa6324194f0ccd395b3cd0ed76f0e">No</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Step 2 - Rig it so it has negative results</p>
<p>Strep 3 - Challange hosts to improve results or game gets denied.</p>
            <p><small>143 posts - 26 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/step-2-make-a-public-game-review/86342">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/step-2-make-a-public-game-review/86342</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 12:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86342</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/step-2-make-a-public-game-review/86342.rss">Step 2 - Make a public game review</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Blood on the Discord - Scheduling Thread</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is a thread where we schedule bIood on the cIocktower sessions on the discord.<br>
lt’s that simpIe.<br>
TempIate (all times in EST)</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Sunday M/D|Monday M/D|Tuesday M/D|Wednesday M/D|Thursday M/D|Friday M/D|Saturday M/D|
| -- | -- | -- | -- | -- | -- | -- |
|5:30||5:30||5:30||5:30||5:30||5:30||5:30|
|6:30||6:30||6:30||6:30||6:30||6:30||6:30|
|7:30||7:30||7:30||7:30||7:30||7:30||7:30|
|8:30||8:30||8:30||8:30||8:30||8:30||8:30|
|9:30||9:30||9:30||9:30||9:30||9:30||9:30|
|10:30||10:30||10:30||10:30||10:30||10:30||10:30|
</code></pre>
<div align="center">
Week of January 24, 2021
</div>
<div class="md-table">
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Time</th>
<th>Sunday</th>
<th>Monday</th>
<th>Tuesday</th>
<th>Wednesday</th>
<th>Thursday</th>
<th>Friday</th>
<th>Saturday</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>5:30</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>6:30</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>7:30</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>8:30</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>9:30</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>10:30</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>x</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div><p>If you want to sign up, put your name either down below, or edit your name into the proper slot.</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/blood-on-the-discord-scheduling-thread/85824">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/blood-on-the-discord-scheduling-thread/85824</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 04:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85824</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/blood-on-the-discord-scheduling-thread/85824.rss">Blood on the Discord - Scheduling Thread</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>I want to design a role madness setup, where do I even start?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[GGhana]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>see title</p>
<p>Is it possible to have a role madness game that is also a 9er? Because I don’t really want to have a big setup.</p>
            <p><small>23 posts - 8 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-want-to-design-a-role-madness-setup-where-do-i-even-start/85521">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-want-to-design-a-role-madness-setup-where-do-i-even-start/85521</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 17:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85521</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-want-to-design-a-role-madness-setup-where-do-i-even-start/85521.rss">I want to design a role madness setup, where do I even start?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Weekly Monday Discussion #6 - Queue Changes</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chloe]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1><font color="tomato">Welcome to the Weekly Monday Discussion!</font></h1>
<p>Feel free to use this thread to discuss ideas.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Interview with a Celebrity Queue Representative</summary>
<p><strong>Chloe:</strong> “Yo kat, what are your thoughts on my queue ideas?”</p>
<p><strong>kat:</strong> "tbh we should poll it <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/f/9/f94951808c3a992e2a3c98266ddc95fa81bd50de.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="zzhYo8i2gVtrx2QcUEK30hU0Dme" width="23" height="23">"</p>
<p><strong>Chloe:</strong> “Weekly Monday Discussion? <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/eyes.png?v=9" title=":eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":eyes:">”</p>
<p><strong>kat:</strong> “no it’s thursday you can’t do this”</p>
<p><strong>Chloe:</strong> “Of course I can.”</p>
<p><strong>kat:</strong> “i will delete it”</p>
<p><strong>Chloe:</strong> “Wtf number are we even on”</p>
<p><strong>kat:</strong> “aaaaaaaaaaaaaa”</p>
<p><strong>DatBird:</strong> “6?”</p>
<p><strong>Arete:</strong> “6.”</p>
<p><strong>kat:</strong> <em>angry noises</em></p>
<p><strong>Chloe:</strong> “Okay I sent you guys a draft.”</p>
<p><strong>kat:</strong> “where are the funny comments smh”</p>
<p><strong>Chloe:</strong> <em>adds something vaguely funny.</em></p>
<p><strong>kat:</strong> “4/10. easily room for ‘its not monday’ banter by me smh”</p>
<p><strong>Chloe:</strong> “fine.”</p>
</details>
<hr>
<p><strong>Please read all of these (And read them carefully) before responding!</strong></p>
<p><font color="tomato"><strong>Idea 1</strong></font> - The mod/review team will use their best judgement to place games throughout the “Waiting to Start” portion of the queue, in order to maximize variety in terms of game size and game type. Reviewed games will no longer simply be placed at the bottom.</p>
<p>ie. We will attempt to make sure that there are not multiple mashes within a short period of time, or a large amount of vanilla setups clumped together. (This is similar to what we do now, but, rather than scrambling to find a small setup, we will have organization weeks/months beforehand).</p>
<p><font color="tomato"><strong>Idea 2</strong></font> - Create two queues. One for small games (15p maximum) and one for large games (more than 15 players). Reviewed games will be placed at the bottom of the respective queue.</p>
<p><font color="tomato"><strong>Idea 3</strong></font> - Create two queues. One for small <em>and/or</em> open/semi-open setups, and one for large <em>and/or</em> closed/rolemadness setups. Reviewed games will be placed at the bottom of the respective queue.</p>
<p><font color="tomato"><strong>Idea 4</strong></font> - Implement a scheduled queue system. Users will request a date for their game to run. Slots in the schedule will be pre-determined months beforehand, and will be separated based on gamesize. An example of a scheduled queue system is the <a href="https://www.mafiauniverse.com/forums/threads/29224-2021-Unified-Queue-Thread">Mafia Universe Queue</a>.</p>
<p><font color="tomato"><strong>Idea 5</strong></font> - Change the queue system, but to something else. (Explain your idea in a reply)</p>
<p><font color="tomato"><strong>Idea 6</strong></font> - Don’t change anything.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>The following poll has public results.</strong> Do not vote if you are not comfortable with people viewing your selection.<br>
<strong>Results are always visible</strong>, but we suggest that you answer <em>before</em> looking at them, as to not bias your choice.</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-max="6" data-poll-min="1" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="always" data-poll-charttype="bar" data-poll-type="multiple" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<div class="poll-title">Multiple answers can be selected:</div>
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="115fb65034c2010a5617646f1a07c487">Idea 1</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="46ccf5ffc7c7708f655d4a4f40788536">Idea 2</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="f0a201e002c5a04e2e1b0d520ddf3e81">Idea 3</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="803b146e73dc4dd9a7287223841f1ad2">Idea 4</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="e3156628b2ef74f08a4dbe7f75982e68">Idea 5</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="3a7f01bff3bc68cbd8fb58c2c3f61f8c">Idea 6</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p><font color="tomato"><strong>Final note:</strong></font> The results of this poll and discussion may not reflect the mod/review team’s decision, but answers will be taken into consideration and play a role in our selection.</p>
            <p><small>28 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/weekly-monday-discussion-6-queue-changes/85458">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/weekly-monday-discussion-6-queue-changes/85458</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85458</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/weekly-monday-discussion-6-queue-changes/85458.rss">Weekly Monday Discussion #6 - Queue Changes</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Catgirl Angel Dayless Discussion Thread</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Discussion</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everyone talks about Dayless like it’s a <em>meme</em>. Well, that ends today. Note that this is <em>not</em> a signup thread.</p>
<p>Rolelist:<br>
<strong>1x Angel</strong><br>
<strong><font color="green">3x Town Neighbor/izers</font></strong><br>
<strong><font color="green">3x Town Vanilla</font></strong><br>
<strong><font color="red">1x Mafia Neighbor/izer</font></strong><br>
<strong><font color="red">1x Mafia Goon</font></strong></p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="green">Town Neighbor/izer</font></h1>
<p>You share a neighborhood with all other Neighbor/izers. Each night, everyone in the neighborhood may come to a consensus on who else gets to be a Neighbor/izer of their respective alignment. They gain that card immediately upon agreement.</p>
<p>A gun is given to one random person with this card. Only they know that they have a gun. Once they die, the gun is moved to another person with this card. Once everyone with this card dies, any vanilla Town in the neighborhood is given the gun. They can use this gun to shoot anyone else in the neighborhood. This can cause their target to flip as either “died” or “shot” (if an Angel dies from the shot due to the compulsive bodyguarding, it will always show as “died”), by choice of the gunbearer.</p>
<p>You win if the neighborhood has no Mafia in it.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="green">Vanilla Town</font></h1>
<p>You cannot do anything until you receive the Town Neighbor/izer card.</p>
<p>You win if the neighborhood has no Mafia in it.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="red">Mafia Neighbor/izer</font></h1>
<p>You share a neighborhood with all other Neighbor/izers. Each night, everyone in the neighborhood may come to a consensus on who else gets to be a Neighbor/izer of their respective alignment.</p>
<p>You share a night chat with your teammate. Each night, you may come to a consensus on who to kill. You may pick <em>anyone</em>.</p>
<p>You win if the neighborhood has no Town in it.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="red">Mafia Goon</font></h1>
<p>You are not in the neighborhood until you are given the Mafia Neighbor/izer card, but you share a night chat with your teammate. Each night, you may come to a consensus on who to kill. You may pick <em>anyone</em>.</p>
<p>You win if the neighborhood has no Town in it.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1>Angel</h1>
<p>You are not in the neighborhood until you are given the Angel Neighbor/izer card (just pretend it exists).</p>
<p>You are randomly assigned to protect one random person. You have a night chat with that person. If your contract is to die, you will die instead.</p>
<p>You win if your contract survives to the end of the game.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I probably made a game-breaking mistake somewhere. Sorry.</p>
            <p><small>134 posts - 20 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/catgirl-angel-dayless-discussion-thread/85315">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/catgirl-angel-dayless-discussion-thread/85315</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 04:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85315</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/catgirl-angel-dayless-discussion-thread/85315.rss">Catgirl Angel Dayless Discussion Thread</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
