<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[CLASS SUGGESTION] The Abomination (Neutral)/The Madman (Unseen/Cultist)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-abomination-neutral-the-madman-unseen-cultist/3815</link>
    <description>
**The Abomination (Neutral)**

**Day Ability 1:** Trollbox (Infinite uses)
Produce a statement that is under another character’s name (identical to the fool).

**Night Ability 1:** Distract Guards (3-4 uses)
The abomination targets a player for the purposes of distracting the guards that are examining the player. Thus, if the King sends guards to himself, the guards will be distracted from the King. Distracting the guards results in leaving players vulnerable to being assaulted by any “offensive” or “killer” class.

Example: 
1. King sends guards to A. Abomination distracts A. The guards will be ineffective, leading the King to be vulnerable to other hostile players.
2. King sends guards to B. Abomination distracts A. The guards will remain effective since the abomination had distracted A rather than B.

**Night Ability 2 (Optional)**: Disgust (1 or 2 uses)
Disgust a player by throwing tomatoes or vomiting on the player, causing the player to remain inactive at the table for one turn.

**Lore:** 
&quot;The abomination&quot; is perceived to be the ugly, horrific, and abnormal monster of the village, town, or kingdom. The subject refuses to bathe, snarls at citizens, terrorizes children, throws tomatoes at people, vomits in public, and conducts numerous other &quot;abnormal&quot; acts within the village, town, or kingdom. The &quot;Abomination&quot; is Identical to the &quot;fool&quot; or a &quot;village idiot&quot;. However, the &quot;abomination&quot; is hated by the entire village, town, and kingdom, resulting in his deep hatred towards the royal family. The OBJECTIVE of the &quot;Abomination&quot; involves surviving until the FIRST KING is EXECUTED, regardless as to whether it is during the night or day.

**Comments:** 
OBJECTIVE: Survive until the King is executed either during the day or night.
---------------


**The Madman/Mad Man**

**Day Ability 1:** Disruption (One use)
The Madman undergoes a tantrum at the table, preventing each and every player from SPEAKING or ACCUSING an individual of treason. His role is revealed to the entire table. The table undergoes complete silence, without the ability to accuse any player for committing treason. for 5-10 seconds with the statement “The Madman disrupts the courts/tables” prior to transitioning into the night.

**Day Ability 2:** Enraged Stabbing (One use)
The Madman snaps in a state of insanity, causing The Madman to charge and attack a random B.D. or neutral player within the table. The targeted player is automatically executed. However, the Madman&#39;s role and class is automatically exposed to the table directly after using the ability.

**Night Ability 1:** Frighten (Unlimited uses)
The Madman frightens a player, causing the player to remain within their room during the night. In other terms, the player is occupied for the night.

**Night Ability 2 (Optional)**: Stabbing/Madman Rampage (1 or 2 uses)
Attack any player during the night. However, &quot;The Madman&#39;s/Mad Man&#39;s&quot; class and faction is automatically revealed to one random player within the table.

**Lore:** 
&quot;The Madman/Mad Man&quot; underwent a total state of insanity directly after being converted to the Unseen. Due to the village&#39;s, town&#39;s, and kingdom&#39;s hatred towards &quot;The Abomination&quot;, it seeks to fulfill the wishes of the Unseen considering that the Unseen accepts &quot;The Abomination&quot; for who he is. Thus, to the villagers, towns&#39; people, or kingdom, &quot;The Abomination&quot; is perceived to be a &quot;Mad Man&quot; considering that it&#39;s characteristics exceeded beyond the boundaries of it&#39;s former self... it is now a potential murderer.

**Comments:** 
OBJECTIVE: Defeat the B.D. and Neutral players in order to win as the UNSEEN.

---------------</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-abomination-neutral-the-madman-unseen-cultist/3815.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[CLASS SUGGESTION] The Abomination (Neutral)/The Madman (Unseen/Cultist)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dlimit33]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Abomination (Neutral)</strong></p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1:</strong> Trollbox (Infinite uses)<br>
Produce a statement that is under another character’s name (identical to the fool).</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1:</strong> Distract Guards (3-4 uses)<br>
The abomination targets a player for the purposes of distracting the guards that are examining the player. Thus, if the King sends guards to himself, the guards will be distracted from the King. Distracting the guards results in leaving players vulnerable to being assaulted by any “offensive” or “killer” class.</p>
<p>Example:</p>
<ol>
<li>King sends guards to A. Abomination distracts A. The guards will be ineffective, leading the King to be vulnerable to other hostile players.</li>
<li>King sends guards to B. Abomination distracts A. The guards will remain effective since the abomination had distracted A rather than B.</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2 (Optional)</strong>: Disgust (1 or 2 uses)<br>
Disgust a player by throwing tomatoes or vomiting on the player, causing the player to remain inactive at the table for one turn.</p>
<p><strong>Lore:</strong><br>
“The abomination” is perceived to be the ugly, horrific, and abnormal monster of the village, town, or kingdom. The subject refuses to bathe, snarls at citizens, terrorizes children, throws tomatoes at people, vomits in public, and conducts numerous other “abnormal” acts within the village, town, or kingdom. The “Abomination” is Identical to the “fool” or a “village idiot”. However, the “abomination” is hated by the entire village, town, and kingdom, resulting in his deep hatred towards the royal family. The OBJECTIVE of the “Abomination” involves surviving until the FIRST KING is EXECUTED, regardless as to whether it is during the night or day.</p>
<h2>
<strong>Comments:</strong><br>
OBJECTIVE: Survive until the King is executed either during the day or night.</h2>
<p><strong>The Madman/Mad Man</strong></p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1:</strong> Disruption (One use)<br>
The Madman undergoes a tantrum at the table, preventing each and every player from SPEAKING or ACCUSING an individual of treason. His role is revealed to the entire table. The table undergoes complete silence, without the ability to accuse any player for committing treason. for 5-10 seconds with the statement “The Madman disrupts the courts/tables” prior to transitioning into the night.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong> Enraged Stabbing (One use)<br>
The Madman snaps in a state of insanity, causing The Madman to charge and attack a random B.D. or neutral player within the table. The targeted player is automatically executed. However, the Madman’s role and class is automatically exposed to the table directly after using the ability.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1:</strong> Frighten (Unlimited uses)<br>
The Madman frightens a player, causing the player to remain within their room during the night. In other terms, the player is occupied for the night.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2 (Optional)</strong>: Stabbing/Madman Rampage (1 or 2 uses)<br>
Attack any player during the night. However, “The Madman’s/Mad Man’s” class and faction is automatically revealed to one random player within the table.</p>
<p><strong>Lore:</strong><br>
“The Madman/Mad Man” underwent a total state of insanity directly after being converted to the Unseen. Due to the village’s, town’s, and kingdom’s hatred towards “The Abomination”, it seeks to fulfill the wishes of the Unseen considering that the Unseen accepts “The Abomination” for who he is. Thus, to the villagers, towns’ people, or kingdom, “The Abomination” is perceived to be a “Mad Man” considering that it’s characteristics exceeded beyond the boundaries of it’s former self… it is now a potential murderer.</p>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong><br>
OBJECTIVE: Defeat the B.D. and Neutral players in order to win as the UNSEEN.</p>
<hr>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-abomination-neutral-the-madman-unseen-cultist/3815/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-abomination-neutral-the-madman-unseen-cultist/3815/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3815-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-abomination-neutral-the-madman-unseen-cultist/3815.rss">[CLASS SUGGESTION] The Abomination (Neutral)/The Madman (Unseen/Cultist)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
