<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Botanist (Blue Dragon) converts to Harvester (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244</link>
    <description>**Botanist** (Blue Dragon) - A plant expert capable of manipulating the cycle of life.

Passive:
**Whispering Willow** - If you are killed at night, you will be able to speak to the living as a ghost the next day only. However, you cannot hear other ghosts during that day.

Day Ability:
**Sweet Pansy** - Give a player a flower of peace, preventing them from using any offensive or killing abilities that night. (2 uses.)

Night Ability 1:

**Toxic Thorns** - Place a deadly thorn bush in the path of your visitors, causing injury to Cult or Unseen who visit you on that night. [Causes bleeding to Cultists and Poisoning to Unseen!] (4 Uses.)

_^ The reason for the different effects is so Cult can claim they&#39;ve been made to bleed BY Cult, and Unseen can claim they&#39;ve been poisoned BY Unseen._

Night Ability 2:

**Sympathy Bouquet** - If the player you select is killed on the same night you choose them, living players will be able to hear their ghost speaking for the next day only. However, they cannot hear other ghosts during that day. (Unlimited use.)

_^ Allows a player who just died to give &quot;final information&quot; to all living players._



Converts to...



**Harvester** (Unseen) - A grim grower who places greenery above humanity.

Day Ability:
**Fly Trap** - Lure a player to visit you that night. [Redirects their action to you at the end of the night.] (2 Uses.)

Night Ability 1:
**Snarled Vine** - Place a twisted vine in the path of your visitors, removing all of their immunites for that night. [Works on people drawn in with Fly Trap, as well.] (3 Uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**Corpse Flower** - Select a dead member of the Unseen to speak the next day, in the name of the &quot;ghost&quot; of whoever the Assassin kills that night. (2 uses.)

_^ So if the Assassin successfully kills any target, the DEAD Unseen member you selected will be prompted to speak IN THE NAME of that dead player as a ghost. In other words, they will impersonate the ghost of the Unseen&#39;s target the next day, faking the ability of &quot;Sympathy Bouquet&quot; above._

_tl;dr - This allows a dead Unseen member to &quot;Troll Box&quot; the player Unseen just killed._</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 05:00:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Botanist (Blue Dragon) converts to Harvester (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll think that over. (Not putting it off, will think about what specifically I’d tweak, etc.)</p>
<p>Fly Trap was essentially “they visit you if they use a night action”, but I can see how I wrote it incorrectly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 05:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23244-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244.rss">[Class Suggestion] Botanist (Blue Dragon) converts to Harvester (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Botanist (Blue Dragon) converts to Harvester (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dusked]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How would Fly Trap work? If used on the prince per-say, he would immediately know you’re a harvester.<br>
Possibly change it so it redirects their ability to yourself at the end of the night (Similar to the Court Wizard swapping or being Debauched)</p>
<p>Toxic Thorns is amazing in concept, but there is some issues. If you’re converted, the Cult Leader / Mastermind will now be bleeding/poisoned. Once discovered that they are bleeding/poisoned and killed/executed, they would immediately assume he converted you since he visited you.<br>
Considering it only has 2 uses, it should make you immune to death/conversion at night, since many BD classes have the ability to make themselves immune. (Butler, CW, Hunter ect.)</p>
<p>Making the Botanist a magic user would be cool, since it would buff Sorcerer and allow different magic user claims.</p>
<p>All in all it’s a really cool idea and adds some unique concepts to the game!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 04:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23244-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244.rss">[Class Suggestion] Botanist (Blue Dragon) converts to Harvester (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Botanist (Blue Dragon) converts to Harvester (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Botanist</strong> (Blue Dragon) - A plant expert capable of manipulating the cycle of life.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Whispering Willow</strong> - If you are killed at night, you will be able to speak to the living as a ghost the next day only. However, you cannot hear other ghosts during that day.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Sweet Pansy</strong> - Give a player a flower of peace, preventing them from using any offensive or killing abilities that night. (2 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:</p>
<p><strong>Toxic Thorns</strong> - Place a deadly thorn bush in the path of your visitors, causing injury to Cult or Unseen who visit you on that night. [Causes bleeding to Cultists and Poisoning to Unseen!] (4 Uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ The reason for the different effects is so Cult can claim they’ve been made to bleed BY Cult, and Unseen can claim they’ve been poisoned BY Unseen.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 2:</p>
<p><strong>Sympathy Bouquet</strong> - If the player you select is killed on the same night you choose them, living players will be able to hear their ghost speaking for the next day only. However, they cannot hear other ghosts during that day. (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p><em>^ Allows a player who just died to give “final information” to all living players.</em></p>
<p>Converts to…</p>
<p><strong>Harvester</strong> (Unseen) - A grim grower who places greenery above humanity.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Fly Trap</strong> - Lure a player to visit you that night. [Redirects their action to you at the end of the night.] (2 Uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Snarled Vine</strong> - Place a twisted vine in the path of your visitors, removing all of their immunites for that night. [Works on people drawn in with Fly Trap, as well.] (3 Uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Corpse Flower</strong> - Select a dead member of the Unseen to speak the next day, in the name of the “ghost” of whoever the Assassin kills that night. (2 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ So if the Assassin successfully kills any target, the DEAD Unseen member you selected will be prompted to speak IN THE NAME of that dead player as a ghost. In other words, they will impersonate the ghost of the Unseen’s target the next day, faking the ability of “Sympathy Bouquet” above.</em></p>
<p><em>tl;dr - This allows a dead Unseen member to “Troll Box” the player Unseen just killed.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 04:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23244-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-botanist-blue-dragon-converts-to-harvester-unseen/23244.rss">[Class Suggestion] Botanist (Blue Dragon) converts to Harvester (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
