<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>General Forum Improvement Suggestions</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207</link>
    <description>Just a few things I thought of, posting here for feedback and so it&#39;s a more permanent list than on the Discord .

1: Could we pin some links on the landing page, maybe in a small grey box near the bottom? Having quick access to things like i42&#39;s website, ToL&#39;s website, the KS page, the Greenlight page, the Wiki, etc. would be very nice.
2: For the mobile categories page, is it possible to only show only pinned posts instead of recent posts? This would make getting to important information much easier and clean up the mobile landing page, which really needs it in my opinion.
3: Can we have a separate &quot;Strategic Discussion&quot; forum? Lumping it in with Classes/Roles is a bit crowded.
4: The user card picture has a size of 580 pixels by 250 pixels, but the preferences page says it&#39;s 590 pixels by default. If that number on the preferences page could be corrected that would be convenient to those trying to add a user card picture.
5: Can we get options to sort posts by Likes as well as Replies and Views?
6: What exactly does &quot;Top&quot; use to determine which posts to display? I can&#39;t make heads or tails of it. A bit of clarification would be super cool.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 18:27:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>General Forum Improvement Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A few more:<br>
1: Can we get some way to show the original poster of a post on mobile? Right now it just shows the icon of the most recent reply.<br>
2: Can we get a way to disable having different boards from showing up in “Latest”? Because I don’t need to be notified about anything in Off-Topic or Roleplay.<br>
3: Higher trust level posters should be able to make posts of less than 20 characters.<br>
4: You should make the Roleplay board’s icon 3D, it looks weird as the only 2D one <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-207-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207.rss">General Forum Improvement Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>General Forum Improvement Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good suggestions –</p>
<p>For now, we probably only have time for <span class="hashtag">#1</span> to focus more on KS and development. However we’d definitely like to dive into this more at a later date<br>
I’ll bookmark this post.</p>
<p>The top is sorted by trending, from what I can tell. For that, we’re using the default mechanics of Discourse.</p>
<p>Just on my cell, excuse my brevity</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 03:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-207-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207.rss">General Forum Improvement Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>General Forum Improvement Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just a few things I thought of, posting here for feedback and so it’s a more permanent list than on the Discord .</p>
<p>1: Could we pin some links on the landing page, maybe in a small grey box near the bottom? Having quick access to things like i42’s website, ToL’s website, the KS page, the Greenlight page, the Wiki, etc. would be very nice.<br>
2: For the mobile categories page, is it possible to only show only pinned posts instead of recent posts? This would make getting to important information much easier and clean up the mobile landing page, which really needs it in my opinion.<br>
3: Can we have a separate “Strategic Discussion” forum? Lumping it in with Classes/Roles is a bit crowded.<br>
4: The user card picture has a size of 580 pixels by 250 pixels, but the preferences page says it’s 590 pixels by default. If that number on the preferences page could be corrected that would be convenient to those trying to add a user card picture.<br>
5: Can we get options to sort posts by Likes as well as Replies and Views?<br>
6: What exactly does “Top” use to determine which posts to display? I can’t make heads or tails of it. A bit of clarification would be super cool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 21:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-207-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/general-forum-improvement-suggestions/207.rss">General Forum Improvement Suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
