<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[class suggestion] The Chef</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965</link>
    <description>Name- Chef

Alignment/type-BD/support

Passive 1-leftovers- feed your leftovers to any wolves sent to you (immune to wolves)

Passive 2-

Day ability 1-Chefs choice (2 charges) Invite 3 players to eat your signature dish with you tonight, filling them with your delicious cooking and occupying them and yourself for the night (Players that are occupy immune will not attend)

Night ability 1-Room service (infinite charges) deliver food to a player&#39;s room tonight, healing them if they dont leave their room that night. 

Night ability 2- Brace- (2 charges) keep your trusty cleaver by your side tonight, bracing for an attack. If you&#39;re attacked tonight you will successfully defend yourself and the attacker will bleed. 

Win requirements-BD Win

I&#39;m really bad at the ability descriptions so here is how I imagine them-

CHEFS CHOICE- I imagine this to give those 3 players, as day turns to night, get a notification that either says &quot;you accepted an invitation to dinner tonight with (whoever else attended) and were occupied&quot; or &quot;you declined a dinner invitation tonight&quot; and the occupied targets obviously couldn&#39;t use an ability that night. 

The point of this (other than occupying targets) is that the chef gains information on who can and can&#39;t be occupied, the players that were occupied can also see who was at dinner so they can verify who is not immune to being occupied. (But they don&#39;t know who was invited that was immune, only chef knows who he invited that didn&#39;t show up)  
An even bigger idea would be if, during the night after the day this was used, the chef and the targets that were occupied are at a table and can talk to each other that night. And empty chairs are shown for each occupy immune player that didn&#39;t show up. 

I think this ability seems a bit...involved, and gives a BUNCH of information.  which is why I don&#39;t think it should have more than two charges. But the two days it&#39;s used, the chef can gather quite a bit of info on occupation status.  

ROOM SERVICE- With all the info the chef can get during the day, I wanted to make his night abilities a little less... crazy. So for this ability to heal the target, they would have to be in their room for the night, as in they&#39;d have to not use an ability or use an ability that doesn&#39;t count as &quot;visiting&quot; another player. So if a player wants healed the chef is capable of that, but at a price. Because if the chef could heal like the phys, it&#39;d be OP. And it makes sense, in order to get a healing benefit from room service, you&#39;d have to take it easy for the night. 

BRACE- i put this ability in because otherwise chef would be way too vulnerable as he can be converted or killed by anything but wolves. But not giving the ability 2 charges would be OP. So if you&#39;re a chef and feeling a little paranoid you can chose to stay awake at night with your cleaver and fend off and attack, also causing them to bleed (yay cleaver!). This does seem like the hunters trap ability however only players trying to attack and kill the chef this night will be stopped and start bleeding. This does not stop conversion, reaping, possession, etc. only abilities that will kill chef tonight. (Asassinate, emerald potion) 


Feel free to say how you&#39;d tweak the abilities if you feel this wouldn&#39;t be a balanced player. this is my first class suggestion so I&#39;m sure there are 200 reasons it wouldn&#39;t work. Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 16:52:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[class suggestion] The Chef</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you! I saw a bunch of suggestions that were all neutral so I wanted to think of a BD class to suggest. And heck the devs can tweak any of the abilities or passives the want. I only know how to suggest things not balance them haha</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 16:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7965-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965.rss">[class suggestion] The Chef</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[class suggestion] The Chef</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WillyCoyote]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> I Think Cook/Chef is the most lacking role in this game, I mean in every court people have to eat, right?</p>
<p>I think you should change Chef’s Choice to target 2 players, because 3 is too much (there is no skill in the game with 3 targets).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 16:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7965-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965.rss">[class suggestion] The Chef</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[class suggestion] The Chef</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whoops I didn’t know editing this would bump it. Was just editing it to put it in the class cup.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7965-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965.rss">[class suggestion] The Chef</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[class suggestion] The Chef</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Name- Chef</p>
<p>Alignment/type-BD/support</p>
<p>Passive 1-leftovers- feed your leftovers to any wolves sent to you (immune to wolves)</p>
<p>Passive 2-</p>
<p>Day ability 1-Chefs choice (2 charges) Invite 3 players to eat your signature dish with you tonight, filling them with your delicious cooking and occupying them and yourself for the night (Players that are occupy immune will not attend)</p>
<p>Night ability 1-Room service (infinite charges) deliver food to a player’s room tonight, healing them if they dont leave their room that night.</p>
<p>Night ability 2- Brace- (2 charges) keep your trusty cleaver by your side tonight, bracing for an attack. If you’re attacked tonight you will successfully defend yourself and the attacker will bleed.</p>
<p>Win requirements-BD Win</p>
<p>I’m really bad at the ability descriptions so here is how I imagine them-</p>
<p>CHEFS CHOICE- I imagine this to give those 3 players, as day turns to night, get a notification that either says “you accepted an invitation to dinner tonight with (whoever else attended) and were occupied” or “you declined a dinner invitation tonight” and the occupied targets obviously couldn’t use an ability that night.</p>
<p>The point of this (other than occupying targets) is that the chef gains information on who can and can’t be occupied, the players that were occupied can also see who was at dinner so they can verify who is not immune to being occupied. (But they don’t know who was invited that was immune, only chef knows who he invited that didn’t show up)<br>
An even bigger idea would be if, during the night after the day this was used, the chef and the targets that were occupied are at a table and can talk to each other that night. And empty chairs are shown for each occupy immune player that didn’t show up.</p>
<p>I think this ability seems a bit…involved, and gives a BUNCH of information.  which is why I don’t think it should have more than two charges. But the two days it’s used, the chef can gather quite a bit of info on occupation status.</p>
<p>ROOM SERVICE- With all the info the chef can get during the day, I wanted to make his night abilities a little less… crazy. So for this ability to heal the target, they would have to be in their room for the night, as in they’d have to not use an ability or use an ability that doesn’t count as “visiting” another player. So if a player wants healed the chef is capable of that, but at a price. Because if the chef could heal like the phys, it’d be OP. And it makes sense, in order to get a healing benefit from room service, you’d have to take it easy for the night.</p>
<p>BRACE- i put this ability in because otherwise chef would be way too vulnerable as he can be converted or killed by anything but wolves. But not giving the ability 2 charges would be OP. So if you’re a chef and feeling a little paranoid you can chose to stay awake at night with your cleaver and fend off and attack, also causing them to bleed (yay cleaver!). This does seem like the hunters trap ability however only players trying to attack and kill the chef this night will be stopped and start bleeding. This does not stop conversion, reaping, possession, etc. only abilities that will kill chef tonight. (Asassinate, emerald potion)</p>
<p>Feel free to say how you’d tweak the abilities if you feel this wouldn’t be a balanced player. this is my first class suggestion so I’m sure there are 200 reasons it wouldn’t work. Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 23:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7965-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-chef/7965.rss">[class suggestion] The Chef</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
