<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Include numbers in the postgame lobby</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/include-numbers-in-the-postgame-lobby/33445</link>
    <description>Since the game shifts to the postgame lobby very quickly after it ends, people usually discuss the game they just played there for a bit.  It&#39;s a bit awkward, though, to go from using people&#39;s in-game names to using their account names, since you have to constantly check the list of players to see who everyone was.

Since numbers are used for everything in-game, I suggest prepending player&#39;s numbers from the games in front of their account name when they speak in the postgame lobby, eg:

&quot;[1] Aquillion:  Good game!&quot;

That will make it easier to track discussions of the game without having to constantly cross-reference the list of users to remember who everyone was.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 18:34:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/include-numbers-in-the-postgame-lobby/33445.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Include numbers in the postgame lobby</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since the game shifts to the postgame lobby very quickly after it ends, people usually discuss the game they just played there for a bit.  It’s a bit awkward, though, to go from using people’s in-game names to using their account names, since you have to constantly check the list of players to see who everyone was.</p>
<p>Since numbers are used for everything in-game, I suggest prepending player’s numbers from the games in front of their account name when they speak in the postgame lobby, eg:</p>
<p>“[1] Aquillion:  Good game!”</p>
<p>That will make it easier to track discussions of the game without having to constantly cross-reference the list of users to remember who everyone was.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/include-numbers-in-the-postgame-lobby/33445/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/include-numbers-in-the-postgame-lobby/33445/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-33445-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/include-numbers-in-the-postgame-lobby/33445.rss">Include numbers in the postgame lobby</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
