<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How do you play hunter?</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432</link>
    <description>Been playing about a week, new to social deduction games. The hunter class seems off to me. It&#39;s BD but in majority of games I&#39;ve played with a Hunter it brings nothing but pain to the BD team. Sometimes they trap a hostile n1 and it just unceremoniously bleeds to death d3 because everyone refused to heal the unconfirmed guy asking for it but many more times I see the same thing happen to a friendly BD. 

I don&#39;t know what situation arises where you know to wolf somebody where they just wouldn&#39;t already be put up and executed on the stand within 2 days. If you&#39;re wrong with your wolf or traps you have no consequences unlike the knight who dies if he picks the wrong target to kill or the prince who loses his execute.

If your team gets it wrong and executes you they lose 2 members. I think I&#39;ve seen retribution kill an evil target one time so I see how it happens but I&#39;ve seen it kill a friendly what feels like 90% of the time. 

If you think you&#39;re vulnerable and trap yourself you will injure any teammates who also picked up on that and move to protect you (right? I&#39;m not sure what the exact mechanics on trap are).

Worst case scenario is you could trap yourself n1 n2, bleed 2 bds, wolf 2 more bd by accident n3 and n4, and then get converted and continue unleashing hell on your old teammates. Or you bleed 4 teammates and then are put on the stand and executed (and idk how you get out of it once your deemed sus as a hunter), and take another teammate out with you for 6 possible bd deaths on d5 all caused by you inadvertently. 

Also when someone visits you and gets trapped, they just know your a hunter (unless I&#39;m mistaken and something else can cause you to bleed the same way when you visit).

And then on top of this your skills both have 2 uses which means if you mess up the early game in any of these ways, you can&#39;t really help recover because you no more night utility.

I&#39;m new so my perspective may not be the best and I don&#39;t know the history of balancing these sorts of games but it seems to me that hunter would make more sense as evil or neutral, while the Poacher class seems like a slam dunk for BD (maybe with butlers they give too many occupies for BD for balance).

Plz help I am not a huntard by choice but by ignorance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 06:10:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How do you play hunter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m of the opinion that Hunters should claim publicly fairly early, especially if the court is otherwise silent during the day. Hunter is very rarely claimed by scum because it’s a unique role with the ability to kill. So, if a hunter exists in the game and you fake claim it, the real hunter is going to wolf you and kill you. Because of this, Hunter claims tend to be pretty safe in believe in cult games. In unseen games, there is always the risk the hunter was converted, but this is a fairly low chance. It’s also safer for Hunters to out themselves than most, since evil classes risk your traps if they try to kill you.</p>
<p>In any case, if the King is proves themselves, you should definitely let at least the King know your role, so they can pass on info from other roles to you and let you do the dirty work without having to out themselves.</p>
<p>One final thing: A common strategy is ‘baiting’ people to visit you.  This strategy can work but it can also backfire spectacularly.  It’s more likely to work when you are going hard for BD; giving good advice, pointing out things, voting correctly, etc… in such cases you are a more likely target so the odds of getting a bad guy and not a good guy are higher.  The problem is, you’re also far more likely to attract the attention of good roles trying to protect you.  I personally think this is too risk, but if you do want to bait, this is the way to do it.</p>
<p>The bad way is to try to look suspicious, or ask for protection, or really anything else.  This is just as likely to get BD protective or investigative classes killed on your traps than it is to catch bad guys.  Traps should mostly be a defense to give you the freedom to publicly reveal early, not an offensive weapon.  You have your wolf for when you want to kill offensively.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 06:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4432-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432.rss">How do you play hunter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do you play hunter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maroon" data-post="4" data-topic="4432">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Maroon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>roles</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>Inaudible scream</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 05:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4432-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432.rss">How do you play hunter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do you play hunter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maroon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you’re asking how do <strong>I</strong> play hunter, the answer is “badly.”</p>
<p>If you’re asking how the good hunter players I’ve seen played them, it seemed to be about getting a good feel for who wasn’t trustworthy and bleeding 'em at the right time. It’s a nice late-game class when everyone understands what roles players are claiming and people start getting a sense of who can and can’t be trusted; one or two key kills at that point will flip the result of the whole game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 04:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4432-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432.rss">How do you play hunter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do you play hunter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I tend to kill more scum than bd as hunter, it should be treated like Veteran from town of Salem</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 23:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4432-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432.rss">How do you play hunter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do you play hunter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You don’t have to use your abilities every night ;p</p>
<p>Also, Wolfing can mostly be used when Scum Reading people, since most of the time if you were to present your scum read in court no one would believe you.</p>
<p>Traps can be used when you feel in danger (And no that’s not n1)</p>
<p>Finally his Ability titled “Retribution” can be used in order to get possible scum voting you up. You could claim something completely different in order to fool scum or claim your class and punish those who mislynched you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 23:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4432-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432.rss">How do you play hunter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do you play hunter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LiesnDeceit420]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Been playing about a week, new to social deduction games. The hunter class seems off to me. It’s BD but in majority of games I’ve played with a Hunter it brings nothing but pain to the BD team. Sometimes they trap a hostile n1 and it just unceremoniously bleeds to death d3 because everyone refused to heal the unconfirmed guy asking for it but many more times I see the same thing happen to a friendly BD.</p>
<p>I don’t know what situation arises where you know to wolf somebody where they just wouldn’t already be put up and executed on the stand within 2 days. If you’re wrong with your wolf or traps you have no consequences unlike the knight who dies if he picks the wrong target to kill or the prince who loses his execute.</p>
<p>If your team gets it wrong and executes you they lose 2 members. I think I’ve seen retribution kill an evil target one time so I see how it happens but I’ve seen it kill a friendly what feels like 90% of the time.</p>
<p>If you think you’re vulnerable and trap yourself you will injure any teammates who also picked up on that and move to protect you (right? I’m not sure what the exact mechanics on trap are).</p>
<p>Worst case scenario is you could trap yourself n1 n2, bleed 2 bds, wolf 2 more bd by accident n3 and n4, and then get converted and continue unleashing hell on your old teammates. Or you bleed 4 teammates and then are put on the stand and executed (and idk how you get out of it once your deemed sus as a hunter), and take another teammate out with you for 6 possible bd deaths on d5 all caused by you inadvertently.</p>
<p>Also when someone visits you and gets trapped, they just know your a hunter (unless I’m mistaken and something else can cause you to bleed the same way when you visit).</p>
<p>And then on top of this your skills both have 2 uses which means if you mess up the early game in any of these ways, you can’t really help recover because you no more night utility.</p>
<p>I’m new so my perspective may not be the best and I don’t know the history of balancing these sorts of games but it seems to me that hunter would make more sense as evil or neutral, while the Poacher class seems like a slam dunk for BD (maybe with butlers they give too many occupies for BD for balance).</p>
<p>Plz help I am not a huntard by choice but by ignorance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 23:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4432-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/how-do-you-play-hunter/4432.rss">How do you play hunter?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
