<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468</link>
    <description>The Ashe thread is not possible to use for turbo and semi unfair. For the hosts and for the players. So I made this brand new Grand Idea FoL Turbo Thread. Turbo hosts can choose from this list and the Ashe list.
# Rules:
* All posts must contain a class. This could be a new one or an existing one from the Ashe thread. If you want to transfer classes over go ahead but they are allowed to be rejected by an FoL Moderator or me, the creator of the thread. Hosts can reject any classes they want.
* Bastard Mechanics can added to the game but like classes, can be rejected by me or the FoL Moderator team. Hosts can reject any Bastard Mechanics they want.
* You must include a number of classes/bastard mechanics at the top of your class. 
* [Class Template](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-template/47799) use this for the class template.
* [color=red]**Classes can NOT prevent others from spawning, unless you created both classes or the other player gave permission.**[/color]
* [color=red]**You can edit parts of classes in the future.**[/color]
* [color=red]**Consecutive duplicate posts off a class is banned unless that class is similar if not vanilla town.**[/color]
# Information:
If a converted class is not given, Neutrals and scum faction classes should automatically be considered immune, and Blue Dragon should be considered convertable, with their unseen version having the same abilities that their Blue Dragon form does.

Converted classes can spawn at the start of a game.

There is no limit to the number of factions that can appear.

The King can be any faction of those that appear in the game, even new ones. If a Buttered Popcorn faction member is rolled, you can have a Buttered Popcorn King. The chance for each individual King to appear is always the same as any other King.

# Extra Rules:
* All classes can&#39;t just be &quot;The Alchemist&quot; as it can get annoying for the person hosting the game. All classes must show abilities and others. If you want to add a post restriction to a class. Post the class in the thread and add a new passive or ability that you want to.
* Classic Wincons for factions - These can be changed if wanted:
**Good Factions:** *Your objective is to defeat the evil faction(s) and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
**Evil Factions:** *Your objective is to defeat the good faction(s), any other evil faction(s) and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
**Neutrals:** *Survive* - This is just the base wincon a player will get if a wincon is not stated, I recommend putting a custom one for Neutral classes.
**Neutral Killers:** *Defeat the main factions and any other Neutrals that dare stand in your way.*

#### And to start this thread:
**1**
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;steblue&quot;&gt;The Butler&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;steblue&quot;&gt;Blue Dragon Offensive&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Dutiful (Passive)&lt;/strong&gt; - Immune to occupation and target changing.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nightshade Wine (Day)&lt;/strong&gt; - Poison The King, causing him to die tonight if not healed. The king will not be informed if he is poisoned. If the King is apart of the Blue Dragon, you will commit suicide. - 1 use, available starting Day 2&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Serve Wine (Night)&lt;/strong&gt; - Occupy a player by getting them drunk. - Infinite uses&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Concentrated Wine (Night)&lt;/strong&gt; - Throw a party, occupying all players who visit you tonight (Bypasses occupy immunity). - 2 uses&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Your objective is to defeat the Evil Faction(s), and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 11:36:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Post Count makes it harder. Just keep it class count otherwise people who put more than 1 class in one always mess it up from that.</h1>
<h1>34</h1>
<hr>
<h1><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/15">Vanilla Town</a></h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 11:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Emilia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>31<br>
Vanilla god<br>
Everything you say in your classcard becomes true<br>
<em>you have already won</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 07:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But post count makes it so much easier to roll, as you use a random number generator,  and go to that post number, by a url. Someone chicks fairly easily make a thing that just takes in a url for the post, the number of posts, and output a link that leads directly to a randomly chosen post in the topic.</p>
<h1>30</h1>
<p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/6?u=simon">Mafia Goonitzen</a><br>
Named Litizen with a mafia faction and win con</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 04:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>That’s 30.</h1>
<h1>31</h1>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Rule Breaker</h1>
<p><strong>Suicide (Passive)</strong> - You will commit suicide at the start of Day 4.<br>
<em>Get modkilled or end the game before Day 4</em></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<p>It’s not based on the post count it’s based on the class count.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 02:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h6>(Its post <span class="hashtag">#24</span>, so it <em>should</em> be 24, but yall keep doubling up in posts)</h6>
<h1>26</h1>
<blockquote>
<h2>Mr Rogers</h2>
<h3>Town Beloved</h3>
<p><strong>The Neighborhood (Passive)</strong> - You have a night chat, starting with yourself and 1 random person with whom you can win (town/benign neutral). Anyone in this chat gains the night ability <strong>Sharing is Caring</strong><br>
<strong>Permanent Resident (Passive)</strong> - If you would leave your night chat, you are instead added back into it at the start of the next night. Any actions you use instead are not used if you are not in a night chat. <em>If you are converted, you are added to the scum night chat if there is one, but instead become a neutral with the win condition of “Survive” and a passive stating that the first time you would die, you do not.</em><br>
<strong>Welcome! (Day)</strong> - Add target player to your night chat(s). this doesn’t count as a visit, and cannot be redirected. This does nothing, and doesnt count as using an action, if you are not in a night chat - infinite uses, once per day<br>
<strong>Lets Play a Game! (Day)</strong> - occupy target player in a night chat with you, bypassing occupy immunity. - 3 uses, once per day. cannot be used in conjunction with <strong>Welcome!</strong><br>
<strong>Sorry, Time to Leave (Night)</strong> - Remove target player from your night chat(s). If this would target someone not in a night chat with you, it instead targets a random person who <em>is</em> in a night chat with you. - infinite uses, once per night, at the end of the night.<br>
<strong>Sharing is Caring</strong> - You may ask the host to show target player who is in a night chat with you your <em>full</em> class card. This cannot be framed, and you cannot give fake cards with this ability. If an NK or other not-evil-faction scum uses this on you, you may choose to become a neutral as stated in the passive <strong>Permanent Resident</strong> - infinite uses, any amount of times per night, upon use (host should give the other person the card when this is used or close after if possible)</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>That’s 28</h1>
<h1>29</h1>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1>Unlucky Host</h1>
<p><strong>This player can pick their class</strong><br>
<em>They don’t win if they don’t pick a class lol</em></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(unless one is the converted form of the other they should be separate posts, and even then they should be given separate numbers. the purpose of this is so the mod can generate a random number and go to that post number)</p>
<h2>25</h2>
<h1><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/6?u=simon">Litizen</a></h1>
<h3>except they’re neutral with the wincon of: survive</h3>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>25</h1>
<h1>The Circus Leader</h1>
<p><strong>Cult Special</strong><br>
<strong>Train (Passive)</strong>  - Instead of the traditional Cult Alts system, the converted will retain a random ability when they are converted.<br>
<strong>Brainwash (Night)</strong>  - Change target player into the Cult version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown<br>
<strong>Blood of Mithras (Night)</strong>  - Kill a Cult player and a non-Cult player. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
<h1>26</h1>
<p>All scum are now lone wolves. Reroll this slot.</p>
<p>Lost Wolf (Passive) - You do not know who your scummates are. You are not in the factional chat.</p>
<h1>27</h1>
<p>The Demon (Unofficial Class)<br>
Neutral Killer<br>
Cloak Of Mithras (Passive) - Immune to death at night, occupation and target changing.<br>
Haemophilia (Day) - Increases the power of Funeral Pyre tonight. - 3 uses, 1 day cooldown<br>
Funeral Pyre (Night) - Set your target ablaze, killing them. If Haemophilia is used, the target is immune to visits from others except you, and anyone who attempts to visit them is also killed by the flames. - Infinite uses<br>
Your objective is to defeat all factions and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>24</h1>
<h1>The Mustardmind</h1>
<p><strong>Unseen Special</strong><br>
<strong>Lurking Presence (Passive)</strong>  - If you are killed within the first 3 nights your next in line will take your place as Mastermind.<br>
<strong>Dirty Work (Day)</strong>  If there are no more Unseen members left, you can become The Assassin at the beginning of the night. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Convert (Night)</strong>  - Change target player into the Unseen version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>22</h1>
<h1>The Witch</h1>
<p><strong>Neutral Offensive</strong><br>
<strong>Determined (Passive)</strong>  - You are immune to most occupation and redirection abilities.<br>
<strong>Innocent Hag (Passive)</strong>  - You wll appear as a Court Wizard to all checks.<br>
<strong>Witchcraft (Night)</strong>  - Control someone each night. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the good faction(s) and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
<h1>23</h1>
<p>The Lost Assassin<br>
Unseen Killer<br>
Lost Wolf (Passive) - You do not know who your scummates are. You are not in the factional chat.<br>
Assassinate (Night) - Kill a player. - Infinite uses<br>
2-for-1 (Night) - Kill two target players. - 1 use (shared)<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>21</h1>
<h1>The Court Wizard</h1>
<p><strong>Blue Dragon Support</strong><br>
<strong>Magical Barrier (Night)</strong>  - Protect a player from negative effects and conversion tonight. Does not prevent attacks. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Ice Ward (Night)</strong>  - Prevent anyone else from visiting your target. - 2 uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>20</h1>
<h1>The Fool</h1>
<p><strong>Neutral Social</strong><br>
<strong>Trickery (Passive)</strong>  - Immune to being occupied at night. Additionally, the night after your execution, all players who voted to execute you will be redirected to visit themselves.<br>
<strong>Masquerade (Night)</strong>  - Appear as the class, faction and type of your target to investigations tonight. Abilities that change the apparent class of your target will not affect Masquerade. Additionally, if you die you will also appear as the class. You will not know the class of your target. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to be executed for treason.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>19</h1>
<h1>The Mercenary</h1>
<p><strong>Neutral Support</strong><br>
<strong>Looking for Work (Passive)</strong>  - You have a predetermined target. If your original target dies, you will randomly select another.<br>
<strong>Failure (Passive)</strong>  - If your original target and your new target die, you will commit suicide.<br>
<strong>Stand Guard (Night)</strong>  - Protect your target from visits, and grant yourself immunity to death tonight. - 4 uses<br>
<strong>Rebound (Night)</strong>  - Kill a player who accused your target of treason earlier in the day. - 1 use<br>
<em>Your objective is to ensure that your target remains alive until the end of the game, your target is [x].</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>18</h1>
<p>Lucky GM! You choose what class or effect should this spot have.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><big><strong>17</strong></big></p>
<h1><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/17">Mafia Goon</a></h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 22:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><big><strong>16</strong></big></p>
<blockquote>
<p><big><font color="red"><strong>Mafia Goon</strong></font></big><br>
<font color="red"><strong>Mafia Useless</strong></font></p>
<p><strong>Useless (Passive)</strong> - You have no abilities, but can preform the factional kill.</p>
<p><em>Your objective is to defeat the Good Faction(s), any other evil faction(s), and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GamerPoke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>15</h1>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><strong><font color="black">Zynx The Fella</font></strong></h1>
<p><strong><font color="black">Whisperers Killer</font></strong><br>
<strong>Terror (Passive)</strong> - Players with paranoia will be redirected to themselves if they try to visit you, not bypassing immunity. Additionally, any players with paranoia will be attacked if they no action. Players will not be notified when they get paranoia.<br>
<strong>Chaotic (Passive)</strong> - Immune to redirection,<br>
occupation, and death.<br>
<strong>Spook (Day)</strong> - Inflict paranoia on a player, and will take effect at the beginning of the night. [Infinite Uses]<br>
<strong>Howl (Day)</strong> - Kill all players with paranoia tonight bypassing kill immunities. You can use this along with the other day ability. [1 Use]<br>
<strong>Nightmare (Night)</strong> - Occupy a player. [Infinite Uses]<br>
<strong>Eclipse (Night)</strong> - Kill a player while occupying them. [3 Uses]<br>
<em>You win when you have killed everyone who hasn’t won yet. (NK who is against people winning)</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can repost that with a class if you want.</p>
<hr>
<h1>14</h1>
<h1><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/4">Vanilla Town</a></h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 20:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can we just add no bastard mechanics</p>
<p>also change it so no classes can have permanent death immunity(only one time immunity) cause trying to get people to follow your wagon is a fucking pain in the ass</p>
<hr>
<p>13</p>
<blockquote>
<p><big> <strong><font color="steblue">Mayor</font></strong> </big><br>
<strong><font color="steblue">BD Social</font></strong></p>
<p><strong>Reveal (Day)</strong> - Reveal yourself as the <strong><font color="steblue">Mayor</font></strong> and permanently make your vote count as 3. You cannot be lynched the day you reveal and may choose to do so right before you get lynched. This cannot be prevented in any way and you cannot lose or gain charges through other players. [1 Use]<br>
<strong>Send Agent (Night)</strong> - Send an agent after a player, learning who they visit tonight. This cannot be occupied or redirected directly, and you will learn who your agent was redirected to if they were redirected or if they were prevented. This ability will be disabled upon revealing as the <strong><font color="steblue">Mayor</font></strong>. [2 Uses]<br>
<em>Your goal is to defeat the scum factions and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 20:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>11</h1>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="cyan">Mastermind of the Killing Games</font></h1>
<p><strong>Danganronpa Special</strong><br>
<strong>Abuse of Regulations (Passive)</strong> - If you are lynched day 1, you will be able to still talk in the Danganronpa Chat at night.<br>
<strong>Impaled (Passive)</strong> - You are death immune at night once.<br>
<strong>Convert (Night)</strong> - Convert a player into the Danganronpa faction. This can not be used if there is already 3 members of the Danganronpa faction. - Infinite Uses (1 day cooldown)</p>
</blockquote>
<h1>12</h1>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="cyan">Masterminds Spy</font></h1>
<p><strong>Danganronpa Killer</strong><br>
<strong>Apprentice (Passive)</strong> - If the Mastermind dies, you will become the new Mastermind.<br>
<strong>Blackened Murder (Night)</strong> - Kill a player. - Infinite Uses.<br>
<strong>Chapter 3 (Night)</strong> - Kill two players. - 1 use.</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 18:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lightsin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>10</h1>
<blockquote>
<h2><font color="orange"> Tachanka </font></h2>
<p><strong><font color="orange"> Town Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Bulletproof Shield(Passive)</strong> Immune to Death at night when LMG is active.<br>
<strong>Pocket Jäger(Passive)</strong>  Immune to bleeding.<br>
<strong>LMG MOUNTED AND LOADED(Night)</strong> Mount your LMG, bathing your visitors that would dare take the hostage with lead.<br>
<em>standard town goal</em><br>
<strong>Immune to Conversion</strong></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 19:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>9</h1>
<h1><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/5">Vanilla Town</a></h1>
<hr>
<p>Everyone edit your posts so they are a number lower. I’m getting a moderator to delete Merc’s post.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/simon">@Simon</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 17:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>8</h1>
<p>I propose that posts without classes be treated as “reroll this slot” classes, but not effecting the numbers, so that part goes untouched (i.e. continue numbering as if posts without classes had a class with the correct number)</p>
<h1><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/6?u=simon">Litizen</a></h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 17:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><big><strong>7</strong></big></p>
<blockquote>
<p><big><font color="green"><strong>Panicked War Veteran</strong></font></big><br>
<font color="gray"><strong>Town Killer</strong></font></p>
<p><strong>Paranoia</strong> (Passive) - If a player were to attack you at night they will die with you.</p>
<p><strong>Shoot</strong> (Night) - Attack a player. Disables your <strong>Paranoia</strong> passive. You cannot leave a deathnote with this ability. <em>(1 Use)</em></p>
<p><em>Defeat the scum faction and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Converts into <font color="purple"><strong>The Enforcer</strong></font>, <font color="red"><strong>Bouncer</strong></font>, <font color="solblue"><strong>Knight</strong></font>, or any offensive based conversion for other factions.</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 17:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><big><strong>6</strong></big></p>
<blockquote>
<p><big><font color="green"><strong>Ex-Bodyguard</strong></font></big><br>
<font color="grey"><strong>Town Support</strong></font></p>
<p><strong>One-Shot Bulletproof</strong> (Passive) - Immune to death once. When you are attacked you will be informed of it.</p>
<p><strong>Scream</strong> (Day) - Make a player unable to perform any day actions. They will not be informed. <em>(3 Uses)</em></p>
<p><strong>Guard</strong> (Night) - Redirect all attacks toward the target to yourself. <em>(Infinite Uses)</em></p>
<p><em>Defeat the scum faction and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Converts into <font color="purple"><strong>The Enforcer</strong></font>, <font color="red"><strong>Bouncer</strong></font>, <font color="solblue"><strong>Knight</strong></font>, or any other support based conversion for other factions.</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 17:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75468-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/grand-idea-fol-turbo-edition/75468.rss">Grand Idea FoL - Turbo Edition</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
