<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>This is what I love about deceptive abilities</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548</link>
    <description>I just played one of the funnest games ever.  I got converted n1 to Illusionist (my favorite class) and telepathied that a player was linked and took 20 seconds to claim Knight.  Despite his protestations that Psychic was converted, he got executed (and was Princess).  I chose something that wasn&#39;t Psychic as my claim (of course), then poss jumped leaving a Psychic corpse with logs identifying himself as &quot;The NOT converted Psychic&quot;, it was so funny because people were raging that the psychic was a gamethrower and was getting reported.

Poss ended up possessing both assassins though, MM got wolfed and it was BD King vs Poss.  So BD won.  Was still fun.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>This is what I love about deceptive abilities</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SabreOverdrive]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>**Most NK’s are usually are hard to win on ToL, **<br>
Sorc is probably the most hardest, as we all know from the inq that always appears<br>
Reaper is probably the moderate due to the Silence effect of reaped players but it’s scattered day abilities.<br>
Poss is the easiest due to switching to a confirmed BD and taking their will and knowing their class, they can also facelift to make it look like a BD died but a Poss actually did, so then they can make it look like a BD just died, but it was a jump.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47548-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548.rss">This is what I love about deceptive abilities</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This is what I love about deceptive abilities</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is why I think Possessor currently has the most potential.</p>
<p>Personally I think that Sorcerer should have a day faction check and a visit check as a side effect of magic cloak.</p>
<p>Reaper should be able to read and edit the logs of reaped player’s before their body dies. It would definitely make him harder to identify and would make chill more useful.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47548-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548.rss">This is what I love about deceptive abilities</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This is what I love about deceptive abilities</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just played one of the funnest games ever.  I got converted n1 to Illusionist (my favorite class) and telepathied that a player was linked and took 20 seconds to claim Knight.  Despite his protestations that Psychic was converted, he got executed (and was Princess).  I chose something that wasn’t Psychic as my claim (of course), then poss jumped leaving a Psychic corpse with logs identifying himself as “The NOT converted Psychic”, it was so funny because people were raging that the psychic was a gamethrower and was getting reported.</p>
<p>Poss ended up possessing both assassins though, MM got wolfed and it was BD King vs Poss.  So BD won.  Was still fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47548-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/this-is-what-i-love-about-deceptive-abilities/47548.rss">This is what I love about deceptive abilities</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
