<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[New Class] The Retired - Blue Dragon Investigative</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791</link>
    <description>**The Retired v1.0**

There were always stories about the man who lived at the edge of the town, that he did so to escape the law, that he did so to grind up victims, that he did so to hold some dark secret. Many of these stories never seem to be true, though he always had to live with it; he just wanted to be free of the whispers and rumours. The Retired knew that in his old days, he only had a bit of time remaining before he would die suspicious. He knew that someday his past would catch up with him, no matter how long it takes to wash yourself clean of what you&#39;ve done, 40 years is still not enough. One day he heard stories that there was a villainous shadow at work in Castle Aldiart, and he determined that this would be his chance to show his ways have changed; he had a life now and he would be damned if others would be dragged into what he left.

&gt; Class Name : The Retired
&gt; Class Faction : Blue Dragon
&gt; Class Type : Investigative
&gt; 
&gt; Win Condition: Have all the threats to the Blue Dragon eliminated.
&gt; 
&gt; **Passives:**
&gt; Suspicious Past: The Retired always shows up as Suspicious to Investigative abilities.
&gt; 
&gt; Never Again: If The Retired would be Converted, instead they would be Killed.
&gt; 
&gt; **Day Abilities**
&gt; Eye for Treachery (Day, Unlimited)
&gt; Target a player. You find out if they used a Day Ability at the end of the day.
&gt; 
&gt; **Night Abilities**
&gt; Letter For You (Night, 2 Uses)
&gt; Target a player other than **The King** or **The Prince** (you will be prevented if it is used on the latter). If you die that player receives a list of everyone who targeted you that night. If **The Mastermind** is still **In the Shadows** this will not reveal them.
&gt; 
&gt; Underworld Psychology (Night, Unlimited)
&gt; The next day whenever a player is Tried you find out exactly how many of the Execute votes match up with the Executed&#39;s faction; even if they weren&#39;t Executed.

The Retired originally was built as a Social class, but he slowly turned into an investigative. I had trouble coming up with day abilities that didn&#39;t day prove and I decided to go a different route entirely. **The Retired** is an old Unseen/Cult who managed to make it out of the life alive and has tried to live a normal life.

It has a series of Investigative abilities that push Blue Dragon to make executions, and while it is difficult to utilize, a series of used **Underworld Psychology** can help the Blue Dragon start to narrow things down. Their ability to find Day uses with **Eye for Treachery** helps them to find Assassins, Cult Leaders and other nasty people. **Letter For You** allows them to provide information to other, more trustworthy people on the death of **The Retired**.

Ultimately the class is fairly difficult to play but a well placed **Letter For You** can find dangerous targets and confirm others while providing information to Blue Dragon that isn&#39;t always readily found.

By sheer virtue of it existing, it adds doubt to investigative claims and adds some claimspace to desperate Unseen and Cult.

I&#39;m not really sure where else to take it, but I love the idea of a Miller in ToL just for the extra claimspace. Stepping on the toes of The Noble is really easy to do (with how broad the Noble is). Any ideas would be appreciated.
 
[details=&quot;Changelog&quot;]
v1.0 Created
[/details]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:48:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Retired - Blue Dragon Investigative</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hubaris" data-post="1" data-topic="72791">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hubaris/40/3990_2.png" class="avatar"> Hubaris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Suspicious Past: The Retired always shows up as Suspicious to Investigative abilities.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Eyy Miller in ToL I like this already</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hubaris" data-post="1" data-topic="72791">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hubaris/40/3990_2.png" class="avatar"> Hubaris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Never Again: If The Retired would be Converted, instead they would be Killed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Interesting concept, I’d prefer it was a day-ability rather than a passive however</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hubaris" data-post="1" data-topic="72791">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hubaris/40/3990_2.png" class="avatar"> Hubaris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Eye for Treachery (Day, Unlimited)<br>
Target a player. You find out if they used a Day Ability at the end of the day.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hubaris" data-post="1" data-topic="72791">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hubaris/40/3990_2.png" class="avatar"> Hubaris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Letter For You (Night, 2 Uses)<br>
Target a player other than <strong>The King</strong> or <strong>The Prince</strong> (you will be prevented if it is used on the latter). If you die that player receives a list of everyone who targeted you that night. If <strong>The Mastermind</strong> is still <strong>In the Shadows</strong> this will not reveal them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is somewhat similar to will-o-wisp before its current status. It is a very strong ability in its current state</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hubaris" data-post="1" data-topic="72791">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hubaris/40/3990_2.png" class="avatar"> Hubaris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The next day whenever a player is Tried you find out exactly how many of the Execute votes match up with the Executed’s faction; even if they weren’t Executed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is also a fairly strong ability. Telling everyone to execute and having say a BD die will reveal how many neutrals/ evils are left in-game, and instead of getting stronger, it gets weaker overtime.</p>
<p>I give this a 7/10, I like the direction you are taking with this class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72791-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791.rss">[New Class] The Retired - Blue Dragon Investigative</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Retired - Blue Dragon Investigative</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubaris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Retired v1.0</strong></p>
<p>There were always stories about the man who lived at the edge of the town, that he did so to escape the law, that he did so to grind up victims, that he did so to hold some dark secret. Many of these stories never seem to be true, though he always had to live with it; he just wanted to be free of the whispers and rumours. The Retired knew that in his old days, he only had a bit of time remaining before he would die suspicious. He knew that someday his past would catch up with him, no matter how long it takes to wash yourself clean of what you’ve done, 40 years is still not enough. One day he heard stories that there was a villainous shadow at work in Castle Aldiart, and he determined that this would be his chance to show his ways have changed; he had a life now and he would be damned if others would be dragged into what he left.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Class Name : The Retired<br>
Class Faction : Blue Dragon<br>
Class Type : Investigative</p>
<p>Win Condition: Have all the threats to the Blue Dragon eliminated.</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
Suspicious Past: The Retired always shows up as Suspicious to Investigative abilities.</p>
<p>Never Again: If The Retired would be Converted, instead they would be Killed.</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities</strong><br>
Eye for Treachery (Day, Unlimited)<br>
Target a player. You find out if they used a Day Ability at the end of the day.</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities</strong><br>
Letter For You (Night, 2 Uses)<br>
Target a player other than <strong>The King</strong> or <strong>The Prince</strong> (you will be prevented if it is used on the latter). If you die that player receives a list of everyone who targeted you that night. If <strong>The Mastermind</strong> is still <strong>In the Shadows</strong> this will not reveal them.</p>
<p>Underworld Psychology (Night, Unlimited)<br>
The next day whenever a player is Tried you find out exactly how many of the Execute votes match up with the Executed’s faction; even if they weren’t Executed.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Retired originally was built as a Social class, but he slowly turned into an investigative. I had trouble coming up with day abilities that didn’t day prove and I decided to go a different route entirely. <strong>The Retired</strong> is an old Unseen/Cult who managed to make it out of the life alive and has tried to live a normal life.</p>
<p>It has a series of Investigative abilities that push Blue Dragon to make executions, and while it is difficult to utilize, a series of used <strong>Underworld Psychology</strong> can help the Blue Dragon start to narrow things down. Their ability to find Day uses with <strong>Eye for Treachery</strong> helps them to find Assassins, Cult Leaders and other nasty people. <strong>Letter For You</strong> allows them to provide information to other, more trustworthy people on the death of <strong>The Retired</strong>.</p>
<p>Ultimately the class is fairly difficult to play but a well placed <strong>Letter For You</strong> can find dangerous targets and confirm others while providing information to Blue Dragon that isn’t always readily found.</p>
<p>By sheer virtue of it existing, it adds doubt to investigative claims and adds some claimspace to desperate Unseen and Cult.</p>
<p>I’m not really sure where else to take it, but I love the idea of a Miller in ToL just for the extra claimspace. Stepping on the toes of The Noble is really easy to do (with how broad the Noble is). Any ideas would be appreciated.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Changelog</summary>
<p>v1.0 Created</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72791-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-retired-blue-dragon-investigative/72791.rss">[New Class] The Retired - Blue Dragon Investigative</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
