<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483</link>
    <description>**SFOL Echoes**

NOTE: This is not a bastard game, nor closed roles.

Game is built off of the foundation of Throne of Lies, using Conversion, King, Royal Blood, etc.
Flavor is from the Fire Emblem Game: Echoes, Shadows of Valentia


I tried making town classes as least confirming as possible.





[details=&quot;Basic Plan&quot;]
King

“Good” King (Scum): King Rudolf (30%) 
“Evil” King (Town): Chancellor Desaix (70%)
If Neut is elected: Specific

Unconvertible + Guaranteed
Prince: Berkut
Paladin: Fernand

3 classes cap for non-Unique

Common Roles: (Doesn’t have same abilities but fills the niche)

Rigelians ---&gt; Members of The Deliverance (Conversion)

Hunter: Slayde ---&gt; Mycen
Knight: Knight ----&gt; Lukas
Sheriff: Cavalier ---&gt; Mathilda
Observer: Arcanist ---&gt; Kliff 
Princess: Sky Knight ---&gt; Clair
Butler: Myrmidon ---&gt; Python (Flavor of card changes to a Archer)
Drunk: Mercenary ---&gt; Gray
Court Wizard: Mage ---&gt; Luthier
Physician: Cleric ----&gt; Silque
Mystic: Nuibaba ----&gt; Delthea
Squire: Soldier ---&gt; Forsythe
Priest: Rinea ---&gt; Tatiana (Flavor of card changes to a Cleric)
Special Niche: Baron ---&gt; Ezekiel
Special Niche: Archer ---&gt; Tobin


Starting Deliverance (Cap varies)
Clive - (Killer)
Alm - (De facto leader) (Converter)(Always replaceable)
1 Random non-Unique Deliverance

**You cannot gain or receive Nobility status by changing classes.**

Neutrals

Bandits - Survivor Neutrals (Possibly not needed) (Might change to NPCs)
Faye, the Lover - ToS Witch (Ensure Alm survives by the end) ---&gt; Faye
Jedah - ToL Scorned (Ensure targets get lynched OR survive to see Duma win) 
(Targets can be any Rigelian, except for Berkut, + non-Alm/non-Clive starting Deliverance member)

NK: DUMA

Q&amp;A: If Clive attacks Rinea or Lover Faye at night, will they be converted instead? Yes! In this situation, conversion will take priority over death. 


(Didn’t think there would be enough space for Celica’s path)

[/details]

[details=&quot;Mechanics and Feedback&quot;]

:shield: = Unique
:crossed_swords: = Guaranteed
:fire: = Magical 
:crown: = Nobility

Unique and Guaranteed are the same as the normal kind that&#39;s found on FoL.

There is no bleeding nor poison.

Magical is a characteristic that is mostly used for Deliverance members to find certain classes. Magical is tied to classes that are flavor-wise magic users in Fire Emblem.
Nobility is taken as a modified version from ToL 1.2. 
All Nobility gain another secret vote when voting someone else as King, and will only be taken into effect or shown if it actually matters.

Arcanist&#39;s first visit check is based on who people target first if they have the mounted target ability or multiple visits. 
Kliff and Faye&#39;s tracker and watcher result will give in the order that the plsyer inputted, so the first visit will always be the first person the target visited.

Nuibaba/Delthea has access to a neighborhood, where they can add and remove people. The people in that neighborhood will know who each other are, but Nuibaba/Delthea will talk through the host. The neighborhood can only be used at night.

Feedback is based on the limited version from EFOL 1.
Meaning: Players will not know if they are attacked and healed, just healed, empowered, mind warped, and missed, dodged, or survived Day Attacks. For non-Investigative classes, players will not know if they were occupied or redirected. 


Basically means that most of the time, there will be a &quot;you slept peacefully&quot; or its easier variant, no feedback at all. 

Exceptions: 
Investigative classes will be given no feedback from their ability if occupied or visit prevented, and will only be told that they were redirected, not who they were redirected to.
Investigative classes will also get normal feedback from their abilities when not occupied or prevented. 
All players will be told that they were killed, converted, changed classes, put in jail, and connected to the neighborhood. 

Order of Mechanics:
- Jail, Link
- Visit Prevention
- Redirection (Bypassing Immunity)
- Occupation
- Redirection 
- Mind Warp, Frame, Empowerment
- Investigative Check
- Guard, Death Immunity
- Attacks
- Heals
- Conversions

[/details]

[details=&quot;Class List&quot;]

[quote]
For 16 players (Deliverance Cap = 4)

Chancellor Desaix/King Rudolf
Berkut
Fernand/Cavalier
Clive
Alm
Rigelian Support
Random Rigelian x6
Random Rigelian/Random non-NK Neutral x2
Faye/Jedah/Brigand
Mad Lord Duma
[/quote]

[quote]
For 20 players (Deliverance Cap = 6) *Standard 

Chancellor Desaix/King Rudolf
Berkut
Fernand/Cavalier
Clive
Alm
Random non-Unique Deliverance
Rigelian Offensive
Rigelian Support
Random Rigelian x8
Random Rigelian/Random non-NK Neutral x2
Faye/Jedah/Brigand
Mad Lord Duma
[/quote]

[quote]
For 24 players (Deliverance Cap = 8)

Chancellor Desaix/King Rudolf
Berkut
Fernand/Cavalier
Clive
Alm
Random non-Unique Deliverance x2
Rigelian Killer
Rigelian Offensive
Rigelian Investigative
Rigelian Support x2
Random Rigelian x8
Random Rigelian/Random non-NK Neutral x2
Faye/Jedah/Brigand
Mad Lord Duma

[/quote]

[/details]

[details=&quot;Factions&quot;]
- [color=brown]The Rigelians (The Evil Town)[/color]
- [color=green]The Deliverance (The Good Scum)[/color]
- [color=gray]Neutrals (Selfish people and 1 crazy god)[/color]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Kings&quot;]

[quote]
[color=green]**King Rudolf**[/color]
[color=green]Deliverance Special[/color]

**Inheritance (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, [color=green]**Alm**[/color] has the priority on becoming King.
**Maker of Prophecy (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two. If you target a member of the Deliverance at night, from that point on you will be added to the Deliverance Members’ chat if not already in it.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose another player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Royal Might (Night)** - Choose a player and make them appear NS to all checks. Your target will have a 10% increased chance of a successful day attack. - oo uses
_Your objective is to subdue the Rigelian Army and the Mad Lord Duma._
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Chancellor Desaix**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Special[/color]

**Dynastic Fall (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, all [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] will lose their Nobility status for the next election.
**Valentian Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose another player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Blackmail (Night)** - Choose a player. They will be conversion immune until you choose another player with this ability. - oo uses 
_Your objective is to crush the Deliverance alongside the Mad Lord Duma._
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Saint King Alm**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Special[/color]
(From [color=green]Alm[/color])

**The True Heir (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, all [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] will lose their Nobility status for the next election, and any Deliverance member in line can become Alm even without the passive **Ram&#39;s Banner**.
**The Saint King (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two, and you will continue to be in the chat of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color], but will not add to their member cap.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Falchion (Night)** - Choose any two players. They will be immune to death tonight. If you target [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color], he will instead be killed, bypassing all immunities, occupation, redirection and visit prevention. - 4 uses
**Valentia’s Hero (Night)** - Choose a player and convert them to the [color=green]Deliverance[/color].  - oo uses
_Your objective is to subdue the Rigelian Army and the Mad Lord Duma._
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=gray]**King Lima**[/color]
[color=gray]Neutral Special[/color]
(From [color=gray]Brigand[/color])

**Lavish (Passive)** - If anyone visits you, you use up an extra use of the night ability being used that night. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. 
**Valentian Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose any player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 4 uses
**Hide (Night)** - Prevent all visits to you tonight. - 2 uses
_Your objective is to survive no matter the costs._
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=gray]**Acolyte Jedah**[/color] :fire: 
[color=gray]Neutral Special[/color]
(From [color=gray]Jedah[/color])

**Devoted Acolyte (Passive)** - You share a direct chat with the [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color]. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. 
**Valentian Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose any player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Offer Soul (Night)** - Guarantee that [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma&#39;s**[/color] actions are successful tonight. - 2 uses
Your objective is to ensure that Mad Lord Duma destroys the world.
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=gray]**Acting Queen Faye**[/color] 
[color=gray]Neutral Special[/color]
(From [color=gray]Lover Faye[/color])

**Head over Heels (Passive)** - If [color=green]**Alm**[/color] is about to be lynched, you will pardon him using Decide Fate by default, even if you’ve already used it. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. 
**Valentian Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose another player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Lover’s Grace (Night)** - Prevent all visits to [color=green]**Alm**[/color] tonight. - 2 uses
_Your objective is to ensure your love Alm survives the destruction of the world._
[/quote]

[quote]
**D[color=red]U[/color]M[color=blue]A[/color] [color=brown]A[/color][color=gray]W[/color]A[color=red]K[/color][color=gold]E[/color]N[color=gray]E[/color][color=orange]D[/color]** :fire:
[color=gray]Neutral Special[/color]

**God Status (Passive)** - You are immune to death, bleeding, occupation, and target change. You are able to use both day abilities and night abilities in the same phase.
**Destroyed Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two. When there are no members of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] left, your vote will count as six. If you are lynched, there will be no more Kings except for [color=green]**Saint King Alm**[/color].
**Divine Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today.  - oo uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - oo uses
**Upheaval (Night)** - All players except you will gain the wrong feedback from their results, if they would get any, and be randomly redirected to any player except you. - oo uses
**Ocular Beam (Night)** - Kill 2 players. - oo uses
_Your objective is to ensure that you destroy the world._
[/quote]

[/details]

[details=&quot;Rigelians&quot;]

[details=&quot;Unique Classes&quot;]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Berkut**[/color] :shield: :crown: :crossed_swords: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Special[/color]

**Phantasm (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. Immune to any attacks from [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color] as long as Starting [color=green]**King Rudolf**[/color] is alive. 
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Lock and Order (Day)** - Choose a player and lock them up in the dungeon. You and your prisoner can send a single 1000 character message to one another over the course of the night. - oo uses.
**Kriemhild (Night)** - Exact justice upon your prisoner and kill them, bypassing all immunities. If you kill a Rigelian, you will lose the rest of your uses. If you kill [color=brown]**Fernand**[/color] or [color=brown]**Rinea**[/color], you will die alongside them. - 2 uses
**Cease Thy March (Night)** - Default the [color=brown]Rigelian&#39;s[/color] weapon choice to match that of the [color=green]Deliverance&#39;s[/color] tomorrow, regardless of the vote. - 1 use

[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Slayde**[/color] :shield: :crown: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Killer[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Sir Mycen[/color]

**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Coup (Day)** - Place a mark of death on the King for the next two nights that causes any visit to the King to kill him, bypassing all immunities. If the King turns out to be [color=brown]**Chancellor Desaix**[/color], you will be killed for treason the following night. - 1 use
**Quick Assault (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 2 use
**Elite Vanguard (Night)** - Summon your elite fighters to protect you, granting you death immunity for the night. You will kill any attackers bypassing immunity. - 3 uses
**Garrison (Night)** - Grant a player death immunity. They gain 10% accuracy for all Day Attacks tomorrow.  - 2 use
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Nuibaba**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Social[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Delthea[/color]

**Mental Link (Passive)** - All players hypnotized by you will be added to your private neighborhood. You will be able to talk at night. If converted, your neighborhood will not change.
**Hypnotize (Day)** - Bring a player’s mind under your control at the start of tonight. - oo uses 
**Arcane Power (Day)** - Remove cooldown from Mire. - 2 uses
**Mire (Night)** - Remove a player from your control at the end of the night. They will lose all protections from Day Attacks tomorrow if they have any. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Fernand**[/color] :shield: :crown: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]

**Trusted Commander (Passive)** - When jailed by [color=brown]**Berkut**[/color], he will know that you are [color=brown]**Fernand**[/color]. Gain 1 use of all limited abilities each time the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] win a battle using Axes.
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Traitor’s Sight (Night)** - Check a player. Determine if they are part of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. - oo uses
**Bane of Deliverance (Night)** - Choose two players. Protect them from conversion to the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. If both players are not Nobility, this is ineffective. Cannot be used Night 1.  - 1 use
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Rinea**[/color] :shield: :fire: :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Social[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Tatiana[/color]

**Empathetic Noble (Passive)** - You will be able to communicate with fallen soldiers at night. If you are visited by any member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color], you will be converted. 
**By His Side (Passive)** - You cannot step up to be King, as your only wish is to spend your days at [color=brown]**Berkut&#39;s**[/color] side.
**Message of Mercy (Day)** - Send a private message to a player anonymously. They may not reply back. - 2 uses
**Resurrection (Night)** - Bring a dead player back to life. - 1 use
[/quote] 

[/details]

[details=&quot;Common Classes&quot;]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Paladin**[/color] :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Ezekiel[/color]

**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Commander’s Presence (Day)** - Your vote during today&#39;s battle will secretly count as 3 when totaling the end result. - 3 uses
**Bolster (Day)** - Choose a player. Their Day Attacks will be 20% more accurate today. - 1 uses
**Triad Check (Night)** - Choose two weapons, designating one as the fake and real choice of the Deliverance. If both match the choices of the Deliverance, you will be notified. If matched, gain 1 use of Bolster. - oo uses
**Veteran Lancer (Night)** - For tomorrow&#39;s battle, if the [color=green]Rigelian&#39;s[/color] weapon is Lances, you will win the battle even if you tie. - 2 uses

[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Baron**[/color] :crown: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Killer[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Lukas[/color]

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Ridersbane (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Mounted** passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them. 
**Javelin Toss (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance of killing them. Decreases by 5% if the weapon the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] chose today is Axes. - 2 uses
**Defend (Night)** - Watch over a player, and sacrifice your life to kill their attackers. Bypasses death immunity. - oo uses
**Heavy Armor (Night)** - Choose a player. You will redirect any attacks from them, bypassing redirection immunity, and gain death immunity tonight. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Cavalier**[/color] :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Mathilda[/color]

**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Expedition (Night)** - Choose a player. Determine if that player is the same alignment as the previous player you checked. Neutrals and Rigelians will be considered NS. - oo uses
**Interrogate (Night)** - Choose a player. Determine the most recent night they have been  visited by a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Arcanist**[/color] :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Kliff[/color]

**Dark Aura (Passive)** - If you are lynched, your accuser will be occupied the following night, bypassing immunities. 
**Faint Wisp (Night)** -  Choose a player and light their path. You will see who they visit first tonight. - oo uses
**Ghastly Eyes (Night)** -  Choose a player and watch their surroundings. You will discover who visits them. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Sky Knight**[/color] :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Clair[/color]

**Airborne (Passive)** - You bypass visit prevention and all players who target you with Day Attacks have 10% less chance to hit. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] used Bows during today&#39;s battle, this passive is disabled until the next day.
**Blue Bloods (Night)** - Determine if a player is of Valentian Nobility. - oo uses 
**Aerial Spy (Night)** - Choose a player and discover their faction. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Mercenary**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Offensive[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Gray[/color]

**Swordsmanship (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] win a battle with Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.
**Subdue (Day)** - Disable a player&#39;s immunities tonight. - 3 use
**Parry (Night)** - Occupy a player. - oo use
**Sweeping Blow (Night)** - Choose a player and occupy all players who visit them. - 2 use
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Myrmidon**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Offensive[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Python[/color]

**Swordsmanship (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] win a battle with Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.
**Crosswise Cut (Day)** - Attack 2 players. You will have a 10% chance to individually kill them. - 2 use
**Enforce (Night)** - Choose a player and redirect them to a target. - oo use
**Harsh Battlecry (Night)** - Choose a player. You will prevent them from performing any day attacks tomorrow. - 2 use
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Mage**[/color] :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Luthier[/color]

**Firewall (Day)** - Prevent all visits to a player tonight. You may not target them tomorrow. - 2 use 
**Empower (Night)** - Choose a player and guarantee their night ability is successful and bypasses immunities and protections. - oo uses
**Excalibur (Night)** - Choose two players and swap their positions. - 3 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Cleric**[/color] :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Silque[/color]

**Warp (Day)** - Teleport a player and bring them to you today. For the rest of today, any day attacks and abilities that target them will be ineffective, but they will die alongside you if you die to a day attack. - 3 uses
**Recover (Day)** - Choose a player and heal their wounds. - oo uses
**Physic (Day)** - Choose a player and heal their wounds, bypassing visit prevention. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Archer**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Killer[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Tobin[/color]

**Anti-Air (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Airborne** passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them. 
**Loose Barrage (Passive)** - If you kill a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] with your attacks, you will be unable to use any abilities the following day.
**Snipe (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a -10% chance to hit them with 0 uses. Each use you have on Snipe increases your chances of hitting your target by 20%. Expends all uses after a successful hit. - 0 uses
**Curved Shot (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 0 uses
**Precision Firing (Night)** - Gain 1 use of a Day Ability of your choice. - oo uses
**Warding Arrow (Night)** - You will gain 10% accuracy for any day attack tomorrow that targets a magic user. - 3 uses

[/quote]

[quote]
[color=brown]**Soldier**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Forsyth[/color]

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Promote (Night)** - Choose a dead non-Unique [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] class and gain its passives and abilities. You will not gain Nobility status from becoming a class that does have it. - oo uses
**Shieldbearer (Night)** - Choose another player and make them and you immune to death tonight. - 1 use

[/quote]

[/details]

[/details]

[details=&quot;Deliverance&quot;]

[quote]
[color=green]**Clive**[/color] :shield: :crown: :crossed_swords:
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

**Iron-Clad (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you. Any day attack targeting you will have 10% less chance of killing you. 
**Ridersbane (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Mounted** passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them. 
**Hit and Run (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 30% chance of killing them. - oo uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Sharpened Lance (Night)** - Attack a player. - oo uses
**Lunge (Night)** - Attack a player, bypassing death immunity. Swaps all targeting actions between you and the player you&#39;re attacking except for you. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Alm**[/color] :shield: :crown: :crossed_swords:
[color=green]Deliverance Special[/color]

**Hero&#39;s Brand (Passive)** - Immune to death at night, occupation, and redirection. Cannot die to any attacks from Duma even if they bypass immunity while there is a living [color=green]**King Rudolf**[/color].
**Rigel&#39;s Heir (Passive)** - If Starting [color=green]**Alm**[/color], you will appear as a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] to all checks on you and the day after a [color=green]**King Rudolf**[/color] dies at night, you will have the priority ascension to the throne. All day attacks targetting you will have 20% less accuracy. 
**Commandeering (Day)** - If [color=green]**Clive**[/color] is dead, choose another [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member. They will become [color=green]**Clive**[/color] at the start of tonight. - 2 use (Shared)
**True Sacrifice (Day)** - Your conversions will bypass conversion protection and **Hero&#39;s Brand** will be disabled tonight. - 2 uses (Shared)
**Recall to Light (Night)** - Choose a player. You will convert them to the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
**Double Lion (Night)** - For tomorrow&#39;s battle, if the [color=green]Deliverance&#39;s[/color] weapon is Swords, you will win the battle even if you tie. - 3 uses (Shared)

[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Sir Mycen**[/color] :shield: :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

**Military Hero (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you. If [color=green]**Alm**[/color] uses **Commandeering** on you, they will not lose a use of its ability.
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Veteran Knight (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance of killing them. - 2 uses
**Hero of Yore (Night)** - Prevent all visits to a [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member. The first time you successfully block a visit, gain 1 use of **Piercing Blow**. - 3 uses
**Piercing Blow (Night)** - Kill a player. Bypasses healing. - 0 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Gray**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Offensive[/color]

**Swordsmanship (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] wins a battle using Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.
**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Subdue (Day)** - Disable a player&#39;s immunities tonight. - 3 uses
**Sunder (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. Increases by 10% if you voted Swords in today&#39;s battle. - 3 uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Parry (Night)** - Occupy a player. - oo use
**Windsweep (Night)** - Occupy a player and all players who visit them. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Tobin**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

**Anti-Air (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Airborne** passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them. 
**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Snipe (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a -10% chance to hit them with 0 uses. Each use you have on Snipe increases your chances of hitting your target by 20%. Expends all uses after a successful hit. - 1 use
**Curved Shot (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 2 uses
**Precision Firing (Night)** - Gain 1 use of a Day Ability of your choice. - 4 uses
**Ranged Charge (Night)** - Allow for the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] to choose Bows in tomorrow&#39;s battle. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Kliff**[/color] :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Investigative[/color]

**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Sagittae (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance to kill them. If they are Magical, you will lose 25% accuracy. If they have the **Armored** passive, you will gain 25% accuracy. - 2 uses
**Sense Aura (Day)** - Choose a player and determine if they are Magical at the start of tonight. - 3 uses
**Bright Wisp (Night)** - Choose a player and see who they visit and who visits them. - oo uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Faye**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Special[/color]

**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Unwavering Love (Passive)** - You will not count towards the member cap of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] and can use both day abilities in the same day.
**Anew (Day)** - Choose a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. They are able to use one Day Attack twice today, and will only count as using it once. - 2 uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Imbue (Day)** - Choose a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] and guarantee their action is successful tonight, bypassing immunities and protections. - 2 uses
**Bright Wisp (Night)** - Choose a player and see who they visit and who visits them. - oo uses
**Rescue (Night)** - Choose a player and prevent all visits to them. They will be targeted by any non-Investigative abilities that target you as well tonight. - 3 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Lukas**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Ridersbane (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Mounted** passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them. 
**Javelin Toss (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance of killing them. Decreases by 5% if the weapon the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] chose today is Axes. - 2 uses
**Zofian Shield (Night)** - Prevent all visits to a player.  - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
**Rallying Cry (Night)** - Choose a [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member and guarantee their action is successful tonight, bypassing all protections and immunities. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Silque**[/color] :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

**Invoke (Day)** - Summon soldiers to protect the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. The first successful attack targeted at any member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] will not kill them. - 3 uses
**Recover (Night)** - Heal a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. Their vote in tomorrow&#39;s battle will count secretly as two. - oo uses
**Nosferatu (Night)** - Choose a player and a class. If that player dies tonight or tomorrow during a Day Attack, they will be revealed as the class you chose. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Clair**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Investigative[/color]

**Airborne (Passive)** - You bypass visit prevention and all players who target you with Day Attacks have 10% less chance to hit. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] used Bows during today&#39;s battle, this passive is disabled until the next day.
**Surveillance (Day)** - Determine the class of the player who is in [color=brown]**Berkut&#39;s**[/color] jail at the start of tonight. - 1 use
**Blue Bloods (Night)** - Choose two players and determine if either are Valentian Nobility. - oo uses 
**Pinpoint (Night)** - Discover a player&#39;s exact class if they are a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color]. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Forsyth**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Lieutenant by Merit (Passive)** - If [color=green]**Alm**[/color] uses Commandeering on you, they will not lose a use of its ability. You will keep this passive even after you change classes from being [color=green]**Forsyth**[/color] or a [color=brown]**Soldier**[/color].
**Promote (Day)** - Choose a dead non-Unique [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] or [color=green]Deliverance[/color] class and gain its passives and abilities tonight. You will become the convert form if you choose a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] class. You will not gain Nobility status from becoming a class that does have it. - oo uses
**Shieldbearer (Night)** - Choose another player and make them and you immune to death tonight. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Python**[/color]
[color=green]Deliverance Offensive[/color]

**Anti-Air (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Airborne** passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them. 
**Double Shot (Day)** - Attack 2 players. You will have a 20% chance to individually kill them. - 2 use
**Hunter&#39;s Volley (Day)** - Force a player to use their top night ability tonight, if they have uses left. - 1 use
**Notched Threat (Night)** - Choose a player and redirect them to a target. - oo use
**Smoke Arrow (Night)** - Choose a player. You will prevent them from using any day  attacks tomorrow. - 3 use
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Mathilda**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Investigative[/color]

**The Betrothed (Passive)** - If [color=green]**Alm**[/color] uses Commandeering on you, they will not lose a use of its ability.
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Pinpoint (Night)** - Discover a player&#39;s exact class if they are a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color]. - oo use
**Warding Guard (Night)** - Choose a player and determine if they are Magical. - 3 uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Luthier**[/color] :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

**Firewall (Day)** - Prevent all non-[color=green]Deliverance[/color] visits to a player tonight.  - 2 use 
**Thunder (Night)** - Stun a player. They will get incorrect feedback from their abilities tonight. - oo uses
**Excalibur (Night)** - Choose two players and swap their positions. - oo uses
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Delthea**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Social[/color]

**Mental Link (Passive)** - All players stunned by you will be added to your private neighborhood. You will be able to talk at night. Your neighborhood will not change if you are converted.
**Aura (Day)** - Stun a player, bringing them under your control at the start of tonight. - oo uses 
**Hasten (Day) - Remove cooldown from Ragnarok. - 2 uses
**Ragnarok (Night)** - Remove a player from your control at the end of the night. If they are not a [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member, all Day Attacks targeting them will be 30% more accurate tomorrow. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Tatiana**[/color] :shield: :fire: :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Social[/color]

**By His Side (Passive)** - You cannot step up to be King, as your only wish is to spend your days at [color=green]**Ezekiel&#39;s**[/color] side.
**Saintful Words (Passive)** - While you are alive, dead members of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] may talk directly in the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] chat. You will not count towards the member cap.
**Outcry of Rebellion (Day)** - Send a private message to a player anonymously. They may not reply back. - 2 uses
**Revival (Night)** - Bring a dead member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] back to life as their first [color=green]Deliverance[/color] class. If [color=green]**Starting Alm**[/color] or [color=green]**Clive**[/color] is revived, the player holding their position will revert to their previous class. - 1 use
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=green]**Ezekiel**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Commander’s Presence (Day)** - Your vote during today&#39;s battle will secretly count as 3 when totaling the end result. - 3 uses
**Gradivus (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 15% chance to kill them. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] chose Lances the previous night, gain 20% accuracy. - 3 uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Lancer&#39;s Poise (Night)** - For tomorrow’s battle, if the [color=green]Deliverance’s[/color] weapon is Lances, you will win the battle even if you tie. Overrides Veteran Lancer. - 2 uses 
**Rallying Cry (Night)** - Choose a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. All of their Day Attacks will gain 20% accuracy tomorrow. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]


[/details]

[details=&quot;Neutrals&quot;]

[quote]
[color=gray]**Lover Faye**[/color] :shield:
[color=gray]Neutral Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Faye[/color]


**Lovestruck (Passive)** - Once you visit [color=green]**Alm**[/color], you will know their identity. If you visit 2 members in the same turn, or are visited by any member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color], you will be converted and not count towards the member cap.
**Whisper (Day)** - Send a single 1000 character message to a player. They cannot send a message back. - 1 use
**Stalking Eyes (Night)** - Watch over two players. You will know who they visit and who visited them. - oo uses
**Love&#39;s Sacrifice (Night)** - Guard a player. If they would die from any cause, prevent their death. Stays on the player until moved to someone else. - oo uses
_Your objective is to ensure that your love, Starting Alm, survives the destruction of the world or that the Deliverance wins._
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=gray]**Jedah**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=gray]Neutral Offensive[/color]

**Duma’s Servant (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection. If [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color] targets you, they will be prevented from visiting instead.
**Rigel&#39;s Conjuring (Day)** - Choose a player, you will make them appear a member of the Deliverance tonight. If you target Mad Lord Duma, you will know their identity. - oo uses
**Telepathy (Day)** - Choose a player. You may send a single 1000 character message to that player, and they may send one back as well. - 2 uses
**Incarnation (Night)** - Choose two players. You will swap their positions tonight. Bypasses target change immunity. - 2 uses
**Hand of Duma (Night)** - Choose one of your targets. Force them to target another player of your choice. - 3 uses
_Your objective is to see at least 3 Rigelians and 1 Deliverance lynched or to ensure that Mad Lord Duma destroys the world._
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=gray]**Brigand**[/color]
[color=gray]Neutral Support[/color]

**Plunderer (Passive)** - Each time either side votes for Axes in a battle, you will gain 1 use of your choice ability.
**Wanted! (Passive)** - If you are lynched, the player who accused you will gain death immunity that night and be healed that night. Your accuser will also be conversion immune that night if a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] or reset 1 cooldown for any member of the faction if part of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color].
**Reap the Spoils (Night)** - Heal any player, including yourself. - 2 uses
**Trusty Axe (Night)** - Kill a player. - 0 use
_Your objective is to survive no matter the cost._
[/quote]

[quote]
[color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color] :shield: :crossed_swords: :fire:
[color=gray]Neutral Killer[/color]

**The Power of Madness (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection when there is no King. You are immune to death at night and will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Spread Darkness (Day)** - You will be able to choose two targets tonight. Only able to be used after Starting [color=green]**Alm**[/color] is dead.  - 2 uses
**Discard Soul (Day)** - Your attacks will bypass death immunity tonight. - 2 uses
**Ocular Beam (Night)** - Attack a player. - oo uses
**Mad Wrath (Night)** - Attack a player and occupy them. - 3 use
_Your objective is to destroy the world and those who are not your servants._
[/quote]

[/details]

[details=&quot;Specials&quot;]

[details=&quot;Battles&quot;]

**Battles**

Starting Day 2, at the start of each day, the [color=brown]Rigelian Army[/color] and the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] will meet to engage in battle. The winning side will gain useful prizes each day that sometimes could swing the tide of the game. 

This is based off of the classic &quot;Weapon Triangle&quot; from Fire Emblem, where Axes beat Lances, Lances beat Swords, and Swords beat Axes, much like Rock, Paper, Scissors.

**How it works**:

1. Members of The [color=green]Deliverance[/color] will give a claim of what they will choose for the battle the night before: either [color=red]Swords[/color], [color=green]Axes[/color], or [color=blue]Lances[/color]. This will be displayed in bold text alongside some descriptive narrative at the start of the day.
2. The [color=green]Deliverance[/color] will also give the real choice. There may be abilities that a class can use which allows them to choose [color=gray]Bows[/color], forcing a tie the following day regardless of the [color=brown]Rigelians’[/color] choice.
3. There will be 1 day in real time for all alive members to come to a vote in the thread by choosing Swords, Axes, or Lances. Some classes may have special abilities that affect this phase.
4. The [color=green]Deliverance[/color] will come to blows against the [color=brown]Rigelian Army[/color] and the choices of both sides will be revealed.


If Rigelians Win: Conversion Immunity that night (Can be bypassed by some abilities)
If Deliverance Wins: Choice of removing one cooldown from any ability
If Tie: Nothing happens

[/details]

[details=&quot;Day Attacks&quot;]

**Day Attacks**

Starting Day 2, during the day, some classes will be able to directly attack their targets by using Day Abilities. Unlike night attacks, this will have a result based on luck. Different from most other Day Abilities, all Day Attacks can be used during Battles. Each different ability has different hit rates, and some classes have passives and abilities that can increase hit rate or decrease hit rate of various players.

The way notifications for Day Attacks work, is anyone who can use a Day Attack will message me the name of their ability in the DM. I will RNG it and see the result. The person who used the Day Attack will either get &quot;It wasn&#39;t successful&quot; or &quot;You killed them&quot; the only way &quot;You killed them&quot; shows up is if the target actually ends up dead. &quot;It wasn&#39;t successful&quot; can be due to a miss, a day attack prevention, or even an immunity. The person who was targeted will never get any notifications.

The only target Day Attacks may not go for is the King. Everyone else is fair game.

Be warned though; it may not be your greatest plan to trust in the RNG.

[/details]

[/details]

Please leave feedback and balancing, I need the stuff because this is probably really imbalanced at this current state</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 01:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>from you guys I mean</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/61</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 01:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Btw there’s a flaw in all of this but now you can’t fix it muwahaha</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/60</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 01:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Editing is closed for now</p>
<p>until end of the first game</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/59</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 01:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Shuri can you gimme your analysis</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/58</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 20:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mmm hmm.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/57</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 04:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so does this mean you’re finally looking through it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/56</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 21:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bumping for tomorrow.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/55</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 17:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0cfba944d00b9d4b3aeef44bc8b5e886b71eae8d.gif" alt="6ef" data-base62-sha1="1QQUv0EYYGnu2IpJ9np8VmIWZlj" width="320" height="168"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/54</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 15:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bump again who wants a look at this</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/53</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 14:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>maybe next time</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/52</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 15:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this doesn’t have Celica’s route</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/51</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 15:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(If I don’t screw my exams up… I think I’m screwed for the one tomorrow)</p>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/2/289f2bac954481be5b49696e3018ccc129311c8d.jpeg" alt="CelicaTeam" data-base62-sha1="5Nm7shoNlPUgCxO82msIfkB8hwV" width="353" height="500"><br>
They’ll have to wait unfortunately…</p>
<p><em>“Anyone want some flour? It’s delicious, or so I’ve heard… from Boey.”</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/50</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 15:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thank you Shuri</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/49</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 15:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Poke Poke.</em><br>
I’ll help after my exams finish in 2 days <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/48</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 15:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/eyes.png?v=9" title=":eyes:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/47</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 15:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>okay I guess that’s a bit better</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/46</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 03:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>and I play smash so I know who corrin is and stuff</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/45</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 03:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I also played that mobile FE game soo <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/44</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 03:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am ready to handle their torches and pitchforks Celeste</p>
<p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":fire:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/pick.png?v=9" title=":pick:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":pick:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/43</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>You just triggered a whole subreddit</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/42</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tokyo Mirage Sessions isn’t a real FE game</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/41</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Livicus" data-post="39" data-topic="71483">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/livicus/40/9286_2.png" class="avatar"> Livicus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you never played a game of Fire Emblem</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thats actually false, i have played FE</p>
<p><strong>If you count Mirage Sessions <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/40</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would invite you as a co host but it seems like you never played a game of Fire Emblem before so you won’t be interested and that you’ll probably be hosting an FM at a similar time as me</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/39</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So likely after Holy Grail ok</p>
<p><em><strong>Totally not trying to figure out optimal times</strong></em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/38</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this is on the list</p>
<p>way down</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483/37</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71483-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-more-second-draft/71483.rss">SFOL Echoes Class Cards + More - [Second Draft]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
