<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fool/Scorned suggestion</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976</link>
    <description>Hey guys. This game is the best. Seriously I&#39;m addicted. Literally the ONLY problem I have with this game is becoming fool/scorned and HERE IS WHY. 

So if I become the fool, my job is to get myself executed. I don&#39;t care about anything else. I don&#39;t care which side wins. And if I WIN, we&#39;ll now I have to sit in the graveyard for the rest of the game with ZERO vested interest in the results of the game. And if I leave I don&#39;t get gold for winning. I don&#39;t like working to get myself killed and then having to sit there for 30 minutes not caring what happens. I feel like as fool or scorned, when you die you already know if you&#39;ve won or lost and it should be safe to leave the game at that point if you&#39;ve won. You already didn&#39;t get to be part of the actual game. I feel very compelled to just leave the game if I get fool so I can join a new game because then I get to actually play the game and I don&#39;t impact the game I left since I&#39;m a fool/scorned. I TOTALLY get why you can&#39;t leave a game when you die and get gold if your team ends up winning. I don&#39;t understand why if a fool or scorned wins, they can&#39;t get their winnings if they leave right after they die. Other than that, this game is so fun to play, love it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 12:39:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fool/Scorned suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree, you should get gold after winning as fool immediately, not at end</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 12:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6976-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976.rss">Fool/Scorned suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool/Scorned suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You make a good point actually. It’s still fun to do that. But at the same time as a fool, I don’t care who wins, and now that my game is over it’d be nice to leave and go to another game where I can play. But if the devs don’t agree, I suppose i could kill the rest of the time playing the prediction game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6976-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976.rss">Fool/Scorned suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool/Scorned suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t. I just am tempted to. And only with the fool. Because if a fool left the game it would not hurt the game. I’m definitely not one of the people that leaves whenever I get a boring BD class, because even if they’re boring they can still help. All I’m saying is when you die as fool or scorned it’d be nice to be able to leave at that point since your role and vested interest in the outcome of the game is done.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 12:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6976-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976.rss">Fool/Scorned suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool/Scorned suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t leave a game just to get a new class</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6976-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976.rss">Fool/Scorned suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool/Scorned suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can bet for gold, or try and work out who is who.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 05:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6976-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976.rss">Fool/Scorned suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fool/Scorned suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys. This game is the best. Seriously I’m addicted. Literally the ONLY problem I have with this game is becoming fool/scorned and HERE IS WHY.</p>
<p>So if I become the fool, my job is to get myself executed. I don’t care about anything else. I don’t care which side wins. And if I WIN, we’ll now I have to sit in the graveyard for the rest of the game with ZERO vested interest in the results of the game. And if I leave I don’t get gold for winning. I don’t like working to get myself killed and then having to sit there for 30 minutes not caring what happens. I feel like as fool or scorned, when you die you already know if you’ve won or lost and it should be safe to leave the game at that point if you’ve won. You already didn’t get to be part of the actual game. I feel very compelled to just leave the game if I get fool so I can join a new game because then I get to actually play the game and I don’t impact the game I left since I’m a fool/scorned. I TOTALLY get why you can’t leave a game when you die and get gold if your team ends up winning. I don’t understand why if a fool or scorned wins, they can’t get their winnings if they leave right after they die. Other than that, this game is so fun to play, love it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 03:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-6976-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fool-scorned-suggestion/6976.rss">Fool/Scorned suggestion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
