<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary (The Last Job)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary-the-last-job/1328</link>
    <description>**Lore Link:**
https://tol.wikia.com/Mercenary

**Lore Subject:**
The Last Job

**Lore:**

Well, here we are, Castle Adiart.  I had been hired to lead a band of travelers to the castle for safety, as the threat of brigands and thugs outside of the castle walls has been increasingly growing.  I was just accepting my payment when a courier approached me with a message.  I can barely make out his face from the long hood he wears over his head.  He must have just come out of the storm like I did.

&quot;Greetings miss,&quot; he says with a sense of urgency in his voice.  &quot;I was told you would be arriving soon.  Please, read this business proposal from another potential employer.&quot;

I begrudgingly take the letter from his hand.  &quot;I just finished a job, and I usually take a day of rest before accepting another.&quot;

He responds quickly, as if expecting my exact reply.  &quot;Oh, please just read the proposal.  No traveling will be required, and I&#39;m certain you&#39;ll find the payment to be to your liking.  I must be going; many more messages to deliver.&quot;

Before I can offer thanks, he has turned around and rushed off.

I seclude myself in an empty room to read the letter.

It reads,  &quot;My lady, truly fate has brought you to Castle Adiart this evening.  I hope your recent travels have not made you weary, for I require a very specific task from you.  Rumors spread around the castle that there is dissent towards the current rule and that a coup is stirring.  The King has ordered court meetings to occur each day now until the perpetrators are found.  I require extra protection both during these meetings and outside of these meetings within the premises of the castle itself.  The family and servants of Castle Adiart have been known to get aggressive in their accusations and even resort to martial law to carry out the King&#39;s demands in cases.  Please meet me in the grand ballroom in 15 minutes, so we can meet personally.&quot;

There is no signature on the letter indicating who I&#39;m to be protecting.  Instead, at the bottom of the letter lists the sum that the patron is willing to pay.  My eyes instantly go wide.  A cool bead of sweat runs down my face.  This is more money than any job I&#39;ve ever been offered.  The sum could cover my expenses for multiple years.  I may finally be able to retire from this dangerous life, finally settle down, maybe finally start a family.

I take a moment to find a servant to secure quarters for the evening, only to discover that my room is already prepared.  I quickly retreat to the room, and don a fresh set of fine clothes before meeting my employer.  I rush to the grand hall, and when I arrive, I&#39;m surprised to find it so empty.  On a stormy evening like this, usually some kind of entertainment will be set up to distract guests and royal retinue from the worries of the storm.  As I&#39;m marveling at the various tapestries strewn about the hall, the far door opens.  Stepping forward is a middle-aged gentlemen, with soft features, wearing a mix of gold and red fabrics.  If I didn&#39;t know any better, I&#39;d say he could even be one of the royal family.

He introduces himself and explains he&#39;s just a common servant in service to the King.  He explains how he requires my protection at all hours of the day and night, that I&#39;ll be permitted to stay outside of his room, and that I&#39;ll even be given a seat at the daily court meetings.

&quot;Do not expect me to have any say or any idea as to the current matters of the castle,&quot; I try to explain to him.  &quot;I plan to be completely silent during these court meetings unless I am individually addressed.&quot;

&quot;That&#39;s perfectly fine,&quot; he says with a grin.  &quot;Well then, I think they&#39;re waiting on us.&quot;

&quot;What?!&quot;  I exclaim in a voice that was definitely too loud for a king&#39;s grand ballroom.

&quot;Ah yes, the court is scheduled to convene right now.  So sorry you have not had much time to rest from the road, but the meeting should not last too long.  Shall we?&quot;

As I follow my new employer outside of the ballroom, one thought keeps rushing through my head.

&quot;This is it.  This could be the last job.  Just perform this easy task for this nobleman, stay quiet during the meetings, and stay alert during the evenings.  No travel, no brigands, no wild animals, no monsters.  Then, I can retire from this mercenary life forever.&quot;

............................

Night 5

This contract has already gone on longer than I would have suspected.  Each morning, the court convenes, and it appears each morning, there&#39;s one less member present.  There&#39;s never any explanation as to why someone doesn&#39;t show.  It&#39;s only just today that I&#39;ve begun to realize what&#39;s going on around me.  People are dieing!  Someone in this court is dissatisfied with the accusations being thrown around and is taking matters into their own hands!  I write this right now while sitting outside of the nobleman&#39;s room.  I&#39;ve been trying to determine what position of power my employer has within the court, but he&#39;s silent through most of the meetings.  Occasionally, I&#39;ll see him lean over and whisper something in the King&#39;s ear, but aside from that, nothing else.  He&#39;s one of the most calm members on the court, excluding myself of course because I have no idea what the problem is.

_A sound of footsteps can be heard down the lonely, dark hallway_

&quot;Hello, who goes there?&quot;  I call out into the darkness.

No answer

&quot;Hello?  I know you&#39;re there.  State your business.&quot;

No answer

I draw my blade and am ready to defend myself and my employer.  This must surely be the Assassin who&#39;s been killing off the Court members.

&quot;I will strike you down this night, Assassin!&quot;

Emerging from the hallway is a figure I recognize.  I&#39;ve seen this guy around the castle multiple times and he sits near the King during the meetings.  This is a loyal Knight of the King, or so he claims.  He stands before me not in his armor, but his nightclothes.  Probably trying to be quiet in his approach for the kill.

As he draws closer, I can see his sword in his hand.

&quot;Mr. Knight, I give you one final opportunity to stand down.  I have no business in the politics of your court, but if you take one step closer, I will strike you down and report your crimes of murder to the King tomorrow.&quot;

He says nothing, but continues just boldly walking forward.  He&#39;s just a few feet from me now.  I swing my blade with the conviction that this must be the killer.  He quickly blocks my cross slash and is prepared with a strike of his own.  As his blade arcs through the air, I counter the arc and drive his blade to the ground.

We continue to fight furiously..  He fights like a madman, slashing me a couple of times.  I&#39;ve pierced him only once, but it didn&#39;t even seem to phase him.  Who or what is this man?  Our blades now clash together, and for the first time I can see his full face.  His eyes are shock white, no pupils or irises at all.

&quot;What sort of foul sorcery is this?  Who are you?&quot;

No response

The fighting continues.  Finally, I see an opening in his guard.  I feint my blade up high, as I then duck.  His sword passes just inches from my head.  I take the opportunity to lunge and bury the sword deep in his chest.

I take a moment to catch my breath and staunch my wounds.  I stare at my bloodied blade.  I tear off a piece of my cloak to wipe as much blood as I can off the blade.  I&#39;ll find some water soon.  I&#39;ll have to explain all of this to the King and to my employer tomorrow morning.  There&#39;s some evil magic at work in this castle.

To Be Continued  

**Comments/Explanations**:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 21:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary-the-last-job/1328.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary (The Last Job)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malchior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Lore Link:</strong><br>
<a href="https://tol.wikia.com/Mercenary" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://tol.wikia.com/Mercenary</a></p>
<p><strong>Lore Subject:</strong><br>
The Last Job</p>
<p><strong>Lore:</strong></p>
<p>Well, here we are, Castle Adiart.  I had been hired to lead a band of travelers to the castle for safety, as the threat of brigands and thugs outside of the castle walls has been increasingly growing.  I was just accepting my payment when a courier approached me with a message.  I can barely make out his face from the long hood he wears over his head.  He must have just come out of the storm like I did.</p>
<p>“Greetings miss,” he says with a sense of urgency in his voice.  “I was told you would be arriving soon.  Please, read this business proposal from another potential employer.”</p>
<p>I begrudgingly take the letter from his hand.  “I just finished a job, and I usually take a day of rest before accepting another.”</p>
<p>He responds quickly, as if expecting my exact reply.  “Oh, please just read the proposal.  No traveling will be required, and I’m certain you’ll find the payment to be to your liking.  I must be going; many more messages to deliver.”</p>
<p>Before I can offer thanks, he has turned around and rushed off.</p>
<p>I seclude myself in an empty room to read the letter.</p>
<p>It reads,  “My lady, truly fate has brought you to Castle Adiart this evening.  I hope your recent travels have not made you weary, for I require a very specific task from you.  Rumors spread around the castle that there is dissent towards the current rule and that a coup is stirring.  The King has ordered court meetings to occur each day now until the perpetrators are found.  I require extra protection both during these meetings and outside of these meetings within the premises of the castle itself.  The family and servants of Castle Adiart have been known to get aggressive in their accusations and even resort to martial law to carry out the King’s demands in cases.  Please meet me in the grand ballroom in 15 minutes, so we can meet personally.”</p>
<p>There is no signature on the letter indicating who I’m to be protecting.  Instead, at the bottom of the letter lists the sum that the patron is willing to pay.  My eyes instantly go wide.  A cool bead of sweat runs down my face.  This is more money than any job I’ve ever been offered.  The sum could cover my expenses for multiple years.  I may finally be able to retire from this dangerous life, finally settle down, maybe finally start a family.</p>
<p>I take a moment to find a servant to secure quarters for the evening, only to discover that my room is already prepared.  I quickly retreat to the room, and don a fresh set of fine clothes before meeting my employer.  I rush to the grand hall, and when I arrive, I’m surprised to find it so empty.  On a stormy evening like this, usually some kind of entertainment will be set up to distract guests and royal retinue from the worries of the storm.  As I’m marveling at the various tapestries strewn about the hall, the far door opens.  Stepping forward is a middle-aged gentlemen, with soft features, wearing a mix of gold and red fabrics.  If I didn’t know any better, I’d say he could even be one of the royal family.</p>
<p>He introduces himself and explains he’s just a common servant in service to the King.  He explains how he requires my protection at all hours of the day and night, that I’ll be permitted to stay outside of his room, and that I’ll even be given a seat at the daily court meetings.</p>
<p>“Do not expect me to have any say or any idea as to the current matters of the castle,” I try to explain to him.  “I plan to be completely silent during these court meetings unless I am individually addressed.”</p>
<p>“That’s perfectly fine,” he says with a grin.  “Well then, I think they’re waiting on us.”</p>
<p>“What?!”  I exclaim in a voice that was definitely too loud for a king’s grand ballroom.</p>
<p>“Ah yes, the court is scheduled to convene right now.  So sorry you have not had much time to rest from the road, but the meeting should not last too long.  Shall we?”</p>
<p>As I follow my new employer outside of the ballroom, one thought keeps rushing through my head.</p>
<p>“This is it.  This could be the last job.  Just perform this easy task for this nobleman, stay quiet during the meetings, and stay alert during the evenings.  No travel, no brigands, no wild animals, no monsters.  Then, I can retire from this mercenary life forever.”</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>Night 5</p>
<p>This contract has already gone on longer than I would have suspected.  Each morning, the court convenes, and it appears each morning, there’s one less member present.  There’s never any explanation as to why someone doesn’t show.  It’s only just today that I’ve begun to realize what’s going on around me.  People are dieing!  Someone in this court is dissatisfied with the accusations being thrown around and is taking matters into their own hands!  I write this right now while sitting outside of the nobleman’s room.  I’ve been trying to determine what position of power my employer has within the court, but he’s silent through most of the meetings.  Occasionally, I’ll see him lean over and whisper something in the King’s ear, but aside from that, nothing else.  He’s one of the most calm members on the court, excluding myself of course because I have no idea what the problem is.</p>
<p><em>A sound of footsteps can be heard down the lonely, dark hallway</em></p>
<p>“Hello, who goes there?”  I call out into the darkness.</p>
<p>No answer</p>
<p>“Hello?  I know you’re there.  State your business.”</p>
<p>No answer</p>
<p>I draw my blade and am ready to defend myself and my employer.  This must surely be the Assassin who’s been killing off the Court members.</p>
<p>“I will strike you down this night, Assassin!”</p>
<p>Emerging from the hallway is a figure I recognize.  I’ve seen this guy around the castle multiple times and he sits near the King during the meetings.  This is a loyal Knight of the King, or so he claims.  He stands before me not in his armor, but his nightclothes.  Probably trying to be quiet in his approach for the kill.</p>
<p>As he draws closer, I can see his sword in his hand.</p>
<p>“Mr. Knight, I give you one final opportunity to stand down.  I have no business in the politics of your court, but if you take one step closer, I will strike you down and report your crimes of murder to the King tomorrow.”</p>
<p>He says nothing, but continues just boldly walking forward.  He’s just a few feet from me now.  I swing my blade with the conviction that this must be the killer.  He quickly blocks my cross slash and is prepared with a strike of his own.  As his blade arcs through the air, I counter the arc and drive his blade to the ground.</p>
<p>We continue to fight furiously…  He fights like a madman, slashing me a couple of times.  I’ve pierced him only once, but it didn’t even seem to phase him.  Who or what is this man?  Our blades now clash together, and for the first time I can see his full face.  His eyes are shock white, no pupils or irises at all.</p>
<p>“What sort of foul sorcery is this?  Who are you?”</p>
<p>No response</p>
<p>The fighting continues.  Finally, I see an opening in his guard.  I feint my blade up high, as I then duck.  His sword passes just inches from my head.  I take the opportunity to lunge and bury the sword deep in his chest.</p>
<p>I take a moment to catch my breath and staunch my wounds.  I stare at my bloodied blade.  I tear off a piece of my cloak to wipe as much blood as I can off the blade.  I’ll find some water soon.  I’ll have to explain all of this to the King and to my employer tomorrow morning.  There’s some evil magic at work in this castle.</p>
<p>To Be Continued</p>
<p><strong>Comments/Explanations</strong>:</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary-the-last-job/1328/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary-the-last-job/1328/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 05:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1328-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary-the-last-job/1328.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary (The Last Job)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
