<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Xel&#39;corian Mind Snatchers Neutral/Offensive</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-xelcorian-mind-snatchers-neutral-offensive/30932</link>
    <description>Passive 1
Neural Link: You are immune to death twice. If attacked a random infested player will be bled and die in two nights. (bypasses death immunity)

Passive 2
Empty Host: You are immune to bleeding and nightshade poison.


Day Ability 1
Hive Mind: Cause yourself and ALL infected to accuse someone of treason, no one can revoke their accusation. (The person infected the longest will accuse first, order of other accusations is random) 

2 uses 1 day cool down

Day Ability 2:
Subtle Influence: Can only be used during a trial. Causes ALL infested players to automatically choose to execute or pardon the player that is on trial (people pardoned by this ability cannot be accused of treason for the rest of the day)

1 use

Night Ability 1
Spread Infestation: Infect a player with an otherworldly parasite parasite revealing their journal to you that night and allowing them to be affected by your other abilities.  (Up to 5 people can be infected at once)  

Infinite uses with no cool down

Night Ability 2 
Internal Hemorrhaging: Causes 3 infested players of your choice to bleed and die in 2 nights (bypasses death immunity)

2 uses 1 night cool down. 

Win Condition: Have 5 infected players killed in anyway, or survive.

Lore
Those blessed with magical capabilities devote their lives to the art of the arcane. For they must if they dream of conjuring more than a simple shower of harmless magical dust. As even the creation and formation of simple ice can fail spectacularly without the proper skill or concentration. But, there are none incantations so vastly complicated and open to failure as rituals to commune with creatures from other spheres. Blood spilled at the wrong moment, sacrifices offered up too late, or chants of power interrupted by a lapse in concentration. All can at best bring a ritual to a close. At worst... terrible horrors are brought from other planes, stranded in their new permanent home, but not bound properly, or inhibited in any shape or form. The extra terrestrial beings of Xel&#39;cor are but one of many examples. Cunning asexually reproducing parasites that merge with the brains of host victims, subtly assimilating their knowledge, and eventually their host into a hive mind structure after a length process in which the parasite permanently fuses itself with the host&#39;s brain. While those deemed unworthy or of no purpose are cast aside, brains budging as blood cells erupt and rupture until the host being&#39;s life ebbs away. An ever growing colony spans the world, from simple villages to the castle Adiart.


Comments
Personally I believe the addition of a neutral killer that has a win condition that isn&#39;t specifically tied to killing everyone would be good for the game as people often aren&#39;t a fan of NKs having a extremely low winrate. Though they still understand why that has to be the case. Which is why I&#39;d like to suggest the idea of a slower paced NK that has the potential to kill people in droves if allowed too, without being over powered due to a slower pace associated with its play style. Being more so focused on a staging and executing a grander plan over the course of the game to fulfill objectives instead of chipping away at the player count every turn like the current NKs. The way I see it the current NKs can be described as very aggressive (sorc) middle of the pack (poss) slow (reaper) Which is why I&#39;d like to see an NK that&#39;s very slow, but ultimately rewarding and fun to play. Which I hope something like this would be to the player base as it rewards skill and proper planning with a fair amount of strategy involved throughout the course of game. Thank you for reading, please post what you think about it, I&#39;m eager to hear about what the community thinks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 14:37:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-xelcorian-mind-snatchers-neutral-offensive/30932.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Xel&#39;corian Mind Snatchers Neutral/Offensive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[A_COCO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Passive 1<br>
Neural Link: You are immune to death twice. If attacked a random infested player will be bled and die in two nights. (bypasses death immunity)</p>
<p>Passive 2<br>
Empty Host: You are immune to bleeding and nightshade poison.</p>
<p>Day Ability 1<br>
Hive Mind: Cause yourself and ALL infected to accuse someone of treason, no one can revoke their accusation. (The person infected the longest will accuse first, order of other accusations is random)</p>
<p>2 uses 1 day cool down</p>
<p>Day Ability 2:<br>
Subtle Influence: Can only be used during a trial. Causes ALL infested players to automatically choose to execute or pardon the player that is on trial (people pardoned by this ability cannot be accused of treason for the rest of the day)</p>
<p>1 use</p>
<p>Night Ability 1<br>
Spread Infestation: Infect a player with an otherworldly parasite parasite revealing their journal to you that night and allowing them to be affected by your other abilities.  (Up to 5 people can be infected at once)</p>
<p>Infinite uses with no cool down</p>
<p>Night Ability 2<br>
Internal Hemorrhaging: Causes 3 infested players of your choice to bleed and die in 2 nights (bypasses death immunity)</p>
<p>2 uses 1 night cool down.</p>
<p>Win Condition: Have 5 infected players killed in anyway, or survive.</p>
<p>Lore<br>
Those blessed with magical capabilities devote their lives to the art of the arcane. For they must if they dream of conjuring more than a simple shower of harmless magical dust. As even the creation and formation of simple ice can fail spectacularly without the proper skill or concentration. But, there are none incantations so vastly complicated and open to failure as rituals to commune with creatures from other spheres. Blood spilled at the wrong moment, sacrifices offered up too late, or chants of power interrupted by a lapse in concentration. All can at best bring a ritual to a close. At worst… terrible horrors are brought from other planes, stranded in their new permanent home, but not bound properly, or inhibited in any shape or form. The extra terrestrial beings of Xel’cor are but one of many examples. Cunning asexually reproducing parasites that merge with the brains of host victims, subtly assimilating their knowledge, and eventually their host into a hive mind structure after a length process in which the parasite permanently fuses itself with the host’s brain. While those deemed unworthy or of no purpose are cast aside, brains budging as blood cells erupt and rupture until the host being’s life ebbs away. An ever growing colony spans the world, from simple villages to the castle Adiart.</p>
<p>Comments<br>
Personally I believe the addition of a neutral killer that has a win condition that isn’t specifically tied to killing everyone would be good for the game as people often aren’t a fan of NKs having a extremely low winrate. Though they still understand why that has to be the case. Which is why I’d like to suggest the idea of a slower paced NK that has the potential to kill people in droves if allowed too, without being over powered due to a slower pace associated with its play style. Being more so focused on a staging and executing a grander plan over the course of the game to fulfill objectives instead of chipping away at the player count every turn like the current NKs. The way I see it the current NKs can be described as very aggressive (sorc) middle of the pack (poss) slow (reaper) Which is why I’d like to see an NK that’s very slow, but ultimately rewarding and fun to play. Which I hope something like this would be to the player base as it rewards skill and proper planning with a fair amount of strategy involved throughout the course of game. Thank you for reading, please post what you think about it, I’m eager to hear about what the community thinks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-xelcorian-mind-snatchers-neutral-offensive/30932/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-xelcorian-mind-snatchers-neutral-offensive/30932/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30932-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-xelcorian-mind-snatchers-neutral-offensive/30932.rss">[Class Suggestion] Xel&#39;corian Mind Snatchers Neutral/Offensive</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
