<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Thief (Neutral Special)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937</link>
    <description>&gt; **Thief**
&gt;Neutral Special
&gt; _(has an item based system similar to mercenary&#39;s brilders or reaper&#39;s souls called jewels)_
&gt;
&gt; **Passive 1** - Jewels!: If you are attacked at night, lose 2 jewels and continue living, starts off with 3 jewels.
&gt;
&gt; **Passive 2** - Code of Honour:  If you are killed or executed during the day, your logs will be wiped and you will not be able to speak after you are sentenced for treason
&gt;
&gt;**Day Ability 1** - Greedy Pressure: Force someone to vote someone else _(including them self)_, Can be used as many times in the day, pressured players will follow your execution or pardon vote, lose 1 jewel. _(Infinite uses)_
&gt;
&gt;**Night Ability 1** - Steal: Make a player lose 1 use of all their limited use abilities, Gain 1 jewel for every use of an ability you stole. Players stolen from will be notified _(Infinite uses)_
&gt;
&gt;**Night Ability 2** - Supply: Give a non blue dragon player +1 use for all their abilities, Gives Reaper +1 soul and Sorcerer can use 2 day abilities in the same day. You will be notified if your target was a member of the blue dragon. Lose 1 jewel if they are a member of the blue dragon, Gain 1 jewel if they are not _(only gives alch +1 stoneskin)  (After using this ability, you may not supply your target for another two nights.)  (Infinite uses)_
&gt;
&gt;**Win Condition**: Survive to see the defeat of the blue dragon.
&gt;_(Stalls the game cause of their pressure mechanic)_

I currently think that supply is more of an investigative mechanic then a support mechanic, I&#39;m also not too sure if it should a be a social, offensive, support or special class type.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 08:43:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Thief (Neutral Special)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds boring to play but sounds like it’s fun to get extra stuff<br>
Also don’t like it’s wincon<br>
and passive 2 is obviously to make sure they don’t out evils I guess?<br>
I mean it’s okay but it sounds boring and I rather Ne’s not survive SS works better as a evil helper.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 08:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73937-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937.rss">Thief (Neutral Special)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thief (Neutral Special)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That one was a bit more on the fly I suppose yeah</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 08:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73937-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937.rss">Thief (Neutral Special)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thief (Neutral Special)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Charrlous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do kind of agree with your suggestion of only being able to use it on a player with a limit, perhaps, every time you supply 1 player, the price goes up by 1-2 jewels, to discourage them from just pocketing the sorcerer or something.<br>
Currently I changed it to “You may not supply your target for another two nights”</p>
<p>alch is just only gets stoneskin potion</p>
<p>Im kinda ehh on the code of honour thing, supposing alchemists also have an investigative ability, but supposing evils are their only ally, I agree with it. I’ll add it in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 08:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73937-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937.rss">Thief (Neutral Special)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thief (Neutral Special)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Charrlous" data-post="1" data-topic="73937">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/observer-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Charrlous:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong> - Jewels!: If you are attacked at night, lose 2 jewels and continue living, starts off with 3 jewels</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Charrlous" data-post="1" data-topic="73937">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/observer-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Charrlous:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2</strong> - Supply: Give an evil player +1 use for all their abilities, Gives Reaper +1 soul and Sorcerer can use 2 day abilities in the same day. You will be notified if your target was a member of the blue dragon. <strong>Lose 1 jewel</strong></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Charrlous" data-post="1" data-topic="73937">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/observer-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Charrlous:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Win Condition</strong> : Survive to see the defeat of the blue dragon.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like the idea of this class, however, I think supply in it’s current form is somewhat detrimental to the thief’s wincon as a sorcerer etc can just kill you regardless.<br>
My suggestion would have it function as an investigative action, where supply will give either an evil/NK or neutral (besides alch) an extra limited use and <strong>if</strong> an ability is given in such a fashion, you receive 3 jewels back so +2 jewels, the drawback being you may only supply (or attempt to) each player once per game.</p>
<p>The reason this is investigative is you will be given feedback if your supply did anything or not, thus you are informed if your target is evil or not regardless of frames/warps.</p>
<p><strong>Do I think the Thief should be able to find the MM in this way before n3?</strong> Absolutely, if he can find allies then that is great, however if he is executed he may just blab whoever MM is anyway, so I propose a solution to this problem here:</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2: Code of Honour:</strong> If you are killed or executed during the day, your logs will be wiped and you will not be able to speak after you are sentenced for treason</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 06:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73937-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937.rss">Thief (Neutral Special)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thief (Neutral Special)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Charrlous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p><strong>Thief</strong><br>
Neutral Special<br>
<em>(has an item based system similar to mercenary’s brilders or reaper’s souls called jewels)</em></p>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong> - Jewels!: If you are attacked at night, lose 2 jewels and continue living, starts off with 3 jewels.</p>
<p><strong>Passive 2</strong> - Code of Honour:  If you are killed or executed during the day, your logs will be wiped and you will not be able to speak after you are sentenced for treason</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1</strong> - Greedy Pressure: Force someone to vote someone else <em>(including them self)</em>, Can be used as many times in the day, pressured players will follow your execution or pardon vote, lose 1 jewel. <em>(Infinite uses)</em></p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1</strong> - Steal: Make a player lose 1 use of all their limited use abilities, Gain 1 jewel for every use of an ability you stole. Players stolen from will be notified <em>(Infinite uses)</em></p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2</strong> - Supply: Give a non blue dragon player +1 use for all their abilities, Gives Reaper +1 soul and Sorcerer can use 2 day abilities in the same day. You will be notified if your target was a member of the blue dragon. Lose 1 jewel if they are a member of the blue dragon, Gain 1 jewel if they are not <em>(only gives alch +1 stoneskin)  (After using this ability, you may not supply your target for another two nights.)  (Infinite uses)</em></p>
<p><strong>Win Condition</strong>: Survive to see the defeat of the blue dragon.<br>
<em>(Stalls the game cause of their pressure mechanic)</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>I currently think that supply is more of an investigative mechanic then a support mechanic, I’m also not too sure if it should a be a social, offensive, support or special class type.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 06:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73937-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/thief-neutral-special/73937.rss">Thief (Neutral Special)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
