<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Apostle</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690</link>
    <description> **The Initiation**


One of our scouts have made documentation of a cult meeting before their attack on the Castle. 

It was neatly organized, and attached to a raggedy sheet that contained black words. A primary source. 

This is the information presented, and connected to various occupations within.
__________________

Cult Leader: Assemble, my children. Mithras calls for his newest follower to be inducted into the family. Bring him out at once. 

_Various grunts, followed by kicking, and screaming by a masculine voice assumed to be the Apostle._

Cult Leader: Mithras needs a form to take in order to inscribe his demands. It is your privilege to serve. 

Apostle: To be a puppet for a non-existent phantom?

Cult Leader: Begin the process. We will not tolerate heresy.

_Firstly, the mark of Corax spreads out over the target&#39;s arm as they are paralyzed. The ritualist creates a black insignia below the target&#39;s feet. Blood is poured into the nose until the victim drowns, then poured into all other orifices while chanting occurs. They are then reincarnated as what appears to be walking blood bags inside human bodies._ 

Apostle: I can hear him! Quick, get me something to write on now! 

Cult Leader: Do as he asks. This normally lasts for merely a few minutes.

Apostle: Here! Here! Read this!

Cult Leader (Reading): &quot;**You have failed Corax for the last time. He has sent the Reaper to lay waste to the land. It will provide some assistance, mortal, but beware. You have missed the boy. Do you recall the boy?**&quot; 

 &quot;There have been many.&quot;, he says as words appear onto the paper.

**The boy whom you have sent into the crypt. The boy of ash who has escaped. He who always carried the flower from his mother. He now lies in his basement crafting potions until the day&#39;s end. The flower. The rose is in his suit. His essence must be brought to us, or you will suffer eternal punishment.  This is how you will find the boy. He wears a hood, he does not show his face, and he lives with the hired hand and the dark one.  He does not shut his mouth, but  every mention of the Reapers chills him to the bone. Poor creature ingested so many trace amounts of nightshade out of pure fear that his body can absorb it for nutrients. Use his paranoid mind against him. Draw him out. Prove yourself to us by bringing him to Corax, and banishing this Reaper from this plane of existence. Then, and only then, will the world be yours.**&quot;

___


Comments/Explanations

I chose the Apostle because of his former roles, the Noble and Psychic. The Noble and Psychic are both social roles with the knack for messages, and the Apostle happens to be the resident social role. The Noble is good with paper especially and this is why the Apostle chose to channel Mithras&#39; words into ink. 

There isn&#39;t any real lore about the process of how people are forced to become cultists.

This blood-bag idea was formed by the appearance of the Cult King. Looking at it, you see one eye is reddish, and the other is sealed shut, presumably by congealed blood. In his eye. 
________

Also, There is little connection between The Assassin (Discussed in the Reapers of Corax (In the Reapers wikia), and the Assassin who refuses to have his free speech taken away. 

It intrigued me to know why the Unseen never show up while the Cult do, and vice versa, and it would make sense that they just hide as Blue Dragon members as they do in-game, except they seem to do it so well nobody can tell the difference between Blue Dragon and Unseen when they&#39;re playing a Cult game. This is because they haven&#39;t begun their assault yet, and they can clearly use their occupations(BD Classes) as alibis because they aren&#39;t killing and converting people.

This offers some connection between this specific Assassin, and the aforementioned hiding done by the Unseen into the Blue Dragon when the Cult attacks. It would seem fitting that he&#39;d be a Physician(Or an Alchemist, but an Alchemist would have no reason to attack the Blue Dragon, considering that in my lore samples based on the theory that the Blue Dragon are evil, the Alchemist as a neutral would have just gotten there to make potions and leave. This makes sense according to game logic because the Alchemist is immune to conversion. However, the Physician is left.) This makes perfect sense, and the reason why is below.

The Physician is **immune** to **poison**. The Assassin knows much about **poison**. You may think the connection is shattered because the Assassin is not immune to his own poison, or any poisoning, but this all comes together when you connect the Assassin trying to save the castle from the evil Blue Dragon to the Assassin that was tortured by The Reapers&#39; Penance, a sect of Cultists. 

Both of these Assassins are the same person. Allow me to illustrate a logical chain of events.

Boy is kidnapped by cultists, Boy is locked in a crypt by cultists, Boy suffers minor damage due to inhalation of toxic materials in the stale air from corpses with various rotting organs hanging out and decaying, Boy devotes life to studying toxic chemicals due to trauma, trauma  leads to abuse of poisons to create a &quot;high&quot;, Boy becomes immune to poisoning, Boy becomes physician only because there are very few people as qualified as him despite the clear conflict of interest (abusing chemicals), Boy finds new purpose in life as he realizes the Blue Dragon are oppressing the people, Boy becomes Assassin after being recruited by the Mastermind.

If you haven&#39;t noticed, I drew out this thread of time **BEFORE** answering the apparent flaw in my thinking, and the answers are clear. **The Assassin never actually dies of poisoning, whether it happens to be the Alchemist, or a Court Wizard sending his poison back at him. He actually dies of overdose.** _But wait, if he dies of overdose, how come the Physician doesn&#39;t?_ is a question I can almost hear being asked. The answer is that the Physician has his own room filled with chemicals that he knows can counteract the Nightshade, while the Assassin had to leave his room to enter the Unseen night room.

This means that the two Assassins are in fact the same person, which connects the dots between motivations for each faction, further highlighting the backstory of the Assassin being a Physician.

There is more evidence, being that the Physician can literally perform autopsies mid-game and find the killer, and the Assassin happens to be a killer class, good with a knife.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 18:47:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Apostle</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thats deep</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 18:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1690-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Apostle</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Apostle</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Initiation</strong></p>
<p>One of our scouts have made documentation of a cult meeting before their attack on the Castle.</p>
<p>It was neatly organized, and attached to a raggedy sheet that contained black words. A primary source.</p>
<p>This is the information presented, and connected to various occupations within.</p>
<hr>
<p>Cult Leader: Assemble, my children. Mithras calls for his newest follower to be inducted into the family. Bring him out at once.</p>
<p><em>Various grunts, followed by kicking, and screaming by a masculine voice assumed to be the Apostle.</em></p>
<p>Cult Leader: Mithras needs a form to take in order to inscribe his demands. It is your privilege to serve.</p>
<p>Apostle: To be a puppet for a non-existent phantom?</p>
<p>Cult Leader: Begin the process. We will not tolerate heresy.</p>
<p><em>Firstly, the mark of Corax spreads out over the target’s arm as they are paralyzed. The ritualist creates a black insignia below the target’s feet. Blood is poured into the nose until the victim drowns, then poured into all other orifices while chanting occurs. They are then reincarnated as what appears to be walking blood bags inside human bodies.</em></p>
<p>Apostle: I can hear him! Quick, get me something to write on now!</p>
<p>Cult Leader: Do as he asks. This normally lasts for merely a few minutes.</p>
<p>Apostle: Here! Here! Read this!</p>
<p>Cult Leader (Reading): “<strong>You have failed Corax for the last time. He has sent the Reaper to lay waste to the land. It will provide some assistance, mortal, but beware. You have missed the boy. Do you recall the boy?</strong>”</p>
<p>“There have been many.”, he says as words appear onto the paper.</p>
<p><strong>The boy whom you have sent into the crypt. The boy of ash who has escaped. He who always carried the flower from his mother. He now lies in his basement crafting potions until the day’s end. The flower. The rose is in his suit. His essence must be brought to us, or you will suffer eternal punishment.  This is how you will find the boy. He wears a hood, he does not show his face, and he lives with the hired hand and the dark one.  He does not shut his mouth, but  every mention of the Reapers chills him to the bone. Poor creature ingested so many trace amounts of nightshade out of pure fear that his body can absorb it for nutrients. Use his paranoid mind against him. Draw him out. Prove yourself to us by bringing him to Corax, and banishing this Reaper from this plane of existence. Then, and only then, will the world be yours.</strong>"</p>
<hr>
<p>Comments/Explanations</p>
<p>I chose the Apostle because of his former roles, the Noble and Psychic. The Noble and Psychic are both social roles with the knack for messages, and the Apostle happens to be the resident social role. The Noble is good with paper especially and this is why the Apostle chose to channel Mithras’ words into ink.</p>
<p>There isn’t any real lore about the process of how people are forced to become cultists.</p>
<p>This blood-bag idea was formed by the appearance of the Cult King. Looking at it, you see one eye is reddish, and the other is sealed shut, presumably by congealed blood. In his eye.</p>
<hr>
<p>Also, There is little connection between The Assassin (Discussed in the Reapers of Corax (In the Reapers wikia), and the Assassin who refuses to have his free speech taken away.</p>
<p>It intrigued me to know why the Unseen never show up while the Cult do, and vice versa, and it would make sense that they just hide as Blue Dragon members as they do in-game, except they seem to do it so well nobody can tell the difference between Blue Dragon and Unseen when they’re playing a Cult game. This is because they haven’t begun their assault yet, and they can clearly use their occupations(BD Classes) as alibis because they aren’t killing and converting people.</p>
<p>This offers some connection between this specific Assassin, and the aforementioned hiding done by the Unseen into the Blue Dragon when the Cult attacks. It would seem fitting that he’d be a Physician(Or an Alchemist, but an Alchemist would have no reason to attack the Blue Dragon, considering that in my lore samples based on the theory that the Blue Dragon are evil, the Alchemist as a neutral would have just gotten there to make potions and leave. This makes sense according to game logic because the Alchemist is immune to conversion. However, the Physician is left.) This makes perfect sense, and the reason why is below.</p>
<p>The Physician is <strong>immune</strong> to <strong>poison</strong>. The Assassin knows much about <strong>poison</strong>. You may think the connection is shattered because the Assassin is not immune to his own poison, or any poisoning, but this all comes together when you connect the Assassin trying to save the castle from the evil Blue Dragon to the Assassin that was tortured by The Reapers’ Penance, a sect of Cultists.</p>
<p>Both of these Assassins are the same person. Allow me to illustrate a logical chain of events.</p>
<p>Boy is kidnapped by cultists, Boy is locked in a crypt by cultists, Boy suffers minor damage due to inhalation of toxic materials in the stale air from corpses with various rotting organs hanging out and decaying, Boy devotes life to studying toxic chemicals due to trauma, trauma  leads to abuse of poisons to create a “high”, Boy becomes immune to poisoning, Boy becomes physician only because there are very few people as qualified as him despite the clear conflict of interest (abusing chemicals), Boy finds new purpose in life as he realizes the Blue Dragon are oppressing the people, Boy becomes Assassin after being recruited by the Mastermind.</p>
<p>If you haven’t noticed, I drew out this thread of time <strong>BEFORE</strong> answering the apparent flaw in my thinking, and the answers are clear. <strong>The Assassin never actually dies of poisoning, whether it happens to be the Alchemist, or a Court Wizard sending his poison back at him. He actually dies of overdose.</strong> <em>But wait, if he dies of overdose, how come the Physician doesn’t?</em> is a question I can almost hear being asked. The answer is that the Physician has his own room filled with chemicals that he knows can counteract the Nightshade, while the Assassin had to leave his room to enter the Unseen night room.</p>
<p>This means that the two Assassins are in fact the same person, which connects the dots between motivations for each faction, further highlighting the backstory of the Assassin being a Physician.</p>
<p>There is more evidence, being that the Physician can literally perform autopsies mid-game and find the killer, and the Assassin happens to be a killer class, good with a knife.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 01:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1690-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-apostle/1690.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Apostle</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
