<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>CW rework entry, or how to give CW a purpose</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599</link>
    <description>**Court Wizard**

**Day abilities:**
***Duplication:*** The selected target&#39;s single target night ability will target an additional target of your choice. 1/2 uses.

_You select a target to empower, and the extra target they will affect. I&#39;m not sure whether the target you empowered target should know of duplication taking effect, because then it would be impossible to fake claim CW, instead the CW gets the feedback related to the second target. Maybe it&#39;s best to get a very generic message if it fails, such as &quot;your duplication was ineffective&quot;. It is intentional that this ability can backfire, for instance you could target an assassin and give them a free 2 for 1. Duplication will fizzle if either target can&#39;t be visited, either you or your empowered target gets occupied, if your empowered target uses a multitarget ability, or if they are the prince/king (no double guards or exes)._
***Barrier:*** Now a day ability, will obviously take effect at night. Can now target self. 2 uses.

_This makes it impossible both use duplication and barrier on the same target._

**Night abilities:**
***Calm mind :*** Your target is immune to conversion for two nights. Can only target the same target once. Unlimited uses. 

_Not sure if that ability is good enough for a filler yet, however, the premise is that with having more meaningful abilities, CW&#39;s filler ability won&#39;t feel as bad._
***Tornado:*** same

__________________

**Sage**

**Day abilities:**
***Silence:*** Same as reaper chill. 1 use.

**Night abilities:**
***Wall of fire:*** same
***Tornado:*** same</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 14:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>CW rework entry, or how to give CW a purpose</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like Duplication!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 14:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54599-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599.rss">CW rework entry, or how to give CW a purpose</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CW rework entry, or how to give CW a purpose</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ninjarobot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Court Wizard</strong></p>
<p><strong>Day abilities:</strong><br>
<em><strong>Duplication:</strong></em> The selected target’s single target night ability will target an additional target of your choice. 1/2 uses.</p>
<p><em>You select a target to empower, and the extra target they will affect. I’m not sure whether the target you empowered target should know of duplication taking effect, because then it would be impossible to fake claim CW, instead the CW gets the feedback related to the second target. Maybe it’s best to get a very generic message if it fails, such as “your duplication was ineffective”. It is intentional that this ability can backfire, for instance you could target an assassin and give them a free 2 for 1. Duplication will fizzle if either target can’t be visited, either you or your empowered target gets occupied, if your empowered target uses a multitarget ability, or if they are the prince/king (no double guards or exes).</em><br>
<em><strong>Barrier:</strong></em> Now a day ability, will obviously take effect at night. Can now target self. 2 uses.</p>
<p><em>This makes it impossible both use duplication and barrier on the same target.</em></p>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong><br>
<em><strong>Calm mind :</strong></em> Your target is immune to conversion for two nights. Can only target the same target once. Unlimited uses.</p>
<p><em>Not sure if that ability is good enough for a filler yet, however, the premise is that with having more meaningful abilities, CW’s filler ability won’t feel as bad.</em><br>
<em><strong>Tornado:</strong></em> same</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Sage</strong></p>
<p><strong>Day abilities:</strong><br>
<em><strong>Silence:</strong></em> Same as reaper chill. 1 use.</p>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong><br>
<em><strong>Wall of fire:</strong></em> same<br>
<em><strong>Tornado:</strong></em> same</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54599-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cw-rework-entry-or-how-to-give-cw-a-purpose/54599.rss">CW rework entry, or how to give CW a purpose</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
