<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186</link>
    <description>Name: Esper
Alignment: Neutral Support

Passive 1 - Prepared: If able will automatically self heal whenever you would otherwise die

Day ability - Mind link: talk to your target anonymously for the entire following night. A psychic will be unable to link with you or your target. It will fail if your target is in jail (infinite)

Night ability 1 - Mind Read: Learn your targets class (infinite)

Night ability 2 - Kill aura: Kill your target and prevent all visitors. Will not consume a use if your target survives. (1 - will get an additional use every 5 kills)

Goal: Win only with neutrals

Note: can only spawn in games with at least 1 NK.

Kill Aura is supposed to have 2 uses. The first is killing. The preventing visitors will mean that a phys/Knight/obs won&#39;t be on them. The 2nd use is for preventing invests from being on the neutrals. Since you don&#39;t lose a use if they survive and most of the neutrals are at least sometimes Immune other than the fool it can help them stay under cover.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:26:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What do you mean same conditions? You do realize that the win condition is slightly easier than the NK. For one survival is technically not required. If you die but the NK wins then that’s a neutral win for you.</p>
<p>I’ll set it to every 5. If there are 15 kills then it’s just you left unless the priest revived someone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wolfy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But actually, heres another thing. If they can win of neutrals only,they need the same conditions as neutral killers like the reaper and possoor to give them the chance</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wolfy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh never mind. I got confused! I thought when you used it everyone will be vetted essentially. I misunderstood that people would have been prevented and I now know realise the similarities between thee Esper and the Sage and Assassin.</p>
<p>Forget my arguments then. I just think at leastchange the number of killes to about 4 or five rather then 10, but limit to about three uses max</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Kill aura is not a vet ability because anyone else trying to visit your target will simply be told “something prevented you from visiting your target”. They are not injured and I’m not sure why you think that it does.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 12:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wolfy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not arguing, but the way you say that with the Kill Aura that anyone that visits you and prevents all visitors, that already sounds like the Hunter’s Spike ability. The spike ability is therefore considered as a vet one as anyone that visits you, they will be prevented and end up being injured.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="15" data-topic="3186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s basically the same thing as a sage fire wall and an assassin.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The way this sounds, does not sound the same as the Sage’s  firewall and the Assassin.</p>
<p>If you check the wiki, this is slightly different to the way you’re describing it. Just wanted to make this a point. As I said, not arguing, but just wanted to put that ahead</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It isn’t a vet ability. It’s basically the same thing as a sage fire wall and an assassin. If you reach the end of the game and your still alive then you have won. The game won’t end while you have enemies alive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 10:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wolfy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="1" data-topic="3186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night ability 2 - Kill aura: Kill your target and prevent all visitors. Will not consume a use if your target survives. (1 - will get a second use once 10 people are dead)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="12" data-topic="3186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m thinking after 10 deaths you get a second use?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That would be cool I guess, but it is not assured that there will be ten deaths. Maximum number of players is sixteen with up to three Cult and three Unseen. A game can actually finish with at least 8 deaths potentially 10 with a reaper or possessor, but by then, the game would already be over. Maybe the number could be reduced slightly. However, the only thing I find is that this is kinda OP as a vet ability. The Hunter in my opinion should be the only one that could do that as it has the bleeding effect where the physician may be able to heal the target that made the mistake of visiting them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>FYI Im just going to say that a CW, Merc and butler using consecrated wine will stop your kill as will them being in jail or being night immune (that last 2 is obvious though).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 22:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you. This was the analysis I was wait for (sort of). I will do that.</p>
<p>Also to your questions.</p>
<p>How is this different from NK in KPN? - I simply don’t see what you mean by NK’s not getting at least 3 kills normally. As Reaper I will usually end the game with at least 5 soul’s. Also the limited usage means you might save your kills for important targets only (not saying 3 is a small amount. Just that it is less than NK usually. More like Prince).</p>
<p>Why invest when you could kill? - a lot of the time the information is more valuable than the kill. As SK in ToS some of my best plays were possable because I simply didn’t do anything until the very end. Because of this no one suspected me and I won. If I could spend the time as Possessor/Reaper checking people’s roles without killing them I totally would.</p>
<p>Note: although you have provided sufficient reason why having 3 is too much. I still feel link 1 might be too little. Maby there could be conditions where you get more? I’m thinking after 10 deaths you get a second use?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 22:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Before I start, let’s call Esper what it really is – a Neutral Killer.<br>
Some Neutral Killers can’t even pull off 3 kills in a game anyway, so what makes the Esper different?</p>
<p>3 KPNs (NK, Esper, Assassin/CL)  in a game is too much, and is too fast paced for the nature of this game.</p>
<p>And it’s honestly almost more powerful if not more powerful than our traditional NKs because Physicians, Knights, Court Wizards(?) and Kings cannot save your target anymore. The chance of you hitting the Mastermind or NK is low when the game starts.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="1" data-topic="3186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Passive 1 - Prepared: If able will automatically self heal whenever you would otherwise die</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Interesting idea. This means that you confirm yourself to killer classes. If the NK hits you, they know to team up with you, but if Assassin or CL hits you, you’re in trouble. Knights can still find you I suppose. Neat mechanic to “signal” to your NK partner.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="1" data-topic="3186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Kill Aura is supposed to have 2 uses. The first is killing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol no</p>
<p>Dude, I’m not going to waste it on who I <em>think</em> the NK is. I’m going to try to kill all the invests before they can find the NK. If I think the invest is targeting the NK tonight, why don’t I just kill the invest guaranteed since nobody can visit him? Then he can’t relay his info to BD. This is an ability that will be used every night until you’re out of uses.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="1" data-topic="3186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Day ability - Mind link: talk to your target anonymously for the entire following night. A psychic will be unable to link with you or your target. It will fail if your target is in jail (infinite)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This ability doesn’t make sense to me on this class. If you use this on a BD member, you’ve alerted the town that there is an Esper in the game since they realize there aren’t 3 people in the conversation like the Psychic does. I would only ever use this ability once I’ve hit an immune class, but if the Mastermind is still alive, you can’t reliably know that your target was NK. This day ability would likely go unused most of the time just to avoid your presence and to avoid alerting MM who you are.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="1" data-topic="3186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night ability 1 - Mind Read: Learn your targets class (infinite)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Normally I’d say this ability is powerful, but because I’d be using Killing Aura every night possible to assist my NK partner, I’d say this won’t have much use. I understand you are trying to make some synergy here between Mind Linking your NK partner after Mind Reading a BD member, but this requires you to</p>
<p>a) Be out of killing auras (in my very strong opinion)<br>
b) Also know who your NK is beyond a shadow of a doubt</p>
<p>As an Esper, why would you want to obtain information about that person if you can simply kill them?<br>
Even if you Mind Read them, there’s always a chance your NK or Assassin will kill them anyway, causing you to have wasted a precious night.</p>
<p>The opportunity cost of using Mind Read is so insanely high when you have the goals the Esper has and Kill Aura.</p>
<p>So after all that analysis, I think:</p>
<p><strong>Killing Aura needs 1 use only.</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 22:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mind link is not supposed to hide you. You use mind link on neutrals who won’t out you and people who are desperate who you can blackmail maby. The Esper’s mind read is why he can get more information than any other class. That’s 1 exact class per night plus more if your linked with someone who will talk.</p>
<p>ESPER CANNOT CLAIM PSYCHIC</p>
<p>He isn’t designed too and he shouldn’t try to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 22:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insert_Cancer_Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And yet again, if someone forces you use Telepathy you’re done for. I think that Psychic itself actually challenges that class investigation claim because both he and Esper get the same amount of investigative results per night. For Mindlink once you mindlink someone knows theres an Esper because remember, you use Mindlink in Daytime. I got no other comments</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For now I’m setting kill aura at 3. Like I said I’m not sure how meny it would actually need but it needs to be able to win with the NK dead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1: Reaper and Soulcatcher are both rarely outed as immune. The few times when they are is small enough that im ok with it. 2: if it were a survivor role then you could just use mind link to prove it like the Alch used too. 3: As it is right now it would get more information than any other class in the game. That is important for this class right now but if it was a survivor role it would be too much. 4: It isn’t clear to me how much it would need to kill on its own. Unlike the Alch it is very important that people are dying fast so it would need more than 2 uses Incase the NK is killed. That being said you are right that it might be too much. I would like to suggest that you don’t use class type as justification for changing the classes abilities. The class type is chosen last.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insert_Cancer_Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Look, there are flaws: 1. Sure it is, that’s why I say change it. But if there’s no Physician then you WILL be outed, because this role is like the Reaper and Soulcatcher. 2. How is it easily proveable? They could just ask you to use Telepathy and you’re done for. 3. This is exactly why a survivor goal would be perfect! It gives the class a lot more flexibility. 4. 4 kills for a Neutral Support is way to much, change it back to 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As a survivor it is OP because it is A: better than night immune. B: easily provable and C: gets lots of info.</p>
<p>Also what’s wrong with the passive? Or are you saying that it should be changed if I also change the goal?</p>
<p>I should probably also tell you that I upped the usage of kill aura to 4</p>
<p>And remember that if you are attacked then you are healed rather than immune. They wouldn’t out you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 19:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insert_Cancer_Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How is it Op? It can only kill twice and if you’re attacked people will out you as an Esper. Becoming King is only possible if they kill king and there isn’t a royal blood character in game. (All I recommend is that you change the passive to If you kill the same night you are attacked you will come back to life)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 19:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This role is OP as a survivor. And remember that if the other neutrals die you can still<br>
A: become king<br>
Or<br>
B: bid your time until late game and kill the last few people yourself with kill aura (should probably give it more uses for this)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 18:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insert_Cancer_Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do agree this is better as a Support role. This role’s goal however is almost impossible to accomplish. If you have only 2 neutrals and the other one dies, its an instant loss. This is a decent role, but the win condition is very, very difficult to win as. Again, this is better as a “Survivor” goal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 18:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Esper (Neutral Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Name: Esper<br>
Alignment: Neutral Support</p>
<p>Passive 1 - Prepared: If able will automatically self heal whenever you would otherwise die</p>
<p>Day ability - Mind link: talk to your target anonymously for the entire following night. A psychic will be unable to link with you or your target. It will fail if your target is in jail (infinite)</p>
<p>Night ability 1 - Mind Read: Learn your targets class (infinite)</p>
<p>Night ability 2 - Kill aura: Kill your target and prevent all visitors. Will not consume a use if your target survives. (1 - will get an additional use every 5 kills)</p>
<p>Goal: Win only with neutrals</p>
<p>Note: can only spawn in games with at least 1 NK.</p>
<p>Kill Aura is supposed to have 2 uses. The first is killing. The preventing visitors will mean that a phys/Knight/obs won’t be on them. The 2nd use is for preventing invests from being on the neutrals. Since you don’t lose a use if they survive and most of the neutrals are at least sometimes Immune other than the fool it can help them stay under cover.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 17:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3186-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/esper-neutral-support/3186.rss">Esper (Neutral Support)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
