<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>An explanation of recent events</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233</link>
    <description>I was banned from the ToL Discord.

Here are the facts. I will not use names and refer to everyone with single letters repeated 3 times, starting with AAA.

I&#39;m part of a Discord server that *was* a server for Guides+ to hang out, away from the hustle and bustle of ToL. This Server will henceforth be referred to as Site B

On November 20th, 2018 I was demoted from Moderator to Community Guide following two unrelated incidents in which I lost my temper. I said I was okay with this, but I was not.

On January 12th, 2019, the owner of Site B, AAA, said that the server was no longer affiliated with Throne of Lies, and was now a place for friends to hang out and talk about whatever they wanted.

Soon afterwards, I vented in Site B about my demotion, I had a lot of rage built up inside me and wanted to vent to people who knew what I was talking about, rather than other friends I have that don&#39;t know about Throne of Lies.

In these messages I said some unsavoury things about XBlade that I will not repeat, and these were passed on, without my knowledge, by a member of Site B, BBB. This led to my further demotion from Guide to not-guide.

I would like to point out that I do not blame BBB for this, but it was absolutely the wrong thing to do.

After this I had a private conversation with XBlade and we made our opinions on the matter clear to one another.

On January 29th, 2019, I left the Discord server of my own free will.

Cut to today, January 31st, 2019.

A member of the server, CCC, invites someone, DDD, to join Site B, to chill out and relax and all that cool stuff.

At roughly 3:45 PM UTC, DDD posts a wall of text directed at me that was, in my opinion, an attack, no screenshots exist of this message because DDD was banned from Site B soon after and the messages were deleted.

At 3:53, another member of the server, EEE, mentions that XBlade attempted to discredit Site B in a private chat.

At 4:36, EEE is banned from the ToL discord server, and it becomes evident that there is another person, FFF, in Site B passing information to XBlade.

FFF has since been banned from Site B, if i recall correctly.

At 4:46, I rejoin the official server, less than 8 minutes later I am banned for &quot;Supreme shit talking&quot;.

That&#39;s everything you need to know, I suspect I will be banned from the forums soon and this thread deleted.

I don&#39;t want to tell you how to feel about this, I simply want people to know why it happened.

I intend to stay in the forums for as long as possible, running FoL and FM games, trying to stay out of the way of the moderators.

In case this is my last post here, goodbye everyone, I&#39;ll never forget this community. I wouldn&#39;t say I love you *all* but there&#39;s a fair few of you I quite like : P

Jazz out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 08:21:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off-Topic (Thronepass)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>An explanation of recent events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 08:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75233-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233.rss">An explanation of recent events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An explanation of recent events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apologies, that was my ~4am</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Mod demotion</p>
</blockquote>
<p>You risked the mod team’s reputation by threatening people with bans, abusing your mod powers and cursing at others after multiple warnings.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Guide demotion</p>
</blockquote>
<p>You disrespected the person you essentially volunteered for. This means you held power over a community you have 0 respect to the one that leads it.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Unsavory things about Xblade</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This wasn’t just a single event; this has been going on since the mod demotion (quite a long time ago, now).</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Now</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The community ban will remain active. Everyone makes their own decisions, and you made all of these decisions yourself without consideration of who it may affect.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>TL;DR:</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Mod was demoted after multiple warnings. Dev liked former mod, so let her stay as Guide. Guide consistently trash talks dev over a long period of time, finally gets removed from the community and is surprised when it shouldn’t be a surprise at all.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Active games</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I apologize to the community for any games this may affect. However, this was a decision that Jazz could have avoided with the community in mind, but did reflect upon this consideration. While I’m saddened that a FoL host will be removed from this forum, she has lost my trust, went against our guidelines, and led personal attacks.</p>
<p>(Deleted the replies above before context from my reply was added. This topic will remain locked, as it’s not a discussion)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 08:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75233-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233.rss">An explanation of recent events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An explanation of recent events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rezid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75233-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233.rss">An explanation of recent events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An explanation of recent events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75233-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233.rss">An explanation of recent events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An explanation of recent events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was banned from the ToL Discord.</p>
<p>Here are the facts. I will not use names and refer to everyone with single letters repeated 3 times, starting with AAA.</p>
<p>I’m part of a Discord server that <em>was</em> a server for Guides+ to hang out, away from the hustle and bustle of ToL. This Server will henceforth be referred to as Site B</p>
<p>On November 20th, 2018 I was demoted from Moderator to Community Guide following two unrelated incidents in which I lost my temper. I said I was okay with this, but I was not.</p>
<p>On January 12th, 2019, the owner of Site B, AAA, said that the server was no longer affiliated with Throne of Lies, and was now a place for friends to hang out and talk about whatever they wanted.</p>
<p>Soon afterwards, I vented in Site B about my demotion, I had a lot of rage built up inside me and wanted to vent to people who knew what I was talking about, rather than other friends I have that don’t know about Throne of Lies.</p>
<p>In these messages I said some unsavoury things about XBlade that I will not repeat, and these were passed on, without my knowledge, by a member of Site B, BBB. This led to my further demotion from Guide to not-guide.</p>
<p>I would like to point out that I do not blame BBB for this, but it was absolutely the wrong thing to do.</p>
<p>After this I had a private conversation with XBlade and we made our opinions on the matter clear to one another.</p>
<p>On January 29th, 2019, I left the Discord server of my own free will.</p>
<p>Cut to today, January 31st, 2019.</p>
<p>A member of the server, CCC, invites someone, DDD, to join Site B, to chill out and relax and all that cool stuff.</p>
<p>At roughly 3:45 PM UTC, DDD posts a wall of text directed at me that was, in my opinion, an attack, no screenshots exist of this message because DDD was banned from Site B soon after and the messages were deleted.</p>
<p>At 3:53, another member of the server, EEE, mentions that XBlade attempted to discredit Site B in a private chat.</p>
<p>At 4:36, EEE is banned from the ToL discord server, and it becomes evident that there is another person, FFF, in Site B passing information to XBlade.</p>
<p>FFF has since been banned from Site B, if i recall correctly.</p>
<p>At 4:46, I rejoin the official server, less than 8 minutes later I am banned for “Supreme shit talking”.</p>
<p>That’s everything you need to know, I suspect I will be banned from the forums soon and this thread deleted.</p>
<p>I don’t want to tell you how to feel about this, I simply want people to know why it happened.</p>
<p>I intend to stay in the forums for as long as possible, running FoL and FM games, trying to stay out of the way of the moderators.</p>
<p>In case this is my last post here, goodbye everyone, I’ll never forget this community. I wouldn’t say I love you <em>all</em> but there’s a fair few of you I quite like : P</p>
<p>Jazz out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75233-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/an-explanation-of-recent-events/75233.rss">An explanation of recent events</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
