<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Yet Another BARD (Blue Dragon) &amp; SIREN (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298</link>
    <description>Let&#39;s nail down a Bard concept once and for all by making it a &quot;situationally powerful&quot; class.

**Bard**
Icon: A beautiful singer with lute.

Passive:
**Truth is Beauty** - You are notified the moment a day ability is used on you, though you will **not** be told which ability was used or which player/class used it.

_^ Normal ability notices still apply though, like if you get poisoned or bled. It will tell you someone used an ability on you, then the normal poisoned/bled notice. Other abilities with no pre-existing notice will just tell you an unnamed ability was used on you._

Day Ability:
**Sing Praises** - Perform a ballad praising another player. Cause a targeted player&#39;s words to appear in **bold text** and their next vote to count for two. Cannot be used on King or yourself. (2 uses.)

_^ A recurring problem I see in rounds is people not paying attention to someone with important information. This is a direct counter to that kind of issue. Raise a player&#39;s voice, and give them a small voting boost._

Night Ability 1:
**Soulful Serenade** - Sing a healing tune to your audience tonight. You, and all who visit you tonight will be healed as if selected by a Physician. (4 uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**Trained Mockingbird** - Release a mockingbird to repeat your target&#39;s words to you. Select a player to also see their results if they&#39;re an investigative class. (Unlimited use.)

_^ In other words, select the Observer and you&#39;ll see what he sees from the results of his abilities. If he doesn&#39;t get results, or your target isn&#39;t an investigative, you&#39;ll just get no results. I made this unlimited because I feel like it&#39;s pretty situational and there&#39;s a high risk of not getting results._

----

Converts to...

----

**Siren** (Unseen)
Icon: A creepy-looking singer with long, talon-like fingernails.

Passive:
**Beauty is Truth** - You will be told if a Blue Dragon uses a day ability on you, as well as their class. (IE: &quot;The Prince has used a day ability on you.&quot; or &quot;A Noble has used a day ability on you.&quot; Normal messages you&#39;d usually see also still apply like with the Bard&#39;s passive. You **do not** see the player&#39;s name.)

Day Ability:
**Pointed Ridicule** - Perform a limerick mocking another player. Cause a targeted player&#39;s words to appear in **bold text** and their next vote to count for two. Cannot be used on King or yourself. (2 uses. Remaining uses inherited from Bard class&#39; day ability.)

_^ Mostly there so you can&#39;t be called out as converted by losing the ability, but ideally you would use this to boost a bad player or an evil player and make them seem more important or correct. Use on a Scorned, your Mastermind, whatever._

Night Ability 1:
**Battle Hymn** - Choose a member of the Unseen to sing a rallying song to. They will gain occupation immunity, and their visitors will be occupied. Does not work on occupy-immune classes. (2 uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**Clever Crow** - Release a mischievous crow to get a player lost. Select two targets. The first will be **falsely** told they were redirected to the second. (4 uses.)

_^ The results don&#39;t change other than the false redirect message. Can be used to confuse pretty much any class with a night ability. For one example, you might trick a Sheriff into thinking he was redirected and make him think he found the other player was Unseen._</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 02:14:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Yet Another BARD (Blue Dragon) &amp; SIREN (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So for battle Hymenwould it say you were occupied visiting your target or you were occupied? Because if it is the first it could be a negative effect because the BD would not the Unseen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 02:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52298-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298.rss">[Class Suggestion] Yet Another BARD (Blue Dragon) &amp; SIREN (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Yet Another BARD (Blue Dragon) &amp; SIREN (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love it, btw I also love you’re channel</p>
<p>Edit: ty so much for liking my comment!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 01:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52298-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298.rss">[Class Suggestion] Yet Another BARD (Blue Dragon) &amp; SIREN (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Yet Another BARD (Blue Dragon) &amp; SIREN (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let’s nail down a Bard concept once and for all by making it a “situationally powerful” class.</p>
<p><strong>Bard</strong><br>
Icon: A beautiful singer with lute.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Truth is Beauty</strong> - You are notified the moment a day ability is used on you, though you will <strong>not</strong> be told which ability was used or which player/class used it.</p>
<p><em>^ Normal ability notices still apply though, like if you get poisoned or bled. It will tell you someone used an ability on you, then the normal poisoned/bled notice. Other abilities with no pre-existing notice will just tell you an unnamed ability was used on you.</em></p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Sing Praises</strong> - Perform a ballad praising another player. Cause a targeted player’s words to appear in <strong>bold text</strong> and their next vote to count for two. Cannot be used on King or yourself. (2 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ A recurring problem I see in rounds is people not paying attention to someone with important information. This is a direct counter to that kind of issue. Raise a player’s voice, and give them a small voting boost.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Soulful Serenade</strong> - Sing a healing tune to your audience tonight. You, and all who visit you tonight will be healed as if selected by a Physician. (4 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Trained Mockingbird</strong> - Release a mockingbird to repeat your target’s words to you. Select a player to also see their results if they’re an investigative class. (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p><em>^ In other words, select the Observer and you’ll see what he sees from the results of his abilities. If he doesn’t get results, or your target isn’t an investigative, you’ll just get no results. I made this unlimited because I feel like it’s pretty situational and there’s a high risk of not getting results.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Converts to…</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Siren</strong> (Unseen)<br>
Icon: A creepy-looking singer with long, talon-like fingernails.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Beauty is Truth</strong> - You will be told if a Blue Dragon uses a day ability on you, as well as their class. (IE: “The Prince has used a day ability on you.” or “A Noble has used a day ability on you.” Normal messages you’d usually see also still apply like with the Bard’s passive. You <strong>do not</strong> see the player’s name.)</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Pointed Ridicule</strong> - Perform a limerick mocking another player. Cause a targeted player’s words to appear in <strong>bold text</strong> and their next vote to count for two. Cannot be used on King or yourself. (2 uses. Remaining uses inherited from Bard class’ day ability.)</p>
<p><em>^ Mostly there so you can’t be called out as converted by losing the ability, but ideally you would use this to boost a bad player or an evil player and make them seem more important or correct. Use on a Scorned, your Mastermind, whatever.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Battle Hymn</strong> - Choose a member of the Unseen to sing a rallying song to. They will gain occupation immunity, and their visitors will be occupied. Does not work on occupy-immune classes. (2 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Clever Crow</strong> - Release a mischievous crow to get a player lost. Select two targets. The first will be <strong>falsely</strong> told they were redirected to the second. (4 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ The results don’t change other than the false redirect message. Can be used to confuse pretty much any class with a night ability. For one example, you might trick a Sheriff into thinking he was redirected and make him think he found the other player was Unseen.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 01:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52298-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-yet-another-bard-blue-dragon-siren-unseen/52298.rss">[Class Suggestion] Yet Another BARD (Blue Dragon) &amp; SIREN (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
