<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rekcana - Court Wizard Contest </title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622</link>
    <description>Court Wizard Update:

Day ability: 

Barrier: One time Use similar to Physician Bleed Protection: Prevents player from being converted. [this ability only remains in effect while the CW is alive, giving it kind of a chant or channeled spell feel. This would promote the protection of a CW] (played receives notification when the enchant is placed on them, and if it blocks a conversion both for the CW and effected player)

Night Abilities: 


Teleport: Unlimited Uses: Allows the swapping of the Court Wizard with a selected target. [I personally enjoy the swap aspect of the game and this gives the court Wizard some self protection to keep his Barriered target safe] I wanted to limit this to only swapping himself and the target tho to balance its unlimited usage and add risk to swapping with high value targets. 

Since you said you didn&#39;t like the unlimited tornado ideas I figured I&#39;d try out something new. The lore of wizards is powerful magic but since we can&#39;t go an offensive style I figured a disruptive style might fit. Illusion is powerful but also has risk involved because if that person is subject to a invest of any kind they will come back as blue dragon and Support/Social which can hurt them later on if they claim something that isn&#39;t Support Social and it conflicts with logs.

Illusion: Unlimited uses: The court wizard creates an illusion version of himself -will show BD, Support/Social- at the target location and becomes the target of all abilities good and bad. [only able to stop one attack that night] 

Second Ability. 

Spirit Contact: 2-3 Uses. Allows for contact with the dead the following night. [I feel like the Psychics ability to contact the dead was useful to the balance of the possessor, this gave them a focus target before jumping bodies so I feel like moving and limiting it to CW could help make them a valuable target for people to focus on killing early]


Sage:

Day Ability: None

Night Ability: 

Teleport/Illusion: Same as before but illusion sage shows as Unseen/Support Social

Death Calls: 1 time use | Similar to Spirit Contact the Sage spends One night to summon an ally the following night to carry out one attack. (If you us use the ability on dead player 6, if would show as a visit from 6)  [im not sure how well this would fit in balancing for unseen, but seeing as it&#39;s a one time use that consumes 2 nights to activate/use I think it would balance itself and if the sage becomes the assassin during the time it takes to summon it&#39;s wasted anyways]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 11:45:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rekcana - Court Wizard Contest </title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think it should protect the CW from conversion</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 11:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54622-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622.rss">Rekcana - Court Wizard Contest </source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rekcana - Court Wizard Contest </title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RawkHawk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the day barrier is interesting, but don’t have it tell other players they are protected. Having confirming day abilities is always a bad route.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54622-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622.rss">Rekcana - Court Wizard Contest </source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rekcana - Court Wizard Contest </title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rekcana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Court Wizard Update:</p>
<p>Day ability:</p>
<p>Barrier: One time Use similar to Physician Bleed Protection: Prevents player from being converted. [this ability only remains in effect while the CW is alive, giving it kind of a chant or channeled spell feel. This would promote the protection of a CW] (played receives notification when the enchant is placed on them, and if it blocks a conversion both for the CW and effected player)</p>
<p>Night Abilities:</p>
<p>Teleport: Unlimited Uses: Allows the swapping of the Court Wizard with a selected target. [I personally enjoy the swap aspect of the game and this gives the court Wizard some self protection to keep his Barriered target safe] I wanted to limit this to only swapping himself and the target tho to balance its unlimited usage and add risk to swapping with high value targets.</p>
<p>Since you said you didn’t like the unlimited tornado ideas I figured I’d try out something new. The lore of wizards is powerful magic but since we can’t go an offensive style I figured a disruptive style might fit. Illusion is powerful but also has risk involved because if that person is subject to a invest of any kind they will come back as blue dragon and Support/Social which can hurt them later on if they claim something that isn’t Support Social and it conflicts with logs.</p>
<p>Illusion: Unlimited uses: The court wizard creates an illusion version of himself -will show BD, Support/Social- at the target location and becomes the target of all abilities good and bad. [only able to stop one attack that night]</p>
<p>Second Ability.</p>
<p>Spirit Contact: 2-3 Uses. Allows for contact with the dead the following night. [I feel like the Psychics ability to contact the dead was useful to the balance of the possessor, this gave them a focus target before jumping bodies so I feel like moving and limiting it to CW could help make them a valuable target for people to focus on killing early]</p>
<p>Sage:</p>
<p>Day Ability: None</p>
<p>Night Ability:</p>
<p>Teleport/Illusion: Same as before but illusion sage shows as Unseen/Support Social</p>
<p>Death Calls: 1 time use | Similar to Spirit Contact the Sage spends One night to summon an ally the following night to carry out one attack. (If you us use the ability on dead player 6, if would show as a visit from 6)  [im not sure how well this would fit in balancing for unseen, but seeing as it’s a one time use that consumes 2 nights to activate/use I think it would balance itself and if the sage becomes the assassin during the time it takes to summon it’s wasted anyways]</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 15:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54622-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rekcana-court-wizard-contest/54622.rss">Rekcana - Court Wizard Contest </source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
