<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Ashe&#39;s Lore Suggestion] The Aristocrat</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040</link>
    <description>The title was already used so I just made it Ashe&#39;s Lore Suggestion ;)

Of the many Nobles visiting Castle Adiart, there are a few who would betray the Blue Dragon in a moment for more power or wealth. However, they would betray any organization for more personal gain, so they were not seen as fit for the Unseen. The Unseen had their eyes on a particular Noble, who didn&#39;t hold a seemingly large amount of power or standing in the court. This was the reason for choosing them however, as they were very ordinary. The Mastermind knew that to take the throne, they would need a noble to take the seat of power when the opportunity arose, but not any noble that would be suspected.

Thus, the plan was set into action. On a particular night in the Castle, the Mastermind approached a specific Noble. This Noble was suspicious of such a late night visit, but welcomed in the Mastermind all the same. As the Mastermind began to try to convince the Noble of what a seat of power could mean for him, the Noble grew less suspicious. The Mastermind told great stories of how Adiart&#39;s next king would bring a new &quot;golden age&quot; of prosperity. The Noble asked, &quot;How would I be placed into this position?&quot; The Mastermind smiled and said, &quot;With the help of my organization, the Unseen, we can help you to get into a position of power, and be the true ruler of Adiart!&quot; 

The Noble was convinced, and agreed to rise when an opportunity to become King occurred, not knowing of the Mastermind&#39;s plan to have the current King assassinated. The Mastermind left, leaving behind someone who was no longer the Noble, but the Aristocrat.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:02:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Ashe&#39;s Lore Suggestion] The Aristocrat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was hoping for an Aristocat</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3040-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040.rss">[Ashe&#39;s Lore Suggestion] The Aristocrat</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Ashe&#39;s Lore Suggestion] The Aristocrat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The title was already used so I just made it Ashe’s Lore Suggestion <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Of the many Nobles visiting Castle Adiart, there are a few who would betray the Blue Dragon in a moment for more power or wealth. However, they would betray any organization for more personal gain, so they were not seen as fit for the Unseen. The Unseen had their eyes on a particular Noble, who didn’t hold a seemingly large amount of power or standing in the court. This was the reason for choosing them however, as they were very ordinary. The Mastermind knew that to take the throne, they would need a noble to take the seat of power when the opportunity arose, but not any noble that would be suspected.</p>
<p>Thus, the plan was set into action. On a particular night in the Castle, the Mastermind approached a specific Noble. This Noble was suspicious of such a late night visit, but welcomed in the Mastermind all the same. As the Mastermind began to try to convince the Noble of what a seat of power could mean for him, the Noble grew less suspicious. The Mastermind told great stories of how Adiart’s next king would bring a new “golden age” of prosperity. The Noble asked, “How would I be placed into this position?” The Mastermind smiled and said, “With the help of my organization, the Unseen, we can help you to get into a position of power, and be the true ruler of Adiart!”</p>
<p>The Noble was convinced, and agreed to rise when an opportunity to become King occurred, not knowing of the Mastermind’s plan to have the current King assassinated. The Mastermind left, leaving behind someone who was no longer the Noble, but the Aristocrat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 16:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3040-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ashes-lore-suggestion-the-aristocrat/3040.rss">[Ashe&#39;s Lore Suggestion] The Aristocrat</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
