<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418</link>
    <description>## Three Kingdoms but Worse

What will happen if USA, India, and Russia launch all of their nuke? Hell if I know.

We&#39;re not talking about them anyway.

In this world, there are 5 communities under a leader each. The group can be a country, kingdom, democrat or technocracy for all I care, but they are communities. Buuut when there are 5 superpower groups in the world that has *infinite* resource and *almost infinite* manpower, do you think humans can live peacefully?

Pfft. As if. 

You are a leader of a community! Your job is to make your community flourish by all means possible! And there we go.

# Sign-up
Fill up this sheet.

&gt;**Community Name**: Self explanatory. Country/kingdom/federation name
&gt;**Government Form**: Monarchy/democracy/dictatorship/whatever. This might affect the game.
&gt;**Leader Title**: The title of you, glorious leader &lt;Player 1&gt;
&gt;**Aide&#39;s Title**: The title of second class leader &lt;Player 2 if anyone wants to join instead of making their own country&gt;
&gt;**Community Ideal**: The community&#39;s philosophy as a whole. This might affect the game.
&gt;**Technology Focus**: Magic oriented? Technology oriented? Tea oriented? Go wild.

#  Game Mechanic
1. The game is divided into Planning, Execution, and Reporter Phase.
2. In Planning Phase, the Leader and Aide will submit one action each.
3. Some actions cannot be taken unless special facilities are built beforehand
4. Building facilities (like school, bunker, etc) requires one planning action. However, the construction may take longer than one Execution Phase.
5. There is no way to clear the game, however, should all communities except for one are destroyed, the survivor is declared Leader of the World and may end the game.

## Planning Phase
In this phase, you are free to ask GM questions, discuss with your aide, or communicate with other team. At the end of this phase, you should submit two actions to perform by your community. This action can be anything from **/Train soldier squad**, **/Build research facility**, or **/Host Miss Universe Contest**.

## Execution Phase
At this phase, your plan will be executed. You will be notified if it succeed, failed, or if something prevent it from being accomplished.

## Reporter Phase
At this phase, the Reporter Acolytes of Information Temple will print a newspaper regarding of any *visible* actions performed by communities.Training soldiers, of course, cannot be hidden unless there is a training facility that house them.

# Rules
1. I am God. You leaders are mortal. Obey me. My words are law. 
2. This game does not stress on realism. The God&#39;s words are final. 
3. The God encourages shenanigans such as magic, bio-punk civilisation, and Cthulhu.
4. Have fun! This game is likely to be one serious mess, but go build yourself a crazy community.
5. I reserve the right to add, changes, and bend the rules as I see fit.
6. **This game will require a Discord as there will be a discord server later.**

### Community List
1. Dawei-ist Theocracy **Leader**: Bishop Marluxion **Aide**: Patriach Mercenary
2. Our Kingdom of Family Guy **Leader**:Honored Peter Griffin, Pug the F*cking Strong **Aide**: Stewie Griffin, Squid the One with Blaster
3. Anti-Revolt Commonwealth **Leader**: Ms. Callie &#39;Twil1ght&#39; **Aide**: Dignitary Gayde
4. Bitch the Suplex City **Leader**: Beast BlueStorm **Aide**: Advocate Nerbo &#39;Nerbins&#39; the Desperate
5. New West Anglia **Leader**: Grand Duchess Jasmine

[details=Community Biodata]
&gt;# Dawei-ists Theocracy
&gt;*&quot;Do you know dawei?&quot;*
&gt;**Community Name** : Dawei-ists
**Government Form** : Theocracy
**Leader Title** : Bishop Marl
**Aide’s Title** : Matriarch / Partiarch (Aide Name)
**Community Ideal** : A country ruled by a fanatic religion called “Daeweism” . They seek to all someday meet their god, Dawei.
&gt;**Technology Focus** : Blood Rituals, human sacrifice, summoning Eldritch Creatures from the void. &gt;All that jazz.

&gt; # Our Kingdom of Family Guy
&gt;
&gt;*“eheheh, hey lois. remember when we started a communist uprising?”*
**Government Form**  : Communism
**Leader Title**  : Your Honored Peter Griffin: Pug the Fucking Strong
**Aide’s Title**  : The Stewie Griffin: Squid the One with the Blaster
**Community Ideal**  : You must follow what the leader says or you will be executed. You have some freedom so it is not entirely communism (to prevent the game from being boring). Also since it is not true communism. High ranks get lots. Also you gotta like Family Guy, if you dont like Family Guy. You will be executed.
**Technology Focus**  : Nuclear oriented that extracts the nuclear radiation from the NuclearBurrito in the Maximus salt cave. Also Family Guy
**Execution style:**  The one on execution is forced to wear a chicken costume with absolutely no visible sight holes. Then the Peter Griffin beats them up until they are dead.

&gt;# Anti-Revolt Commonwealth
&gt;
&gt;*heated debate in the parliarment*
**Community Name** : Global Anarchists
**Government Form** : Merciless Democracy
**Leader Title** : HCCR (Head Of Control And Counteracting Revolutions): Ms. Callie
**Aide’s Title** : FSSM (First Secretary of State For Supervisory Matters) : Dignitary Geyde
**Community Ideal** : Leftwing, Rightwing and Center together… Isn’t it beatiful?
Indeed but unfortunately not everyone want live in peace. Our neighbours aren’t our enemies but just ***confused*** . We have to show them the way and unite this world once more. However any people that would work with other societies with our formal approval, to those people we cannot show them mercy and any attempts to overtake the control by any of the parties, they would be brutally crushed. We will won no matter of the cost.
**Technology Focus** : Fascist’s Militarism And Propaganda / Communist’s Sabotage and Revolts / Democratic Economy Structure / Theocratic’s Sorcery / Republic’s Ministry Of Security And Terror / Monarchist’s Tradition And Contacts

&gt;# Bitch the Suplex City 
&gt;
&gt;*&quot;PROTEIN!&quot;*
&gt;**Community Name**  : Suplex City,  ***BITCH***
**Government Form**  : Dictatorship
**Leader Title**  :
&gt;
&gt;* Full Title - The Reigning, Defending, Undisputed Universal Champion, The Beast Incarnate, BlueStorm
&gt;* Short Title - The Beast, BlueStorm
&gt;
&gt;**Aide’s Title**  :
&gt;
&gt;* Full Title - Ladies and Gentlemen, My Name is Nerbo, Advocate and Right Fist Man to the Beast Incarnate, BlueStorm
&gt;* Short Title - The Advocate, Nerbo the Desperate
&gt;
&gt;**Community Ideal**  : Disrespect The Advocate, and The Beast will crush you. Disrespect The Beast… and The Beast will crush you. Do as The Advocate says and you may gain favour. Stay away from The Beast and you will gain the reward of not being crushed.
**Technology Focus**  : Strength-based. Procuring anything possible in order to grow a melee-strong arsenal with the ability to take the heaviest shots as if they were feathers.


&gt;# New West Anglia
&gt;
&gt;*&quot;All hail Her Excellency, the Grand Duchess of New West Anglia!&quot;*
&gt;**Community Name** : New West Anglia
**Government Form** : Monarchy
**Leader Title** : Grand Duke/Grand Duchess, often referred to in formal settings as “His/Her Excellency the Grand Duke/Duchess of New West Anglia and Protector of the Anglish people”
**Aide’s Title** : Arbiter, formally referred to as “His/Her highness”
**Community Ideal** : The pursuit of progress and innovation, nothing is perfect and so everything can be improved, and if something can be improved then it should be improved, obviously.
**Technology Focus** : S T E A M P O W E R. Specifically, NWA use steam to power everything, their obsession with innovation means that, with the right combination of willpower, resources and sometimes just plain foolhardiness, anything can be accomplished with steam and gears.
[/details]
____
Ask me if anything is unclear. @Shurian is my Co-Host. :blue_heart:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 02:03:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Roleplaying</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlueStorm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Planning Phase 5 Start”</p>
<p><em>Looks at thread title</em></p>
<p>Coulda fooled me</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/137">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/137</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 02:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-137</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h3>Reporter Archaeologist Corner!</h3>
<p>Today at the excavation site of an ancient civilisation, I, Reporter Archaeologist Arc has discovered a written document of an extinct nation, the Tea Party.</p>
<p>Continuing from the last report, Tea-ligion, the way of life followed by Tea Party community, is the core of Tea Party Community. Tea-ligion states that tea is the ultimate plant of all plant and it can solve every problem in the world given the right treatment.</p>
<p>Traditional Tea Party meetings are always held over tea and snacks, showing their respect for tea. A text obtained by a fellow botanist reveals a secret that had able Tea-ligion, and Tea Party, to reign over the world. How could a community focused on tea rule the world?</p>
<p>In the next print, we will discuss the reason behind Tea Party world domination.</p>
<hr>
<h1>Planning Phase 5 start</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/136">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/136</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 14:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-136</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Reporter Phase 4</h1>
<p>“Hello, World! This is Reporter Bishop from Mass Media Network. Today in this world we have five countries reigning supreme! Let us here from our Reporter Acolytes what they have in store!”</p>
<hr>
<h4>Dawei-ist Theocracy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Dawei from Dawei-ist Theocracy!</p>
<p>Bishop Marl and Matriarch Mercenary has started a <strong>large excavation</strong>! Rumours around say they are creating a whole subterranean level. A clever way to increase their territory, I must say!</p>
<p>I also took the time to stroll around the Grand Chapel! I must say, it’s a very large chapel, but rumours around… I will investigate this more.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Our Kingdom of Family Guy</h4>
<p>“This is Reporter Bishop. Acolyte Guy didn’t send us his report this time around. We apologise for the inconvenience.”</p>
<hr>
<h4>Anti-Revolt Commonwealth</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Rev from Anti-Revolt Commonwealth!</p>
<p>Ms. Callie and Dignitary Geyde has broadcasted <strong>fiery political speech for patriotism</strong>! It’s just a hunch, but I’m sure of a propa- whoops! Can’t say anymore if I want to save my neck!</p>
<p>There is also rumours of <strong>a messenger leaving the mansion</strong> heading outside of the community. I wonder what that is?</p>
<hr>
<h4>Bitch the Suplex City</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Plex from Bitch the Suplex City!</p>
<p>Beast Bluestorm and Advocate Nerbo has started training <strong>soldiers</strong>! From the look of the recruits, I dare say they are stronger than average soldiers!</p>
<p>The construction of <strong>FuryGround, grand martial art training complex</strong> is also finished! I can expect many martial artists around, but that is not all!</p>
<p><strong>Representative from Dawei Theocracy, Our Kingdom of Family Guy, Anti–Revolution Commonwealth, and New West Anglia has arrived</strong> in Suplex City! The representative of each country will reside in the newly built FuryGround, for the moment.</p>
<p>Incidentally, the construction of <strong>Research Lab</strong> is finished! It doesn’t take long, does it?</p>
<p>And hear me out, <strong>I see Advocate Nerbo going around the city</strong> again! He seems to be answering questions from the populace and taking suggestions. I want to meet him more now~</p>
<hr>
<h4>New West Anglia</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Angel from New West Anglia!</p>
<p>Grand Duchess Jasmine and Arbiter Kai have appoint <strong>soldiers to the Border Wall</strong>. This will make the security tighter, but luckily, I have received special permission from the Grand Duchess itself to pass the border freely.</p>
<p>They have also finished the construction of <strong>Research Lab</strong>. I’m sure it will be an important building for the future.</p>
<p>This is just a rumour, but <strong>Dawei Missionaries are no longer seen on the street</strong>. I wonder what happened to them?</p>
<hr>
<p>“And there we have it, folks! Reporter Bishop here from Mass Media Network will say good bye. Our Acolytes can only search from information in-person for now, but some money has helped to changed that.”</p>
<p>“We have also finished the construction of a nuclear bunker considering some rather alarming movement in a certain community. Acolyte Guy, unfortunately, hasn’t been able to be contacted lately. We will look into this matter at a later date.”</p>
<p>“And today, our special service <strong>Private Channel has been used</strong>! We thank our costumer for using our service.”</p>
<p>“Let us continue to today’s special section!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/135">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/135</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 14:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-135</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Changing community name is a big deal especially for the people</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/134">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/134</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 04:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-134</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure just spend an action on it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/133">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/133</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 04:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-133</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/damafaud">@Damafaud</a> can we rename our country to Petoria</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/132">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/132</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 00:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-132</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We’re saving it for WoL 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/131</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 22:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-131</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly surprised that none of you chose to make doofania with a bunch of wacky inventions</p>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9950d859823eceb0b5de0f35cb47d4fd31b8086f.jpeg" alt="lv3ovtb6w1621" data-base62-sha1="lSigimeYomFR7R2NH4EFZs36Arl" width="666" height="500"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/130</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 20:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-130</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h3>Reporter Interviewer Net Corner!</h3>
<p><strong>Interviewer Net</strong>: Hello, hello! Today we have an interview with one of the great leaders from our local communities, <strong>The Beast BlueStorm</strong>! Let’s hear what he has to say on some issues of today!</p>
<p><strong>Interviewer Net</strong>: Thank you for making time off your busy schedule! For a starter, would you care to share your stance on the recently constructed Nuclear Bomb Creation Facility in Our Kingdom of Family Guy? The news, as a whole, is a big shock to everyone!</p>
<p><strong>Beast BlueStorm</strong>: I believe this to be an attempt at a show of force by Pug Griffin, and I will let it be known that should they come to us with threats of war, that we will find allies and we will not back down.</p>
<p><strong>Interviewer Ne</strong>t: Thank you. Mass Media Network is also concerned of this development. We have an obligation to spread information and to risk our life for it, but the death of an Acolyte is always undesirable.</p>
<p><strong>Interviewer Net</strong>: Moving on to the next question, other than Our Kingdom of Family Guy, Anti-Revolution Commonwealth has also been actively improving their military. Do you see them as a cause of concern, or at least, consideration?</p>
<p><strong>Beast BlueStorm</strong>: While the improvement of military units may seem like a possible concern, there is currently no reason for us to worry until these troops are mobilised. If or when that time comes, I assure the people of Suplex City that we will be prepared.</p>
<p><strong>Interviewer Net</strong>: And for good reason! Your attention to public healthcare and public in general has been noted by your people and our Network. It is interesting to see someone who cares about their people.</p>
<p><strong>Interviewer Net</strong>: Last question. Do you have any plans for Suplex City? Tell us how would you develop your community in the future.</p>
<p><strong>Beast BlueStorm</strong>: While I cannot disclose anything specific at present, I can say that there are big plans to improve the health, morale, and wellbeing of our people. They are, after all, the most important part of this kingdom. We have big plans to create a community that is strong both in togetherness and physical prowess.</p>
<p><strong>Interviewer Net</strong>:  I see. Thank you for your time. Do you have any closing statements for our readers?</p>
<p><strong>Beast BlueStorm</strong>: Just the one - if you ever see Advocate Nerbo in the streets again, don’t be afraid to give him suggestions on how to improve our community! We’re always looking for new ideas.</p>
<p><strong>Interviewer Net</strong>: Thank you for your time!</p>
<hr>
<h3>Reporter Archaeologist Corner!</h3>
<p>Today at the excavation site of an ancient civilisation, I, Reporter Archaeologist Arc has discovered a written document of an extinct nation.</p>
<p>The document speaks of a community called Tea Party, led by Mad Hatter Dama and his trusty advisor, Alice. This Tea Party is an ancient community, known from reference of other sources, similar to that of a theocracy. However, their religion is not necessarily a religion. Tea-ligion, the ideal of the nation, is closer to a way of life than a religion.</p>
<p>Many archaeologists doubt the existence of this community. Partly, this is due to the sparse and few sigsn and heritages of their civilisation. However, I do believe that this lack of evidence is caused by their custom, mainly, Tea-ligion.</p>
<p>I will continue this report on the next print.</p>
<h1>Planning Phase 4 start</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/129</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 13:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-129</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Reporter Phase 3</h1>
<p>“Hello, World! This is Reporter Bishop from Mass Media Network. Today in this world we have five countries reigning supreme! Let us here from our Reporter Acolytes what they have in store!”</p>
<hr>
<h4>Dawei-ist Theocracy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Dawei from Dawei-ist Theocracy!</p>
<p>Bishop Marl and Matriarch Mercenary has built a <strong>Hospital</strong>! That will sure come in handy in case of an epidemic.</p>
<p>Incidentally, the construction of the <strong>Grand Chapel</strong> is finished! I must say, it’s a very large chapel, fit to be the pride of Dawei Theocracy!</p>
<p>They have also <strong>sent a group of Missionaries into New West Anglia</strong>! What a noble quest!</p>
<p>Speaking of missionaries, <strong>missionaries from Our Kingdom of Family Guy has entered Dawei Theocracy</strong>. I’m not sure of the others, but the Grand Chapel sure does a good impression on Dawei!</p>
<hr>
<h4>Our Kingdom of Family Guy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Guy from Our Kingdom of Family Guy!<br>
A group of <strong>Dawei Missionaries have been seen</strong> in public area, and there are a few converts, too!</p>
<p>Pug Griffin and Squiddy Griffin has sent <strong>missionaries to Dawei Theocracy</strong>! What a noble quest!</p>
<p>There are also <strong>station sentries on Border Wall</strong>. Is it an increase in security? They sure look a bit scary.</p>
<p>…finally,  <strong>THE NUCLEAR BOMB CREATION FACILITY IS FINISHED</strong>. As my request to change post has been denied, I will take steps to preserve my life!</p>
<hr>
<h4>Anti-Revolt Commonwealth</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Rev from Anti-Revolt Commonwealth!</p>
<p>Ms. Callie and Dignitary Geyde has created <strong>tanks</strong>! I don’t know how many there are, but it sure looks like Commonwealth will have one, strong military!</p>
<p>They have also finished the construction of a <strong>Research Lab</strong>! Knowledge is power! And research is the easy way to get it.</p>
<p>There is also rumours of <strong>something hush hush happening</strong> in the circle of those that know better. This Reporter will try to dig into this matter. Hope my life isn’t in danger.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Bitch the Suplex City</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Plex from Bitch the Suplex City!</p>
<p>Beast Bluestorm and Advocate Nerbo has started construction of <strong>Research Lab</strong>! Knowledge is power! And research is the easy way to get it. The lab is so huge, I don’t think it will be finished soon.</p>
<p>On a side note, I have heard rumours of <strong>heavylifting competition</strong> going around! This might be our first festival in a while!</p>
<hr>
<h4>New West Anglia</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Angel from New West Anglia!</p>
<p>Grand Duchess Jasmine and Arbiter Kai have started the construction of a <strong>Research Lab</strong>! Knowledge is power! And research is the easy way to get it. The lab is so huge, I don’t think it will be finished soon.</p>
<p>A group of  <strong>Dawei Missionaries have been seen</strong>  in public area, and there are a few converts, too!</p>
<p>There are also some recruitment for <strong>soldiers</strong>! The city is now filled with more scary looking people.</p>
<hr>
<p>“And there we have it, folks! Reporter Bishop here from Mass Media Network will say good bye. Our Acolytes can only search from information in-person for now, but some money has helped to changed that.”</p>
<p>“We have also started a construction of a nuclear bunker considering some rather alarming movement in a certain community. Acolyte Guy, unfortunately, won’t move from his post anytime soon. Keep your spirit high, Acolyte Guy!”</p>
<p>“And today, our special service <strong>Private Channel has been used</strong>! We thank our costumer for using our service.”</p>
<p>“Let us continue to today’s special section!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/128</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 13:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-128</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Reporter Phase 2</h1>
<p>“Hello, World! This is Reporter Bishop from Mass Media Network. Today in this world we have five countries reigning supreme! Let us here from our Reporter Acolytes what they have in store!”</p>
<hr>
<h4>Dawei-ist Theocracy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Dawei from Dawei-ist Theocracy!</p>
<p>Bishop Marl and Matriarch Mercenary has started a <strong>religion-centred parenting program</strong>! It sure will raise the level of piety among the common people!</p>
<p>They have also <strong>sent a group of Missionaries into Our Kingdom of Family Guy</strong>! What a noble quest!</p>
<hr>
<h4>Our Kingdom of Family Guy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Guy from Our Kingdom of Family Guy!<br>
A group of <strong>Dawei Missionaries have been seen</strong> in public area, and there are a few converts, too!</p>
<p>Pug Griffin and Squiddy Griffin has built a <strong>Border Wall</strong>! Crossing the border will be more difficult now, but luckily, I know some smuggl- oops!</p>
<p>They have also built… <strong>A NUCLEAR BOMB CREATION FACILITY</strong>. I will request a transfer of post immediately.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Anti-Revolt Commonwealth</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Rev from Anti-Revolt Commonwealth!</p>
<p>Ms. Callie and Dignitary Geyde has started to <strong>recruit soldiers</strong>! I don’t know how many there are, but it sure looks like Commonwealth will have one, strong military!</p>
<p>They have also started the construction of a <strong>Research Lab</strong>! Knowledge is power! And research is the easy way to get it. The lab is so huge, I don’t think it will be finished soon.</p>
<p>They have also finished their <strong>Tank Factory</strong>! They can now mass product tanks with ease.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Bitch the Suplex City</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Plex from Bitch the Suplex City!</p>
<p>Beast Bluestorm and Advocate Nerbo has started construction of <strong>FuryGround, a Grand Martial Arts Training Complex</strong>! It sure is useful for martial artists all over the community! The complex is so big, I don’t think it will be finished soon.</p>
<p>On a side note, I have received the honour to <strong>shake hand with Advocate Nerbo when he’s on the street</strong>! Wow! I don’t know what’s a leader doing walking around, but there was a good deal of cheers!</p>
<hr>
<h4>New West Anglia</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Angel from New West Anglia!</p>
<p>Grand Duchess Jasmine has built a <strong>Border Wall</strong>. Crossing the border will be more difficult now.</p>
<p>This is some hush-hush news, but there is a rumour around about <strong>someone leaving New West Anglia Mansion</strong>. I wonder who that is?</p>
<hr>
<p>“And there we have it, folks! Reporter Bishop here from Mass Media Network will say good bye. Our Acolytes can only search from information in-person for now, but some money has helped to changed that.”</p>
<p>“We have also started a construction of a nuclear bunker considering some rather alarming movement in a certain community. Acolyte Guy, unfortunately, won’t move from his post anytime soon.”</p>
<p>“And today, our special service <strong>Private Channel has been used</strong>! We thank our costumer for using our service.”</p>
<p>“See you in the next newspaper!”</p>
<h1>Planning Phase 3 start</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/127</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 11:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-127</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Damafaud" data-post="114" data-topic="74418">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/damafaud/40/1266_2.png" class="avatar"> Damafaud:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>seem oppressed with the threat of execution!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>good gamers.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/126</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-126</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Reporter Phase 1</h1>
<p>“Hello, World! This is Reporter Bishop from Mass Media Network. Today in this world we have five countries reigning supreme! Let us here from our Reporter Acolytes what they have in store!”</p>
<hr>
<h4>Dawei-ist Theocracy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Dawei from Dawei-ist Theocracy!</p>
<p>Bishop Marl and Matriarch Mercenary has started the construction of a <strong>Grand Chapel</strong>! From what I hear around, the Grand Chapel is intended as a religious center for the theocracy. Such a piteous leader! The chapel is so grand, I don’t think it will be finished soon.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Our Kingdom of Family Guy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Guy from Our Kingdom of Family Guy!</p>
<p>Pug Griffin and Squiddy Griffin has built a <strong>Military Training Camp</strong>! Military is of course important for any community.</p>
<p>They have also built a <strong>Convention Center</strong>. A place for the people to gather, a new social building! This will surely please the people.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Anti-Revolt Commonwealth</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Rev from Anti-Revolt Commonwealth!</p>
<p>Ms. Callie and Dignitary Geyde has built a <strong>Military Training Camp</strong>! Military is of course important for any community.</p>
<p>They have also started the construction of a <strong>Tank Factory</strong>! Could it be that the Commonwealth is looking for more than just security? The factory is so huge, I don’t think it will be finished soon.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Bitch the Suplex City</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Plex from Bitch the Suplex City!</p>
<p>Beast Bluestorm and Advocate Nerbo has built a <strong>Gym</strong>! What a considerable step for the community’s health.</p>
<p>They have also changed the curriculum to make <strong>Physical Education a mandatory subject</strong> until high school level! I don’t know much about sport, but this will surely give the younger generation more exercise!</p>
<hr>
<h4>New West Anglia</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Angel from New West Anglia!</p>
<p>Grand Duchess Jasmine has established <strong>Inventor Guild</strong> as a kingdom-wide organisation! She also has successfuly recruited inventors from all over the kingdom. With the inventors under one banner, New West Anglia will walk far and wide in the realm of technology development!</p>
<hr>
<p>“And there we have it, folks! Reporter Bishop here from Mass Media Network will say good bye. Our Acolytes can only search from information in-person for now, but it will definitely change in the future.”</p>
<p>“And today, our special service <strong>Private Channel has been used</strong>! We thank our costumer for using our service.”</p>
<p>“See you in the next newspaper!”</p>
<h1>Planning Phase 2 start</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/125</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 09:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-125</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So when are you gonna actually join then</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/124</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 09:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-124</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hm…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/123</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 18:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-123</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/join</strong> fuck it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/122</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 17:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-122</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Planning Phase 1 is underway… 1 slot still remains…</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/121</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 06:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-121</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If nobody will take the slot in 24 hours I can take it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/120</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 06:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-120</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/119</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-119</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Such as the roman empire.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/118</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 16:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-118</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wanna join</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/117</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 16:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-117</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lots of good things are 13 years or more out of style. Don’t hate</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/116</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-116</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Damafaud" data-post="114" data-topic="74418">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/damafaud/40/1266_2.png" class="avatar"> Damafaud:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>nuclear</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/nuclearburrito">@NuclearBurrito</a> wow i didn’t realize you liked family guy</p>
<p>huh, thought that show went out of style like 13 years ago</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/115</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 15:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-115</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Reporter Phase 0</h1>
<p>“Hello, World! This is Reporter Bishop from Mass Media Network. Today in this world we have five countries reigning supreme! Let us here from our Reporter Acolyte what they have in store!”</p>
<hr>
<h4>Dawei-ist Theocracy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Dawei from Dawei-ist Theocracy!</p>
<p>There is nothing here except for the mansion of the leaders and citizen houses. The citizens wear cloaks and robes and mutter some frightening thing that can induce terror.</p>
<p>I can safely say we have an <strong>occult-oriented community</strong> in the development.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Our Kingdom of Family Guy</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Guy from Our Kingdom of Family Guy!</p>
<p>There is nothing here except for the mansion of the leaders and citizen houses. The citizens speak in a weird slang and seem oppressed with the threat of execution!</p>
<p>I can safely say we have a <strong>nuclear and specific cultural community</strong> in the development.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Anti-Revolt Commonwealth</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Rev from Anti-Revolt Commonwealth!</p>
<p>There is nothing here except for the mansion of the leaders and citizen houses. The citizens communicate in a roundabout headache inducing headache every time.</p>
<p>I can safely say we have a <strong>cultural and societal melting pot community</strong> in the development.</p>
<hr>
<h4>Bitch the Suplex City</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Plex from Bitch the Suplex City!</p>
<p>There is nothing here except for the mansion of the leaders and citizen houses. The citizens are obsessed with muscle and seem oppressed with the threat of death!</p>
<p>I can safely say we have a <strong>strength-centered community</strong> in the development.</p>
<hr>
<h4>New West Anglia</h4>
<p>This is Acolyte Angel from New West Anglia!</p>
<p>There is nothing here except for the mansion of the leaders and citizen houses. The citizens are used to using steam engine and tinkering everything all day long</p>
<p>I can safely say we have a <strong>steam-based technology community</strong> in the development.</p>
<hr>
<p>“And there we have it, folks! Reporter Bishop here from Mass Media Network will say good bye. Our Acolytes can only search from information in-person for now, but it will definitely change in the future.”</p>
<p>“See you in the next newspaper!”</p>
<h1>Planning Phase 1 start</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/114</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 15:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-114</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>The game will start soon</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418/113</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 15:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-74418-113</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/world-of-leaders-planning-phase-5/74418.rss">World of Leaders Planning Phase 5</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
