<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090</link>
    <description>**Faction:** _Neutral_

**Class Type:** _Investigative_

**Passives:** **Looting**: If a player with a piece of the Grand Finale dies at night, you will take it. 
**Hypnotic Voice:** Night immune once.  You will keep this passive when your class changes.

**Day abilities:** 

**The Grand Finale!** (infinite uses): Show them your true self! (can only be used if you have all 2 pieces, 4 pieces are in the game, but you only require 2 to transform)

**Night abilities**: 
**Where is it?!** (infinite uses): Check a player, if they have a piece of the Grand Finale, you will bypass their occ immunity and occupy time for the night and take it. (if they don&#39;t hae a piece, you won&#39;t do anything, but you will visit them)
**Last Dance** (infinite uses): Attack a player and take their piece of the Grand Finale (you will not attack them if the don&#39;t have, but you will visit them). 


_Showing your true self means that you choose between 3 forms:_ 

The Bard?: Win condition: Survive. (this would replace alch&#39;s Win Condition if they change the Alchemist) 

**Night abilities:** Sing and dance! (3 uses): Prevent everyone visting you tonight.

The Musician: Win condition: Kill a non-Blue Dragon player.

**Passives:** **Perfect:** Occupy and redirection immune. 

**Day Abilities:** **Follow my voice:** Make a player say something and force them to vote another player, they won&#39;t be notified about any of this. 
**Night Abilities:** 
**Crescendo!** (2 uses): The chosen player will target themselves. (The Prince, The Drunk and The Court Wizard will get occupyed instead.) 
**Hypnotised** (1 use): This player will vote up another player from their own faction. If the targeted player gets reaped, you won&#39;t lose an use, but they won&#39;t vote anyone up. Neutrals will vote up someone randomly.

The Maestro: Win Condition: Save a non-Blue Dragon player from getting executed or from getting attacked.

**Passives:** 
**His Favourite Musician:** The Prince won&#39;t be able to execute you for one time when he tries to. **Oops:** The court will get notified, that there&#39;s a Maestro amoungst them.

**Day Abilities: 
The Great Story** (1 use): Every Blue Dragon member will not be able to use their day abilities, except The Prince.

**Night Abilities: 
Your friend**(infinite uses): Determine if a player is the Neutral Killer or an Unseen member or a Cult member. Prevent any attack targeting them, if the Prince tries to execute them, you will get killed instead. 

Thanks to **Geyde** for the help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 06:08:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><big><font color="purple">Maestro</font></big></p>
<p>Maestro is the Evil transition class from the Bard, and as such helps evils with their win condition.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Maestro: Win Condition: Save a non-Blue Dragon player from getting executed or from getting attacked.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This win condition is fairly easy to achieve, but befitting of an evil support class.</p>
<p><big><font color="red">Changes</font></big></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>His Favourite Musician:</strong> The Prince won’t be able to execute you for one time when he tries to. <strong>Oops:</strong> The court will get notified, that there’s a Maestro amoungst them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remove this passive. If you were to be executed by the prince, you would immediately die the next day. Pointless</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The Great Story</strong> (1 use): Every Blue Dragon member will not be able to use their day abilities, except The Prince.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I just wanted to comment on this. I couldn’t find out anything broken you could do with it.</p>
<p>This class seems almost entirely balanced, and doesn’t appear to need any further changes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 06:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I’m back again.</p>
<hr>
<p>The different classes that the bard can change into, as previously confirmed, have a relationship of BD-sided, Neutral, and Evil-sided.</p>
<p>Maintaining these alignments while also reasonably making all options applicable is one of the intentions of this post.</p>
<hr>
<p><big><font color="pink">Minstrel</font></big></p>
<p>The minstrel is the Neutral transition class from the Bard, and as such follows a Neutral goal.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Win condition: Survive. (this would replace alch’s Win Condition if they change the Alchemist)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Since this is their new wincon, it is important to give them ways to defend themselves against both attacks AND poison/bleed affects.</p>
<p><big><font color="red">Changes</font></big></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong> Sing and dance! (3 uses): Prevent everyone visting you tonight.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Reduce the uses of this ability to 2 to be better in line with stoneskin from alch. A class should be able to defend themselves, but not unreasonably so.</p>
<p>Earlier, I referred to the necessity of having a way for true neutrals to save themselves from poison / bleed effects (although the recent change to alchemist contradicts this). So, I advise the addition of a day ability to help this.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Reinvigorating Tune (Day)</strong> - All who visit you this night will be healed. You will be cured of poison/bleed if anyone visits you. <em>(Single Use)</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>In this manner, the ability prevents the Minstrel from being entirely self-sufficient, but gives them a method of saving themselves from poison/bleed. Notably, this ability is a sacrificial one in a sorc game, considering it saves everyone but yourself from the bomb.</p>
<p>Also, a quick last minute change. Changing this to a social class to better line up with what it can do.</p>
<p><font color="pink">Final</font></p>
<blockquote>
<p><big><font color="pink">Minstrel</font></big><br>
<font color="grey">Neutral Social</font></p>
<p><strong>Reinvigorating Tune (Day)</strong> - All who visit you this night will be healed. You will be cured of poison/bleed if anyone visits you. <em>(Single Use)</em></p>
<p><strong>Sing and dance! (Night)</strong> - Prevent everyone visting you tonight <em>(2 Uses)</em></p>
<p><em>Your objective is to Survive until the end of the game.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<p><big><font color="lightblue">Musician</font></big></p>
<p>The Musician is the BD aligned transformation for the Bard.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Win condition: Kill a non-Blue Dragon player.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is almost entirely impossible to win with this class in the event of it being a cult game, as cult kills relatively rarely. Thus, it is being changed to make it a more compelling choice in those games.</p>
<p><big><font color="red">Changes</font></big></p>
<blockquote>
<p><em>Your objective is to live to see 3 Non-BD players die.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>This change to the win condition keeps it a viable option no matter if it is cult/unseen.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Change class type to Offensive</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The abilities of the Musician are almost entirely focused on redirection.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Removal of Hypnotised</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Auto-outing evils is very unfun to play against. Also consider the possibility of finding mm before n3 with this.</p>
<p><font color="lightblue">Final</font></p>
<blockquote>
<p><big><font color="lightblue">Musician</font></big></p>
<p><strong>Perfect (Passive)</strong> - Immune to most occupation and redirection abilities.</p>
<p><strong>Follow my Voice (Day)</strong> - Make a player say something and force them to vote another player. They won’t be notified about this. <em>(2 Uses)</em></p>
<p><strong>Crescendo! (Night)</strong> - Player will target themselves tonight <em>(Infinite Uses)</em></p>
<p><em>Your objective is to live to see 3 non-BD players die</em></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scratch what I said about the major overhaul being necessary. I’m wrong about that, my b. I can definitely see where you are coming from about the choice of faction.</p>
<p>Still, the particulars (not the ideas) about the classes need a slight tweak. I’m mostly referring to the BD aligned Musician being very difficult in cult games</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 08:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markneu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was referring to the other classes, and they are made that way for a reason. I wanted to make this class to actually choose a path they want to. Choose to be the part of the Blue Dragon, Choose to be the Evil in the castle, or just stay as a Bard who tells the great stories of Castle Adiart. That was the idea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You are referring to how that would work, correct?</p>
<p>Assuming you are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Day ‘Grand Finale’ is selected, and much like Alch’s concoct potion, it opens up a list of 3 different classes</li>
<li>The selected class becomes your new class at the beginning of the night.</li>
</ul>
<p>As for the other classes (if you were referring to that), they need a major overhaul. Currently, the classes have a certain relationship:</p>
<p>The Bard? (you should make this the minstrel) is a true neutral class<br>
The Musician is BD sided<br>
Maestro is evil sided</p>
<p>In design, focusing on blurring the lines should have importance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 07:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markneu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also, may I ask another question? The changing into another class part, have you got any ideas, or are they okay?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 07:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No problem. I enjoy pretty much everything I see on the lore section, so getting it to a point at which it could conceivably be in the game is something to strive for.</p>
<p>I’ll have my ideas for the classes the Bard can ‘evolve’ into posted at 6pm (or sometime around there) today!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 07:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markneu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you very much, that is a lot of help! I am very happy someone helped me out with this!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 07:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/markneu">@markneu</a></p>
<p>/summon</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 22:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is going to be an extremely long post, so buckle in.</p>
<hr>
<p><big><font color="pink">Bard : Class Identity</font></big></p>
<p>This class attempts to collect pieces of a composition to ascertain their true purpose. They will attempt to gain these through any means necessary.</p>
<ul>
<li>Should be able to kill/check to gain these pieces.</li>
<li>Should NOT have any abilities that do not contribute to this purpose.</li>
</ul>
<p>In addition, upon further inspection, this class bears MANY similarities to Inquisitor. In order to keep the classes’ identity distinct, all changes proposed will be in the direction of moving it away from inq.</p>
<hr>
<p><big>Tidying Up</big></p>
<ul>
<li>Necessary for easier reading and functionality. Baseline.</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The one and the only:</strong> Unique.<br>
<strong>I have a free will</strong> : Conversion Immune.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As already mentioned in this thread, these two passives are unnecessary. Neutral classes are already immune to conversion, and a class being unique should be marked with <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/star.png?v=9" title=":star:" class="emoji" alt=":star:"> or <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">.</p>
<p>Given that the removal of these two would free up a spot, check the <strong>solving issues</strong> section for a proposed addition to their passives.</p>
<hr>
<p><big> Additions / Removals </big></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Writing:</strong> Occupy and redirection immune.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remove. Preserve this as a potential claim for evils while also freeing up space for other passives.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Looting</strong> (infinite uses): Take a dead player’s piece of the Grand Finale (if they had one).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remove. Makes space for the Looting Passive (see later)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>A great song</strong> (2 uses): The chosen player will not be able to use their day abilities or prevents them if they already used them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remove. Doesn’t fit with class identity. This class is about gaining all the pieces to then transition.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Alert (Passive)</strong>:  Night immune once. <em>You will keep this passive when your class changes.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Addition. Almost necessary in order to get the pieces.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Looting (Passive)</strong>: If a player with a piece of the Grand Finale dies at night, you will take it.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Addition. Buff the class to be more efficient.</p>
<hr>
<p><big>Solving Issues</big></p>
<ul>
<li>Unspecified amount of pieces needed for Grand Finale.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>How to fix:</strong> Set it to a value. Personally, I’d advise 2 being the amount required to change classes, with 3/4 in game in total as to not make this another Inquisitor.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>How would the UI work when you have all the pieces?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>How to fix:</strong> Make ‘the Grand Finale’ a day ability.</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<p>You will receive replies for the classes that the bard will turn into at around 6PM PST 10/14.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 22:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AdriMemeMan18]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Interesting idea…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 22:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Where is it?!</strong> (infinite uses): Check a player, if they have a piece of the Grand Finale, you will bypass their occ immunity and occupy time for the night and take it.<br>
<strong>Last Dance</strong> (1 use): Attack a player and take their piece of the Grand Finale (if they have one).<br>
<strong>The Grand Finale!</strong> (infinite uses): Show them your true self! (can only be used if you have all of the pieces)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Classes can only have up to 2 night abilities</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 20:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="markneu" data-post="1" data-topic="73090">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/mastermind-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> markneu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The one and the only:</strong> Unique.<br>
<strong>I have a free will</strong> : Conversion Immune.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>These aren’t passives they’re just things a class can be</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 20:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Bard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[markneu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Faction:</strong> <em>Neutral</em></p>
<p><strong>Class Type:</strong> <em>Investigative</em></p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong> <strong>Looting</strong>: If a player with a piece of the Grand Finale dies at night, you will take it.<br>
<strong>Hypnotic Voice:</strong> Night immune once.  You will keep this passive when your class changes.</p>
<p><strong>Day abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>The Grand Finale!</strong> (infinite uses): Show them your true self! (can only be used if you have all 2 pieces, 4 pieces are in the game, but you only require 2 to transform)</p>
<p><strong>Night abilities</strong>:<br>
<strong>Where is it?!</strong> (infinite uses): Check a player, if they have a piece of the Grand Finale, you will bypass their occ immunity and occupy time for the night and take it. (if they don’t hae a piece, you won’t do anything, but you will visit them)<br>
<strong>Last Dance</strong> (infinite uses): Attack a player and take their piece of the Grand Finale (you will not attack them if the don’t have, but you will visit them).</p>
<p><em>Showing your true self means that you choose between 3 forms:</em></p>
<p>The Bard?: Win condition: Survive. (this would replace alch’s Win Condition if they change the Alchemist)</p>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong> Sing and dance! (3 uses): Prevent everyone visting you tonight.</p>
<p>The Musician: Win condition: Kill a non-Blue Dragon player.</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong> <strong>Perfect:</strong> Occupy and redirection immune.</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities:</strong> <strong>Follow my voice:</strong> Make a player say something and force them to vote another player, they won’t be notified about any of this.<br>
<strong>Night Abilities:</strong><br>
<strong>Crescendo!</strong> (2 uses): The chosen player will target themselves. (The Prince, The Drunk and The Court Wizard will get occupyed instead.)<br>
<strong>Hypnotised</strong> (1 use): This player will vote up another player from their own faction. If the targeted player gets reaped, you won’t lose an use, but they won’t vote anyone up. Neutrals will vote up someone randomly.</p>
<p>The Maestro: Win Condition: Save a non-Blue Dragon player from getting executed or from getting attacked.</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
<strong>His Favourite Musician:</strong> The Prince won’t be able to execute you for one time when he tries to. <strong>Oops:</strong> The court will get notified, that there’s a Maestro amoungst them.</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities:<br>
The Great Story</strong> (1 use): Every Blue Dragon member will not be able to use their day abilities, except The Prince.</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities:<br>
Your friend</strong>(infinite uses): Determine if a player is the Neutral Killer or an Unseen member or a Cult member. Prevent any attack targeting them, if the Prince tries to execute them, you will get killed instead.</p>
<p>Thanks to <strong>Geyde</strong> for the help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 20:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73090-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-bard/73090.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Bard</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
