<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562</link>
    <description>Lore Link: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Mercenary

Lore Subject: The Mercenary Contract

Lore:

**Oath of Allegiance and Protection**

This contract hereby solidifys and exclaims the oath between Swordsman and Client that the first party of the swordsman (Signed below) will to the best of their ability protect and extend the life of the client (Signed below) and in return the second party will extend the gift of shelter and wealth upon the first party so long as they fulfil their duties to the utmost proficiency including: Night watch, Poison testing, Intimidation, Verbal support, Intervening in political dangers, Intervening in real dangers, Attention to clothing details and physical embrace in traumatic situations. This does **not** include unwanted attentions or issuing verbal commands outside of these parameters. Should this be breached the First Party may dole out a suitable punishment. Should the second party have paid the additional fee the first party may also be obligated to apply the wrath of their deceased client. Should the first party not follow this protocol they may be subject to subsequent blacklisting or even stripped of their sword in shame.

The Second Party is obligated to ensure the well living of the first party as well as ensure they do not endanger their own life in a way that will damage the reputation of the first party. Stupidity of the second party does not entitle them to a refund.

This Document is to be stored at Guild headquarters for observation at a later date.

Signed: ________ of the Second party (In Pen)                                        

 Signed: ________ of the First Party (In Blood)                                         


Comments: I&#39;ll be honest this was a first draft but I felt the idea of having a contract that Mercenaries had to fill out would be a really cool lore addition. Sadly I&#39;m not a lawyer so I did my best to make it sound as legally binding as i could I can feel there&#39;s something missing though. Hope you guys like the idea if it needs changes let me know.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 00:13:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good job</p>
<p>But spelling error: “Solidifys” to Solidifies</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 00:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-562-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore Link: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Mercenary" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Mercenary</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: The Mercenary Contract</p>
<p>Lore:</p>
<p><strong>Oath of Allegiance and Protection</strong></p>
<p>This contract hereby solidifys and exclaims the oath between Swordsman and Client that the first party of the swordsman (Signed below) will to the best of their ability protect and extend the life of the client (Signed below) and in return the second party will extend the gift of shelter and wealth upon the first party so long as they fulfil their duties to the utmost proficiency including: Night watch, Poison testing, Intimidation, Verbal support, Intervening in political dangers, Intervening in real dangers, Attention to clothing details and physical embrace in traumatic situations. This does <strong>not</strong> include unwanted attentions or issuing verbal commands outside of these parameters. Should this be breached the First Party may dole out a suitable punishment. Should the second party have paid the additional fee the first party may also be obligated to apply the wrath of their deceased client. Should the first party not follow this protocol they may be subject to subsequent blacklisting or even stripped of their sword in shame.</p>
<p>The Second Party is obligated to ensure the well living of the first party as well as ensure they do not endanger their own life in a way that will damage the reputation of the first party. Stupidity of the second party does not entitle them to a refund.</p>
<p>This Document is to be stored at Guild headquarters for observation at a later date.</p>
<p>Signed: ________ of the Second party (In Pen)</p>
<p>Signed: ________ of the First Party (In Blood)</p>
<p>Comments: I’ll be honest this was a first draft but I felt the idea of having a contract that Mercenaries had to fill out would be a really cool lore addition. Sadly I’m not a lawyer so I did my best to make it sound as legally binding as i could I can feel there’s something missing though. Hope you guys like the idea if it needs changes let me know.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 23:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-562-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-mercenary/562.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Mercenary</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
