<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Im alch again but this time evil used me</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454</link>
    <description>so there was a guy called minimono. he was an ass. I was alch. things going good for them. I used my killing poison attacked mm and a bd got healed. at the end of game, I knew there was 2 or 3 evils and an evil king left. there was like 6 ppl last day. what im not cool about is. the ass asked me to kill a phys and says you will win and won&#39;t die. I trusted him and killed the phys which I never voted a confirmed bd. I used 4 of my stone potions already. and then he asked me not to heal 9 the last night. then what happened in the next day is, 9 got converted to evil and I got killed by ass as well evil king. what is this ass thinking? he just thinking like oh we can now convert 9 now so why not just kill some random alch for fun? he really did it despite my coop with him, btw he was acting like an all mighty god to me and asked me to do everything since he want me to coop with him. and in the end, he says he kill me because I didn&#39;t reply to all his wisps which also include the one he made on the last 5 seconds. isn&#39;t this guy toxic? I don&#39;t want to meet somebody like this as well in real life. he&#39;s just using ppls trust to get their own goal.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 11:15:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Im alch again but this time evil used me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Toughen up Butter Cup , when playing a neutral you got to watch your own back . Sometimes you win , sometimes you die . You are not on anyone’s side .</p>
<p>Stop being so trusting its a social DECEPTION game , people are meant to lie .</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 11:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10454-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454.rss">Im alch again but this time evil used me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Im alch again but this time evil used me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am sad that this happened to you.</p>
<p>Hope you have a better experience next game <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 11:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10454-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454.rss">Im alch again but this time evil used me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Im alch again but this time evil used me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mkoplsham]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so there was a guy called minimono. he was an ass. I was alch. things going good for them. I used my killing poison attacked mm and a bd got healed. at the end of game, I knew there was 2 or 3 evils and an evil king left. there was like 6 ppl last day. what im not cool about is. the ass asked me to kill a phys and says you will win and won’t die. I trusted him and killed the phys which I never voted a confirmed bd. I used 4 of my stone potions already. and then he asked me not to heal 9 the last night. then what happened in the next day is, 9 got converted to evil and I got killed by ass as well evil king. what is this ass thinking? he just thinking like oh we can now convert 9 now so why not just kill some random alch for fun? he really did it despite my coop with him, btw he was acting like an all mighty god to me and asked me to do everything since he want me to coop with him. and in the end, he says he kill me because I didn’t reply to all his wisps which also include the one he made on the last 5 seconds. isn’t this guy toxic? I don’t want to meet somebody like this as well in real life. he’s just using ppls trust to get their own goal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 11:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10454-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/im-alch-again-but-this-time-evil-used-me/10454.rss">Im alch again but this time evil used me</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
