<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613</link>
    <description>•[color=Grey]Peace Keeper[/color]                 

&gt;**Faction - Neutral**
**Class - offensive**

&gt;**Lore**: As this silly war grew, the peace keeper felt sick. After losing his son because of the war he decides to only trust them who are Neutral in the war. Maybe they could help end this… or if all else fails the NK could get rid of them all.

&gt;**Passive 1:**
_**Little hope**_ - on days where no one die, you gain death immunity that night.
&gt;
&gt;**Passive 2** 
_**Grim Determination**_ (Passive) - You are immune to occupation, redirection and target changing. Suggestion from @ShadowKnight 

&gt;**Day Ability 1:**
_**Privite matters**_ - All whispers to and from you will be hidden from the public. _(3 uses) [same as mystic]_ 
&gt;
&gt;**Day Ability 2:**
**_Stolen potions_** - make yourself immune to death tonight. (2 uses)

&gt;**Night ability 1:**
_**Showing your true colors**_ - pick a player, if they are neutral then know which class they are 
_(Unlimited uses)_ 
&gt;
&gt; _Ex. ([Player name] is not neutral) or ([player name] is a **Neutral!** They are a **Sellsword**!_ 

&gt;
&gt;**Night ability 2:**
_**Stand Guard**_ - Prevent others from visiting your target. You can not target the same player two nights in a row. Will not notify anyone on protection. _(unlimited uses) [same as merc]_

&gt;**Win condition** -  Find a neutral player and help them achieve their goal. **_(You can only win if you have found them with your night ability first)_** [if you find multiple neutrals with your night ability then helping 1 of them achieve their goal will count as a win towards you]

&gt;Notes: 

Changes:
- total rework


Below is @ShadowKnight suggestion for PK. I really like the idea so I’m showing his suggestion for it below. Remember this is from @ShadowKnight not from me. 
  
Ashen Communion (Passive) - At the start of every day, you will receive information about the Neutral players in the game.

Grim Determination (Passive) - You are immune to occupation, redirection and target changing.

Peace Offering (Day) - [Unavailable before Day 3]. Choose a Neutral player other than the Neutral Killer. Tonight, they will receive an offer to change their goal to be the same as yours. If they agree, they will gain one use of Emerald Potion. Once a Neutral has accepted the Offering or has refused it twice, you can no longer use it on that player. - Infinite uses.

Gray Veils (Day) - All Neutral players will detect as Blue Dragon tonight. - 2 uses.

Unbreakable Peace (Night) - Visit a player. If they are Neutral, they will be healed and protected from negative effects. If they are not, they will be occupied. - Infinite uses.

Conspire (Night) - [Unavailable before Night 3]. Create a group chat among all Neutral players that share the same goal as you. - 5 uses.

Goal: See all non-neutral factions defeated.

Notes: Ashen Communion reveals the following information:

Start of Day 1: How many neutrals are currently in the game.
Start of Day 2: What neutral classes are currently in the game.
Start of Day 3 onwards: What neutral classes are currently in the game and what number of player corresponds to each.

Edit: Yes, Peace Offering can grant a one-use Emerald Potion to classes like Fool, Scorned and the like. Conspire automatically includes both the Peace Keeper and the Neutral Killer, as their goals are naturally aligned, then adds all neutrals that accepted the Peace Ofdering.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 15:26:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>will this be a good class to play along with in the game?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It is balanced and has a clear and concise flow, so yes, it would work.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>will you have fun playing this class?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Personally I don’t enjoy playing old Merc-like classes, so likely not. This class works, it’s just that I dislike playing Support Neutrals in general.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>do you think this class is too overpowered or too underpowered?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Quite fine. It may be a bit too easy to win if it pairs with the Merc or the Inq, but the issue is because those classes win too easily rather than being with this.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>do you think this class will change the game in a positive or negative way?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Positive. The NKs need more love.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 15:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>Yeah, I think so.</li>
<li>Definitely!</li>
<li>I would say slightly underpowered? Tough call. Seems reasonably balanced.</li>
<li>It depends on the player. “Neuts Out” types will hate more Neutral classes to deal with, while pro-Neutral players will love it. Overall I’d say a pro-Neutral class would be a good addition to the game.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 00:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Alice" data-post="29" data-topic="66613">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/alice/40/32176_2.png" class="avatar"> Alice:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>IF A CLASS HAS THE NK WINNING AS ITS WINCON THEN IT’S NOT A PRO-BD CLASS AND IT WILL BE EXECUTED ON SIGHT IF THEY OPENLY CLAIM THAT.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t care if the class is against BD. To be honest It can be split most games he spawns anyways. Say the NK was killed early during some games. Then the PK can open claim if he wants or wait until a neutral is outed so they can team. It takes some strategy to know if the court will be in your favor or not. That’s what’s I like about this class.</p>
<p>All I want is these 4 question answered for is this class</p>
<ol>
<li>will this be a good class to play along with in the game?</li>
<li>will you have fun playing this class?</li>
<li>do you think this class is too overpowered or too underpowered?</li>
<li>do you think this class will change the game in a positive or negative way?</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 23:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even if it helps BD or not how is the class in general</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 12:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Alice" data-post="36" data-topic="66613">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/alice/40/32176_2.png" class="avatar"> Alice:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The fact that this class is a neutral who will at times be required to go against BD’s wincon is enough for any BD to want to execute it regardless</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is Alchemist tho. The Alchemist’s win condition can, at times, be directly against BD. It’s just that people don’t quite realise that because it’s not spelled out.</p>
<p>Is PK not as useful? Perhaps. But yeah, I wouldn’t recommend outing as PK in general. Sometimes it might work, but you gotta read the room.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 10:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>publicly claim PK and say the only neutrals left are BD-aligned, and then the odds of you getting executed would be low-ish</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Though there would be no way for BD to certify your claim that all remaining neutrals lean towards them. And there’s also the fact that BD will almost always execute you if you claim a class and then swap to another claim halfway as you could be an evil fakeclaiming PK. The fact that this class is a neutral who will at times be required to go against BD’s wincon is enough for any BD to want to execute it regardless if the NK is alive or not.</p>
<p>It’s not a guaranteed execution to claim PK after the NK is dead, it’s just that it’s extremely risky to do this in a game where BD is highly distrustful of neutrals as this class would be far less trusted than Alchemists because of their uselessness to BD and that their wincon can even go against them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 09:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s done, we can go back to the Peace Keeper ideas. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 02:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This got off topic very fast</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 02:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think a big misunderstanding here is people assuming this class can be claimed openly, like the Alch, Merc or Inquisitor, which seems to be the salient point of contention.</p>
<p>My proposal was not at all about that, since it was designed to allow for a fairly decent fake Butler claim. If the NK died, then you could, if you wanted, publicly claim PK and say the only neutrals left are BD-aligned, and then the odds of you getting executed would be low-ish (but not non-existent).</p>
<p>I don’t think a neutral class that defends other neutrals is something you should be able to publicly claim right at the start, precisely because there are a good number of neutrals that seek to harm BD in some way, and in some cases outright see them lose the game. If this class defends all neutrals, it by necessity cannot claim publicly unless NK is dead and all neutrals left are pro-BD.</p>
<p>The only way you can make a class like this publicly claimable is if instead of them defending all neutrals, they work like the old merc with contracts, and begin “aligned” with a pro-BD neutral (Inq, Alch, Merc) and can only re-align themselves to another neutral (including NK) if their starting neutral dies. This works in that it helps avoid BD killing neutrals, since doing so frees up the PK to align with NK, sellsword, fool, scorned, etc. This works backwards with evils, since they now have an incentive to kill the PK’s target (unless it’s alch) to try and get them to re-align with a more evil-aligned neutral. The problem is, of course, that it has the same issues as the old version of Merc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 02:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Mercenary and the Inquisitor are also fine. The issue is that in order to maximize their chances of winning, the PK would have to be helping all neutrals at the same time to achieve their goals, which means that he’ll be trying to help Sellswords, trying to get a BD member lynched for the Scorned, waste the court’s nights by executing Fools, and vote with the NK if it comes down to that.</p>
<p>He can help true neutrals or even BD-aligned neutrals, the issue here is that nobody will know which neutrals will spawn except for the NK, which outright needs BD to lose for them to win. If a class has a wincon that explicitly requires BD to lose if all neutrals have died too early or if they were the only neutral to spawn, then there’s no way in hell to make this a BD-friendly class no matter how much OP tries.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 01:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only acceptable class that I would allow them to win with is alch</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 01:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="26" data-topic="66613" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>… why’s that</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<blockquote>
<p>However the main issue that will make them prime targets for executions is that:<br>
1.You’ll be spending much of the game trying to find neutrals, but half of the non-killing neutrals along with all the Neutral Killers are classified as evil and would be executed on sight, going against your wincon. This means that by default an open PK claim would have to lie in their logs and not out Fools, the Scorned, the Sellsword, or the NK. Any smart BD in turn would execute any player that is protecting evils on policy which would include any PK claim.<br>
2.One of their wincons basically relies on giving the win to the NK if all other neutrals are dead. Keeping a class that has this wincon alive is just pure unadulterated stupidity as you’re basically giving the NK an additional vote for no damn good reason at all.<br>
3.Even BD-aligned and true neutrals such as Mercenaries and Alchemists are periodically executed providing suspicion is drawn to them, and often times for good reason as scum often claims those classes from time to time. Unless you’re actively outing neutrals, which would go against your wincon, then people are going to call BS on your PK claim.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>In short, yes, this class can help BD by giving immunity to BD-siding neutrals, but at the same time it’s far too scummy of a class for BD to let live to the point that in the majority of the games you’re better off executing them then leaving them alive.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>If what you two are trying to do is creating a pro-Neutral class that BD won’t execute on sight upon claiming then it’s a hopeless endeavor. There are very few ways that a PK can help the Blue Dragon as a whole as it basically requires at least one Mercenary to spawn and be confirmed while the sheer amount of anti-BD Neutrals completely outweigh the benefits. Also.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And finally.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong><em>IF A CLASS HAS THE NK WINNING AS ITS WINCON THEN IT’S NOT A PRO-BD CLASS AND IT WILL BE EXECUTED ON SIGHT IF THEY OPENLY CLAIM THAT.</em></strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong><em>IF A CLASS HAS THE NK WINNING AS ITS WINCON THEN IT’S NOT A PRO-BD CLASS AND IT WILL BE EXECUTED ON SIGHT IF THEY OPENLY CLAIM THAT.</em></strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong><em>IF A CLASS HAS THE NK WINNING AS ITS WINCON THEN IT’S NOT A PRO-BD CLASS AND IT WILL BE EXECUTED ON SIGHT IF THEY OPENLY CLAIM THAT.</em></strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong><em>IF A CLASS HAS THE NK WINNING AS ITS WINCON THEN IT’S NOT A PRO-BD CLASS AND IT WILL BE EXECUTED ON SIGHT IF THEY OPENLY CLAIM THAT.</em></strong></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Aside from having to help evil neutrals like the Fool, Scorned, or Sellsword accomplish their goals, in the event that the PK is the only neutral that spawns or all neutrals die early, then he’ll be forced to side with the NK over BD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 01:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sarun needs a picture.</p>
<p>Btw</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 01:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Because it has no use to BD</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 01:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>… why’s that</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>generally I really like this! But I tried changing the win con so that he will be more under the radar from BD mostly claiming merc to them. This new rework forces the PK to find a neutral and help them achieve their goal instead of trying to have one survive to the end. Also this will work really well for BD, say if NK is dead and you have a confirmed alch/merc. The PK can out himself to the court without getting exe on sight.</p>
<p>Oh also really love this idea:</p>
<p>Unbreakable Peace (Night) - Visit a player. If they are Neutral, they will be healed and protected from negative effects. If they are not, they will be occupied. - Infinite uses.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I still want to exe in sight</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Attention to everyone, I have completely reworked this class again. Now the abilities are based around his new won con, which is to find a neutral and help them achieve their end goal. This makes him a bit more claimable so BD doesn’t kill on sight but also can still help NK win if he finds NK.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>3 cult<br>
1 Prince</p>
<p>Exe the fool.<br>
Prince jails the CL and exe.<br>
No trials<br>
Prince jails the other cl and exe<br>
Prince jails the last cl and exe</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>So yeah, no allcaps needed, friend. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
<p>It wasn’t necessarily directed to you, though. It’s just that way too many people here want a pro-Neutral class that  won’t get executed by openly claiming it to BD. This is impossible to work out as more often than not they will be required to help Sellswords, Fools, and Scorneds which by default go against BD’s goals. That, and if they are the last non-NK neutral or even the only Neutral that spawned then they are basically required to help the NK as their only wincon. Regardless of their kit, any pro-Neutral class is going to be classified as evil by default because in circumstances when a Merc/Inq/Alch die early or don’t spawn, then by default they will have to help evils or even the NK.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 09:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I never said that my take on it would be fine to claim, that’s why I said when I posted my suggestion that it might get discarded, since I knew it wasn’t what NOBLE1 had in mind. The entire reason they have an infinite occupation night ability (plus occupation immunity) was to allow them to claim Butler to BD, just like Alch can claim Physician if they so choose.</p>
<p>So yeah, no allcaps needed, friend. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 07:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If what you two are trying to do is creating a pro-Neutral class that BD won’t execute on sight upon claiming then it’s a hopeless endeavor. There are very few ways that a PK can help the Blue Dragon as a whole as it basically requires at least one Mercenary to spawn and be confirmed while the sheer amount of anti-BD Neutrals completely outweigh the benefits. Also.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>you can be true neutral if you bond with Alch/Fool/Scorned.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Fools and Scorneds are by nature anti-BD. If the Fool wins then the court ends up wasting a day to execute him and then one or two more days because of his passive. The only ones that benefit from less executions are evils. The Scorned basically needs to get a member of the Blue Dragon executed for them to win, and which faction benefits from this the most should be obvious.</p>
<p>Anyway, here’s my review on that PK’s iteration.</p>
<ol>
<li>I’d make Ashen Communion a bit more conditional and less specific. Here’s my version of it.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>
<p>Ashen Communion (Passive) - At the start of the game, you will know the identity of all non-NK neutral players. If the NK remains the last neutral alive while you have still not won, then their identity will be revealed to you.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The current Ashen Communion is terrible as it has no counterplay against competing neutrals. If there’s an Inquisitor and a Sorcerer on the same game then you just need to survive a few days in and it’ll be guaranteed an instant victory. This also applies to other pro-BD/anti-BD neutrals in general such as the Mercenary vs. the Scorned or whatnot. To prevent this then the class should be hidden and the NK should not be revealed unless they’re the last neutral in the match.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Added three nights of night immunity to Grim Determination.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>
<p>Grim Determination (Passive) - You are immune to occupation, redirection and target changing. You are immune to death at night until past the third night.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>There’s a reason why almost all neutrals have some form of night immunity in their kit. The fact that they’re only one person means that they need some enhanced form of survival against night kills.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>The bond needs to be made until death and switchable.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>
<p>Peace Bond (Day) - [Unavailable on Day 1] You will bind yourself to a target player provided they are not aligned to either major factions. While bound to that player, any whispers from them to you or viceversa will be hidden from the public. You may only be bound to one Neutral player at a time and you will only be unbound on their death.- Infinite uses.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>In short, this should prevent the PK from bailing out or switching just the right time as another non-bound neutral would win. This ability has auto-confirmation, but since the PK would fall under scum due to their victory conditions then that shouldn’t matter.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>This ability is kind of pointless as it is. Observer Peeks are rare and it’s counterproductive to use this if your target’s a Fool, so I’m proposing a different versioned tailored specifically to each Neutral.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>
<p>Gray Veils (Day) - Every Neutral gains a bonus depending on their class. - 2 uses.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Fool will gain both have themselves framed and gain night immunity in the coming night.</li>
<li>The Scorned will have both their targets framed in the coming night.</li>
<li>The Alchemist will be automatically pardoned if they are on trial. Cannot be pardoned twice in a row.</li>
<li>The Mercenary and Sellsword will be immune to death in the coming night.</li>
<li>The Inquisitor’s investigative abilities will bypass the Sorcerer’s framing in the coming night…</li>
<li>The Possessor, the Reaper, and the Sorcerer will have all visits to them prevented in the coming night.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
<p>In short, this ability is now several times more useful as faction checks are extremely rare.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>This ability’s somewhat wonky. On one hand, infinite use healing makes non-immune neutrals a bit strong while healing immune neutrals is a bit useless except for Bleeding/Poison/OE. Plus, there’s no need to randomly occupy players when you can heal you target due to your wincon.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>
<p>Unbreakable Peace (Night) - Visit a player. If they are Neutral, they will be healed and protected from negative effects. If your target is immune for this night, then the ability cost is refunded.  - 4 uses.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This should balance out different cases where your target has a ton of night immunity such as the Scorned or no night immunity at all such as a Mercenary.</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>Changed to infinite uses.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>
<p>Conspire (Night) - [Unavailable before Night 2]. Create a group chat between yourself and a bonded player. - Infinite uses.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Coordination should be the bread and butter of this class rather than being a heal bot. Heal bots are boring as hell and unispiring.</p>
<p>And for the last time.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em><strong><font> IF A CLASS HAS THE NK WINNING AS ITS WINCON THEN IT’S NOT A PRO-BD CLASS AND IT WILL BE EXECUTED ON SIGHT IF THEY OPENLY CLAIM THAT.</font></strong></em></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 07:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s a bit out of your control, how about:</p>
<p><em>Goal: See a Neutral player you have bonded with achieve their goal.</em></p>
<p>So the class abilities are:</p>
<p><strong>Ashen Communion (Passive) -</strong> At the start of every day, you will know the identity and class of a Neutral player in the game other than you (the Neutral Killer will always be the last Neutral you will know of).</p>
<p><strong>Grim Determination (Passive) -</strong> You are immune to occupation, redirection and target changing.</p>
<p><strong>Peace Bond (Day)</strong> - [Unavailable on Day 1] You will bind yourself to a target Neutral player revealed to you by Ashen Communion. While bound to that player, any whispers from them to you or viceversa will be hidden from the public. You may only be bound to one Neutral player at a time.- Infinite uses.</p>
<p><strong>Gray Veils (Day)</strong> - All Neutral players will detect as Blue Dragon tonight. - 2 uses.</p>
<p><strong>Unbreakable Peace (Night)</strong> - Visit a player. If they are Neutral, they will be healed and protected from negative effects. If they are not, they will be occupied. - Infinite uses.</p>
<p><strong>Conspire (Night)</strong> - [Unavailable before Night 2]. Create a group chat between yourself, a player you have bonded with and target Neutral player revealed to you by Ashen Communion. - 5 uses.</p>
<p>You can end up being pro-BD if you stay bonded to a Merc/Inq, you can be anti-BD if you bond with the Sellsword or NK, or you can be true neutral if you bond with Alch/Fool/Scorned.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 18:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You make some good points. Maybe a rework of the goal could change to something like “<strong>Win con</strong> - <em>survive to see a neutral complete their goal”</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 18:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowKnight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, this Peace Keeper’s goal is explicitly anti-BD (but also anti-Unseen/Cult), so I thought since BD will want to take you out anyway, might as well give the class the tools to help the NK achieve that goal. There’s no point trying to make the class more BD-friendly when the goal is explicitly anti-BD.</p>
<p>Your suggestion can work, totally, but it requires a rework of the goal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 18:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66613-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-peace-keeper-remake-a-class-that-defends-neutrals/66613.rss">The Peace Keeper(remake) a class that defends neutrals</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
