<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438</link>
    <description>So the next update looks to bring back the old, unconvertible Sheriff. We know that this can work, because it has in the past, and without King&#39;s Allies I can see why @Ellie is making this change. However, I think there&#39;s a few changes that should be made before this patch goes live.

First off, I absolutely love the direction of this change. Making one of Sheriff/Pally guaranteed and unconvertible while making the other convertible is a great idea and will really help to differentiate the gameplay of these two factions.

However, I think we might have taken the wrong road here. With only 3 Unseen, one of whom is the Mastermind, they&#39;re pretty static. The Cult, on the other hand, is much more fluid, with up to 4 members and Cult Leader being an inheritable role. I personally believe that keeping the current Sheriff and instead making the Paladin guaranteed to spawn and unconvertible will result in better gameplay for both factions, and it seems that others agree.

Hopefully this gets changed, because I really do believe that it would be the best direction for the game to go.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 19:30:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>MM and NK aren’t doing sheriff/pally plays anymore. And the reason it matters more now is because cult now has a legit reason to fake claim sheriff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 19:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>While I do hope that sheriff gets reverted I would like to point something out. The fact that sheriff is unconvertable and guarenteed but Paladin isn’t is HUGE for fake claiming in either Unseen or Cult games. Example: Your the N1 convert and you want the sheriff to die. You whisper the king that you are paladin and then when the sheriff speaks up the king will out that he is lying. Sure you die too but that’s no big deal.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>You could do that before, couldn’t you?  It’s not a very good strategy because you’re screwed if another member of your faction dies before you (and will probably have cost your faction the entire game due to it losing two people at once.)</p>
<p>Also, the member of the Unseen who has the most trouble claiming is the Mastermind (plus the initial Assassin, but the Mastermind is more serious because they’re irreplacable.)  There’s absolutely zero room for a Mastermind to claim Sheriff now, and claiming Paladin is obviously insane given that they’re not expendable.</p>
<p>The other class that has trouble claiming is NK, and, again, these changes flatly remove Sheriff as a usable claim for them, since sacrificing yourself isn’t really an option.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 19:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To be fair, almost every single Unseen conversion can safely claim its old class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While I do hope that sheriff gets reverted I would like to point something out. The fact that sheriff is unconvertable and guarenteed but Paladin isn’t is HUGE for fake claiming in either Unseen or Cult games. Example: Your the N1 convert and you want the sheriff to die. You whisper the king that you are paladin and then when the sheriff speaks up the king will out that he is lying. Sure you die too but that’s no big deal.</p>
<p>That’s not the only strategy you can do in regards to this. Claiming sheriff in Cult games for example. It won’t work long term but it doesn’t need to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 13:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The issue isn’t “balance” in the sense of faction-vs-faction win rate.  I feel that people overwhelmingly overestimate the significance of that; unless it would catastrophically shift them to the point where the game ceases to be fun, the impact on that is the least important part of any suggestion, since it can always be balanced out by (unrelated) tweaks elsewhere, since the game is already heavily and intentionally asymmetric, and since it’s extremely difficult to assess long-term win-rate changes as a result of tweaks like these.  The removal of allies in particular absolutely did not need any immediate changes to “balance” it; it should have been done on its own - then, after a period of a few weeks, if it seemed like BD win rates had dropped catastrophically, other adjustments could be made to fix it.</p>
<p>But in general I am strenuously opposed to any changes whose sole purpose is to try and brute-force win rates to be closer together - the important thing is <span class="bbcode-i">tactical</span> balance (ensuring that the game supports a wide range of strategies, so it continues to be interesting and the metagame continues to develop in a healthy manner rather than devolving down to just a few lines of play.)  Sacrificing tactical balance to try and adjust win rates will make the game boring in the long term - and it’s a particularly terrible idea when dealing with changes whose impact is <span class="bbcode-i">entirely speculative</span>.</p>
<p>Beyond that, sheriffs used to be unique, guaranteed, and uncomfortable and it was <span class="bbcode-i">not fun</span>.  It led to tediously boring, obvious gameplay surrounding them, with no real tactical depth.  It leaves evils with fewer roles to claim, makes playing as or against Sheriff boring because every action is nearly “solved”, with the correct choices for BD being glaringly obvious and almost no options for Unseen to force a deviation from this path.  It limits what can happen in a way that severely hurt the gameplay - that was why it was changed in the first place!</p>
<p>Reverting such an important and drastic improvement to the game because “oh, what will BD do without allies?” is silly.  We don’t know how the removal of Allies will impact win rates; and if they do, there are a thousand better ways to buff BD than to go back to the gut-churningly awful situation if unique, guarenteed, unconvertable sheriffs.</p>
<p>Yes, we endured that awfulness before, but (if we really think BD needs a buff to compensate for the removal of allies), why would we make that buff a reversion to a setup for the Sheriff that was widely-loathed and eventually removed due to being so horrifically boring and unfun?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 10:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is to balance out the fact that allies no longer exists. Besides, Sheriff used to be unique, guaranteed and unconfirmable, and the game was still balanced.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 10:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>These changes need to be reverted, fullstop.  They’re going in the completely wrong direction.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Only the King and the Prince should ever be permanently unconvertable.  Conversion is a vital part of the game’s balance, and without it (given the large number of protectives out there, including the guaranteed king), Unseen don’t have enough options to deal with their targets.  The reasons that person (as far as I recall, it was just one person) wanted the Sheriff to be unconvertable were mostly “it makes it tempting to gamethrow as a Sheriff because I’m afraid I’ll get converted if I’m revealed”; but this risk is a core part of the game, and Sheriffs were exposed to it for a reason.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Making the Sheriff both unique and guaranteed is an obviously terrible idea that makes it impossible to fakeclaim Sheriff because the (guaranteed-to-exist, knows-he’s-unique) real Sheriff will immediately counterclaim you - especially when combined with the ridiculous conversion immunity, which together mean that the real sheriff faces almost no risk in revealing to counterclaim you in this manner.  We need to be moving in the direction of providing <span class="bbcode-i">more</span> roles evils can claim, not removing one of the few that was available.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The new ability is unnecessary (Sheriffs were already good at what they did), and, again, makes them harder to fakeclaim.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I just don’t see any benefits to these changes at all - the only thing worth keeping is <span class="bbcode-i">maybe</span> making the Sheriff guaranteed.  If the goal is to differentiate unseen / cult games, there are better ways to do it - certainly better ways than removing Sheriff from the already-short list of things evils can reasonably fakeclaim without extensive prep and luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 09:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>rip</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 23:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TinyDeer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>More like worse at playing <em>against</em> Cult <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 21:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That probably means that you are better at playing cult than Unseen or/and BD</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 20:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TinyDeer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow! This is really surprising - in my games, I feel like Cult wins <em>way</em> more than Unseen, but stats don’t lie! <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 20:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well until they do that Paladin would work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Princess</p>
<p>You’re talking about Princess</p>
<p>Just go through with the Wisp and Window Peek changes</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 17:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay you got a good point</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 17:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve already made a thread like that myself. It’s not happening. I asked Bos and he is strongly against it. Also the change was made because Unseen had it far better than Cult and they needed a better sheriff to keep them in check. However I feel like there needs to be a sort of “sheriff lite” to fake claim as Unseen or scorned for accusing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or you could check that thread above again about reworking Paladin :^)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 17:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sheriff would still spawn in Unseen only and have everything this patch added to him. Exept maybe surveillance and Invest could swap uses?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 17:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Idea! Make Paladin spawnable in Unseen with no changes to his kit other than finding unseen. He could convert into a reskined marshal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 17:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just feel like Sheriff should spawn in both Unseen and Cult games, but be convertible, while Paladin becomes a different class that’s kind of unconvertible but not really</p>
<p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/the-topic-of-sheriff-and-paladin/35300?u=livicus" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/the-topic-of-sheriff-and-paladin/35300?u=livicus</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 16:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One Paladin means one guy to kill instead of two <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Either way, that makes sense, and I love the fact that this differentiates the gameplay even more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d rather them not release all the stats tbh cuz then everyone is gonna think their a dev and start analysing them and shit, which isn’t particularly helpful.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Btw what ARE the winrates?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ellie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Cult’s win rate is much lower than the Unseen’s. The removal of the King’s allies might boost both their win rates, so Sheriff was buffed in order to try to keep things in balance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 13:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With allies gone I don’t see why they shouldnt both be reverted to their old unique and unconvertable state.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 13:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That was implied with “keep the current Sheriff”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 13:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40438-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lets-talk-about-the-new-sheriff/40438.rss">Let&#39;s Talk About the New Sheriff</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
