<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Warlock (Neutral Killer)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-warlock-neutral-killer/48864</link>
    <description>_Warlock_ - _Neutral Killer_
**Goal:** Must kill all members of the main faction in order to win. (Similar to Poss and Reaper)



**Passives:**

**Magic Shield:** Immune to death at night. If he gets poisoned or bled, he&#39;ll cleanse himself the following night, removing poison and bleed once for every person. (Example; Assassin poisons you, you&#39;ll cleanse yourself and remove the poison; if he poisons again, Cleanse won&#39;t happen again). Successful Cleanse will cast a Magic Mark on the person who bled/poisoned you. (See Night Ability 1 for reference)

**Magic Power:** Warlock gathers 1 Magic Point (MP) for every Magic Mark (See Night Ability 1 for reference) he puts on his targets. He can use them in order to use his Daily Abilities. If he owns 2 MP or more, he will be Occupy Immune (Hidden) and Redirection Immune. (Also hidden). (WL starts with 0 MP)



**Daily Abilities:**

**Magic Whirlwind:** Cast two Magic Marks tonight instead of one. You&#39;ll swap the choosen targets. Can&#39;t choose self. (Similar to CW&#39;s Tornado) **(Cost: 2 MP. Won&#39;t give the MP back on casting empowered Magic Mark.)** **Infinite Uses**

**Private Area:** Choose a target to Occupy tonight. They won&#39;t be able to do anything and any visitors to them will receive a Magic Mark. If you choose yourself, ability won&#39;t occupy you. Choosen target (In case it wasn&#39;t you) won&#39;t be able to speak or vote the next day. **(Cost: 2 MP, won&#39;t give MP the following night)** **Infinite Uses**



**Night Abilities:**

**Magic Mark:** Cast a Magic Mark on choosen target tonight. They won&#39;t know about having it. Every successful Magic Mark will give you 1 MP. Marked targets have a chance to show up _Framed_ to Investigative classes, meaning they will show up as Unseen/Cult or Killer/Offensive. You will know who is Marked. **Infinite Uses**

**Magic Explosion:** Cast a powerful explosion on every Marked target, killing them. Won&#39;t kill _Death Immune_ targets. Doesn&#39;t count as a visit. **(Cost: 1 MP)** **Infinite Uses**



**Comments:**

It&#39;s my first class i&#39;ve ever decided to &quot;make&quot;. I like doing this kind of stuff but i&#39;m new to making classes in ToL, yet i still decided to give it a try. I&#39;ll await a fair criticism.
Basically i wanted to create NK with huge killing power; he&#39;s very weak in Early Game, but once he&#39;s done playing around, he&#39;s a huge threat. 
However i don&#39;t think he&#39;s balanced; he has no way to defend himself like Possessor can do with jumps or Reaper with Chill and Reap. He might also seem weak considering that all of the kills are done in one night; if he gets caught before he activates Explosion all of the progress is lost; making the game much harder for Evil Faction because of no kills. It might also seem kinda broken on the other hand because he can wreck the whole evil faction in one click of a mouse; but that requires a lot of nights. 



**FAQ**

**Q:** If Observer follows Warlock who casts Explosion, will it look like he visits all of the marked people?
**A:** As i described _Night Ability 2_, no. His explosion doesn&#39;t count as a visit.

**Q:** How does his _Private Area_ exactly work if he casts it on himself?
**A:** It won&#39;t silence Warlock the next day and won&#39;t occupy him the following night. All his visitors when _Private Area_ is on him will be Marked. However, Warlock will not get MP by Marking a choosen player that night.

**Q:** How does his _Magic Whirlwind_ exactly work?
**A:** It makes his _Magic Mark_ work like CW&#39;s Tornado; but it will also cast a Magic Mark on choosen targets. Warlock can&#39;t choose himself. It basically allows him to fakeclaim CW quite well and cast Magic Mark on two people rather than only one, which can be useful.

**Q:** Does the healing/guarding stop Explosion?
**A:** Healing stops both _Explosion_ and _Magic Mark_ (Won&#39;t remove it if it was for some time already). However, guard can only stop _Explosion_, without killing Warlock.

**Q:** Does the bear stop _Explosion_?
**A:** Yes. But it won&#39;t kill Warlock. Bear can also stop _Magic Mark_ if it&#39;s gonna be casted on bearing Hunter that night; it won&#39;t kill Warlock as well.

**Q:** Can you get rid of _Magic Mark_ somehow?
**A:** No. If it&#39;s already on the target, it cannot be removed. It can be however healed by _Physician_ on the same night Warlock is casting it on the same target.


**Feedback from Abilities:**
1. _You casted Magic Mark on **name** [X]._ (Night)
2. _You could not cast a Magic Mark on **name** [X]._ (Night)
3. _You will create a Private Area around **name** [X]/yourself tonight._ (Day)
4. _You will Empower your Magic Mark tonight._ (Day)
5. _You gained **number** MP._ (Night)
6. _You used **number** MP for **reason**._ (Night)
7. _Your Explosion killed your Mark Targets._ (Night)
8. _Your Explosion did not kill anyone._ (Night)
9. _Your Explosion target was immune._ (Night)
10. _You cleansed off yourself._ (Night)
11. _You now have **number** MP._ (Night)

I&#39;m waiting on your thoughts. Tell me what changes this class needs and if it&#39;s actually balanced. I&#39;ll appreciate any criticism. Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 15:49:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-warlock-neutral-killer/48864.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Warlock (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yuzu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Warlock</em> - <em>Neutral Killer</em><br>
<strong>Goal:</strong> Must kill all members of the main faction in order to win. (Similar to Poss and Reaper)</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Magic Shield:</strong> Immune to death at night. If he gets poisoned or bled, he’ll cleanse himself the following night, removing poison and bleed once for every person. (Example; Assassin poisons you, you’ll cleanse yourself and remove the poison; if he poisons again, Cleanse won’t happen again). Successful Cleanse will cast a Magic Mark on the person who bled/poisoned you. (See Night Ability 1 for reference)</p>
<p><strong>Magic Power:</strong> Warlock gathers 1 Magic Point (MP) for every Magic Mark (See Night Ability 1 for reference) he puts on his targets. He can use them in order to use his Daily Abilities. If he owns 2 MP or more, he will be Occupy Immune (Hidden) and Redirection Immune. (Also hidden). (WL starts with 0 MP)</p>
<p><strong>Daily Abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Magic Whirlwind:</strong> Cast two Magic Marks tonight instead of one. You’ll swap the choosen targets. Can’t choose self. (Similar to CW’s Tornado) <strong>(Cost: 2 MP. Won’t give the MP back on casting empowered Magic Mark.)</strong> <strong>Infinite Uses</strong></p>
<p><strong>Private Area:</strong> Choose a target to Occupy tonight. They won’t be able to do anything and any visitors to them will receive a Magic Mark. If you choose yourself, ability won’t occupy you. Choosen target (In case it wasn’t you) won’t be able to speak or vote the next day. <strong>(Cost: 2 MP, won’t give MP the following night)</strong> <strong>Infinite Uses</strong></p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Magic Mark:</strong> Cast a Magic Mark on choosen target tonight. They won’t know about having it. Every successful Magic Mark will give you 1 MP. Marked targets have a chance to show up <em>Framed</em> to Investigative classes, meaning they will show up as Unseen/Cult or Killer/Offensive. You will know who is Marked. <strong>Infinite Uses</strong></p>
<p><strong>Magic Explosion:</strong> Cast a powerful explosion on every Marked target, killing them. Won’t kill <em>Death Immune</em> targets. Doesn’t count as a visit. <strong>(Cost: 1 MP)</strong> <strong>Infinite Uses</strong></p>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong></p>
<p>It’s my first class i’ve ever decided to “make”. I like doing this kind of stuff but i’m new to making classes in ToL, yet i still decided to give it a try. I’ll await a fair criticism.<br>
Basically i wanted to create NK with huge killing power; he’s very weak in Early Game, but once he’s done playing around, he’s a huge threat.<br>
However i don’t think he’s balanced; he has no way to defend himself like Possessor can do with jumps or Reaper with Chill and Reap. He might also seem weak considering that all of the kills are done in one night; if he gets caught before he activates Explosion all of the progress is lost; making the game much harder for Evil Faction because of no kills. It might also seem kinda broken on the other hand because he can wreck the whole evil faction in one click of a mouse; but that requires a lot of nights.</p>
<p><strong>FAQ</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q:</strong> If Observer follows Warlock who casts Explosion, will it look like he visits all of the marked people?<br>
<strong>A:</strong> As i described <em>Night Ability 2</em>, no. His explosion doesn’t count as a visit.</p>
<p><strong>Q:</strong> How does his <em>Private Area</em> exactly work if he casts it on himself?<br>
<strong>A:</strong> It won’t silence Warlock the next day and won’t occupy him the following night. All his visitors when <em>Private Area</em> is on him will be Marked. However, Warlock will not get MP by Marking a choosen player that night.</p>
<p><strong>Q:</strong> How does his <em>Magic Whirlwind</em> exactly work?<br>
<strong>A:</strong> It makes his <em>Magic Mark</em> work like CW’s Tornado; but it will also cast a Magic Mark on choosen targets. Warlock can’t choose himself. It basically allows him to fakeclaim CW quite well and cast Magic Mark on two people rather than only one, which can be useful.</p>
<p><strong>Q:</strong> Does the healing/guarding stop Explosion?<br>
<strong>A:</strong> Healing stops both <em>Explosion</em> and <em>Magic Mark</em> (Won’t remove it if it was for some time already). However, guard can only stop <em>Explosion</em>, without killing Warlock.</p>
<p><strong>Q:</strong> Does the bear stop <em>Explosion</em>?<br>
<strong>A:</strong> Yes. But it won’t kill Warlock. Bear can also stop <em>Magic Mark</em> if it’s gonna be casted on bearing Hunter that night; it won’t kill Warlock as well.</p>
<p><strong>Q:</strong> Can you get rid of <em>Magic Mark</em> somehow?<br>
<strong>A:</strong> No. If it’s already on the target, it cannot be removed. It can be however healed by <em>Physician</em> on the same night Warlock is casting it on the same target.</p>
<p><strong>Feedback from Abilities:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>
<em>You casted Magic Mark on <strong>name</strong> [X].</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>You could not cast a Magic Mark on <strong>name</strong> [X].</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>You will create a Private Area around <strong>name</strong> [X]/yourself tonight.</em> (Day)</li>
<li>
<em>You will Empower your Magic Mark tonight.</em> (Day)</li>
<li>
<em>You gained <strong>number</strong> MP.</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>You used <strong>number</strong> MP for <strong>reason</strong>.</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>Your Explosion killed your Mark Targets.</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>Your Explosion did not kill anyone.</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>Your Explosion target was immune.</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>You cleansed off yourself.</em> (Night)</li>
<li>
<em>You now have <strong>number</strong> MP.</em> (Night)</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m waiting on your thoughts. Tell me what changes this class needs and if it’s actually balanced. I’ll appreciate any criticism. Thanks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-warlock-neutral-killer/48864/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-warlock-neutral-killer/48864/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 15:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-48864-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-warlock-neutral-killer/48864.rss">[Class Suggestion] Warlock (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
