<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Cult class/convert abilites</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-cult-class-convert-abilites/34346</link>
    <description>Something I&#39;ve always been curious about is the severely limited class types on cult side. 

I&#39;m sure there are great reasons for this! But I was discussing with some of my viewers about how cool it would be if one of the evil factions got a raise ability.

The idea started to form:

I think this should go to cult: cult games are a bit slower in nature and that&#39;s fine in and of itself but I also think they&#39;re stale.

I propose a psychic convert(this also fits lore so bear with me) that is given 1 night resurrection charge and 2 charges of night link. My reasoning is that unseen psychics are able to use day ability but not night link. This would effectively flip it. There&#39;s room to build on this.

The resurrected target: I&#39;m not sure it NEEDS to be a DK but I do like the idea of body jumping for 1 day cycle and 1 night cycle. The target would gain full use of the original targets night and day abilities and since psychic is unique its not required for dead chat to be muted as the body jumped target would be temporarily flipped to the dead party.

The havok this could cause would be AMAZING!

Would the body jumped cult use their day and night to get someone else killed? Put sus on their target or get their target killed?! The possibilities are endless.

Thanks for reading!

~Achtland</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 22:05:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-cult-class-convert-abilites/34346.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Cult class/convert abilites</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Achtland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Something I’ve always been curious about is the severely limited class types on cult side.</p>
<p>I’m sure there are great reasons for this! But I was discussing with some of my viewers about how cool it would be if one of the evil factions got a raise ability.</p>
<p>The idea started to form:</p>
<p>I think this should go to cult: cult games are a bit slower in nature and that’s fine in and of itself but I also think they’re stale.</p>
<p>I propose a psychic convert(this also fits lore so bear with me) that is given 1 night resurrection charge and 2 charges of night link. My reasoning is that unseen psychics are able to use day ability but not night link. This would effectively flip it. There’s room to build on this.</p>
<p>The resurrected target: I’m not sure it NEEDS to be a DK but I do like the idea of body jumping for 1 day cycle and 1 night cycle. The target would gain full use of the original targets night and day abilities and since psychic is unique its not required for dead chat to be muted as the body jumped target would be temporarily flipped to the dead party.</p>
<p>The havok this could cause would be AMAZING!</p>
<p>Would the body jumped cult use their day and night to get someone else killed? Put sus on their target or get their target killed?! The possibilities are endless.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading!</p>
<p>~Achtland</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-cult-class-convert-abilites/34346/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-cult-class-convert-abilites/34346/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34346-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-cult-class-convert-abilites/34346.rss">New Cult class/convert abilites</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
