<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551</link>
    <description>So i bought this game about a week ago and actually quite liked it at first, but the more i play the more frustrated i get. The last 10 games i played started with either evil or neutral king which ruins the game.

Here are my 2 suggestions and my reasoning why i think they are necessary:

**No neutral starting king:**
An evil king is bad for BD but neutral is even worse. Kings are supposed to be the focus of BD efforts to find the cult or unseen, if evil they have to be purged fast and replaced by good kings. Neutral kings ruin the game since they are usually afk for the whole game, refuse to cooperate with anyone and just wait till the end to take a side. This makes the whole game tedious since BDs can not really confirm each other without exposing themself and Cult can replentish their forces if the prince gets one of them. Neutral king games aren&#39;t fun at all since there is nothing happening in the day whatsoever. Votes go nowhere since there is no incentive for the king to step up. Neutral King games have ruined my game experience and there are just so many of them.

**Increase the chance of good starting kings:**
Another reason the game has become incredibly dull for me is that an evil king is an almost guaranteed win for cult. As i said my last 10 games have been with either neutral or evil king and the cult/unseen won all of them. The only fun roles atm are the neutral ones, and you don&#39;t get them that often. I think in 2/3 games the starting king should be good,since as already mentioned, he is a keypoint for BD efforts. Another reason is that Neutrals usually side with Cult/unseen after achieving their goal wich tilts the odds even more in the cults/unseen favor.

Inb4 you are just bad: I actually won most of those games since i somehow attract evil roles and either start evil or get converted early. But usually at least 2 BD investigators are dead by n5 since neutral/evil king doesnt bother with protecting them and other BD classes are unaware of their role.It&#39;s just no fun at all since their is no challange. You never get executed as long as you are not directly confirmed and your log is slightly passable if the king doesn&#39;t pay attention. 90% of my deaths as assassin have been through hunter or guards.

The above mentioned makes the game incredible repetetive for me. I really hope there will be changes.

Sincerely 
Aeon</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 14:28:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That sounds amazing</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 14:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neclord]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s where the healsluts come in! People Staunchly refuse to vote me up under threat of Yolobomb. Keeps Cult/Unseen and useful BD classes that don’t want to die in line.</p>
<p>In order to defeat my network the Prince/Knights/Evils would need to kill anyone who whispers to me. Far too much of a detour to eject a Neut King.</p>
<p>And then, in the event I am voted up, putting/bluffing the “I’ve found a cult/unseen. Kill me and the knowledge dies. Pardon me, and I’ll vote them up. Watch the evils all vote to Exe this.” is a good failsafe that works most of the time.</p>
<p>Ultimately, if you play your cards right as Neut King you can be a force of your own rather than some facton’s side ho.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 13:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d kill you in a heartbeat <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 12:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neclord]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree with this wholeheartedly. Getting to start as Neutral King is one of best experiences this game has to offer. Neuts are far more devoted to you than they otherwise would be, meaning you can have up to two healslut yolobombers doing your bidding.</p>
<p>You’ve just gotta set yourself up as a Neut king and be very bullish about it. People respect that (most of the time).</p>
<p>Legit I’ve had games where I worked with a Poss from D2 because I granted all Neuts diplomatic immunity. The Poss whispered me and revealed himself of his own accord.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 12:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But thats exactly why neutral king is stupid.<br>
Its the games easy mode, requires no skill at all and just loses BD 90% of all games.</p>
<p>almost no BD class can effectivly execute the king. And Neutral kings are useless in early game since they just sit around and wait. Every game i have in which king claims neutral i get the immediat urge to jsut leave cause those games are ALWAYS boring and predictable.</p>
<p>I cant take much more of this. The ratio in wich i get evil/neut kings to good kings is around 4:1.<br>
I start to not care anymore. If i get banned because i leave neut king games i will just quit. I would refund if i could, even though i bought it on sale for less then 10 bucks. Having to sit through 3 tedious shitgames just to have one interesing one simply isnt worth it. I really hope they change this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 14:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I usually play neutral king like a hybrid of good and evil king. I try to find the evils and tell them I am evil king. If they out the other evils then I just out them all and they lose super quickly. Otherwise I guarantee my safety from them and it isn’t hard to betray BD later if I think they will win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 00:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here is the problem with that:<br>
You don’t know who to push and pushing people also gives you unwanted attention. An early call to exe King, especially if he claimed Neut will usually end with you getting executed by some other Neutral or BD. A king usually goes up to day 3 without ever being questioned. By then usually 2-3 BDs have bitten dust, If you are unlucky prince is among them. It also becomes increasingly difficult since the possibility exists that the next king will just be evil/neut as well wich wastes your time.</p>
<p>Since i play evil a lot, a King that does nothing helps me a lot. But i rather win to an evil king doing nothing, than a neutral king. Playing neutral king is also incredibly boring. You have no incentive to do anything but stay alive and everyones knows it. So you just vote outed cults/unseen and NKs while claiming your checks are BD to stay on everyones good side. I really get the urge to just leave or go afk when getting neut king. It is basically doing nothing at all, working with noone and slowly, slowly watch wich sides wins and side with them in the end.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 23:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have said this before. No neutral Starting kings. Most join BD anyways. Make it 50 50.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 20:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I believe Kings will be looked at in general, but if you feel like the game is going nowhere, start making it go places. Push people, see how they react, and see how others react. Build a case from there.</p>
<p>Other than that I would be unopposed to looking at King spawn rates some, especially NKing, but I’m not sure it’s necessary. If the King isn’t helping, execute them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 19:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End neutral starting king please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So i bought this game about a week ago and actually quite liked it at first, but the more i play the more frustrated i get. The last 10 games i played started with either evil or neutral king which ruins the game.</p>
<p>Here are my 2 suggestions and my reasoning why i think they are necessary:</p>
<p><strong>No neutral starting king:</strong><br>
An evil king is bad for BD but neutral is even worse. Kings are supposed to be the focus of BD efforts to find the cult or unseen, if evil they have to be purged fast and replaced by good kings. Neutral kings ruin the game since they are usually afk for the whole game, refuse to cooperate with anyone and just wait till the end to take a side. This makes the whole game tedious since BDs can not really confirm each other without exposing themself and Cult can replentish their forces if the prince gets one of them. Neutral king games aren’t fun at all since there is nothing happening in the day whatsoever. Votes go nowhere since there is no incentive for the king to step up. Neutral King games have ruined my game experience and there are just so many of them.</p>
<p><strong>Increase the chance of good starting kings:</strong><br>
Another reason the game has become incredibly dull for me is that an evil king is an almost guaranteed win for cult. As i said my last 10 games have been with either neutral or evil king and the cult/unseen won all of them. The only fun roles atm are the neutral ones, and you don’t get them that often. I think in 2/3 games the starting king should be good,since as already mentioned, he is a keypoint for BD efforts. Another reason is that Neutrals usually side with Cult/unseen after achieving their goal wich tilts the odds even more in the cults/unseen favor.</p>
<p>Inb4 you are just bad: I actually won most of those games since i somehow attract evil roles and either start evil or get converted early. But usually at least 2 BD investigators are dead by n5 since neutral/evil king doesnt bother with protecting them and other BD classes are unaware of their role.It’s just no fun at all since their is no challange. You never get executed as long as you are not directly confirmed and your log is slightly passable if the king doesn’t pay attention. 90% of my deaths as assassin have been through hunter or guards.</p>
<p>The above mentioned makes the game incredible repetetive for me. I really hope there will be changes.</p>
<p>Sincerely<br>
Aeon</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 19:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23551-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/end-neutral-starting-king-please/23551.rss">End neutral starting king please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
