<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Possessor</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor/499</link>
    <description>Lore link: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Possessor

Lore Subject: Scout and Court Wizard reports on Possessors.

Lore: I&#39;m afraid our attempts to understand this being have come without much merit. Every scout we send out comes back complaining that they were sent on a fools errand and that we should stop trying to find what isn&#39;t there. One report we do have is of a scout who claims his fellow soldier betrayed him and was wounded. The scout returned telling us of the red eyes of his assailant and assured us they were the best of friends and he did not understand why he had done this. A few days later the scouts friend appeared strung from a tree a few miles from where the incident occurred. If indeed encountered by a possessor our Court Wizard has said this on the subject: These beings while magical and fantastic are still subject to their needs and desires. They display a parasitical nature using their host to nourish themselves and in defence. Of course at times these creatures may attack with their host or simply move to another for comfort. However never underestimate such beings. They are wise of the ways of man and if they sense danger upon themselves there is no telling what they may do to continue their parasitic existence.

Comments: Like the Reaper this class should be filled with suspicion and doubt as to their intentions. In game they may side with blue dragon masking that they exist or Black rose or cult to ensure the time of possible danger will pass. The only side they take is their own so their behaviour is likely to mimic that of a cornered rat. Displaying either bargaining or A ferocious counter attack. This role shouldn&#39;t be displayed as necessarily evil but beyond social bonds and only interested in using it&#39;s wits to protect itself in an effort of self preservation.I decided that the class that would have knowledge of this would be the court wizard as the possessor is more magic in nature than any other class.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 23:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor/499.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Possessor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore link: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Possessor" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Possessor</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: Scout and Court Wizard reports on Possessors.</p>
<p>Lore: I’m afraid our attempts to understand this being have come without much merit. Every scout we send out comes back complaining that they were sent on a fools errand and that we should stop trying to find what isn’t there. One report we do have is of a scout who claims his fellow soldier betrayed him and was wounded. The scout returned telling us of the red eyes of his assailant and assured us they were the best of friends and he did not understand why he had done this. A few days later the scouts friend appeared strung from a tree a few miles from where the incident occurred. If indeed encountered by a possessor our Court Wizard has said this on the subject: These beings while magical and fantastic are still subject to their needs and desires. They display a parasitical nature using their host to nourish themselves and in defence. Of course at times these creatures may attack with their host or simply move to another for comfort. However never underestimate such beings. They are wise of the ways of man and if they sense danger upon themselves there is no telling what they may do to continue their parasitic existence.</p>
<p>Comments: Like the Reaper this class should be filled with suspicion and doubt as to their intentions. In game they may side with blue dragon masking that they exist or Black rose or cult to ensure the time of possible danger will pass. The only side they take is their own so their behaviour is likely to mimic that of a cornered rat. Displaying either bargaining or A ferocious counter attack. This role shouldn’t be displayed as necessarily evil but beyond social bonds and only interested in using it’s wits to protect itself in an effort of self preservation.I decided that the class that would have knowledge of this would be the court wizard as the possessor is more magic in nature than any other class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor/499/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor/499/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 23:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-499-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor/499.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Possessor</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
