<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reaper, Neutral Killer, New Ability: Eternal Life</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/reaper-neutral-killer-new-ability-eternal-life/32349</link>
    <description>Day Ability 3
I agree with the sentiment that Reaper needs to become a bit stronger,Eternal Life: Before getting hung, the reaper can use this day ability (requires 1 soul) to choose a living body that will personally be his host body. Giving him his same Night and Day abilities as before and this state consumes 1 soul a night; consequently if there are no souls the Reaper will die. If this person should die, the Reaper will die instead. In case of dying from treason in court, the Reaper would die too.
 -When in this state, Investigator roles will see that the Reaper person is a Neutral. So it&#39;ll be a bit similar to Jump making the new host a neut.
 -The reaper will be the one to die as previously stated if a knight or someone tried to kill the host. And if the Reaper gets hit by a bear or something he will die. 
 -Reaper should either make the host occupy immune or be immune themselves to any occupancy or redirects (this sub point I&#39;m uncertain about).
 -If Psychic connects to the host body he can see that Reaper is in that person. If Observer Follows the host, he will see that the host went into two places. Princess using Flirt will see both of the actual roles of the host and the Reaper allowing for it to be difficult in detecting Reaper for them still. 
 -Cannot use King as host, if Prince or other Neuts are selected it will fail; thus, making the Reaper truly die.

This re-work in my humble opinion feels like a Reaper. And it requires the Reaper to start reaping early for those important souls as reaping or even possessing early gets you killed to quickly currently. The recent Possessor reworks has made awesome Possessor wins from what I&#39;ve seen. I&#39;ve only seen a Reaper win once. This is actually my favorite class, So I&#39;m looking forward to seeing what it can do in the future.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 21:07:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/reaper-neutral-killer-new-ability-eternal-life/32349.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reaper, Neutral Killer, New Ability: Eternal Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iKaey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Day Ability 3<br>
I agree with the sentiment that Reaper needs to become a bit stronger,Eternal Life: Before getting hung, the reaper can use this day ability (requires 1 soul) to choose a living body that will personally be his host body. Giving him his same Night and Day abilities as before and this state consumes 1 soul a night; consequently if there are no souls the Reaper will die. If this person should die, the Reaper will die instead. In case of dying from treason in court, the Reaper would die too.<br>
-When in this state, Investigator roles will see that the Reaper person is a Neutral. So it’ll be a bit similar to Jump making the new host a neut.<br>
-The reaper will be the one to die as previously stated if a knight or someone tried to kill the host. And if the Reaper gets hit by a bear or something he will die.<br>
-Reaper should either make the host occupy immune or be immune themselves to any occupancy or redirects (this sub point I’m uncertain about).<br>
-If Psychic connects to the host body he can see that Reaper is in that person. If Observer Follows the host, he will see that the host went into two places. Princess using Flirt will see both of the actual roles of the host and the Reaper allowing for it to be difficult in detecting Reaper for them still.<br>
-Cannot use King as host, if Prince or other Neuts are selected it will fail; thus, making the Reaper truly die.</p>
<p>This re-work in my humble opinion feels like a Reaper. And it requires the Reaper to start reaping early for those important souls as reaping or even possessing early gets you killed to quickly currently. The recent Possessor reworks has made awesome Possessor wins from what I’ve seen. I’ve only seen a Reaper win once. This is actually my favorite class, So I’m looking forward to seeing what it can do in the future.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/reaper-neutral-killer-new-ability-eternal-life/32349/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/reaper-neutral-killer-new-ability-eternal-life/32349/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 21:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32349-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/reaper-neutral-killer-new-ability-eternal-life/32349.rss">Reaper, Neutral Killer, New Ability: Eternal Life</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
