<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>For the love of god, quit auto-executing scout targets</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108</link>
    <description>I&#39;m sitting in the Nth game of the week where Sheriff calls &quot;someone visited&quot; and unconverted BD gets executed.

This is not the way to play Scout anymore since the change. It used to be, but now the proper response is to re-investigate their faction.

First, I&#39;ll say night 1 is different--it&#39;s known conversion night. If someone isn&#39;t conversion immune, I&#39;ll usually exe.

But any other night--look, only 1/2 to 1/3 of the entire Unseen *can* convert, and they can only do it 1/2 the time unless they&#39;re failing the converts, in which case they only do it 1/3-1/4 of the time.

So that&#39;s, what, 1/4 in the best case to 1/12 in the worst. We can throttle that back a bit because Assassin visits usually die, but the basic point stands:

**It&#39;s way more common for a visit *not* to convert someone than for it to convert someone. My own experience absolutely bears this out, and favoring reinvestigation has saved BD many times.**

So, maybe quit putting them up, Sheriffs? A visit is a great reason to re-investigate for sure, but it&#39;s a shitty reason to out them to the court. BD can be sheep and if you put them up, they&#39;ll probably get executed without much examination. 

And BD, if a Sheriff who doesn&#39;t re-investigate does put them up any day other than d2, QUIT EXEING. If you happen to know that mm is the only one around and the class is convertible, sure, make an intelligent decision. Otherwise, pardoning, occing, and reinvestigating is the right thing to do.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 21:31:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>For the love of god, quit auto-executing scout targets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not that simple. The target could also have been healed/guarded or they were a hiding Fool. For MM visits this can also happen with conversion immune targets such as the Mercenary, the Prince, the Fool again,or in a worst-case scenario, a bearing Hunter.</p>
<p>Though, typically the safest recourse here is the Sheriff checking the visited target the next night, albeit it comes at the price of a night from the Sheriff and a potentially wasted day for BD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 21:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68108-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108.rss">For the love of god, quit auto-executing scout targets</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>For the love of god, quit auto-executing scout targets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Math is quite a bit off if you consider the fact that anyone the Assassin visits and doesn’t successfully kill is also almost always a good lynch as it’s usually NKs, Scorneds or Alchemists</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 08:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68108-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108.rss">For the love of god, quit auto-executing scout targets</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>For the love of god, quit auto-executing scout targets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geoelectric]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sitting in the Nth game of the week where Sheriff calls “someone visited” and unconverted BD gets executed.</p>
<p>This is not the way to play Scout anymore since the change. It used to be, but now the proper response is to re-investigate their faction.</p>
<p>First, I’ll say night 1 is different–it’s known conversion night. If someone isn’t conversion immune, I’ll usually exe.</p>
<p>But any other night–look, only 1/2 to 1/3 of the entire Unseen <em>can</em> convert, and they can only do it 1/2 the time unless they’re failing the converts, in which case they only do it 1/3-1/4 of the time.</p>
<p>So that’s, what, 1/4 in the best case to 1/12 in the worst. We can throttle that back a bit because Assassin visits usually die, but the basic point stands:</p>
<p><strong>It’s way more common for a visit <em>not</em> to convert someone than for it to convert someone. My own experience absolutely bears this out, and favoring reinvestigation has saved BD many times.</strong></p>
<p>So, maybe quit putting them up, Sheriffs? A visit is a great reason to re-investigate for sure, but it’s a shitty reason to out them to the court. BD can be sheep and if you put them up, they’ll probably get executed without much examination.</p>
<p>And BD, if a Sheriff who doesn’t re-investigate does put them up any day other than d2, QUIT EXEING. If you happen to know that mm is the only one around and the class is convertible, sure, make an intelligent decision. Otherwise, pardoning, occing, and reinvestigating is the right thing to do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68108-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/for-the-love-of-god-quit-auto-executing-scout-targets/68108.rss">For the love of god, quit auto-executing scout targets</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
