<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>(Class Suggestion) The Carpenter (BD)/The Sabotager (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440</link>
    <description>Here is a class suggestion:

&gt;**The Carpenter** _(BD Support) (Unique)_

&gt;**Passives**
**1** _Reinforced_ Begin the game with a gate built in your room.

&gt;**Day Abilities**
**1** _Restock_ Remove the cooldown on building a gate for tonight.

&gt;**Night Abilities**
**1** _Build_ Build a gate in your target&#39;s room, built gates prevent non-BD players from visiting, if a non-BD visits the target the gate is destroyed. 1 Night Cooldown. Unlimited Uses. Cooldown shared with Reinforce.
**2** _Reinforce_ Rebuild the gate in your own room. 1 Night Cooldown. One Use. Cooldown shared with Build.

&gt;**Notes** You can only have one gate built on a player at a time. If the NK and Assasin/CL both visit the same target with the task to kill them and they have a gate equipped the player will still die. Knights will still be able to use Cold Steel on a gated player. You can not use build on yourself or the king.

&gt;**Lore**
From a young age, the carpenter was crafty, building hinges out of wood for doors, even though they were declined as they were too weak, the King saw great progression that the boy could make and appointed him as a builder at the age of 20, he did great efforts into building and expanding Castle Adiart, moved on to become one of the best builders in the surrounding area. When he returned, he worked on building gates during blackout, with the shadows covering his recognised outfit being covered in the shadows as he quietly worked for no pay. All the protect the Blue Dragon in their quest to rid the manical Cult of the castle.

&gt;When he is converted he becomes...
**The Sabotager** _(Unseen Support) (Unique)_

&gt;**Passives**
**1** _Last Gate_ Once you are converted, you gain an extra gate, this gate will only affect Neutral Classes. If you become an Assassin or the Mastermind you will lose this gate.

&gt;**Day Abilities**
**1** _Collapse_ Turn a player&#39;s room to rubble, preventing others except Unseen members from visiting them. The player will lose occupy immunity and can&#39;t take their night action. 1 Use.

&gt;**Night Abilities**
**1** _Weaken_ Weaken your own floor, sending a player into a hole into a pit. This occupies the player. 2 Uses.

&gt;**Lore**
After being brought into the Unseen, The Mastermind saw great potential of the abilities of construction to destroy the castle for their own advantage. The Unseen told him to destroy the roof of the executed Fool&#39;s room and threw a dummy in there, the dummy was trapped but completely unharmed, the Carpenter knew the way on how the roof was destroyed so the Assassin could sneak in. This was just an experiment, and luckily, nobody saw anything. This would give the Unseen an advantage in taking down the Blue Dragon.

&gt;**Becomes Ritualist when converted to Cult**</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 19:39:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>(Class Suggestion) The Carpenter (BD)/The Sabotager (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The BD Trapper merc combo.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 19:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54440-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440.rss">(Class Suggestion) The Carpenter (BD)/The Sabotager (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Class Suggestion) The Carpenter (BD)/The Sabotager (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jebus_irl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here is a class suggestion:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The Carpenter</strong> <em>(BD Support) (Unique)</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Passives</strong><br>
<strong>1</strong> <em>Reinforced</em> Begin the game with a gate built in your room.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Day Abilities</strong><br>
<strong>1</strong> <em>Restock</em> Remove the cooldown on building a gate for tonight.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night Abilities</strong><br>
<strong>1</strong> <em>Build</em> Build a gate in your target’s room, built gates prevent non-BD players from visiting, if a non-BD visits the target the gate is destroyed. 1 Night Cooldown. Unlimited Uses. Cooldown shared with Reinforce.<br>
<strong>2</strong> <em>Reinforce</em> Rebuild the gate in your own room. 1 Night Cooldown. One Use. Cooldown shared with Build.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Notes</strong> You can only have one gate built on a player at a time. If the NK and Assasin/CL both visit the same target with the task to kill them and they have a gate equipped the player will still die. Knights will still be able to use Cold Steel on a gated player. You can not use build on yourself or the king.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Lore</strong><br>
From a young age, the carpenter was crafty, building hinges out of wood for doors, even though they were declined as they were too weak, the King saw great progression that the boy could make and appointed him as a builder at the age of 20, he did great efforts into building and expanding Castle Adiart, moved on to become one of the best builders in the surrounding area. When he returned, he worked on building gates during blackout, with the shadows covering his recognised outfit being covered in the shadows as he quietly worked for no pay. All the protect the Blue Dragon in their quest to rid the manical Cult of the castle.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>When he is converted he becomes…<br>
<strong>The Sabotager</strong> <em>(Unseen Support) (Unique)</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Passives</strong><br>
<strong>1</strong> <em>Last Gate</em> Once you are converted, you gain an extra gate, this gate will only affect Neutral Classes. If you become an Assassin or the Mastermind you will lose this gate.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Day Abilities</strong><br>
<strong>1</strong> <em>Collapse</em> Turn a player’s room to rubble, preventing others except Unseen members from visiting them. The player will lose occupy immunity and can’t take their night action. 1 Use.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Night Abilities</strong><br>
<strong>1</strong> <em>Weaken</em> Weaken your own floor, sending a player into a hole into a pit. This occupies the player. 2 Uses.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Lore</strong><br>
After being brought into the Unseen, The Mastermind saw great potential of the abilities of construction to destroy the castle for their own advantage. The Unseen told him to destroy the roof of the executed Fool’s room and threw a dummy in there, the dummy was trapped but completely unharmed, the Carpenter knew the way on how the roof was destroyed so the Assassin could sneak in. This was just an experiment, and luckily, nobody saw anything. This would give the Unseen an advantage in taking down the Blue Dragon.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Becomes Ritualist when converted to Cult</strong></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 19:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54440-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-carpenter-bd-the-sabotager-unseen/54440.rss">(Class Suggestion) The Carpenter (BD)/The Sabotager (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
