<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;m making this thread for support on how to deal with multiple sheriff or Paladin claims, as of update 1.0.e17

This is an early/mid game dilemma I have experienced in two examples outlined below:

In the first example, there were 2 sheriff claims around the mid game I think, the prince took it upon himself to &quot;prove&quot; who the sheriff was by exeing one of the claims. The obvious flaw being that coin flip you hit the actual sheriff (which he did) 
My solution to this problem would be getting both &quot;sheriffs&quot; to surveille and ask people to visit both of them and have them say who visited them the next night. Thereby proving who is sheriff and who isn&#39;t, this isn&#39;t foolproof as with any solution, but I believe it to be the most practical.

The next example is a bit harder to resolve in my opinion.
A **good king** receives 3 paladin claims, which in the majority of circumstances means one is false, how do you deduce which is which?
This one involves a bit of scumreading, in the absence of any other factors, ask each one to provide infomation each day and go from there. Unless the king has a read, they should _not_ out them to each other, but instead ask each one to check someone who hasnt been checked so as to co-ordinate each others. Paladins usually will out themselves when they find cult, a smart evil who is about to be sacrificed would do well to &quot;out&quot; someone as cult. Especially in the early/early-mid game. 


Has anyone else experienced the confusion of too many early investigative claims? How has the court dealt with it? Was it in your opinion a practical solution?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 16:28:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Finitethrills]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds like you had a possessor, or did they change the non-unique limit and I didn’t notice?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 16:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41544-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544.rss">How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t wait for the legendary 7 paladin game (and also an assassin but don’t worry about it).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 16:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41544-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544.rss">How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Uh, but I’ve had a few games where there actually were 3 Paladins yesterday</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41544-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544.rss">How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello, I’m making this thread for support on how to deal with multiple sheriff or Paladin claims, as of update 1.0.e17</p>
<p>This is an early/mid game dilemma I have experienced in two examples outlined below:</p>
<p>In the first example, there were 2 sheriff claims around the mid game I think, the prince took it upon himself to “prove” who the sheriff was by exeing one of the claims. The obvious flaw being that coin flip you hit the actual sheriff (which he did)<br>
My solution to this problem would be getting both “sheriffs” to surveille and ask people to visit both of them and have them say who visited them the next night. Thereby proving who is sheriff and who isn’t, this isn’t foolproof as with any solution, but I believe it to be the most practical.</p>
<p>The next example is a bit harder to resolve in my opinion.<br>
A <strong>good king</strong> receives 3 paladin claims, which in the majority of circumstances means one is false, how do you deduce which is which?<br>
This one involves a bit of scumreading, in the absence of any other factors, ask each one to provide infomation each day and go from there. Unless the king has a read, they should <em>not</em> out them to each other, but instead ask each one to check someone who hasnt been checked so as to co-ordinate each others. Paladins usually will out themselves when they find cult, a smart evil who is about to be sacrificed would do well to “out” someone as cult. Especially in the early/early-mid game.</p>
<p>Has anyone else experienced the confusion of too many early investigative claims? How has the court dealt with it? Was it in your opinion a practical solution?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41544-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-to-deal-with-investigative-claims-that-are-unconfirmed/41544.rss">How to deal with Investigative claims that are unconfirmed</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
