<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Inq/Sorc {Lore Suggestions}</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/inq-sorc-lore-suggestions/56400</link>
    <description>Inq lore

&quot;I know this is because of the magical one, cough cough. She is the one that plagued me with the disease but how did she ever get it in the first place? Oh I know it&#39;s that Alchemist lady, she must have gave it to that soulless witch!  How did she become a hateful Sorcerer, when was a faithful follower of the church? She is too heartless to have tricked me and gave me a plague like this... and now she is trying to rule the kingdom...! 

I need to stop her before she rules over this realm...! I need to get my revenge... REVENGE! Hehehe! She won&#39;t see it coming at all!  Hehehe! I will make sure she&#39;s dead...! I will track her until she dies! If it&#39;s the last thing I do before I fall to this cough... plague cough. Am I thinking this a bit too crazy? Maybe but I&#39;ll still do it! At least I&#39;ll come to peace with myself when I see her dead on the floor....

Cough cough cough! Where is that idiotic Physician! He better get hear before I die of this cough...&quot; 

Sorc lore

&quot;Hahaha, that idiot! He made it so easy for me... he was so trusting that it&#39;s funny! Like what does he think I wanted? Did he want be to be some good person while I could just go help the evil force of the kingdom? He is insane... hahaha! Good thing that stupid Alchemist lady gave me some nightshade to poison his old ugly talkative mouth. Though I do kind of miss that old ugly man but eh who cares about him right?

My Master plan is to take over the world by killing the &quot;stupid good dragons&quot; or whatever they those dummies! Then, become allied with the evil force and then betray them to go on being the new ruler of the kingdom. Or just ally with them to make my life a lot easier!

But before doing all of this I need to learn how to use magic or else I can&#39;t do anything! I heard that the idiotic Court Wizard is magic master, so maybe I should go learn from him or maybe even from the Paladin or Mystic&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 23:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/inq-sorc-lore-suggestions/56400.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Inq/Sorc {Lore Suggestions}</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Inq lore</p>
<p>"I know this is because of the magical one, cough cough. She is the one that plagued me with the disease but how did she ever get it in the first place? Oh I know it’s that Alchemist lady, she must have gave it to that soulless witch!  How did she become a hateful Sorcerer, when was a faithful follower of the church? She is too heartless to have tricked me and gave me a plague like this… and now she is trying to rule the kingdom…!</p>
<p>I need to stop her before she rules over this realm…! I need to get my revenge… REVENGE! Hehehe! She won’t see it coming at all!  Hehehe! I will make sure she’s dead…! I will track her until she dies! If it’s the last thing I do before I fall to this cough… plague cough. Am I thinking this a bit too crazy? Maybe but I’ll still do it! At least I’ll come to peace with myself when I see her dead on the floor…</p>
<p>Cough cough cough! Where is that idiotic Physician! He better get hear before I die of this cough…"</p>
<p>Sorc lore</p>
<p>"Hahaha, that idiot! He made it so easy for me… he was so trusting that it’s funny! Like what does he think I wanted? Did he want be to be some good person while I could just go help the evil force of the kingdom? He is insane… hahaha! Good thing that stupid Alchemist lady gave me some nightshade to poison his old ugly talkative mouth. Though I do kind of miss that old ugly man but eh who cares about him right?</p>
<p>My Master plan is to take over the world by killing the “stupid good dragons” or whatever they those dummies! Then, become allied with the evil force and then betray them to go on being the new ruler of the kingdom. Or just ally with them to make my life a lot easier!</p>
<p>But before doing all of this I need to learn how to use magic or else I can’t do anything! I heard that the idiotic Court Wizard is magic master, so maybe I should go learn from him or maybe even from the Paladin or Mystic"</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/inq-sorc-lore-suggestions/56400/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/inq-sorc-lore-suggestions/56400/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 23:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-56400-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/inq-sorc-lore-suggestions/56400.rss">Inq/Sorc {Lore Suggestions}</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
