<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792</link>
    <description>Hello! First off, I&#39;m glad that the Devs have decided to let us participate in the recreation of the Court Wizard. Nothing says community integration quite like allowing the community to rework a class. With that said, let&#39;s get to it!

**Passive Ability**

_Magical Affinity_ - Through his years of practice in the art of magic, the Court Wizard has gained an affinity to 
harmful magic. This ability would protect the CW from all NK attacks, but just once. I feel that with the inability to talk to the dead, NK classes have gotten very strong due to dead folks not being able to tell the Mystic that they were Reaped or Possessed. Adding this passive to CW would allow a more general counter to the NK&#39;s, along with Inquisitor, and helps to tie together the rest of his kit.

**Day Abilities**

_Enhance!_ - An ability that allows the target to use two night abilities. They will receive a notification at the beginning of the night telling them that a CW has put this on them. This does not work for Fool&#39;s abilities, as he cannot Hide himself while also making himself suspicious. Mystic would still only be able to chose one night ability for balancing purposes. Assassin would not be able to Assassinate and 2-for-1 for balancing purposes. Possessor would not be able to use Puppet Strings and Possess in the same night for balancing purposes. Sorcerer would not be able to use Magic Missile and Circle of Death in the same night for balancing purposes.

**Night Abilities**

_Hypnotic Rest_ - The An ability that makes the target appear as sleeping to those who visit. While it does not make them immune from harmful abilities or death, it does make them Occupy Immune, allowing them to carry out their deeds as necessary. Similar to the current Magic Barrier, but has less impact than CW&#39;s day ability and other night ability are much stronger. This has infinite uses.

_Thaumaturgical Cloak_ - This garment protect the wearer from conversion or attack. The magic in this cloak wares off, however, dissipating the effect. In other terms, this is a spell that protects any player from conversion for 2 nights, or 1 attack, whichever comes first. The CW will have 2 uses of this and is mainly here for a all-around protection of himself and his fellow BD. Can be cast on self.

Shaman (Sage)

**Night Abilities**

_Hypnotic Rest_ - An ability that makes the target appear as sleeping to those who visit. While it does not make them immune from harmful abilities or death, it does make them Occupy Immune, allowing them to carry out their deeds as necessary. Similar to the current Magic Barrier, but has less impact than CW&#39;s day ability and other night ability are much stronger. This has infinite uses.

_Conjure Weapon_ - An ability that guarantees a kill to the Assassin no matter the guards nor heals on a random target. Cannot target King. CW is a very supportive class, and Unseen already has countless things to allow MM to stay alive and to mess with other BD&#39;s. I think allowing the Assassin one guaranteed kill would make for an easier job when it comes to those super priority targets especially with the added fun of RNG.

A lot of these suggestions were just fun stuff or things I thought needed to be implemented into the game as defense mechanisms against the stronger classes (At least in my opinion).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 10:49:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No the devs ask to get a new class design because the class is bad</p>
<p>Not broken</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 10:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Boslof literally asks for the community to help fix it.</p>
<p>Tell me how it’s not broken if the dev asks everyone to help fix it. That’s not bad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 10:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not broken</p>
<p>It’s just bad</p>
<p>Not broken</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Damafaud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Court Wizard is broken</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 09:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t fix what isn’t broken</p>
<p>-Noz quote</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You ruined sage for me</p>
<p>Tornado needs to be on sage</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maximyss" data-post="1" data-topic="54792">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/prince-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Maximyss:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>feel that with the inability to talk to the dead, NK classes have gotten very strong due to dead folks not being able to tell the Mystic that they were Reaped or Possessed. Adding this passive to CW would allow a more general counter to the NK’s, along with Inquisitor, and helps to tie together the rest of his kit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Take away this. How many times have you see. A NK win? Oh wait less than cult/unseen then leave the NK alone</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximyss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello! First off, I’m glad that the Devs have decided to let us participate in the recreation of the Court Wizard. Nothing says community integration quite like allowing the community to rework a class. With that said, let’s get to it!</p>
<p><strong>Passive Ability</strong></p>
<p><em>Magical Affinity</em> - Through his years of practice in the art of magic, the Court Wizard has gained an affinity to<br>
harmful magic. This ability would protect the CW from all NK attacks, but just once. I feel that with the inability to talk to the dead, NK classes have gotten very strong due to dead folks not being able to tell the Mystic that they were Reaped or Possessed. Adding this passive to CW would allow a more general counter to the NK’s, along with Inquisitor, and helps to tie together the rest of his kit.</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities</strong></p>
<p><em>Enhance!</em> - An ability that allows the target to use two night abilities. They will receive a notification at the beginning of the night telling them that a CW has put this on them. This does not work for Fool’s abilities, as he cannot Hide himself while also making himself suspicious. Mystic would still only be able to chose one night ability for balancing purposes. Assassin would not be able to Assassinate and 2-for-1 for balancing purposes. Possessor would not be able to use Puppet Strings and Possess in the same night for balancing purposes. Sorcerer would not be able to use Magic Missile and Circle of Death in the same night for balancing purposes.</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities</strong></p>
<p><em>Hypnotic Rest</em> - The An ability that makes the target appear as sleeping to those who visit. While it does not make them immune from harmful abilities or death, it does make them Occupy Immune, allowing them to carry out their deeds as necessary. Similar to the current Magic Barrier, but has less impact than CW’s day ability and other night ability are much stronger. This has infinite uses.</p>
<p><em>Thaumaturgical Cloak</em> - This garment protect the wearer from conversion or attack. The magic in this cloak wares off, however, dissipating the effect. In other terms, this is a spell that protects any player from conversion for 2 nights, or 1 attack, whichever comes first. The CW will have 2 uses of this and is mainly here for a all-around protection of himself and his fellow BD. Can be cast on self.</p>
<p>Shaman (Sage)</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities</strong></p>
<p><em>Hypnotic Rest</em> - An ability that makes the target appear as sleeping to those who visit. While it does not make them immune from harmful abilities or death, it does make them Occupy Immune, allowing them to carry out their deeds as necessary. Similar to the current Magic Barrier, but has less impact than CW’s day ability and other night ability are much stronger. This has infinite uses.</p>
<p><em>Conjure Weapon</em> - An ability that guarantees a kill to the Assassin no matter the guards nor heals on a random target. Cannot target King. CW is a very supportive class, and Unseen already has countless things to allow MM to stay alive and to mess with other BD’s. I think allowing the Assassin one guaranteed kill would make for an easier job when it comes to those super priority targets especially with the added fun of RNG.</p>
<p>A lot of these suggestions were just fun stuff or things I thought needed to be implemented into the game as defense mechanisms against the stronger classes (At least in my opinion).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54792-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/court-wizard-rework-suggestions-maximyss/54792.rss">Court Wizard Rework Suggestions - Maximyss</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
