<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827</link>
    <description>The past patches have been improving regarding reducing automatic confirmation such as the Butler&#39;s poisoning, but for the most part the game&#39;s mechanical confirmation is still too dominant, so here are a few of my ideas to further minimize it.

_**1. Generalize the feedback from Butlers and Drunks.**_

Similarly to the changes FoL has made. Right now for most games evils that are occupy-immune such as the Possessor and Sorcerer are essentially forced to claim a class that also has immunity to occupation as you&#39;re dead if someone attempts to redirect or occupy you. And now with barrier gone there is additionally one less excuse as to why a person found you to be occupy immune. To add, even without feedback Drunks and Butlers would still have their utility in occupying and redirecting people.

As a secondary approach to minimizing confirmation from Butlers and Drunks, only non-BD aligned occupation immune classes will be told that someone attempted and failed to occupy or redirect in the same vein as the Mastermind&#39;s passive. BD members will still be informed that their abilities were prevented or redirected if they were not immune to occupation.



For the [color = &quot;steblue&quot;]**Blue Dragon**[/color].
&gt;	**Dutiful** (Passive) - Immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.

&gt;	**I am the Liquor** (Passive) - Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.

&gt;**Unstoppable** (Passive) - Immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.

&gt;**Isolation** (Passive) - Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.

For the [color = &quot;purple&quot;]**Unseen**[/color].

&gt;**Can&#39;t Touch This** (Passive)- Immune to occupation, target changing and death at night. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would&#39;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.

For the [color = &quot;red&quot;]**Cult**[/color].

&gt;**Fanatic** (Passive)- 	Immune to Occupation and target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would&#39;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.

For [color = &quot;grey&quot;]**Neutrals**[/color].

&gt;**Trickery** (Passive) -	Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would&#39;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.

&gt;**Resolve** (Passive) - Immune to death at night, occupation and target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would&#39;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.

&gt;**Contracted** (Passive) - Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would&#39;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.

&gt;**Driven** (Passive) - 	Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would&#39;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.

&gt;**Mage Armor** (Passive) - Immune to death at night, occupation, target changing, poison and bleeding. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would&#39;ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.

_**2. Add in a drawback to stepping up with Royal Blood.**_

As of right now there is no reason for royalty not to step up as there is simply no drawback to it while giving the benefit of automatically confirming yourself as a Princess, Noble, or Drunk. In the current meta it is downright impossible to claim a royal class without Royal Blood as when the starting King dies, it automatically confirms all starting claims while at the same time outing the fakes. There needs to be a drawback to stepping up as right now there is nothing to dissuade people from stepping up to confirm themselves, which outs everyone else as either a fake-claim or a newbie player. My idea here would be to prevent players who fail their bid from voting and counting as part of the majority for the day and role-block them for the night as this will add some reasoning for players not to step up and as an excuse for fake-claims. 

&gt;**Royal Blood** (Passive) - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King. If you step up as royalty and fail the bid then you cannot vote for the remainder of the day, you will not count towards majority, and you will be occupied for the coming night.

_**3. Increase the limit of the same non-unique classes appearing to three, but at a reduced chance.**_

This really applies only to Physicians, Sheriffs, and Paladins. Duplicates of these classes appear too damn often to the point that it&#39;s nigh-impossible to fake-claim one on the long term as most games already have two spawning. This essentially will end with you dead as the existence of a third claim means that one of the claimers are evil. The idea behind this is to add a small chance that a third Physician or Sheriff class is a genuine class and to discourage players from executing purely on claims alone as the possibility of three of the same class spawning essentially reduces the viability of executing solely on class claim and allows these common classes to be used as long-term fakeclaims.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:45:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes but give a buff to BD I want a buff to duchess!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70827-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827.rss">A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even if Duchess doesn’t have the ability to sacrifice her royal blood, it wouldn’t detract from the purpose which is to provide a plausible reason for a royal claim not being able to step up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70827-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827.rss">A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How would that work on duchess tho</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70827-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827.rss">A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<ol start="2">
<li>Add in a drawback to stepping up with Royal Blood.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
<p>I agree that royal blood confirmation is a problem but I think you have proposed only one possible way of dealing with it, and it might be quite frustrating to peeps who lost the bid for kingship.  Someone had suggested replacing Princess wisp with some powerful ability that came at the cost of her royal blood.  I like this idea and I think its essence could be implemented in this way:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Dérogeance (Day ability)</strong> - Sacrifice your royal blood in order to buff your abilities tonight. (1 use)</p>
<p>If you are Princess, your Flirt will tell exact class type, and Wisp will tell ability type.<br>
If you are Drunk, your debauch will bypass redirection immunity and, along with happy hour, can target King.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I chose a fancy name because I wanted to be historically accurate <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Noble could not have this ability because he already has two day abilities.  But since he’s instantly confirmable during the day, it shouldn’t really matter.  Not being able to confirm himself with royal blood would make no difference.</p>
<p><strong>EDIT</strong> I figure instead it’d be much simpler to just lose royal blood upon using your second ability (happy hour, flirt, gossip).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70827-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827.rss">A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The past patches have been improving regarding reducing automatic confirmation such as the Butler’s poisoning, but for the most part the game’s mechanical confirmation is still too dominant, so here are a few of my ideas to further minimize it.</p>
<p><em><strong>1. Generalize the feedback from Butlers and Drunks.</strong></em></p>
<p>Similarly to the changes FoL has made. Right now for most games evils that are occupy-immune such as the Possessor and Sorcerer are essentially forced to claim a class that also has immunity to occupation as you’re dead if someone attempts to redirect or occupy you. And now with barrier gone there is additionally one less excuse as to why a person found you to be occupy immune. To add, even without feedback Drunks and Butlers would still have their utility in occupying and redirecting people.</p>
<p>As a secondary approach to minimizing confirmation from Butlers and Drunks, only non-BD aligned occupation immune classes will be told that someone attempted and failed to occupy or redirect in the same vein as the Mastermind’s passive. BD members will still be informed that their abilities were prevented or redirected if they were not immune to occupation.</p>
<p>For the <font color="steblue"><strong>Blue Dragon</strong></font>.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Dutiful</strong> (Passive) - Immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>I am the Liquor</strong> (Passive) - Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Unstoppable</strong> (Passive) - Immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Isolation</strong> (Passive) - Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. The user will not be notified if another player attempted and failed to occupy or redirect them.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>For the <font color="purple"><strong>Unseen</strong></font>.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Can’t Touch This</strong> (Passive)- Immune to occupation, target changing and death at night. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would’ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>For the <font color="red"><strong>Cult</strong></font>.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Fanatic</strong> (Passive)- 	Immune to Occupation and target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would’ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>For <font color="grey"><strong>Neutrals</strong></font>.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Trickery</strong> (Passive) -	Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would’ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Resolve</strong> (Passive) - Immune to death at night, occupation and target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would’ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Contracted</strong> (Passive) - Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would’ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Driven</strong> (Passive) - 	Immune to occupation at night and immune to target changing. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would’ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Mage Armor</strong> (Passive) - Immune to death at night, occupation, target changing, poison and bleeding. Additionally, you will be notified if anyone attempted to occupy you who you would’ve been redirected to if a player attempts to change your target.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><em><strong>2. Add in a drawback to stepping up with Royal Blood.</strong></em></p>
<p>As of right now there is no reason for royalty not to step up as there is simply no drawback to it while giving the benefit of automatically confirming yourself as a Princess, Noble, or Drunk. In the current meta it is downright impossible to claim a royal class without Royal Blood as when the starting King dies, it automatically confirms all starting claims while at the same time outing the fakes. There needs to be a drawback to stepping up as right now there is nothing to dissuade people from stepping up to confirm themselves, which outs everyone else as either a fake-claim or a newbie player. My idea here would be to prevent players who fail their bid from voting and counting as part of the majority for the day and role-block them for the night as this will add some reasoning for players not to step up and as an excuse for fake-claims.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Royal Blood</strong> (Passive) - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King. If you step up as royalty and fail the bid then you cannot vote for the remainder of the day, you will not count towards majority, and you will be occupied for the coming night.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><em><strong>3. Increase the limit of the same non-unique classes appearing to three, but at a reduced chance.</strong></em></p>
<p>This really applies only to Physicians, Sheriffs, and Paladins. Duplicates of these classes appear too damn often to the point that it’s nigh-impossible to fake-claim one on the long term as most games already have two spawning. This essentially will end with you dead as the existence of a third claim means that one of the claimers are evil. The idea behind this is to add a small chance that a third Physician or Sheriff class is a genuine class and to discourage players from executing purely on claims alone as the possibility of three of the same class spawning essentially reduces the viability of executing solely on class claim and allows these common classes to be used as long-term fakeclaims.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 22:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70827-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/a-few-ideas-to-reduce-mechanical-confirmation/70827.rss">A Few Ideas to Reduce Mechanical Confirmation</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
