<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Prince</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471</link>
    <description>This goes here: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Prince

Lore: The Prince

Lore Subject: The Prince of Adiart

While none would care to admit it the Prince wields a terrible power within the court. While the Princess maintains the good relations with the civilians and nobles the Prince holds power within the castle second to none but his father. First in line to the throne the kings guards hold a fierce loyalty towards him and the Black Rose despise his presence. The Prince is the symbol of the power of the court and the fiercest of Blue Dragon&#39;s protection. Like the Princess the Prince has the power to weed out the corruption within the court but unlike his more subtle sister he cannot discern friend from foe so easily as while she instils confidence and hope he provides the fear of cold death at his hands. Might makes right is the motto of the Prince and he will regularly take upon the role of inquisitor to keep the rest of the court in check sometimes going so far as to question his own father and sisters motives. Make no mistake the Prince lives for the good of the Blue Dragons and will gladly take up the mantle of king should he be in a better position to see Justice done or perhaps so he has better means of escaping the assassins that pursue him in his quest to make his home a real sanctuary from evil. Now if only there was a better way of knowing who to execute...

As a child the prince was given a gem in his crown giving him immunity from the temptation of others. The only ideals the Prince will follow are those he wishes, and he wishes for the safety of the court.This gives him the added benefit of being immune to the temptation of the Black rose. It is only because of this the prince can be trusted with the power he wields in his crusade against evil even if he is still  viable to human error.

Comments: 
Again I wanted to tie the royals together through their abilities as I set up the Prince and Princess as opposing ideals here. I also wanted to maintain his classes limited ability to understand who is bad. I also wanted to try to give an explanation as to why he cannot be converted to black rose and the princess can. This ruled out a royal blood explanation but I feel a Macguffin may work just as well</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 20:56:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Prince</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d use training as a reason. After all you want to make sure your successor is trustworthy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 20:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-471-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Prince</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Prince</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This goes here: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Prince" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Prince</a></p>
<p>Lore: The Prince</p>
<p>Lore Subject: The Prince of Adiart</p>
<p>While none would care to admit it the Prince wields a terrible power within the court. While the Princess maintains the good relations with the civilians and nobles the Prince holds power within the castle second to none but his father. First in line to the throne the kings guards hold a fierce loyalty towards him and the Black Rose despise his presence. The Prince is the symbol of the power of the court and the fiercest of Blue Dragon’s protection. Like the Princess the Prince has the power to weed out the corruption within the court but unlike his more subtle sister he cannot discern friend from foe so easily as while she instils confidence and hope he provides the fear of cold death at his hands. Might makes right is the motto of the Prince and he will regularly take upon the role of inquisitor to keep the rest of the court in check sometimes going so far as to question his own father and sisters motives. Make no mistake the Prince lives for the good of the Blue Dragons and will gladly take up the mantle of king should he be in a better position to see Justice done or perhaps so he has better means of escaping the assassins that pursue him in his quest to make his home a real sanctuary from evil. Now if only there was a better way of knowing who to execute…</p>
<p>As a child the prince was given a gem in his crown giving him immunity from the temptation of others. The only ideals the Prince will follow are those he wishes, and he wishes for the safety of the court.This gives him the added benefit of being immune to the temptation of the Black rose. It is only because of this the prince can be trusted with the power he wields in his crusade against evil even if he is still  viable to human error.</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
Again I wanted to tie the royals together through their abilities as I set up the Prince and Princess as opposing ideals here. I also wanted to maintain his classes limited ability to understand who is bad. I also wanted to try to give an explanation as to why he cannot be converted to black rose and the princess can. This ruled out a royal blood explanation but I feel a Macguffin may work just as well</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 12:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-471-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-prince/471.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Prince</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
