<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774</link>
    <description>_**The Court Wizard**_

**Day Ability:**
**Arcane Surge**: Empowers the target, allowing their abilities to target an additional person the following night. Usable only once and will fail if used on the King, Mystic, or Prince. The target will not be notified of being empowered until the night begins. This ability will have no effect if the target uses an ability that naturally hits two targets, only targets the user, or has no target. Can be used on the Court Wizard themselves to target two players with Thaumaturgic Barrier or Thaumaturgic Mirror.

_Reasoning: A powerful and potentially game-changing single-use day ability that will further the Court Wizard’s support function and allow them to make-or-break the game based on their decision-making skills. Arcane Surge is a powerful last-ditch attempt to help Blue Dragon by allowing almost any role to use their abilities on two targets on one single night, such as allowing a Paladin to Smite two different targets at once or allowing the Knight to Cold Steel two suspected evils on a single night. Arcane Surge is not a reliable mean of confirming a Court Wizard claim as it cannot be used on easily-confirmed BDs such as Prince or Mystic, ergo requiring a trusted third-party not to lie about the Arcane Surge&#39;s effects, and also requires a night for its effects to take place. Arcane Surge is also a double-edge sword as if it is used on an Evil killer role it will allow them to kill two targets at once, or if used on the Mastermind or Cult Leader, allow them to convert two players at once._ 

**Night Ability:**
**Thaumaturgic Barrier**: Protects the target from negative effects. Same as previous Magic Barrier, except this Barrier also protects from the Sorcerer’s Magic Dust, the Scorned’s Framing, the Herbalist’s Drug, the Hunter’s Wolf Companion, the Possessor’s Puppet Strings, and will block the Possessor’s Possess. During the following day, the Thaumaturgic Barrier has a lingering effect that will also protect the target from Poisoning and Bleeding, the Assassin’s Distract, the Reaper’s Chill, the Invoker’s Bewilder, and Troll Boxes from either Scorned or Fool. Infinite uses.

QoL Change: If no night-effects were blocked by the Thaumaturgic Barrier, the feedback will appear to the Court Wizard.

_Reasoning: Ultimately, the main reason that the Court Wizard is such a boring class is because its main use ability has little to no effect in the gameplay. While they can block converts, this usually requires a mixture of predictive abilities and the right circumstances for it, so most of the time the Magic Barrier will only block effects from Drunks and Butlers, which are BD classes themselves. In order for the Court Wizard to make a stronger impact in the game, he should be able to block more negative effects from Evil and Neutral classes as well. The lingering effect will also be added to make barrier a more viable ability, however for the sake of keeping the Court Wizard as a scum claim they will not be able to block common BD day abilities like the Noble’s Political Pressure as this will cause them to be easily provable._

**Thaumaturgic Mirror**: If a player attempts to use their ability on the target, the ability will be reflected back to them, resulting in the player using the ability on themselves. This ability bypasses immunity to target changing. Two uses.

_Reasoning: A reworked Tornado with the focus of being a more defensive ability. The current Tornado rarely has game changing moments and is currently used more as a form to confirm the Court Wizard rather than making plays. Plus, the fact that 2 of the 3 NKs along with the MM are occ-immune makes Tornado a very underwhelming ability. Thaumaturgic Mirror’s primary usage will be to reflect attacks back to their attackers while also protecting the target from conversions, and its limited usage will make it an ability more focused on defending BD rather than confirming the Court Wizard._

Ultimately, the focus of my rework is to make the CW a more stronger all-around supporting role without diminishing its value as an evil claim. Thaumaturgic Barrier now has more uses rather than only stopping conversions, especially as it also becomes an invaluable tool against Neutral Killers. Thaumaturgic Mirror is also a less chaotic version of Tornado and also protects its target against incoming attacks, even if their attackers are occ-immune. Finally, Arcane Surge works as strong offensive support ability that needs to be used carefully and cannot be used solely as a means of confirmation.

_**Sage**_

Replace Tornado with an infinite-use Thaumaturgic Mirror.

_**Ritualist**_

Replace Teleportation with Mirror of Corax. Mirror of Corax works the same as teleportation, but if the Ritualist selects only a single target then the effect of Thaumaturgic Mirror will apply.

_Reasoning: A few loose ends I had to tie. This had to be done to allow converted CWs to keep their claim intact. Plus Thaumaturgic Mirror can also reflect CS and prevented investigative roles to target Unseen/Cult members._</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:13:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh my bad lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54774-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774.rss">Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shrimpy" data-post="3" data-topic="54774" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/shrimpy/40/15828_2.png" class="avatar"> Shrimpy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ritualist</p>
<p>Replace Teleportation</p>
<p>no!  teleportation is one of the Cult’s most useful abilities</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<blockquote>
<p>Replace Teleportation with Mirror of Corax. Mirror of Corax works the same as teleportation, but if the Ritualist selects only a single target then the effect of Thaumaturgic Mirror will apply.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I’m not removing Teleportation. I’m just renaming and adding a secondary effect that can be triggered if the Ritualist only selects one target.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54774-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774.rss">Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p><strong>Ritualist</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Replace Teleportation</p>
</blockquote>
<p>no!  teleportation is one of the Cult’s most useful abilities</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 03:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54774-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774.rss">Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tornado is my fav</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 02:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54774-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774.rss">Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em><strong>The Court Wizard</strong></em></p>
<p><strong>Day Ability:</strong><br>
<strong>Arcane Surge</strong>: Empowers the target, allowing their abilities to target an additional person the following night. Usable only once and will fail if used on the King, Mystic, or Prince. The target will not be notified of being empowered until the night begins. This ability will have no effect if the target uses an ability that naturally hits two targets, only targets the user, or has no target. Can be used on the Court Wizard themselves to target two players with Thaumaturgic Barrier or Thaumaturgic Mirror.</p>
<p><em>Reasoning: A powerful and potentially game-changing single-use day ability that will further the Court Wizard’s support function and allow them to make-or-break the game based on their decision-making skills. Arcane Surge is a powerful last-ditch attempt to help Blue Dragon by allowing almost any role to use their abilities on two targets on one single night, such as allowing a Paladin to Smite two different targets at once or allowing the Knight to Cold Steel two suspected evils on a single night. Arcane Surge is not a reliable mean of confirming a Court Wizard claim as it cannot be used on easily-confirmed BDs such as Prince or Mystic, ergo requiring a trusted third-party not to lie about the Arcane Surge’s effects, and also requires a night for its effects to take place. Arcane Surge is also a double-edge sword as if it is used on an Evil killer role it will allow them to kill two targets at once, or if used on the Mastermind or Cult Leader, allow them to convert two players at once.</em></p>
<p><strong>Night Ability:</strong><br>
<strong>Thaumaturgic Barrier</strong>: Protects the target from negative effects. Same as previous Magic Barrier, except this Barrier also protects from the Sorcerer’s Magic Dust, the Scorned’s Framing, the Herbalist’s Drug, the Hunter’s Wolf Companion, the Possessor’s Puppet Strings, and will block the Possessor’s Possess. During the following day, the Thaumaturgic Barrier has a lingering effect that will also protect the target from Poisoning and Bleeding, the Assassin’s Distract, the Reaper’s Chill, the Invoker’s Bewilder, and Troll Boxes from either Scorned or Fool. Infinite uses.</p>
<p>QoL Change: If no night-effects were blocked by the Thaumaturgic Barrier, the feedback will appear to the Court Wizard.</p>
<p><em>Reasoning: Ultimately, the main reason that the Court Wizard is such a boring class is because its main use ability has little to no effect in the gameplay. While they can block converts, this usually requires a mixture of predictive abilities and the right circumstances for it, so most of the time the Magic Barrier will only block effects from Drunks and Butlers, which are BD classes themselves. In order for the Court Wizard to make a stronger impact in the game, he should be able to block more negative effects from Evil and Neutral classes as well. The lingering effect will also be added to make barrier a more viable ability, however for the sake of keeping the Court Wizard as a scum claim they will not be able to block common BD day abilities like the Noble’s Political Pressure as this will cause them to be easily provable.</em></p>
<p><strong>Thaumaturgic Mirror</strong>: If a player attempts to use their ability on the target, the ability will be reflected back to them, resulting in the player using the ability on themselves. This ability bypasses immunity to target changing. Two uses.</p>
<p><em>Reasoning: A reworked Tornado with the focus of being a more defensive ability. The current Tornado rarely has game changing moments and is currently used more as a form to confirm the Court Wizard rather than making plays. Plus, the fact that 2 of the 3 NKs along with the MM are occ-immune makes Tornado a very underwhelming ability. Thaumaturgic Mirror’s primary usage will be to reflect attacks back to their attackers while also protecting the target from conversions, and its limited usage will make it an ability more focused on defending BD rather than confirming the Court Wizard.</em></p>
<p>Ultimately, the focus of my rework is to make the CW a more stronger all-around supporting role without diminishing its value as an evil claim. Thaumaturgic Barrier now has more uses rather than only stopping conversions, especially as it also becomes an invaluable tool against Neutral Killers. Thaumaturgic Mirror is also a less chaotic version of Tornado and also protects its target against incoming attacks, even if their attackers are occ-immune. Finally, Arcane Surge works as strong offensive support ability that needs to be used carefully and cannot be used solely as a means of confirmation.</p>
<p><em><strong>Sage</strong></em></p>
<p>Replace Tornado with an infinite-use Thaumaturgic Mirror.</p>
<p><em><strong>Ritualist</strong></em></p>
<p>Replace Teleportation with Mirror of Corax. Mirror of Corax works the same as teleportation, but if the Ritualist selects only a single target then the effect of Thaumaturgic Mirror will apply.</p>
<p><em>Reasoning: A few loose ends I had to tie. This had to be done to allow converted CWs to keep their claim intact. Plus Thaumaturgic Mirror can also reflect CS and prevented investigative roles to target Unseen/Cult members.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 02:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54774-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/saruns-court-wizard-rework-entry/54774.rss">Sarun&#39;s Court Wizard Rework Entry</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
