<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907</link>
    <description>&lt;big&gt;**FM: Ghost Town**&lt;/big&gt;

### Rules
1. Follow the [Global Forum Rules](http://forum.imperium42.com/t/global-forum-rules-please-read-first/244)
2. Be respectful to the moderators and your fellow players.
3. Don&#39;t be inactive. If you do not post meaningfully on any given day, you will be prodded. Receiving two prods will result in your removal from the game.
4. Do not quote/screenshot private host messages.
5. Don&#39;t throw the game. Always play with the intent of helping your faction win.
6. No editing or deleting posts without express moderator permission.
7. No posting after majority is reached or at night. We won&#39;t lock the thread, and instead the honor system will be used. Repeated or egregious failure to comply will result in your removal from the game.
8. It&#39;s a game - have fun!
9. **Do not talk about the game outside of officially sanctioned channels.** This applies even if you&#39;re dead, even if the person you&#39;re talking to isn&#39;t playing, and even if you think that there&#39;s no way it could possibly have any effect on the game. Just don&#39;t do it. At all.

### Gameplay
- This is a mostly open game. The exception is that there is one bastard mechanic that is closed. I will tell you only that it concerns the dead.
- Due to this mechanic, there will be no spectating allowed.
- Days will last up to 24 hours.
- Nights will last roughly 12 hours.
- Actions are performed by sending myself and Icibalus a message on the PM I send you with your role card.

### Executions
- To accuse someone, say &quot;**/vote [player]**&quot;.
- To rescind your vote, say &quot;**/unvote [player]**&quot;.
- To vote for no lynch, say &quot;&quot;**/vote NoLynch**&quot;.
- Making your vote obvious (bolded, on their own line, etc.) will make it less likely to be missed by us.
- Vote counts will be given whenever the moderators are available to do so. You may request one by pinging both Icibalus and myself.
- Days 1 and 2 will have a deadline lynch - whoever has the most votes when the timer expires will be lynched.
- Days 3 and on will have a plurality lynch - if majority is reached on a player, the day will end immediately with their lynch, but if majority isn&#39;t reached whoever has the most votes when the timer expires will be lynched.
- If majority has been reached, stop posting immediately. Repeated or egregious failure to comply may result in a modkill.

### After The Night
- You will be told what happened to you in your PM, and day will begin.

### Journals and Death Notes
- There will  be no journals or death notes.

### Rolelist
- **[color=#00bF00]Town Investigative[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Town Protective[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Town Killing[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Town Support[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Random Town[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Random Town[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Citizen[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Citizen[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Citizen[/color]**
- **[color=#00bF00]Citizen[/color]**
- **[color=red]Mafia Head[/color]**
- **[color=red]Mafia Tactical/Support[/color]**
- **[color=red]Random Mafia[/color]**
- **[color=grey]Neutral Evil/Benign[/color]**
- **[color=grey]Neutral Killing[/color]**

### Role Cards

---

[details=&quot;Town&quot;]

[details=&quot;Investigative&quot;]

[details=&quot;Sheriff&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Sheriff[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Investigative**
&gt;
&gt;You are the Sheriff in this town and your role is to enforce the law.
&gt;
&gt;Every night you have the ability to investigate one town member to see if they&#39;re up to anything suspicious.
If your target is a member of the Mafia, a Serial Killer, or a Stalker you will know.
However, the Godfather, the Arsonist, and the Bomber hide their tracks too well and will appear as not suspicious to you.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Lookout&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Lookout[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Investigative**
&gt;
&gt;You are a sharp eyed-individual that can recognize people from afar.
In the past people would pay you to watch over them to make sure that nobody would enter or leave their residence unnoticed.
However, since the Mafia invasion, you have decided to use your skills to help eliminate the Mafia.
&gt;
&gt;You may watch one person each night.
You will see who visits that person each night, should someone visit.
You may not watch yourself and you will not know the roles of the visitors, only that they visited.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Investigator&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Investigator[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Investigative**
&gt;
&gt;You&#39;re an inspector, particularly admired for you comparisons between criminals and forming connections among suspects. Always ready for a challenge, you&#39;re excited to see what these petty lowlifes bring to the table.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may question a player.When you question a player you will be informed if they have a connection to the previously questioned player or not. If they are connected then they are of the same alignment (Town, Mafia, Neutral).`
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Spy&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Spy[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Investigative**
&gt;
&gt;You are an agent working out of this town, so you&#39;ve got a keen mind when it comes to tracking. Using it to see what everyone is up to at night could help find the killers.
&gt;
&gt;Every night you may target a player and see who they visited if anyone.
&gt;
&gt;Once per game, you may use a supersensor, allowing you to see who was visited by the Mafia that night.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Protective&quot;]

[details=&quot;Doctor&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Doctor[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Protective**
&gt;
&gt;You are this town&#39;s doctor, and have kept everybody healthy for years.
&gt;
&gt;You have the ability to visit one person each night. If they are attacked that night, you arrive just in time to save their life.
If your target is attacked, both you and your target will receive a message saying your target was attacked but healed.
You also have 1 self-heal, allowing you to instead save yourself if you are attacked.
You can only use the self-heal once, regardless of if you are attacked or not that night, so use it wisely.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Bodyguard&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Bodyguard[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Protective**
&gt;
&gt;You are a trained bodyguard, capable of throwing yourself into harm&#39;s way to save your client.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you can choose one player to protect.
If your target is attacked, both you and the attacker die instead.
If you successfully protect someone, you can&#39;t be saved from death.
Your counterattack ignores night immunity.
You also have 1 bulletproof vest. If somebody tries to attack you when you wear a bulletproof vest, they will receive a message saying that you were immune.
However, you can only use this vest for one night, so choose wisely.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Jailor&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Jailor[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Protective**
&gt;
&gt;Once a figurehead of the law, you experienced a horrific accident and have vowed not to kill anymore. Instead you decide to use your presence as a deterrent to these thugs that have rooted themselves in your hometown.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may choose to follow a player. Your presence scares one malicious person from targeting them.
You will only be informed if you scare away a role who had killing intentions.
Should your target be visited by multiple people with malicious intent, only one will flee.
Roles that use charges will still consume them upon being frightened off. 
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Killing&quot;]

[details=&quot;Vigilante&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Vigilante[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Killing**
&gt;
&gt;You believe that the law of this town is useless against the evil-doers in your town and have decided to take matters into your own hands.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may decide to shoot and kill one town member you believe to be evil.
However, if the person you shoot turns out to be Town, you will be overcome with grief and vow never to shoot again.
You only have 3 bullets, allowing you to perform your night action up to 3 times. Make them count.
You may not shoot on the first night.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Veteran&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Veteran[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Killing**
&gt;
&gt;You&#39;re a war-hardened soldier who is living out his retirement in the small and calm town of Salem.
But your retirement is short-lived, as people begin dying when the Mafia comes to town.
Luckily you still have your gun with you and you can use it to go on alert, killing anyone who comes to your house that night.
&gt;
&gt;Going on alert makes you kill [b]anybody[/b] who comes to your house that night, both evil and good, so use this power carefully or you will do more harm than good.
This can also kill people who are normally night immune, like the Godfather, Serial Killer, and Arsonist.
You are immune to attacks, douses, stalking, and any other harmful night actions while on alert.
You can go on alert only 3 times throughout the game.
You are immune to being roleblocked.
This role is unique - there can only be one of you.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Firebrand&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Firebrand[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Killing**
&gt;
&gt;Flames burn ruthlessly and so does your drive to save this town. No price is too high, and you only have one shot; so you&#39;re determined to make this count.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may douse a player in gasoline.
You may also ignite all of your doused targets, however you may only ignite once so choice your actions wisely.
Your method of killing ignores night immunity and appears identical to the Arsonist&#39;s methods.
The Arsonist cannot ignite your targets, nor can you ignite theirs.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Support&quot;]

[details=&quot;Escort&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Escort[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Support**
&gt;
&gt;You are this town&#39;s escort, usually providing various pleasures in exchange for money.
But, now that evil people are overrunning this town, you decide to use your &quot;skills&quot; to help the town.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you can choose one player to visit.
You will spend the night with your target, who will be too busy to use their role that night, effectively roleblocking them.
Your target will be informed that they were roleblocked.
However, if the person you visit turns out to be a Serial Killer, you become the Serial Killer&#39;s target instead of their intended target.
You are immune to being roleblocked.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Transporter&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Transporter[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Support**
&gt;
&gt;Your job is to move people, no questions asked.
Not only that, but you are very good at it!
You swap two people during the night in the hopes of saving the lives of your fellow innocent town members.
&gt;
&gt;Every night you may transport two people.
The two people will be notified that they were transported.
Any actions against the two people will be swapped. This includes investigations, killings, and being controlled by a witch.
You may not transport yourself.
You are immune to being controlled by a witch.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Retributionist&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Retributionist[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Support**
&gt;
&gt;One of extraordinary conviction, you are determined that there&#39;ll be hell to pay for those killing your fellow citizens.
&gt;
&gt;At night you may choose to remember any non-unique Town role.
You will assume this role the next night. 
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Citizen&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#00bF00]Citizen[/color]
&gt;**[color=#00bF00]Town[/color] Citizen**
&gt;
&gt;You don&#39;t have any special ability and just try to live your life in peace.
&gt;
&gt;Each day you get to vote in an attempt to remove the Mafia from the community.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

---

[details=&quot;Mafia&quot;]

[details=&quot;Head&quot;]

[details=&quot;Godfather&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Godfather[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Head**
&gt;
&gt;You are the lord of crime in this town and have decided that it belongs to the Mafia.
You try to achieve this by systematically killing off one of the citizens each night.
&gt;
&gt;You are unkillable at night. If somebody tries to attack you, they will receive a message saying that you were immune.
As the leader of the Mafia every other member will report to you what happened to them each night
If you are interrogated by a Sheriff, you will appear to be &quot;Not Suspicious&quot;.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Caporegime&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Caporegime[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Head**
&gt;
&gt;A trusted and loyal lieutenant to the influential Godfather. Not being a fan of the killing part, you instead prefer to read and book keep the mafia&#39;s earnings sending your goons to perform the will of the Mafia. For operations such as these you push aside your disgust and instead remind the goons just why you&#39;re in charge around here.
&gt;
&gt;You may target a member in your team at night, retraining them into another Mafia role of your choosing. The player who is being retrained is roleblocked even through immunity if the retraining succeeds. However, should you be retraining yourself this will be ignored.
Should this ability succeed then you must wait an additional night until you may retrain again.
You may not promote players into unique roles, even if they are already an unique role.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Enforcer&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Enforcer[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Head**
&gt;
&gt;You&#39;ve arrived at your destination, at last you will take charge of your own team of Mafiosi. Initially recruited for having an exceptional eye for detail. Finesse that some people miss, you are able to duplicate with near perfection soon after. The Godfather very much appreciated your talents, but told you that you still had much to learn. Honing your innate ability and communication skills over the years you&#39;ve worked hard to prove yourself, today is finally the day you will show that you are worthy of your gift.
&gt;
&gt;As long as you are alive, the Mafia may secretly communicate during the day.
Once each night you may target a member of the Mafia and a person not aligned with the Mafia. Should either role be visited that night by a role which has a directly helpful or harmful ability, you will copy that role and perform its action on your second target, or vice versa. You will do this for all actions being carried out on your targets that night, including self-targeting abilities other than Veteran alerts.
You may not target yourself.
This ability ignores transports and if one of the targets is Witched, the second target will be forced to visit the same player as the first. The Spy will not see which member of the Mafia you visit, but they may see which member of the Town you visit.
You may communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Tactical&quot;]

[details=&quot;Mafioso&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Mafioso[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Tactical**
&gt;
&gt;You&#39;re a goon, following your Godfather&#39;s every command.
It&#39;s not all bad though, because when a higher placement opens up in the Mafia you&#39;ll be the first to take it.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may choose 1 member of the Mafia to shadow. You will carry out their job that night on any target you wish.
You may only do this once per player in the Mafia.
Shadowing a Mafia Head role only grants you their specific passive(s). Night immunity is not applicable.
If a member of the Mafia dies you may permanently assume that role if you wish at any time.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Blackmailer&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Blackmailer[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Tactical**
&gt;
&gt;Everyone who knows you doesn&#39;t want anything to do with you, but typically it&#39;s too late by then. Heck, even among the Mafia you are given the cold shoulder. With a smile almost creepily plastered on your face all the time, you have an unhealthy obsession with your job more so than any other member, and that&#39;s just what the Godfather wanted. You are the Blackmailer.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may visit a single player&#39;s house, you are informed of what roles also visit them.
Each day you can send three anonymous messages to any player. The player may send a message back if they wish.
Anonymous messages are limited to 200 characters.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Disguiser&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Disguiser[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Tactical**
&gt;
&gt;You are a master of disguise, hired for jobs like these for your ability to get people into places they otherwise wouldn&#39;t be able to access.
&gt;
&gt; Three times per game, you may target a member of the Mafia, causing their night action to ignore all protection, redirection, and roleblocks. You may only enable a kill in this fashion once.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Support&quot;]

[details=&quot;Consort&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Consort[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Support**
&gt;
&gt;You were once an escort, giving away services to give your client&#39;s pleasure in exchange for money.
You hated it, however, and felt used every night.
Once the mafia came into town, you didn&#39;t hesitate one moment and managed to join them, offering to use your &quot;skills&quot; to distract townsfolk while each and every one of them was murdered.
&gt;
&gt;Every night you can choose to target one player.
You&#39;ll distract them that night, roleblocking them.
Your target will be informed that they were roleblocked.
However, if the person you visit turns out to be a Serial Killer, you become the Serial Killer&#39;s target instead of their intended target.
You are immune to being roleblocked.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]


[details=&quot;Consigliere&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Consigliere[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Support**
&gt;
&gt;You were a successful investigator in your early days. However, you quickly learned that playing fair doesn&#39;t pay and when the Godfather approached you and asked for you to join them, your choice was easy.
These days, you work as a Consigliere for the Mafia, figuring out what role every person plays in a town to help them make quick work of the towns they take over.
&gt;
&gt;Every night you can choose to target one player.
You&#39;ll investigate them that night, finding out their exact role.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]


[details=&quot;Osservatore&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Osservatore[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Support**
&gt;
&gt;You were a brilliant Spy in your early days, one of the best in the country. However, on one mission you were captured - by the Godfather.
To your great surprise, he wanted to help you retire after all your years of service. The deal was simple. Use your talents to collect sensitive information from the townsfolk and he will rule to grant you whatever you want in this silly little town.
&gt;
&gt;You may watch one person each night.
You will see who they visited, if anyone, as well as who visited them, should someone visit.
You may not watch yourself and you will not know the roles of the visitors, only that they visited.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Deception&quot;]

[details=&quot;Janitor&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Janitor[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Deception**
&gt;
&gt;You are a janitor, hired by the mafia for your skilled method of cleaning crime scenes.
You can clean a crime scene, hiding the role of somebody who died that night.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you can choose to clean a player. If that player dies that night, their role won&#39;t be revealed to the town upon death. However, you WILL see what their role is.
It doesn&#39;t matter who kills your target or what side your target is on, the only thing that matters is that they die that night for your skill to work.
If your target doesn&#39;t die, it will still use up one of your cleanings.
You can only choose to clean a target 3 times during the entire game.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Framer&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Framer[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Deception**
&gt;
&gt;You are a framer, skilled at forging documents.
With your skill, the Mafia was glad to hire you in exchange for your services.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you have the ability to frame one player of your choice. If they&#39;re inspected by the Sheriff or Investigator that night, it&#39;ll say they&#39;re a Mafia member. They will appear to visit the target of the Mafia kill to a Lookout or Spy.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Hypnotist&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Hypnotist[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Deception**
&gt;
&gt;You are the Hypnotist, a master of the inner workings of the mind. You use your skills to daze and confuse those who stand in your way.
&gt;
&gt;Every night you can choose to target 1 player.
Your target&#39;s real night results will be replaced with a false night result of your choosing.
The effect you choose will not actually be done; For example, an investigator hypnotized into thinking he was roleblocked will still receive night results with clues as to which role his target was.  However, he will not know for sure if he slept peacefully.
Other hypnotisms cannot be overwritten and if a player is hypnotized twice by two Hypnotists, they will get two messages.
If you are controlled by a witch, you will make your target think they &quot;slept peacefully.&quot;
You may only choose to hypnotize a target 3 times the entire game.
You can communicate with your allies each night, for as long as they are alive.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Ambusher&quot;]
&gt;### [color=red]Ambusher[/color]
&gt;**[color=red]Mafia[/color] Deception**
&gt;
&gt;You are a hired hitman for the mafia, stealthily carrying out their attacks.
&gt;
&gt;Twice per game, when performing the Mafia factional kill you can choose to cover your tracks, hiding yourself from Lookouts and Spies and making yourself appear &quot;Not Suspicious&quot; to Sheriffs and Investigators.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]
[/details]

---

[details=&quot;Neutral&quot;]

[details=&quot;Evil&quot;]

[details=&quot;Witch&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#8000FF]Witch[/color]
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Evil**
&gt;
&gt;You hate these townsfolk. Every last one of them. They act like witches are evil, not realizing the great things your magic can do.
You&#39;ll show them, you&#39;ll show them all how powerful your magic is! They&#39;ll pay for forcing you to hide like this!
&gt;
&gt;Every night you can choose somebody to control and somebody who you want your controlled player to use their ability on.
You won&#39;t be informed of the end result of your controlling or even if the one you controlled had an ability to use at all!
You&#39;ll have to pay close attention to learn people&#39;s abilities and use them to make the townsfolk suffer.
Your expertise in magic also taught you defensive spells. You have perfected a magical immunity shield, which shrouds your body.
It will discharge the instant you are attacked without protection. The shield will only work against non-Townsfolk, however.
Once the shield has discharged, all attacks will harm you, like any other non-magic user.
The attacker will only know of your immunity to their attack.
You are immune to being roleblocked.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Stalker&quot;]
&gt;### Stalker
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Evil**
&gt;
&gt;A petty criminal who just can&#39;t help themselves. It&#39;s amazing what people take to their graves. So you&#39;ve decided to relieve them from any possessions they have, it&#39;s not like they&#39;re using them anymore.
&gt;
&gt;Each night, you can choose a dead player to steal from.
You will be passively informed of how many charges each dead player has at the beginning of each night. 
You may use their ability as if you were that role for that night and gain any of their special attributes (IE night/roleblock immunity).
For each dead person you may only steal from them once.
You may not steal from unique roles, Witch being the only exception.
When you steal from a killing role, you will only take their passives. You&#39;re not one for killing.
You have no idea how the Bomber&#39;s fuses work, thus you&#39;ve decided against using them.
You must be alive at the end of the game in order to win.
&gt;
&gt;You win with the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Benign&quot;]

[details=&quot;Jester&quot;]
&gt;### [color=pink]Jester[/color]
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Benign**
&gt;
&gt;A crazed madman, you have found nothing but shame in your violent urges, and given the current calamity have decided that now is a good time to find a way out.
&gt;
&gt;When you are lynched, you may choose one of the players that voted for you to die of guilt the next morning. This bypasses all immunities.
&gt;
&gt;You win if you are lynched.
[/details]


[details=&quot;Amnesiac&quot;]
&gt;### [color=lightblue]Amnesiac[/color]
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Benign**
&gt;
&gt;A crazed asylum patient bored of staying on the ward, you have broken free and are determined to take somebody&#39;s place in society.
&gt;
&gt;You have one immunity piercing kill which also cleans its target. You will copy the role of the person you kill and any effects applied to them (being doused, having spent X charges, etc.). If your kill fails or your target dies the same night via another cause then you will leave the town and lose.
&gt;
&gt;You win by copying a role and fulfilling its wincon.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Survivor&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#BBBB00]Survivor[/color]
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Benign**
&gt;
&gt;You just try to live your life in peace.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may don a bulletproof vest, allowing you to survive any direct kill attempts on you that night.
You have four bulletproof vests.
&gt;
&gt;You win if you survive to the end of the game.
[/details]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Killing&quot;]

[details=&quot;Serial Killer&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#0000FF]Serial Killer[/color]
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Killing**
&gt;
&gt;You are nuts! Psychotic! Crazy! Mental! Insane! Over the edge! Uncontrollable! Irrational!
You were once in an asylum, in solitary confinement for first degree murder. Recently released, you have emerged with a new look at life: not to kill just anybody, but to kill everybody!
Your thirst for blood and murder will never be satisfied and although the Godfather approached you, you declined and said that you will kill the Mafia too!
&gt;
&gt;Every night you may kill one person.
You are unkillable at night. If somebody tries to attack you, they will receive a message saying that you were immune.
If someone tries to roleblock you, you will attack them instead of your chosen target.
You win if it is just you and the Godfather remaining.
You lose if it is just you and an Arsonist remaining.
&gt;
&gt;You win with [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Arsonist&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#FF8000]Arsonist[/color]
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Killing**
&gt;
&gt;You love fire.
You love the smell of fire, the sight of fire, and nothing makes you feel better then watching houses burn and seeing and hearing those inside panic and die.
You care for no one but yourself and nothing would make you happier than watching everyone burn.
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may douse one player or ignite all of your doused targets.
If you are doused by another Arsonist, you may wait a night to clean the gasoline off of yourself.
Your method of killing ignores night immunity.
You cover up your tracks very well and you will appear as &#39;not suspicious&#39; to a Sheriff.
You are unkillable at night. If somebody tries to attack you, they will receive a message saying that you were immune.
You win if only you and the Godfather or a Serial Killer remain.
&gt;

&gt;You win with [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]

[details=&quot;Bomber&quot;]
&gt;### [color=#582525]Bomber[/color]
&gt;**[color=grey]Neutral[/color] Killing**
&gt;
&gt;Boom! Nothing is more satisfying than an explosion. Thus you&#39;ve decided to share your love of explosions with everyone. You hope they&#39;ll appreciate this hands on experience with your earth shattering ka-booms!
&gt;
&gt;Each night you may place a device on a player; they will be informed of this.
If a player with a device visits another player with a device, all devices will explode and kill the player holding them. This ignores night immunity.
You may plant a device on yourself; however, visiting a target while you have a device won&#39;t trigger them unless the device on the other player is from a previous night.
You are immune to your explosions.
You are redirection immune.
You are night immune.
&gt;

&gt;You win with [b][color=#582525]Bombers[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b][color=#8000FF]Witches[/color][/b]
&gt;You win with [b]Stalkers[/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#FF0000]Mafia[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill the [b][color=#00bF00]Town[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#FF8000]Arsonists[/color][/b]
&gt;You must kill [b][color=#0000FF]Serial Killers[/color][/b]
&gt;You may spare anyone else
[/details]
[/details]
[/details]
---


### Players
1. Firekitten
2. htm
3. PoisonedSquid
4. MaximusPrime
5. Solic
6. Twil1ght
7. Celeste_Ludenberg
8. Captain
9. PokemonKidRyan
10. Blizer
11. Whammerist
12. GamerPoke
13. Hippolytus
14. Luxy
15. Sarun


### Graveyard
1. 


### Links
-</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 15:44:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Day 2</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1059">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1059</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 15:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1059</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>:^)<br>
and somehow we won shroud</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1058">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1058</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 15:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1058</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh yea. My bad. I should have made it mountainous and RNGed a night kill every night…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1057">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1057</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1057</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you didn’t go far enough Nuclear :^)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1056">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1056</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 14:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1056</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="orangeandblack5" data-post="1050" data-topic="67907">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/orangeandblack5/40/33172_2.png" class="avatar"> orangeandblack5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But people haven’t been making jokes about that <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ahem. FM shroud</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1055">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1055</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1055</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s not a social experiment silly<br>
it’s for shits and gigles first and foremost and just so happened to be a socail experiment along the way</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1054">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1054</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 13:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1054</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s why I pinged Ici not you…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1053">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1053</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 13:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1053</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t remember ever stating that in uncertain terms</p>
<p>That was always secondary to being a meme</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1052">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1052</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 13:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1052</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yh I know it was funny af but the idea that this game was somehow a social experiment and proves jester is bad is just wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1051">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1051</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 13:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1051</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But people haven’t been making jokes about that <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1050">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1050</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 13:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1050</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/icibalus">@Icibalus</a> having a game with everyone as town-aligned citizens would also be shit and unplayable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1049">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1049</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 13:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1049</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this was not simply a game<br>
it was a social experiment</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1048">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1048</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1048</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>But I like Jesters</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1047">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1047</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 08:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1047</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so by the way<br>
if i see anyone else making any “a game with only jesters xD!” jokes<br>
i’lll show you this game and say “No. Bad.”</p>
<p>because Jesters ARE bad.</p>
<p>also that was an unintended consequence we just wanted to laugh at all of yo</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1046">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1046</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 08:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1046</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>at no point did <em><strong>I</strong></em> regret the decisions that brought me to this poiint lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1045">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1045</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 07:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1045</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wrong</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1044">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1044</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1044</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Shtto</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1043">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1043</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1043</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>all classes except mafia have already been rolled for GT2</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1042">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1042</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1042</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Gimme a neut in GT2 pls</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1041">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1041</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1041</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So… I was the witch-Jester? Ffs</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1040">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1040</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1040</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Captain]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fools and jesters are still my fav.Change my mind</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1039">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1039</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 20:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1039</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mission accomplished</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1038">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1038</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 20:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1038</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tbh I kinda hate it too</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1037">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1037</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 20:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1037</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-ghost-town-2-participation-confirmation/71339?u=orangeandblack5" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-ghost-town-2-participation-confirmation/71339?u=orangeandblack5</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1036">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1036</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 20:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1036</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Survivor is a controversial role, that’s all and not everyone is enjoying it which is understandable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1035">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907/1035</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 20:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-67907-1035</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-ghost-town-day-1/67907.rss">[FM] Ghost Town (Day 1)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
