<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047</link>
    <description>Personally, I think when Scorned was changed it was mostly good, but there is still the element of just getting randomly bad luck on your targets. Say your two targets end up being both Investigative and are near confirmed, at that point you are pretty much screwed if evils don&#39;t gain majority. So, what i suggest is a small ability to make sure something like this won&#39;t give you no wiggle room:

Night Ability - Refocus (not set on this name, any suggestions?) [1 use]
Select one target in the first panel, they will no longer be your target. In the second panel, select a new target. This will take effect at the beginning of the next night.

Now, I know what you may be thinking, changing targets could lead to extremely easy wins! That&#39;s why this ability has a delay. Your new target will only apply at the beginning of the next night, meaning if they were executed the next day, this would not grant you the win as they are not your target yet. However, your old target will instantly no longer be a target, meaning that if they end up getting executed the next day you won&#39;t win off of that either. This ability was designed with a desperate change in mind, not just a way to get an easier win. As for this not making sense lore-wise, I was thinking it could be another person who had wronged the Scorned, but to a lesser degree, and was being ignored at first because of it, but due to the Scorned not being able to exact vengeance on their higher profile targets, they decided to take on this lesser offender instead. So, what do you think?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 02:26:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="7" data-topic="3047">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(It’d be…  Jailed, Fool, Mercenary, Sellsword, Scorned, Sage, I think, at this point?)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And poacher.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 02:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think Scorned is mostly fine as-is.  Yes, random bad luck can cost you the game, but this is true for any neutrals (who could just get killed.)  With two targets, it’s less likely to happen.</p>
<p>If you’re really worried, give Scorned a night ability that blocks visits to their targets.  This would be a bit risky, but could be used to help keep them alive.  Also, adding more ways for visits to be blocked would make it harder for people to make easy deductions from it.  I’m not sure it’s needed, though.</p>
<p>(It’d be…  Jailed, Fool, Mercenary, Sellsword, Scorned, Sage, I think, at this point?)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 01:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel you can win as Scorned even without your abilities.</p>
<p>Frame certainly does help, but everyone always seems willing to just lap a Sheriff or Paladin claim right up.</p>
<p>It’s weirdly different than Town of Salem, as people don’t trust Sheriff claims as much.</p>
<p>I do have to say that besides Possessor and Reaper, Scorned is my favorite neutral class.</p>
<p>The goal is probably the best among Neutrals, I’d love to see it as a King.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/biperspectival">@Biperspectival</a>  I feel that isn’t a good goal, as you don’t have to do anything. Some will just get random killed, and some may be super trustworthy and lead the game. The execution with only one person needed is better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 20:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They already had that and it was both borring and hard.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 20:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Biperspectival]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I sort of dislike scorned in general. Sometimes you get lucky and accuse one of your targets d2 and everyone execs them, and sometimes they all die n1 and there’s nothing you can do about it. I think it would be a more interesting challenge to try to get two of three targets killed, but not executed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 20:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I liked old scorned…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 19:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Small Scorned Buff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally, I think when Scorned was changed it was mostly good, but there is still the element of just getting randomly bad luck on your targets. Say your two targets end up being both Investigative and are near confirmed, at that point you are pretty much screwed if evils don’t gain majority. So, what i suggest is a small ability to make sure something like this won’t give you no wiggle room:</p>
<p>Night Ability - Refocus (not set on this name, any suggestions?) [1 use]<br>
Select one target in the first panel, they will no longer be your target. In the second panel, select a new target. This will take effect at the beginning of the next night.</p>
<p>Now, I know what you may be thinking, changing targets could lead to extremely easy wins! That’s why this ability has a delay. Your new target will only apply at the beginning of the next night, meaning if they were executed the next day, this would not grant you the win as they are not your target yet. However, your old target will instantly no longer be a target, meaning that if they end up getting executed the next day you won’t win off of that either. This ability was designed with a desperate change in mind, not just a way to get an easier win. As for this not making sense lore-wise, I was thinking it could be another person who had wronged the Scorned, but to a lesser degree, and was being ignored at first because of it, but due to the Scorned not being able to exact vengeance on their higher profile targets, they decided to take on this lesser offender instead. So, what do you think?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 14:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3047-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/a-small-scorned-buff/3047.rss">A Small Scorned Buff</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
