<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564</link>
    <description>&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]Take a seat while we shuffle the cards. Welcome to Poker Mafia!!![/Color]&lt;/big&gt;

Welcome to my very first Forum Match. Poker Mafia!
This is a mafia game heavily based on gambling and RNG, but there won&#39;t be any bastard mechanics or unfair advantages! If you don&#39;t like RNG you are not forced to gamble, everyone gets free tokens each day!

The game works mostly like a normal forum mafia game, with a town faction, an evil faction and a few neutrals. However, instead of having different roles for each player, most players (except the neutrals and the Godfather) will have classes that start with no abilities.

To get an ability, you need tokens. Players start the game with 5 tokens. At the beginning of each day except day 1 every player gains 3 tokens and can gain more with daytime events related to gambling. You can also &quot;sell&quot; your abilities for tokens.
You don&#39;t buy the abilities directly with tokens, instead you have to bet. Every day there will be a pool of abilities. During the day, you can place any number of tokens on one or multiple abilities, and at the beginning of the night whoever placed the most tokens will get the ability permanently. There is not a maximum number of abilities a single player can have at the same time.

**Host:** Psychoneirik
**Cohost:** Firekitten

&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Rules[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;

https://forum.imperium42.com/t/forum-of-lies-official-hub/1515

&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Gameplay[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;

**General:**
* Days will be 3 IRL days long, or shorter if someone dies
* Nights will be 1 IRL day long
* Actions are done by messaging me
* Mafia will talk through a special Discord server. They have both day and night chat.
* When you receive a card you will have 24 hours to reply, confirming you have received it


**Ability pool and betting:**
* The pool will have abilities equal to the number of players minus 3. There will always be a minimum of 3 abilities in the pool.
* The ability pool changes every day.
* You can place your bets by messaging a host with the number of the ability and the ammount of tokens, for example: &quot;I want to bet 10 tokens on ability #4&quot;. 
* Bets are private and will not be revealed to anyone, except for some specific abilities or events. 
* You can place or change your bets at any point during the daytime.
* Even though I call it betting, getting abilities is more like an auction. The player with the highest amount of tokens in each ability will get said ability.
* If there is a tie, the person with the less number of non-starting abilities will get it. If that is also a tie, it will be solved by rng.
* Each night, a player will get **ALL** the abilities in which they had the most tokens.
* The abilities are given to the player at the beginning of the night, which means they can use them that same night.
* You can have more than 2 day and night abilities. There is no limit.
* Players can only use one day ability per day and one night ability per night. The only exception is The Cheater, who can pay tokens to use more than one ability.
* You are not forced to bet every day. You can save your tokens for a later day.
* To sell an ability send a message to the host telling him which ability you want to sell.
* You cannot have duplicate abilities. If you get an ability you already have you will get increased uses instead.
* You will get 5 tokens back for selling unused abilities, and 1-4 tokens if you have used some of its charges. You will get no tokens for selling abilities with 0 uses.
* Passives are sold for 5 tokens, unless its a one shoot passive that has already triggered (such as death immunity once).
* Abilities that you sell will go back into the pool for anyone to buy. They will have the same remaining uses.
* You will know whether you got an ability or not at the beginning of the night. If you lose a bet, you will not know who got the ability.
* If The Gambler gives a special token to a Leprechaun, they will give them 10 normal tokens instead.

**Events:**
* There will be one event every day.
* Some events require you to vote for someone or pay a certain amount of tokens. This is done through messaging the host.
* The event will end in 24 hours or earlier if everyone has performed the required actions.
* You can discuss about the game and lynch people while an event is running. Lynching someone will immediately end the event.
* The results of the event will be public unless stated otherwise.

**Executions:**
* To accuse someone say &quot;**/lynch [player]**&quot; or &quot;**/vote [player]**&quot;
* If a player gets enough votes they will be lynched.
* Executions end the Day, so be sure to bet before someone is lynched!

**Journals**
* Message me your entire journal, the last draft I receive before you die shall be the one displayed

**Mafia/NK/Neutral specific interactions:**
* Godfather can make himself attack someone, but it would still use up 3 tokens.
* If the GF makes a mafioso kill someone, he uses the 3 tokens. The mafioso DOESN&#39;T get them.
* If a member of the mafia attacks a gambler or leprechaun, the attacker will know their class.
* Gambler wins with mafia but is a neutral class, which means he is allowed to out the cheater or members of the mafia.
* If Godfather sends someone to attack a leprechaun, the mafioso that attacked him will get the bribe.
* If you attack a leprechaun with less than 7 tokens, you will get the bribe AND kill them.
* If you try to attack a gambler you will be prevented from doing it. Which means it wouldn&#39;t count as an attack for abilities purposes.
* If a leprechaun loses their tokens on the day time for any reason, they will die immediately.
* Leprechaun&#39;s passive works like a heal, so he can survive any attacks, poison or bleeding as long as he has enough tokens. Abilities that go through immunity will not kill him, but abilities that go through healing will.


&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#To Join[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;
* To join, simply express interest in joining by saying something like &quot;I want to join&quot; or &quot;/join&quot; or &quot;/in&quot; or &quot;sign me up, coach&quot; or whatever you want

&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Class cards[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;

[details=&quot;Classes&quot;]
&gt; &lt;big&gt; [color=green]Townie[/color] &lt;/big&gt;
&gt; Townie has no starting abilities. They must exchange tokens for them.
&gt; **Goal: Defeat Mafia and The Cheater**

&gt; &lt;big&gt; [color=red]Mafioso[/color] &lt;/big&gt;
&gt; Mafioso has no starting abilities. They must exchange tokens for them.
&gt; **Goal: Defeat Town and The Cheater**

&gt; &lt;big&gt; [color=red]Godfather[/color] &lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Filthy rich (Passive):** You start the game with 10 tokens. You cannot buy any abilities for yourself, instead, any abilities you buy will be given to a mafioso of your choice.
&gt; **Pass the torch (Passive):** You are immune to death at night. If you die, a mafioso of your choice will gain the &quot;Hired Gun&quot; ability.
&gt; **Loan (Day):** Give a player a loan. You will give them 5 tokens. They must pay you 10 tokens back. If two days pass and they don&#39;t pay you back they will die. 3 uses.
&gt; **Hired gun(Night):** Pay 3 tokens to make a mafioso kill a player. If there are no mafiosos alive, you will kill them yourself. (The mafioso won&#39;t get the tokens, they will be lost)
&gt;**Goal: Defeat Town and The Cheater.**

&gt; &lt;big&gt; [color=gray]Leprechaun[/color] &lt;/big&gt;
&gt; Neutral
&gt; **Lucky 7 (Passive):** You start the game with 7 tokens. You are unable to buy abilities from the ability pool.
&gt; **Bribe (Passive):** You will bribe your attackers, giving them 7 tokens to spare your life. If you ever run out of tokens you will die.
&gt; **Cursed Gold (Day):** Select an ability from the ability pool. You will steal all the tokens from anyone that placed a bet on that ability and no one will be able to get said ability. People will be notified when you use this ability, but they won&#39;t know which ability is cursed. 2 uses.
&gt; **Make Deal (Day):** Select a player and make a deal. If they accept, they will give you half of their tokens and become immune to death, occupation an redirection for one night. If they refuse, their class and abilities will be revealed to the whole court. 3 uses.
&gt; **Trickster (Night):** Select a player. They will lose 1 use of all their non-starting abilities, and you will gain 2 tokens for every ability affected. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Goal: Survive.**


&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Gambler[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; Neutral
&gt; **Let the game begin (Passive):** You are unable to buy abilities from the ability pool. You will secretly gain 50% more tokens from events.
&gt; **Persuasion (Passive):** You cannot be killed by Mafia or The Cheater.
&gt; **High stakes (Day):** Select an ability. If that ability has the least amount of tokens at the end of the day you will gain 10 tokens. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Proxy meeting (Day):** Use 10 tokens to send an anonymous message to all Mafia players and The Cheater. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Poker Face (Night)**: Use 10 tokens to learn the exact class of a player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Special Gift (Night):** Use 10 tokens to give a player a special token, they can use it instead of normal tokens to guarantee they will get an ability. The Special token only lasts for the next day and if they don&#39;t spend it they will lose it. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Goal: Survive to see town lose.**

&gt; &lt;big&gt; [color=gray]Cheater[/color] &lt;/big&gt;
&gt; Neutral Killer
&gt; **Card counting (Passive):** Immune to death at night. You know the highest number of tokens on each ability from the pool.
&gt; **Sleight of hand (Passive):** You can pay 5 tokens to use an extra night or day ability. You cannot use the same ability multiple times.
&gt; **All-In (Night):** Kill a player.
&gt; **Rigged event (Night):** Rig tomorrow&#39;s event. No one will win tokens in said event and whoever &quot;wins&quot; the most tokens will die instantly. 1 use. (Only one person can die to this ability).
&gt; **Goal: Defeat the Town and Mafia.**
[/details]

&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Notifications[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;

**Day Notifications**
&quot;The Leprechaun has cursed one of the abilities in the pool! Anyone that places tokens in that ability will lose them!&quot;
&quot;You got 5 tokens from the Godfather. You must pay 10 tokens within the next two days or you will die! To pay, write **/pay loan** in your class card.&quot;
&quot;The Leprechaun has offered you a deal. If you pay him half of your tokens (rounded up, including the ones currently on events or the ability pool) you will become immune to death and occupation tonight. If you refuse, your class will be revealed to the court. Write /accept or /deny on your class card.&quot;
&quot;The event was rigged! The person who &quot;won&quot; the most tokens has died.&quot;


**Night Notifications**
&quot;The Leprechaun has stolen 1 use of all your non-starting abilities!&quot;
&quot;You could not attack [Player]. They are the Gambler.&quot;
&quot;[Player] gave you 7 coins last night to stop you from killing them!&quot;


&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Role List[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;

[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=green] **Townie** [/color]
[color=red] **Godfather** [/color]
[color=red] **Mafioso** [/color]
[color=red] **Mafioso** [/color]
[color=gray] **Leprechaun** [/color]
[color=gray] **Gambler** [/color]
[color=gray] **Cheater (NK)** [/color]


Players:
1. Marluxion [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=green] **Townie** [/color] died N2
2. PokemonKidRyan
3. MaximusPrime -  [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=green] **Townie** [/color] died N3
4. Celeste_Ludenberg
5. Whammerist [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=gray] **Cheater** [/color] lynched d3
6. Moleland - [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=green] **Townie** [/color] died N1
7. Hippolytus - [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=green] **Townie** [/color] died N1
8. CaptainNerbins
9. NightX [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=green] **Townie** [/color] lynched D2
10. NuclearBurrito [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=red] **Mafioso** [/color] died N2
11. boss110 - [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=green] **Townie** [/color] died N3
12. Sam17z
13. Memesky
14. htm
15. Twil1ght - [color=red]**DEAD**[/color], [color=green] **Townie** [/color] _lynched D1_

&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Notable events[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;
[Day 1 ability pool and highest bids](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2/60564/1110)
[Day 1 event results](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2/60564/381)
[Twil1ight was lynched! They were a Townie!](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2/60564/1098)
[Start of day 2, two bodies were found! (Hippolytus and Moleland)](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2/60564/1121)
[Leprechaun revealed Celeste&#39;s class! They are a Gambler!](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2/60564/1212)
[Day 2 ability pool and highest bids](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2-11-15/60564/1924)
[Day 2 event results](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2/60564/1858)
[NightX was lynched!](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-day-2-11-15/60564/1912)

&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Today&#39;s Ability Pool[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;
**The number of abilities in the current pool is: 6!**

**Day 4 Ability Pool**

:shield: = Passive
:sun_with_face: = Day ability
:first_quarter_moon_with_face: = Night ability  

1 - :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Force a player to target another. Cannot force them to target you or themselves. 3 uses.
2 -:sun_with_face: Increases the number of votes required to lynch someone by 1 today. 2 uses.
3 - :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Heal a player from attacks, doesn’t heal poison or bleeding. 4 uses.


&lt;big&gt;[color=Purple]#Today&#39;s Event[/Color]&lt;/big&gt;
-The three boxes: There are 3 boxes. The Blue Box has 20 tokens, The Green Box has 15 tokens and The Red Box has 10 tokens. You may choose one of the boxes. The tokens from each box will be split between the players that picked said box.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 01:03:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="psychoneirik" data-post="2280" data-topic="60564">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/psychoneirik/40/12950_2.png" class="avatar"> psychoneirik:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>-Pay to win: You can pay 10 tokens to instantly gain a random ability. You can do this as many times as you want. Leprechaun and gambler CAN get extra abilities this way.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Wouldve loved that</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2284">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2284</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 01:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2284</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If that event rolled they would have probably lynched the leprechaun with 40 tokens.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2283">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2283</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2283</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also, can you please add those role colors I suggested?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2282">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2282</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2282</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="psychoneirik" data-post="2280" data-topic="60564">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/psychoneirik/40/12950_2.png" class="avatar"> psychoneirik:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lynch Piñata:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is funny to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2281">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2281</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2281</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure, I plan to change some and add more in the future but the ones for this game were the following:</p>
<details>
<summary>
All possible abilities from the pool</summary>
<p>Support</p>
<ul>
<li>(Night ability) Select two players. Anyone that visits one of them will instead visit the other. 4 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Prevent people from visiting a player. Can be used on yourself. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Heal a player from attacks, doesn’t heal poison or bleeding. 4 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Heal a player from poison or bleeding. Doesn’t heal attacks. 4 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Heal a player from attacks, poison or bleeding. 3 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Heal yourself from attacks, poison or bleeding. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Day ability) Make a player immune to poison or bleeding. Can’t target yourself. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Day ability) Make a player immune to death once. Can’t target yourself. 1 use.</li>
</ul>
<p>Passives</p>
<ul>
<li>(Passive) You are immune to poison/bleeding.</li>
<li>(Passive) You will be immune to the next negative effect used on you, except death, poison or bleeding.</li>
<li>(Passive) You are immune to death once.</li>
<li>(Passive) You are immune to occupation and redirection.</li>
<li>(Passive) If you are lynched, you will immediately kill the first person to accuse you.<br>
-(Passive) Whenever you bid at least 1 token on an ability, you will place an extra free token on said ability.<br>
-(Passive) You will gain 50% more tokens from events.<br>
-(Passive) Gain 3 more tokens at the beginning of each day.<br>
-(Passive) Your tokens cannot be decreased by player abilities, such as Loan, Make Deal or Cursed Gold.</li>
</ul>
<p>Scum<br>
-(Night) Make yourself or another player appear as a townie to investigators tonight. 2 uses.<br>
-(Night) Make a player appear as a Mafioso to investigators tonight. 2 uses.<br>
-(Night) Select a player. They will get false results tonight. 3 uses.<br>
-(Night) Every investigative role will get false results tonight. 1 use.<br>
-(Passive) Your visits will be hidden from investigators.</p>
<p>Offensive</p>
<ul>
<li>(Night ability) Occupy a player. 4 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Occupy 2 players. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Force a player to target you. You will be immune to attacks. 3 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Force a player to target you. You will NOT be immune to attacks redirected this way. 4 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Force a player to target another. Cannot force them to target you or themselves. 3 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Force a player to target themselves. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Day ability) Redirect the next targeted day ability to you. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Day abiity) Select a player. If they use a day ability, they will target themselves.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Occupy everyone visiting you tonight. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Select a player except yourself. Occupy everyone visiting them tonight. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Select a player. Redirect all players visiting them to yourself. You will NOT be immune to attacks redirected this way. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Remove a player’s occupation and death immunities and occupy them for the night. 1 use.</li>
</ul>
<p>Social<br>
-(Day) Select a player except yourself. They cannot be lynched today. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Send an anonymous message to the court through the host. 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) Send a private message to another player through the host. They will know who sent it. 3 uses.<br>
-(Day) Select a player. They cannot vote to lynch anyone today. They will not count towards majority. 3 uses.<br>
-(Day) Decreases the number of votes required to lynch someone by 1 today. 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) Increases the number of votes required to lynch someone by 1 today. 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) Target player will be unable to talk for the rest of the day. 1 use.<br>
-(Night) Select a player. You will both be able to send each other two 1000 character messages through the host over the course of the night. 2 uses.<br>
-(Night) Select two players. They will be allowed to send each other two 1000 character messages through the host. The conversation will be later given to you. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Force a player to lynch another. They cannot change or rescind their votes. 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) The next player to lynch anyone will become poisoned and die in 2 days unless healed. Everyone in court will be notified when this ability is used (they won’t know who did it). 2 uses.<br>
-(Night) Select a player. You will get all feedback that player gets tonight. 1 use.</p>
<p>Killer</p>
<ul>
<li>(Night ability) Kill everyone visiting you tonight. You will be immune to attacks. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Make yourself and a target player start bleeding. You will die in a day unless healed. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Bleed everyone visiting you tonight. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Kill 2 players. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Day ability) Imprison a player tonight. You will both be able to send each other two 1000 character messages through the host over the course of the night. You will be able to execute them. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Kill a player. Bypasses heals and death immunity. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Kill a player. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Protect a player, making them immune to death and killing their attackers. 3 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Attempt to kill a player, if they are town you will kill yourself instead. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night ability) Bleed a player. They will die in 1 day unless healed. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Day ability) Poison a player. They will die in 2 days unless healed. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Day ability) Bleed a player. They will die in 2 days unless healed. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Day ability) Kill a player in plain daylight. Everyone will know you did it. 1 use.</li>
</ul>
<p>Investigative</p>
<ul>
<li>(Night) Check if a player is a member of the mafia. 3 uses.</li>
<li>(Night) Select two players. You will be told if at least one of them is a member of the mafia. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night) Check if a player is neutral. 3 uses.</li>
<li>(Night) Follow a player to see who they visit. 4 uses.</li>
<li>(Night) Follow a player to see who visits them. 4 uses.</li>
<li>(Night) Follow a player to see who visits them and who they visit. 3 uses.</li>
<li>(Day) You will be told who the mafia visits tonight. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night) Reveal one of a player’s random non-starting ability. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night) Reveal all of a player’s non-starting abilities. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night) Check the exact class of a player. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Night) Check if a player attacks someone tonight. 2 uses.</li>
<li>(Night) Select a player. Both you and your target will be told who visits you tonight. 1 use.</li>
<li>(Day) Publicly reveal a player’s alignment to the whole court. 1 use.</li>
</ul>
<p>Special:<br>
-(Day) Find out how many tokens a player has currently. 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) Swap all your tokens with another player. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Force the host to start an event. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Instantly steal a random ability from a chosen player. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Gain 1 use of all your limited use abilities, except this one. 1 use.<br>
-(Night) Remove all of a player’s non-starting abilities. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Remove all of your tokens and you will be unable to get tokens for the rest of the game. Gain 3 special tokens. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Remove all of your non-starting abilities. Gain 2 random abilities. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Remove an ability from today’s ability pool. 3 uses.<br>
-(Day) Select a player and give them 5 free tokens. Yay! 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) Gain 5 event tokens. These tokens can only be used in today’s event. You will lose them if you don’t use them. 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) Make a player instantly lose 10 tokens. 2 uses.<br>
-(Day) Give a player other than yourself a special token. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) At the end of the day, you will get a copy of the ability with the least total ammount of tokens<br>
-(Day) At the end of the day, you will get a copy of the ability with the most total ammount of tokens<br>
-(Day) Copy one of your abilities and give it to another player. It will have the same remaining uses as the copied ability. 1 use.<br>
-(Day) Everyone that has no abilities will get a random one. 1 use.</p>
</details>
<p>And these were the events:</p>
<details>
<summary>
All possible events</summary>
<p>Gambling events:<br>
-Raffle: Bet any ammount of tokens. Whoever wins gets all tokens! The more tokens you bet, the higher your chances to win.<br>
-Death Gamble: Secretly bet any ammount of tokens on who you think will be killed tomorrow. If said person dies AT NIGHT, you will double them.<br>
-Animal Race: Bet any ammount of tokens on an animal. If said animal wins, you will get tokens, depending on the animal. Horse: High chance to win. Doubles your wager. Dog: Medium chance to win. Triples your wager. Duck: Low chance to win: 5x wager.<br>
-Coin Flip: Bet any ammount of tokens. You have a 50% chance to double them and a 50% chance to lose them!<br>
-Russian Roulette: Choose a number between 0 and 10. You will get that ammount of tokens. However, there is a chance you might become poisoned and die in one day. The more tokens you ask for, the higher the chance! (You have a 10% chance to be poisoned for every token you ask for)<br>
-The three boxes: There are 3 boxes. The Blue Box  has 30 tokens, The Green Box has 20 tokens and The Red Box has 10 tokens. You may choose one of the boxes. The tokens from each box will be split between the players that picked said box.<br>
-Blackjack: Everyone will be able to pay 2 tokens for a “card”. You can get as many cards as you want as long as you have enough tokens. The player that gets closer to 21 without busting will get all tokens.</p>
<p>Non-Gambling events:<br>
-Every player will be able to secretly vote for a player, except themselves. The player with the most votes will get 10 tokens! The second player will get 5 tokens! Everyone else that got at least 1 vote will get 2 tokens!<br>
-Gift Rain: At random times during the day, a “gift” will appear. The first person to write <strong>/claim</strong> in public will get the gift! That person can choose to open the gift or give it to someone else. Each player can only claim 1 gift. Any abilities you get from gifts will be given to you immediately. If a gambler or Leprechaun claim a gift containing an ability, they will get 5 tokens instead.<br>
-Pawn shop: Any abilities you exchange for tokens today will be worth TRIPLE. Also, everyone is able to gift any ammount of tokens to another player!!!<br>
-Pay to win: You can pay 10 tokens to instantly gain a random ability. You can do this as many times as you want. Leprechaun and gambler CAN get extra abilities this way.<br>
-Lynch Piñata: Whoever is lynched today will have all their tokens split between the players that voted to lynch them.<br>
-Charity: Donate any ammount of tokens. An ammount equal to twice the tokens donated by all players will be given to the player with least tokens. Yay!</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2280">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2280</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2280</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can we see a list of all of the ability’s that could show up in the pool?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2279">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2279</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2279</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Theres also not many offensive abilities soo probs should buff them</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2278">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2278</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2278</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You should nerf Support Classes because theres tons of support abilities</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2277">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2277</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2277</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Basically I want all classes to start with an ability so they have something to do even if they don’t get any abilities from the pool.</p>
<p>As an example, in this game there were like 3 people that didnt use abilities on the first 3 nights because they didn’t have any.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2276">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2276</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2276</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is an ability like that in the ability pool. I was thinking on making most classes like this:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>The Doctor</strong><br>
Town Support<br>
Start the game with a random support ability. Every support ability you get will have 1 extra use.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Making them start with a random ability of a certain type and rewarding them for getting more abilities of the same type from the pool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2275">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2275</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2275</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah I like it how all town are equal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2274">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2274</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2274</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not himself of course.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2273">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2273</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2273</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about a town PR that can give people special tokens as a 3 shot night ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2272">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2272</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 23:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2272</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure. I’m trying to keep them simple though since I want the ability pool to be the main focus of the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2271">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2271</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2271</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerbins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can I help make classes?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2270">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2270</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2270</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2269">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2269</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2269</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Too much math involved <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> , maybe just remove lep and leave the other two neuts?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2268">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2268</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2268</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nvm then</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2267">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2267</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2267</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cursed gold has the potential to steal a lot of tokens though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2266">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2266</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2266</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Too Much</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2265">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2265</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2265</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Btw any idea of the number of tokens leprechaun should get to win? Would 50 be too much?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2264">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2264</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2264</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/+1.png?v=9" title=":+1:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":+1:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2263">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2263</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2263</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about now?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2262">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2262</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2262</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Leprechaun has no survivor abilities</p>
<p>And let the neuts get ability <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2261">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2261</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2261</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about making simpler neutrals like this, but in exchange all neutrals are able to buy abilities normally from the pool:</p>
<p><strong>The Cheater</strong><br>
Immune to death at night. Starts the game with 3 special tokens.<br>
Kill (Night) - Attack a player. Unlimited uses.<br>
<strong>Goal: Defeat both mafia and town.</strong></p>
<p><strong>The Gambler</strong><br>
You win 50% more tokens from events.<br>
(Night) - Become immune to attacks. Unlimited uses, but costs 5 tokens to use.<br>
<strong>Goal: Survive</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2260">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564/2260</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-60564-2260</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-the-mafia-leprechaun-and-gambler-win/60564.rss">[FM] Poker Mafia - THE MAFIA, LEPRECHAUN AND GAMBLER WIN</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
