<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637</link>
    <description># [FM] Camelot (Incomplete)

Hello citizens of Camelot. We need your help stopping the tyrannious Morgan le Fay and her band of traitors. If they rule, all is for naught. Take up your arms and band together to stand up! For Camelot and King Arthur!

## :shield: = **Unique**

## 🎉 = **Convert Immune**

## Role List
[color=Mediumvioletred]Traitor[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Merlin[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]
[color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color]/[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral[/color]
[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral[/color]
[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral Killer[/color]
[color=Black]King Arthur[/color]

# Classcards

## Camelotian

[details=“Botanist&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Botanist[/color]
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Support[/color]**
**Knowledge of Botany (Passive)** - Immune to nightshade and bleeding. 
**Emergency Procedure (Day)** - Target a player. If they are attacked, you will be occupied and will be forced to heal them.
**Nature’s Healing (Night)** - Heal a player from poison or bleeding. If they are successfully healed, they will be immune to the same effect for the rest of the game. - Infinite uses
**Offset (Night)** - Partially heal a player from attack, nightshade, or bleeding. The effects of the status will be delayed by two nights and if they were attacked, the attack will be changed into one-day bleeding. You will not automatically heal them tonight. - Infinite uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Herald&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Herald[/color]
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Social[/color]**
**A Herald’s Premise (Passive)** - Talk to a random member of the Round Table whom attended King Arthur’s meeting last night. The Knight will know whom you are but you will not know who they are.
**Herald’s Decree (Day)** - Speak for the masses. Your vote will count for three today. - 2 uses
**Written Letter (Night)** - The Target Player will be able to write a 200 character message that will be posted by the Host the next day. - Infinite uses
**Blackmail (Night)** - Blackmail a Player. They will not be able to vote the next day. They will not count towards majority.
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Lancelot&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Lancelot[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Killer[/color]**
**Knight of the Round Table (Passive)** - Immune to occupation &amp; is eligible to participate in meetings called by King Arthur.
**Duel (Day)** - Target a player. If that player has the passive *Knight of the Round Table* you will give them a fatal wound (Bleeding) that will kill them in two nights if not healed. - 2 uses
**Wrongful Duel (Night)** - Kill a player. If they are a member of the Camelotian faction you will lose any remaining uses of this ability. - 3 uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=“Lady Nimue&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Lady Nimue[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Support [/color]**
**Bestow (Day)** - Bestow a Sacred Sword upon a target player. They will not recieve the sword until the next day. Players who receive a Sacred Sword are given a use of private DayVig. If this ability targets a *Traitor*, the Sacred Sword will become corrupted, giving the *Traitor* a private DayVig ability in addition to a special night ability. If all Sacred Swords are used and not corrupted, the current King will receive a weapon called Excalibur which targets a random *Traitor* and publicly reveals them to the King. - 4 uses
**Foretell (Night)** - See where a target player is going. This ability can target the King. - 2 uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*

[/details]


[details=&quot;Maelgwn&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Maelgwn[/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Support[/color]**
**Royalty (Passive)** - You may step up before others without this passive.
**Smoldering Heat (Day)** - Extend the day phase by 24 Hours. - 3 uses
**A wish upon the Grail (Day)** - Only usable at the start of the day. Start an event for a random player to receive a wish upon the grail. The grail will have four random options and the wish will be hidden. - 1 use
**Dragonsblood (Night)** - Attack a player. Players attacked will die at the end of the next day phase. If you kill a Neutral Support, Neutral Social, or a Camelotian, you will lose any remaining usages of the ability. - 2 uses
**Dragon’s Blood (Night)** - If you are attacked tonight, the first attacker will have killing abilities disabled for the next night phase. They will be notified. You will be immune to the first attack on your life as long as this ability is used. - 3 uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Hermit&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Hermit[/color]
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Social[/color]**
**Hermitage (Passive)** - Can talk to the dead.
**Full Life (Day)** - Target a player. They will be immune to all day effects but will be occupied during the night. Does not bypass occupation immunity. - Infinite uses
**Teachings of the Hermit(Night)** - Occupy a player &amp; all visitors will be unable to vote the following day. Bypasses occupation immunity. - 3 uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;King&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]King[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Special[/color]**
**King of the Realm (Passive)** - During the night, you will choose an ability that effects all players. The host will give you 5 options.
**Dedication (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection and all your votes count as triple.
**Decide Fate (Day)** - Instantly lynch a player of your choice. If the player is a [color=Honeydew]Camelotian[/color] or [color=Lightseagreen]Neutral[/color], you will lose your passives immediately and commit suicide publicly tommorow morning. - 1 use
**Check Alliance (Night)** - Force Target1 to check and see if Target2 is on their team. [color=Lightseagreen]Neutrals[/color] will appear as compatible no matter what. - Infinite uses
*GOAL: Survive to see the execution of all whom wish destruction upon your Kingdom.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Reeve&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]The Reeve[/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Social[/color]**
**No work? No privacy. (Passive)** You will receive a list of classes who have not done a night action at the end of each night.
**Get back to Work (Day)** - Force a player to use a Day Ability (if they have one) on a target or your choice. The ability will not expend a use. - Infinite uses
**Oversight (Night)** - Publicly announce the Reeve is watching. At the end of the day, the current King and you will receive a list of players who posted less than 20 posts per day for the entire game. A class type pairing will be given to them. Not usable Day One. - 2 uses
**Supervision (Night)** - Talk to a player. A 200 character message from each party will be sent via the host. The target will only see that they are talking to the Reeve. - 5 uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Squire&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Squire[/color]
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Investigative[/color]**
**Next Generation (Passive)** - You survive the first attack on your life but a random Knight of the Round Table dies instead.
**Pat-Down (Night)** - You will see if they have any weapons on their person. You will be able to tell if they are a Killer. - Three uses
**Snoop (Night)** - Snoop in a Player’s quarters. You will be told flavor-text of a random passive they may have. - Infinite uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Merlin&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Merlin[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Special[/color]**
**Mage’s Rites (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and the first attack on your life will fail.
**Activate Rite (Day)** - Activate one of the rites you have created. If you have multiple created, you will be able to decide which one to use. You may target yourself. - Infinite uses
**Rite of Sight (Night)** - Create a minor spell that shields a target player from negative effects excluding death. Will activate the night *Activate Rite* is used. - 3 uses
**Rite of Courage (Night)** - Create a spell that gives a target player enough courage to publicly announce their class. Will activate the same day *Activate Rite* is used. - 2 uses
**Rite of Resurrection (Night)** - Create a spell that gives a dead target player a new chance at life. They will be publicly revived with their old class but with half as many uses. Will activate the day after *Activate Rite* is used. - 1 use
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Provost&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Provost[/color] 🎉
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Investigative[/color]**
**Royal Papers (Passive)** - Immune to occupation.
**Scrutiny (Day)** - Investigate a player. If they are neutral, you will know. - 3 uses
**Investigation (Night)** - Investigate a player. If they are Neutral or Traitorous, they will come up as positive. However, if you visit a Killer class type, you will die. - Infinite uses
**Eagle Sight (Night)** - Look around a player’s room. You will be able to tell what their mindset is based off how they decorate their room. Does not count as visiting. - Infinite uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Maiden&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]Maiden[/color]
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Offensive[/color]**
**Maiden in Distress (Passive)** - If no one visits you, a random Knight of the Round Table will be forcibly redirected to you. Bypasses immunity.
**Kidnapped (Day)** - Find out a Knight of the Round Table at the start of the night. You will be unable to use Reward on anyone other than them for a night. - Infinite uses
**Reward (Night)** - Occupy a target player. This ability will bypass immunity. - Infinite uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;Minstrel&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Honeydew]The Minstrel[/color]
&gt; **[color=Honeydew]Camelotian Support[/color]**
**Musician’s Lute (Passive)** - Immune to occupation but not redirection.
**Concert (Day)** - Empower all Player’s abilities. Killing abilities will bypass immunity, occupation will bypass occupation immunity, etc. for one night. Players will not be told of this. - 1 use
**Tale of the Bard (Night)** - Empower a target player. They will receive an empowered ability according to their class. This ability will be one-use. - Infinite uses
*Goal: Eliminate all whom wish to destroy the Kingdom of Camelot.*

[/details]

## Traitorous
**Our scouts have found their headquarters! However, they do not have any information to report yet.**
## Neutrals

[details=&quot;Alchemist&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Lightseagreen]The Alchemist[/color] 🎉
&gt; **[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral Offensive[/color]**
**Alchemist’s Herbs (Passive)** - Immune to nightshade and bleeding.
**Drugged Potion (Day)** - Randomly assign a player a random status(Nightshade, Bleeding, Night Immunity, etc.) the player will not be notified which was given. - Infinite uses
**Stoneskin Potion (Day)** - Drink a potion that causes your skin to turn harder than stone. All attacks will fail even if it bypasses night immunity. - 3 Uses
**Emerald Potion (Night)** - Cause the player to not be able to talk during the day. If they give information, they will be mod-killed. - 3 uses
**Infectious Touch (Night)** - Cause a player to contract the Plague. They will die in two nights. - 2 uses
*Survive to the end of the game.*
[/details]


[details=“The Lovers&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Lightseagreen]The Lovers[/color]
&gt; **[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral Special[/color]**
**Love at first sight (Passive)** - Two of this class will always spawn if one spawns.
**Cupid’s Arrow (Day)** - If both *The Lovers* use this ability on the same day, then they will be given a grouping of four which will contain their True Love. Usable after Day Three. - 1 Use
**Love’s Wings (Night)** - Make your True Love immune tonight. - 1 Use
**True Love (Night)** - Occupy a player. If they are also *The Lovers* then you win. Bypasses occupation immunity. - 2 uses
*Goal: Survive with your True Love. If either of you die, you lose.*
[/details]


[details=&quot;Agravain&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Lightseagreen]Agravain[/color] :shield: 🎉
&gt; **[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral Killer[/color]**
**Obsession &amp; Compulsion (Passive)** - Immune to death, occupation, poison, bleeding and all negative ailments other than execution. You will instantly recognize(notified) whom ??? is when they appear.
**Master of Mechanics (Passive)** - You will receive the full list of class cards &amp; what the bastard mechanic(s) is for each of them.
**Bastard Sensing (Day)** - Instantly receive the name of the first person who activates a bastard mechanic today or tonight and what bastard mechanic was activated. This ability will not be refunded if no class-based bastard mechanic is initiated. - 3 uses
**Meeting (Day)** - You can call a meeting with ??? tonight, allowing the two of you to converse privately. The host will make the chat. - 3 uses
**Arrogant Slaying(Night)** - Kill the target player. Players killed will not flip during the day phase but you will know what class they were and will receive their journal if they had one. Bypasses night immunity.  - Infinite uses
**Speedy Assassination (Night)** - Kill the target player. You may also choose another player to occupy since you killed the other player quickly. Optionally, you may choose to kill two players instead. - 3 uses
*Eliminate all those who oppose your reign over Camelot. You may spare ???.*
[/details]

[details=“Wind Spirit”]
&gt; ## [color=Lightseagreen]Wind Spirit[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral Offensive[/color]**
**Protection of the Wind (Passive)** - Immune to bleeding and poison. You are immune to death and occupation but not redirection on nights where you do not use an ability.
**Closing Pressure (Day)** - Change the win condition of a neutral to that of your own. If you target a Camelotian or Traitor, it will fail. - 1 use
**Whirlwind (Night)** - Target two players. Anyone who visits them will be redirected to the other. Bypasses occupation/redirection immunity. - Infinite uses
**Wind Storm (Night)** - Cause a violent storm to brew outside the castle. All players will be redirected to a random player, bypassing occupation/redirection immunity. -  1 use
*Goal: Do not let any Neutrals die.*
[/details]

[details=&quot;~~The Wandering Priest~~&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=Lightseagreen]The Wandering Priest[/color] :shield: 🎉
&gt; **[color=Lightseagreen]Neutral Investigative[/color]**
**The Bastard Cycle (Passive)** - You acknowledge the fact that demons are the cause of the bastard mechanics of the game. An unknown amount of demons will spawn randomly spread out through the player base. Players with a demon residing in them will receive bastard mechanics of an unknown origin. You may target dead players with your abilities. You may not have any demons residing inside you.
**Confession (Day)** - Tell how how many demons reside in the player. The result will only be given to you. - Infinite uses
**Unorthodox Methods (Day)** - Perform a exorcism. A demon will be instantly released out of the bastard cycle. - Infinite
**Transmorgify (Night)** - Forcibly relocate demons from target 1 to the target 2. - Infinite uses
**Devilsbane (Night)** - Place Devilsbane on a player, keeping demons from relocating to that player and randomly spreading any demons inside them. - Three uses
*Goal: Remove 75% of the demons that spawned in the game. You do not need to survive until the end of the game as long as you have completed your task.*
[/details]

# Change Log
**1.1:** Removed Alchemist’s Neutrality Passive (If lynched, town will feel bad and will not lynch during the next day phase.)
**1.2:** Added *The Lovers* class, a Neutral Special.
**1.3:** Added *King Arthur*, the King Figure.
**1.4:** Added the Neutral Killer, *Agravain*. Information regarding ??? was expunged before posting.
**1.5:** Added Provost, a Camelotian Investigative also known as the Sheriffs of the Era.
**1.6:** Added Botanist, a Camelotian Support whom heals the citizens of the castle.
**1.7:** Added Herald, a Camelotian Social whom is perfect for a certain player.
**1.8:** Added the Reeve, a Camelotian Social which hates people who slack off and dont speak!
**1.9:** Added the Wandering Priest, a Neutral Investigative that limits the bastard mechanics in the game!
**1.9.1:** Added Maelgwn a Camelotian Support??? with Royal Blood and has the power of a dragon.
**1.9.2:** Nerfed alot of Camelotian Classes</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:29:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>/metwo</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/163">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/163</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-163</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/pre sign up as player if possible…</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/162">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/162</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-162</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everyone bad?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/161">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/161</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-161</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You didn’t deny it <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/160">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/160</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-160</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/orangeandblack5">@orangeandblack5</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/159">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/159</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-159</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Errr sure?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/158">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/158</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-158</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/157">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/157</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-157</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Add a class that converts other people into fools and I will play. THAT is fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/156">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/156</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-156</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Examples of “fun” pls</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/155">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/155</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-155</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/154">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/154</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-154</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It looked p fun to me. The only reason I didnt join was the insane bastardness of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/153">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/153</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-153</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And when tf was this game supposed to be fun</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/152">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/152</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-152</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>makes it a FoL Reskin</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/151">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/151</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-151</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Make sure you keep lots of the fun stuff though, don’t pull it back to just a FoL reskin</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/150">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/150</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-150</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also removed Wandering Priest since its hard on hosts + its bastard exclusive</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/149">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/149</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-149</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mordred is now a generic assassin l0l</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/148">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/148</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-148</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>King Arthur is now dead in dis game xD</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/147">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/147</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-147</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/146">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/146</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-146</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Was I that bad l0l</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/145">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/145</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-145</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Im nerfing King Arthur hard l0l</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/144">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/144</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-144</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Toooo be honessst I dont think im going to take a co-host this time l0l</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/143">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/143</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-143</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Lol</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/142">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/142</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-142</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>*casually pre-signing as Co-Host</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/141">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/141</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-141</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you want a hand again pm me</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/140">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/140</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-140</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FM] Camelot Class Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scum was op cuz no one knew what they did</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/139">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637/139</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 18:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58637-139</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fm-camelot-class-cards/58637.rss">[FM] Camelot Class Cards</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
