<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Ravings of a Madman [Cult Leader]</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425</link>
    <description>The man walked slowly down the corridor and out of Castle Demwir, the words echoing in his head, &quot;What on earth is Corax, not another one of those voices I hope, like that &#39;Mithras&#39; fellow&quot;, &quot;oh do stop wasting my time, I have important business to attend to&quot;, &quot;you&#39;re mad, just get out already!&quot;, his hand clenched into a fist and he punched the wall, it hurt and tore off some skin, he gritted his teeth.
He stepped out into the frosty midwinter&#39;s evening, the ice cold air stung his fresh wound, but he had made up his mind, he was to leave this place and find proof! proof that the men, no, not men, the gods that spoke with him at night were real, he knew they were, but the others were foolish, 
on and on through the night he walked, looking out into the darkness, &quot;Masters!&quot;, he cried, &quot;Masters show me a sign! Prove to me that you are real and that I am not a fool for trusting you!&quot;, but there was nothing... &quot;I see! Of course, I understand&quot;, the man cried into the inky blackness of the night, &quot;I must prove my worth to you! A sacrifice is in order!&quot;, he looked back and saw nothing but the night, he knew he could not turn back, he had to keep moving forward, he was cold, alone and afraid, at last after days of travel he saw it! Castle Adiart!
He broke into a sprint as he ran towards it, but quickly ran out of energy, he had not eaten for a week, and the only water he had been able to drink was from rivers and whatever snow or rain he could catch in his mouth, he collapsed at the door, a servant brought him in, and, seeing his robes, though him to be of a noble status, so quickly hurried to get him some nourishment, he sat with the strange man and listened to the man&#39;s ramblings, about Mithras and Corax, his mission, and the sacrifice he had to make, the servant was hooked, and told the man that he would help with the sacrifice, but in return wished for his own life to be spared, the man agreed, and the two took their places in the castle court, and they waited for a sign... a sign to begin their quest, together.

Author&#39;s Comments:
It&#39;s probably dumb d:
and I should work on the ending it seems rushed</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 20:36:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Ravings of a Madman [Cult Leader]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PolikShadowbliss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dumb?  This is actually pretty good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-425-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Ravings of a Madman [Cult Leader]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Ravings of a Madman [Cult Leader]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The man walked slowly down the corridor and out of Castle Demwir, the words echoing in his head, “What on earth is Corax, not another one of those voices I hope, like that ‘Mithras’ fellow”, “oh do stop wasting my time, I have important business to attend to”, “you’re mad, just get out already!”, his hand clenched into a fist and he punched the wall, it hurt and tore off some skin, he gritted his teeth.<br>
He stepped out into the frosty midwinter’s evening, the ice cold air stung his fresh wound, but he had made up his mind, he was to leave this place and find proof! proof that the men, no, not men, the gods that spoke with him at night were real, he knew they were, but the others were foolish,<br>
on and on through the night he walked, looking out into the darkness, “Masters!”, he cried, “Masters show me a sign! Prove to me that you are real and that I am not a fool for trusting you!”, but there was nothing… “I see! Of course, I understand”, the man cried into the inky blackness of the night, “I must prove my worth to you! A sacrifice is in order!”, he looked back and saw nothing but the night, he knew he could not turn back, he had to keep moving forward, he was cold, alone and afraid, at last after days of travel he saw it! Castle Adiart!<br>
He broke into a sprint as he ran towards it, but quickly ran out of energy, he had not eaten for a week, and the only water he had been able to drink was from rivers and whatever snow or rain he could catch in his mouth, he collapsed at the door, a servant brought him in, and, seeing his robes, though him to be of a noble status, so quickly hurried to get him some nourishment, he sat with the strange man and listened to the man’s ramblings, about Mithras and Corax, his mission, and the sacrifice he had to make, the servant was hooked, and told the man that he would help with the sacrifice, but in return wished for his own life to be spared, the man agreed, and the two took their places in the castle court, and they waited for a sign… a sign to begin their quest, together.</p>
<p>Author’s Comments:<br>
It’s probably dumb d:<br>
and I should work on the ending it seems rushed</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 19:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-425-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-ravings-of-a-madman-cult-leader/425.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Ravings of a Madman [Cult Leader]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
