<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958</link>
    <description>**Merchant** (BD Support) - Converts to **Dealer** (Support) if Unseen or Ritualist if Cult
 
Day Ability 1: Open Trade (**Merchant/Dealer**)
Select 2 players. At the beginning of the night they will get an icon that tells them that a trade was offered with another player whose name and number will be included in the icon. Each player may accept or reject the trade. If both players accept the trade, they will each be informed of whether the other&#39;s night ability resulted in a successful visit, if they stayed home (did nothing or visits do not count such as mystic and prince), if they were occupied, or if their visit was prevented. If one or both players reject the deal, a message will be displayed to both players stating that a deal could not be made. If one of the players making the deal is jailed, it will tell the other player they were prevented. If a player&#39;s night ability fails (such as a failed convert), the other player will be told it was a success, since the player must only successfully visit, not successfully perform their action. Effective only that night. Jailed targets can make deals normally. Cannot target self or king. 3 charges.
**Shortened text**: Allow 2 players the opportunity to share whether they are successful in visiting another player tonight.


Night Ability 1: Empowered Merchandise (**Merchant/Dealer**)
Select 1 player. That player&#39;s night action will be successful. The player can ignore occupy immunity and will be able to visit targets even if the visit should be prevented. Does not allow the empowered player to ignore death immunity. The mastermind&#39;s occupy immunity will not be stripped, but the player attempting the action on the mastermind will think their action was successful (like butler and drunk currently). Grants the empowered player occupy immunity for the night. Empowered players can kill jailed players. The player will not know they are being empowered but will instead get their usual success message. Cannot target self or king. Infinite charges.
**Shortened text**: Ensure a player&#39;s night action is successful.

Night Ability 2: Pay Off (**Merchant**)
Select 1 player. That player becomes immune to conversion that night. The player will not receive a message. You will know if a conversion was prevented. Cannot target self or king. 3 charges.

Night Ability 2: Make Disappear (**Dealer**)
Select 1 player. That player&#39;s logs will not be found by the court if they die tonight.(They will not be blank; there will be nothing at all.) 2 charges.

Lore:
I&#39;m sure someone will come up with better lore than I can.

Comments:
I wanted to make a fun double-edged sword for the BD. Empowering other players could be very rewarding or very costly if used unwisely. In the early game, a merchant should pay off random targets before he knows other players&#39; classes. When the game gets rolling, the merchant can choose to empower BD players who have come out if he believes they need it. If the player the merchant empowers gets converted, however, the merchant will only cause more trouble for the BD so he must be careful. Open Trade is an interesting way to get players to trust or mistrust each other as well as reveal small amounts of information that can only be useful when combined with other factors. The dealer can use Open Trade on his assassin and mastermind to ease communication and merchants/dealers can use the ability to prove their existence at night. It should be fairly easy to claim merchant since the only real confirm-able ability is Open Trade, but since this confirm-ability exists they shouldn&#39;t suffer the fate of court wizards and knights. Merchant is a pretty good possessor claim since the possessor can say he&#39;ll prove himself that night and then simply jump to another player. Make Disappear is a strong tool that the Unseen should use carefully on investigative classes to hide as much information as possible. Use of this ability will alert the court to the existence of a Dealer since the logs of the victim will not be found. If a Merchant/Dealer turns into assassin, he may be found for not using his day ability or may successfully convince the court he ran out of charges. Furthermore, I wanted to poke holes in logs and in jail, which currently have no weaknesses with Empowered Merchandise and Make Disappear.

I&#39;m open to changing the names of any abilities.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 05:13:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scarman12158" data-post="7" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Scarman12158:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s similar, yes but more applicable since it’s not exclusively for killers and it doesn’t ignore death immunity. I’m not sure if similarity to another ability is supposed to be a criticism. I wrote that it has infinite charges since this is the Merchant’s main ability.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The problem isn’t the Merchant here. The problem is the Dealer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 05:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scarman12158" data-post="7" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Scarman12158:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s so you have some proof when you get accused (unlike cw, knight).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s why it is bad.</p>
<p>If I’m NK or starting Assassin or whatever I cannot claim this class because of this ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 05:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scarman12158]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="6" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sooo… nerfed CW.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes. CW is getting changed and I want to retain the anti-conversion ability, but it’s not necessarily weaker because it doesn’t block occupy. This makes butler checks more accurate since it can’t be a false positive like with current Magic Barrier.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="6" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Basically an unlimited use frenzy. Maybe not but you didn’t specify a number of charges. In either case it is a better frenzy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s similar, yes but more applicable since it’s not exclusively for killers and it doesn’t ignore death immunity. I’m not sure if similarity to another ability is supposed to be a criticism. I wrote that it has infinite charges since this is the Merchant’s main ability.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="6" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Eww. I confirmable investigative day ability.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It functions the same way as telepathy in terms of confirmability. It’s so you have some proof when you get accused (unlike cw, knight). In fact, it may even be weaker since you can’t do it during the day and you’d have to convince the court to let you live until the next night. It doesn’t automatically make you innocent since dealer has it too and unless you come out and say it, no one will know who the merchant is based solely on Open Trade.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 02:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scarman12158" data-post="1" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Scarman12158:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night Ability 2: Pay Off (Merchant)</p>
<p>Select 1 player. That player becomes immune to conversion that night. The player will not receive a message. You will know if a conversion was prevented. Cannot target self or king. 3 charges.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sooo… nerfed CW.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scarman12158" data-post="1" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Scarman12158:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night Ability 1: Empowered Merchandise (Merchant/Dealer)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Basically an unlimited use frenzy. Maybe not but you didn’t specify a number of charges. In either case it is a better frenzy.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scarman12158" data-post="1" data-topic="54958">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Scarman12158:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Day Ability 1: Open Trade (Merchant/Dealer)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Eww. I confirmable investigative day ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 16:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Faction?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 16:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Neuts out reee</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 15:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scarman12158]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Perhaps. I tried to imply (drug) dealer or (arms) dealer with the unseen name. Some unseen counterparts have names that aren’t explicitly threatening, like aristocrat and sage, so I tried to make it fit with them. You’re right that the dealer’s unique ability is very sinister, even though he doesn’t kill his target himself. I appreciate the feedback.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 18:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[anon98616575]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is a very unique class idea, and since I can’t really compare it to anything, it would be fun to try. Well done.</p>
<p>I feel like Crimelord would fit better as a name for the Dealer though. His abilities fit a very… shadowy lore.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 16:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Merchant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scarman12158]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Merchant</strong> (BD Support) - Converts to <strong>Dealer</strong> (Support) if Unseen or Ritualist if Cult</p>
<p>Day Ability 1: Open Trade (<strong>Merchant/Dealer</strong>)<br>
Select 2 players. At the beginning of the night they will get an icon that tells them that a trade was offered with another player whose name and number will be included in the icon. Each player may accept or reject the trade. If both players accept the trade, they will each be informed of whether the other’s night ability resulted in a successful visit, if they stayed home (did nothing or visits do not count such as mystic and prince), if they were occupied, or if their visit was prevented. If one or both players reject the deal, a message will be displayed to both players stating that a deal could not be made. If one of the players making the deal is jailed, it will tell the other player they were prevented. If a player’s night ability fails (such as a failed convert), the other player will be told it was a success, since the player must only successfully visit, not successfully perform their action. Effective only that night. Jailed targets can make deals normally. Cannot target self or king. 3 charges.<br>
<strong>Shortened text</strong>: Allow 2 players the opportunity to share whether they are successful in visiting another player tonight.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: Empowered Merchandise (<strong>Merchant/Dealer</strong>)<br>
Select 1 player. That player’s night action will be successful. The player can ignore occupy immunity and will be able to visit targets even if the visit should be prevented. Does not allow the empowered player to ignore death immunity. The mastermind’s occupy immunity will not be stripped, but the player attempting the action on the mastermind will think their action was successful (like butler and drunk currently). Grants the empowered player occupy immunity for the night. Empowered players can kill jailed players. The player will not know they are being empowered but will instead get their usual success message. Cannot target self or king. Infinite charges.<br>
<strong>Shortened text</strong>: Ensure a player’s night action is successful.</p>
<p>Night Ability 2: Pay Off (<strong>Merchant</strong>)<br>
Select 1 player. That player becomes immune to conversion that night. The player will not receive a message. You will know if a conversion was prevented. Cannot target self or king. 3 charges.</p>
<p>Night Ability 2: Make Disappear (<strong>Dealer</strong>)<br>
Select 1 player. That player’s logs will not be found by the court if they die tonight.(They will not be blank; there will be nothing at all.) 2 charges.</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
I’m sure someone will come up with better lore than I can.</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
I wanted to make a fun double-edged sword for the BD. Empowering other players could be very rewarding or very costly if used unwisely. In the early game, a merchant should pay off random targets before he knows other players’ classes. When the game gets rolling, the merchant can choose to empower BD players who have come out if he believes they need it. If the player the merchant empowers gets converted, however, the merchant will only cause more trouble for the BD so he must be careful. Open Trade is an interesting way to get players to trust or mistrust each other as well as reveal small amounts of information that can only be useful when combined with other factors. The dealer can use Open Trade on his assassin and mastermind to ease communication and merchants/dealers can use the ability to prove their existence at night. It should be fairly easy to claim merchant since the only real confirm-able ability is Open Trade, but since this confirm-ability exists they shouldn’t suffer the fate of court wizards and knights. Merchant is a pretty good possessor claim since the possessor can say he’ll prove himself that night and then simply jump to another player. Make Disappear is a strong tool that the Unseen should use carefully on investigative classes to hide as much information as possible. Use of this ability will alert the court to the existence of a Dealer since the logs of the victim will not be found. If a Merchant/Dealer turns into assassin, he may be found for not using his day ability or may successfully convince the court he ran out of charges. Furthermore, I wanted to poke holes in logs and in jail, which currently have no weaknesses with Empowered Merchandise and Make Disappear.</p>
<p>I’m open to changing the names of any abilities.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 23:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54958-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-merchant/54958.rss">[Class Suggestion] Merchant</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
