<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The toxicity of players</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302</link>
    <description>Hello everyone, first off I would like to say I have been enjoying this game thoroughly  for a bit now (It is very very addicting and I can&#39;t set it down I swear.) This being said I never thought of making a forum account until I went through a recent game of mine. 

To bring in some backstory, I played a game as an alchemist (legit, not a Neutral killer etc) Healed the king n1 (as a good little alch) and he was attacked. Next day told him I was an alch and healed him to which he said he was neutral and wanted me to only heal him. A couple days past a couple people died, that night I decided to go poison a cult (King dies of course.) End game comes around and this player curses me out, calling me a lot of profane words etc. stating that I had only one job.. I paid this no mind since a lot of people get toxic (I did report for harassment not sure if that&#39;s a valid report or not but ok.) One thing he said to me stuck out &quot;I will remember your name and next game I&#39;m gonna kill you n1&quot; Whatever.. Next game comes around, I&#39;m hunter and survive n1 (Bear thankfully) only to have a random player ask for my logs d2 and everyone follows. Told him who I was and that I bear&#39;d the previous night to which he said &quot;Lol exe this only newbs bear n1&quot; (King who was new used thumb to exe me) killed phys and me.. Found out after I was dead that this was the king from the previous game.. His logs even said &quot;If I die exe 3 (Which was my number this game).. First thing he said to me was &quot;How does it feel?&quot; Then proceeds to convince other dead that his motives were justified that I threw the game previously for BD etc etc... 

What I am trying to give feedback on or a suggestion is I would like a way to be notified that my reports have been handled and proper punishment has been dealt out.. I understand people have bad days and bad games, but to literally follow someone to purposely throw the game and get them killed is just wrong. I know League of Legends has a system sorta like the one I am suggesting Simply stating that when a report was valid there was a generic thank you for filing the report and that it had been taken care of... I would also like to ask if you could extend the amount of characters required in a report. As I could not possibly fit the entire situation into that chat box (did the best I could). 

Again thank you all for the wonderful game you have made.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 09:39:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s been discussions about handing out thank you notes to people who successfully report people who get a punishment.<br>
At the moment a system like that would be very time consuming, since reports are handled manually.</p>
<p>Also I want to add; What a childish thing to do. “You didn’t heal me one game therefore I want you dead always”<br>
You weren’t the one who attacked him so… And I lol’d at "gamethrew for BD by not healing neut as neut "</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 09:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, change up your name to help avoid that crap.</p>
<p>Still, that’s pretty beyond the pale.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 17:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would be so salty if somebody did that to me. Sorry, bro.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 16:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apparently so, and that was your mistake.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 13:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He said you threw the game for BD… as an Alchemist… who didn’t heal a neutral King?</p>
<p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s definitely reportable, so hopefully mods pick up on it.</p>
<p>Did you use the same name as the previous game?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh well, they will learn.</p>
<p>This game required money to play <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>But I am sorry that it happens to you, hope he get punished <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 07:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The toxicity of players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Womarthehammer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello everyone, first off I would like to say I have been enjoying this game thoroughly  for a bit now (It is very very addicting and I can’t set it down I swear.) This being said I never thought of making a forum account until I went through a recent game of mine.</p>
<p>To bring in some backstory, I played a game as an alchemist (legit, not a Neutral killer etc) Healed the king n1 (as a good little alch) and he was attacked. Next day told him I was an alch and healed him to which he said he was neutral and wanted me to only heal him. A couple days past a couple people died, that night I decided to go poison a cult (King dies of course.) End game comes around and this player curses me out, calling me a lot of profane words etc. stating that I had only one job… I paid this no mind since a lot of people get toxic (I did report for harassment not sure if that’s a valid report or not but ok.) One thing he said to me stuck out “I will remember your name and next game I’m gonna kill you n1” Whatever… Next game comes around, I’m hunter and survive n1 (Bear thankfully) only to have a random player ask for my logs d2 and everyone follows. Told him who I was and that I bear’d the previous night to which he said “Lol exe this only newbs bear n1” (King who was new used thumb to exe me) killed phys and me… Found out after I was dead that this was the king from the previous game… His logs even said "If I die exe 3 (Which was my number this game)… First thing he said to me was “How does it feel?” Then proceeds to convince other dead that his motives were justified that I threw the game previously for BD etc etc…</p>
<p>What I am trying to give feedback on or a suggestion is I would like a way to be notified that my reports have been handled and proper punishment has been dealt out… I understand people have bad days and bad games, but to literally follow someone to purposely throw the game and get them killed is just wrong. I know League of Legends has a system sorta like the one I am suggesting Simply stating that when a report was valid there was a generic thank you for filing the report and that it had been taken care of… I would also like to ask if you could extend the amount of characters required in a report. As I could not possibly fit the entire situation into that chat box (did the best I could).</p>
<p>Again thank you all for the wonderful game you have made.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 04:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-22302-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-toxicity-of-players/22302.rss">The toxicity of players</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
