<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792</link>
    <description>The most important part of the game for any non-Blue Dragon player, is making sure you aren&#39;t executed when accused or in jail - so you need to work out what to claim to avoid being zapped/slashed with a sword/bruatalised with an axe/set alight/any other execution styles I can&#39;t recall. This list is made mostly with scum in mind (Cult/Unseen/Neutral Killers), but is still useful for any neutral Non-BD role as well. I won&#39;t divert too much attention to the idea of sticking to your original class if converted, as that is usually what you should do. I also will not consider the &#39;Fool&#39; role in this list,as that needs an entirely different topic for strategy - and I will not consider it as a potential claim or &#39;soft&#39; defence. I will grade the claims, starting with the worst, ending in the best.

One last thing. Never claim to be the third of any class. Just don&#39;t.

1) [color=grey]**Scorned**[/color]
Seriously? Why not just claim evil? I&#39;ve never seen a scorned not killed upon claiming. Just don&#39;t. 

2) **[color=blue]Psychic[/color]**
This is a terrible claim. People will expect you to send a message or force someone&#39;s vote to prove this role. If you can&#39;t, you&#39;re dead. Never claim psychic unless you are a psychic or an [color=purple]**Illusionist**[/color]. However, people will also expect you to link minds every night. Expect to die when you can&#39;t anymore!

3) [color=blue]**Priest**[/color]
A garbage fake claim now. You will be Counter claimed by the real one (as there is little risk of being killed as it, and it is now convert immune) and the real one can prove itself too easily. Just don&#39;t claim Priest.

4) **[color=blue]Prince[/color]**
Another really bad claim. The Prince is unlikely to Counter-claim you (IE: Call you out as a liar publically) and just quietly execute you at night. So although you probably won&#39;t be lynched claiming it, you have little to no chance of long term survival. Also, being unique, if one is already dead, claiming Prince is a death sentence.

5) **Silence**
This is the absence of saying anything. You need to stand there and say nothing as you are voted up and tried. This requires nerves of steel to pull off, and will only work in a game with a confirmed or suspected [color=grey]**Reaper**[/color] present. Best done if you haven&#39;t spoken all day as people might vote you down, thinking you are reaped. Can also work if you suddenly &#39;clam up&#39; as people are voting you as people might think that the Reaper sent a chill down your spine to silence you. However, the risk with the former is that you need to die the following day or be lynched as you clearly weren&#39;t reaped, and the latter is that people may not realise/believe that chilling touch was what happened to you. Also, in both scenarios, people might lynch you anyway &#39;just in case&#39;. This claim should only be used if your previous fake role is no longer possible or not believable and you don&#39;t have time to plan a different one.

6) [color=blue]**Drunk**[/color]
his class leaves feedback on all it&#39;s abilities so needs to be converted from it to work. Just don&#39;t claim this class as anything other than maybe [color=purple]**Alcoholic**[/color]. Also, with that royal blood passive, you&#39;d better have a good reason to not step up as king.

7) [color=grey]**Mercenary**[/color] 
This claim should only be made if you are a mercenary or **[color=purple]Sellsword[/color]** who has guarded their target at least once, as this role will leave feedback. Your contract might back you up, but even that might not be enough.  Alternatively, you can try claiming this and saying a fellow unseen/cult is your contract, but that again requires putting your team mates at risk should the claim not work. High risk to claim this role in jail, I tend to execute mercenary claims in jail.

8) **[color=blue]Noble[/color]**
This is not as bad as it used to be. As nobles live separate lives now, it does not require cooperation from other players to pull off. However, you better have been noisy with the orders ability, or use private maters frequently, or be an [color=purple]**Aristocrat**[/color] because this claim won&#39;t keep you alive for long.

9) **[color=grey]Alchemist[/color]**
The recent buffings make this class much better for BD to keep alive. However, it is still a neutral, so when the chips are down and a reaper hunt is on - you won&#39;t survive unless you have provable healings on your side.

10) [color=blue]**Hunter**[/color]
This is really not the best claim. This is unique, the real hunter will call you out, and you can&#39;t &#39;Wolf&#39; anyone either. Avoid claiming unless you are certain there is no real hunter in the game, or you are converted from Hunter.

11) [color=blue]**Butler**[/color]
Although you can maybe get away with faking this role, it is best to only claim this if you are a [color=purple]**Servant**[/color] or at least one promoted to assassin, or an [color=bronze]**Invoker**[/color] or [color=bronze]**Cult Leader**[/color] who was one. You can try to claim the actions of a real Butler to force a potential mislynch/escape execution. However, your lifespan would be limited unless Evils win within a day or two. Alternatively, you could try claiming occupying team mates, but that requires them to claim occupied or back up your claim - which is a risk should your claim not work.

12) [color=blue]**Court Wizard**[/color]
Court Wizard is a relatively easy class to fake, as magic barrier is the only &#39;spammable&#39; ability. However, this claim is pretty weak and may be picked off for that reason. Also, [color=blue]**Observer**[/color] will know you are lying, so if you are followed you are screwed.

13) [color=blue]**Observer**[/color]
The longer the game goes on, the harder this role becomes to fake - as your journal will need to be filled with information, and the more you have to fake the more likely someone will spot a hole in your claim. That said, this is fake-able, especially as [color=bronze]**Seeker**[/color] or [color=purple]**Nightwatch**[/color] for a short period of time.

14) [color=blue]**Princess**[/color]
A good claim for most scum, especially **[color=bronze]Seeker[/color]** or [color=purple]**Mastermind**[/color] since they can use their abilities to build a good journal. For other scum, it is harder to pull off unless using team mates classes to make fake results, or using dead people to fluff out a journal (Note: Journals full of dead people look suspicious) This is not unique, and quite hard to disprove as long as you keep a believable journal. Claiming you &#39;wisped&#39; is hard to disprove, especially if you sent the wisp to a team mate. Bonus points come in the form of you being able to get Neutral Killers called out for being immune to assassin/conversion as &#39;Killing roles&#39; in order to &#39;confirm yourself&#39;. Avoid stepping forward for king if you plan to claim Princess as anything other than a [color=purple]**Duchess**[/color], as people will ask why you didn&#39;t step up during the &#39;Royal Blood&#39; call

15) **[color=blue]Sheriff/Paladin[/color]**
Since neither is unique, this claim can work now. Despite that, there are risks involved. You can&#39;t simply claim sheriff/Paladin and then expect peace. You&#39;ll need results and an accurate, believable journal too. If unseen/cult, bus the other (non Mastermind if unseen) player at some point to earn some BD-cred and free up a slot for conversion from time to time. This is harder to prove as a Neutral killing role, so avoid as one of those classes. Also, don&#39;t claim sheriff in a cult game or Paladin in an Unseen game!

16) [color=blue]**Knight**[/color]
A fairly solid claim, especially if you are an assassin or Neutral Killer as this will get a Princess off your back. Guarding people is hard to disprove without observer interference, but you better have a good excuse prepared for why key Blue Dragons weren&#39;t guarded if they died. Furthermore, make sure your journal is better than &#39;Guarded king night 1/2/3/4/5/6/7 etc.&#39; as these look scummy usually. Also, as this is also a common scum claim, people are likely to take a risk and lynch Knight claims.

17) [color=blue]**Physician**[/color]
This claim can work to get you off the stand, and also the heal action is hard to disprove without an observer watching you or tracking you. However people might expect you to heal anyone if they are poisoned or bleeding. This is the best claim for [color=purple]**Herbalist**[/color] as you can drug people to fluff out your journal better. However, if a confirmed Prince dies, you&#39;ll have some explaining to do. Circumstances depending, usually a good claim.

Do you agree with my list? Do you have any suggestions/strategies to add? Post them below! I hope you find this guide helpful.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 21:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 15:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Physician needs to be indicated as “more difficult to claim.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 21:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No more priest, woot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 11:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Welp, need to edit it a little. The point is, fake claiming priest is terrible</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 23:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Moleland" data-post="1" data-topic="1792">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/moleland/40/5104_2.png" class="avatar"> Moleland:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A garbage fake claim now. You will be Counter claimed by the real one (as there is little risk of being killed as it, and it is now convert immune) and the real one dies once it’s job is done.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree with this and have seen people with this attitude in game.</p>
<p>Death Chat can win games and does win games. Priest is <em>incredibly</em> valuable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 21:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Updated for latest patch</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 12:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s a good point. I’ll update for that</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 18:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>new patch makes it so noble no longer crier</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 18:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Updated for latest patch</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/31</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 15:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scorned and fool claims should die, so Ye. Fake Butler can work, but if it goes wrong, it goes wrong big time, eh <a class="mention" href="/u/theplex">@ThePlex</a>?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 18:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was so satisfying to see that win screen. I just claimed something random to physic and it worked</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yep, I’ve had this strategy work a few times. High risk, but high reward, too.</p>
<p>Here’s another pro-tip: tell your Assassin that if he ever hits somebody immune at night, immediately have them say “I was attacked” and have another scum buddy claim physician and that they healed them. Haven’t seen this fail yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 16:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I once pulled off a butler claim as MM by me “occupying” my fellow and they would confirm that. I never got lynched and won the game</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 16:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think claiming Prince is fine if you KNOW you are screwed and will hang anyway. This has the potential to make BD pardon you for the day just to have the Prince execute you at night. This prevents the Prince from snagging another one of your teammates when you would have died anyway.</p>
<p>Sometimes the Prince even outs himself, which can be even better.</p>
<p>The only sucky thing about this strategy is that you can out an Evil King accidentally if he believes you are the real Prince and forces an Execute.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 16:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Me likey.</p>
<p>Although you put Scorned at the very top, I’ve seen WAY too many BD teams leave a “Scorned” alone for too long…</p>
<p>What do you think about claiming Fool, Mole? <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smirk.png?v=9" title=":smirk:" class="emoji" alt=":smirk:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 16:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Updated for current game meta</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 12:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>well if that develops than it will become good idea to claim scorned as evil to pretend to be fool.</p>
<p>it will likely end in your being executed by prince.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 18:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s a pro-tip: never claim Scorned unless you are Fool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 18:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What if Prince is dead?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 18:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Probably</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 17:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you will need to end up claiming anyway in dungeon</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 17:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not a perfect strat, but it can work</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 14:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>exactly. they were silent and still got executed</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 14:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Reaped people can’t talk lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 14:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>being silent gets you killed. Have seen actually reaped people do it several times before, they always die.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1792-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/fake-claim-guide-work-in-progress/1792.rss">Fake-claim guide (work in progress)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
