<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Suggestion] New Evil Faction: The Anarchists</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022</link>
    <description>**The Anarchists**


_For anarchists, title has no value when compared to the common cause. A world that gives power to those by birthright is a world worth reshaping._


* The Anarchist&#39;s objective is to eliminate all royalty/nobility classes and the neutral killer (Drunks, princesses, nobles, the prince and the current king).

* Anarchist members don&#39;t know who one another are initially and don&#39;t meet at night to talk. They must communicate via whispers during the day.

* Each match begins with 2 anarchists, and there can be up to 4 anarchist members at one time.
Every anarchist member is the same class: _The Revolutionary_

* The anarchists also win if one of their members manage to become king.




**Anarchist Class:** _The Revolutionary_

**Class Type:** Special (see below)

**Passives:**

_Chaotic Nature:_ When Investigated, will return a random class type. In addition, when being occupied, there is a 50% chance of showing the occupier that you are occupy immune (you will still be occupied however)

**Day Abilities:**

_True Motives_ (2 Uses): Reveal a member of the anarchists.

_Coded Messages_ (2 Uses): All whispers to and from you this day will be hidden.

_Conflagration_ (1 Use): Light someone on fire, they will burn to death in 2 days (Only available after 3 days of being an anarchist).

**Night Abilities:**

_Propaganda_ (Unlimited Uses) [1-Day Cooldown]: Convince your target to join the anarchists (Does not work on royalty or neutrals).

_Time Bomb_ (Unlimited Uses): Leave a clockwork bomb at the targeted player. It will explode in one day killing everyone who visits that night.



**New Blue Dragon Class:** _The Detective_

**Class Type:** Investigative

**Passives:**

**Day Abilities:**

_Decode_ (3 Uses): Reveal when target player uses a hidden whisper this day.

**Night Abilities:**

_Sleuth_ (Unlimited Uses): Determine if a player is a member of the Anarchists

_Thwart the Plot_ (2 Uses): Diffuse a planted bomb or prevent a bomb being planted at the targeted player (Cannot target yourself).



**Special Notes:**

* Since there is a very high chance that the king will die early on, only the Good King will spawn in this game.

* There will be at least 3 non-prince/king royalty classes that spawn for the BD to keep each match consistent.

* An Anarchist has to have been an Anarchist for two days before they can step forward as king.

* The Anarchists also win if the Sorcerer manages to become king, because they would&#39;ve become an Evil King. 



**Interaction Notes:**

* Coded Messages will return a random anarchist in chat excluding duplicates from the previous use.

* Time bomb&#39;s explosion functions the same way as the Sorcerer&#39;s _Circle of Death_.

* Propaganda will only return if the conversion was successful or not, not if the target is already an anarchist.

* Decode only informs the detective that a hidden whisper was used by the target, it doesn&#39;t show the 
recipient.


**Guarding against Time Bomb:**

* All types of guarding (King&#39;s guards, Knight, DK, Mercenary, and Hunter&#39;s bear) will prevent a bomb from being planted and function the same way as stopping a normal attack.

* The Mercenary&#39;s guard will protect both the target and the Mercenary from the explosion.

* The Knight/DK guard will save the target from the explosion, but sacrifice the defender.

* The King&#39;s guards/Hunter&#39;s bear will not protect against a bomb exploding.

* Debauching an anarchist&#39;s time bomb will prevent the bomb from being planted and will function the same as a normal debauched attack.

* Healing will save a target from dying to an explosion, but not prevent a bomb from being planted.


Let me know what you think or if you need any clarifications!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 12:27:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] New Evil Faction: The Anarchists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Aren’t these guys supposed to be a faction? It seems unfair that these guys have such an easy wincon. Just keep bombing the king until he dies and then step up. Since everyone in the faction can convert you will probably have converted a noble who can step up and win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 12:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39022-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022.rss">[Suggestion] New Evil Faction: The Anarchists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] New Evil Faction: The Anarchists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Curaga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the idea of hunting the royalty is super fun, but I think having random ability feedback would cause too much confusion. It would interrupt the “deduction” side of the game.</p>
<p>Having an enemy faction that doesn’t meet at night I also like, and using hidden whispers is a neat idea for that too. I do think, however, that just by having Nobles in the game, spying on hidden messages would already be taken care of. I think adding a special investigative class to also hunt for them might be unfair, especially considering how powerful his investigating abilities sound. I would say that Sheriff could work very well in an Anarchist game, since the Anarchists would be spreading so quickly that it would give his Scout ability more use.</p>
<p>I’m also uncertain about the time bomb being the method of killing, but I would have to try it to decide for certain. My problem with it is that it seems hard to understand for such an integral tool of the evil faction.</p>
<p>Regarding the king, having him <em>always</em> be good in one of these games would take away from the deduction aspect as well. Rather, let the king still be able to be allied with the Anarchists, but make a win condition of the Anarchists entail either having an evil/neutral king or having the good king die.</p>
<p>Overall, I like your idea!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 03:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39022-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022.rss">[Suggestion] New Evil Faction: The Anarchists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] New Evil Faction: The Anarchists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[revengeclaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Anarchists</strong></p>
<p><em>For anarchists, title has no value when compared to the common cause. A world that gives power to those by birthright is a world worth reshaping.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>The Anarchist’s objective is to eliminate all royalty/nobility classes and the neutral killer (Drunks, princesses, nobles, the prince and the current king).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anarchist members don’t know who one another are initially and don’t meet at night to talk. They must communicate via whispers during the day.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Each match begins with 2 anarchists, and there can be up to 4 anarchist members at one time.<br>
Every anarchist member is the same class: <em>The Revolutionary</em></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The anarchists also win if one of their members manage to become king.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Anarchist Class:</strong> <em>The Revolutionary</em></p>
<p><strong>Class Type:</strong> Special (see below)</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong></p>
<p><em>Chaotic Nature:</em> When Investigated, will return a random class type. In addition, when being occupied, there is a 50% chance of showing the occupier that you are occupy immune (you will still be occupied however)</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities:</strong></p>
<p><em>True Motives</em> (2 Uses): Reveal a member of the anarchists.</p>
<p><em>Coded Messages</em> (2 Uses): All whispers to and from you this day will be hidden.</p>
<p><em>Conflagration</em> (1 Use): Light someone on fire, they will burn to death in 2 days (Only available after 3 days of being an anarchist).</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities:</strong></p>
<p><em>Propaganda</em> (Unlimited Uses) [1-Day Cooldown]: Convince your target to join the anarchists (Does not work on royalty or neutrals).</p>
<p><em>Time Bomb</em> (Unlimited Uses): Leave a clockwork bomb at the targeted player. It will explode in one day killing everyone who visits that night.</p>
<p><strong>New Blue Dragon Class:</strong> <em>The Detective</em></p>
<p><strong>Class Type:</strong> Investigative</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities:</strong></p>
<p><em>Decode</em> (3 Uses): Reveal when target player uses a hidden whisper this day.</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities:</strong></p>
<p><em>Sleuth</em> (Unlimited Uses): Determine if a player is a member of the Anarchists</p>
<p><em>Thwart the Plot</em> (2 Uses): Diffuse a planted bomb or prevent a bomb being planted at the targeted player (Cannot target yourself).</p>
<p><strong>Special Notes:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Since there is a very high chance that the king will die early on, only the Good King will spawn in this game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There will be at least 3 non-prince/king royalty classes that spawn for the BD to keep each match consistent.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>An Anarchist has to have been an Anarchist for two days before they can step forward as king.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Anarchists also win if the Sorcerer manages to become king, because they would’ve become an Evil King.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Interaction Notes:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Coded Messages will return a random anarchist in chat excluding duplicates from the previous use.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Time bomb’s explosion functions the same way as the Sorcerer’s <em>Circle of Death</em>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Propaganda will only return if the conversion was successful or not, not if the target is already an anarchist.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Decode only informs the detective that a hidden whisper was used by the target, it doesn’t show the<br>
recipient.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Guarding against Time Bomb:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>All types of guarding (King’s guards, Knight, DK, Mercenary, and Hunter’s bear) will prevent a bomb from being planted and function the same way as stopping a normal attack.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Mercenary’s guard will protect both the target and the Mercenary from the explosion.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Knight/DK guard will save the target from the explosion, but sacrifice the defender.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The King’s guards/Hunter’s bear will not protect against a bomb exploding.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Debauching an anarchist’s time bomb will prevent the bomb from being planted and will function the same as a normal debauched attack.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Healing will save a target from dying to an explosion, but not prevent a bomb from being planted.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Let me know what you think or if you need any clarifications!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 03:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39022-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-new-evil-faction-the-anarchists/39022.rss">[Suggestion] New Evil Faction: The Anarchists</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
