<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Priest/Soulcatcher/Paladin Lore Idea</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/priest-soulcatcher-paladin-lore-idea/360</link>
    <description>So Fade and I (-cough- Mostly Fade -cough-) Wrote more lore ideas!~ 

Also, these lore is linked in with [url=http://forum.imperium42.com/t/photine-goddess-of-light-lore-idea-p/200]Photine&#39;s[/url] lore so you should probably check that out ;)

------------

[b]Lore Subject:[/b] Priest

[b]Lore:[/b] The Priest was born with the blessing of souls just like all her mother&#39;s before her of the course of 1000 years. She made a vow, that she would serve the goddess of light Photine by guiding all souls and combating all evil.

This blessing gives the Priest power over the very souls from the goddess Photine. The priest&#39;s main powers are to speak with the dead and even revive them once a year. However, there are other powers, that the Priest will not use because everyone will look down at her for it.

The Priest like the Paladin’s main goal is to stop Mithras from his evil but unlike the Paladin, the Priest focuses on guiding souls to a safe place, where Photine’s holy light, prevents Mithras from getting to them and other creatures.

The Priest came to Castle Adiart after she heard rumours of treason within those walls. As a supporter of the bluedragon, for their attempts at peace and how they kept the land safe for everyone. She rushed to the castle to support them, what she would find she would not believe.

-----

[b]Lore Subject:[/b] Soulcatcher

[b]Lore:[/b]As it turns out, not even the blessing of souls was able to prevent the Priest from joining the blackrose. Is that even a bad thing? After all, Photine only hates Mithras so would she even care if the Priest joined them?

The Soulcatcher now uses the blessing of souls to capture, as they depart from the deceased using them for her own gains. Her most famous use of the souls is using the last of their life force to cheat death, this causes great pain that will last 100 years to the soul but does not kill it. 
This form of magic is taboo but photine understands that the soulcatcher needs to use it to reach her goals but with sorrow to the souls that get hurt.

All the souls understand what has happened to her and what she intends to do to them. So the Soulcatcher understands it&#39;s pointless to talk with them anymore, she now focuses all her effect helping the blackrose instead of talking with the dead.

What did the Mastermind offer the Soulcatcher to join? How will this benefit her in the quest for Photine? Only time shall tell.

------

[b]Lore Subject:[/b] Paladin

[b]Lore:[/b] The Paladin was born with the blessing of justice, passed down from father to son over the course of 1000 years. The blessing of justice gives the Paladin the power to find and defeat the work of Mithras.

The blessing of justice grants the Paladin the ability to locate the area where the cult reside and kill them but that is not all, this blessing also allows the Paladin to protect those closest to him from the cult with a blessing of light that shields the mind from Mithras brainwashing.

The Paladin has been spent his life eliminating the cult, and other people who worship Mithras, and because of the blessing of justice he always knows where they reside.

Now the Paladin has come to Castle Adiart, with the knowledge that the cult is up to no good trying to destroy the bluedragon, and threaten the stability of the kingdom itself, in the name of Photine he will destroy them or die trying.

------

Fade will probably add some type of explanation/comments below ;) Cause after all he did most of the writing, he probably has the most explanation to this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 03:17:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/priest-soulcatcher-paladin-lore-idea/360.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Priest/Soulcatcher/Paladin Lore Idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Queen_Alfa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So Fade and I (-cough- Mostly Fade -cough-) Wrote more lore ideas!~</p>
<p>Also, these lore is linked in with <a href="http://forum.imperium42.com/t/photine-goddess-of-light-lore-idea-p/200" data-bbcode="true">Photine’s</a> lore so you should probably check that out <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lore Subject:</span> Priest</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lore:</span> The Priest was born with the blessing of souls just like all her mother’s before her of the course of 1000 years. She made a vow, that she would serve the goddess of light Photine by guiding all souls and combating all evil.</p>
<p>This blessing gives the Priest power over the very souls from the goddess Photine. The priest’s main powers are to speak with the dead and even revive them once a year. However, there are other powers, that the Priest will not use because everyone will look down at her for it.</p>
<p>The Priest like the Paladin’s main goal is to stop Mithras from his evil but unlike the Paladin, the Priest focuses on guiding souls to a safe place, where Photine’s holy light, prevents Mithras from getting to them and other creatures.</p>
<p>The Priest came to Castle Adiart after she heard rumours of treason within those walls. As a supporter of the bluedragon, for their attempts at peace and how they kept the land safe for everyone. She rushed to the castle to support them, what she would find she would not believe.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lore Subject:</span> Soulcatcher</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lore:</span>As it turns out, not even the blessing of souls was able to prevent the Priest from joining the blackrose. Is that even a bad thing? After all, Photine only hates Mithras so would she even care if the Priest joined them?</p>
<p>The Soulcatcher now uses the blessing of souls to capture, as they depart from the deceased using them for her own gains. Her most famous use of the souls is using the last of their life force to cheat death, this causes great pain that will last 100 years to the soul but does not kill it.<br>
This form of magic is taboo but photine understands that the soulcatcher needs to use it to reach her goals but with sorrow to the souls that get hurt.</p>
<p>All the souls understand what has happened to her and what she intends to do to them. So the Soulcatcher understands it’s pointless to talk with them anymore, she now focuses all her effect helping the blackrose instead of talking with the dead.</p>
<p>What did the Mastermind offer the Soulcatcher to join? How will this benefit her in the quest for Photine? Only time shall tell.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lore Subject:</span> Paladin</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lore:</span> The Paladin was born with the blessing of justice, passed down from father to son over the course of 1000 years. The blessing of justice gives the Paladin the power to find and defeat the work of Mithras.</p>
<p>The blessing of justice grants the Paladin the ability to locate the area where the cult reside and kill them but that is not all, this blessing also allows the Paladin to protect those closest to him from the cult with a blessing of light that shields the mind from Mithras brainwashing.</p>
<p>The Paladin has been spent his life eliminating the cult, and other people who worship Mithras, and because of the blessing of justice he always knows where they reside.</p>
<p>Now the Paladin has come to Castle Adiart, with the knowledge that the cult is up to no good trying to destroy the bluedragon, and threaten the stability of the kingdom itself, in the name of Photine he will destroy them or die trying.</p>
<hr>
<p>Fade will probably add some type of explanation/comments below <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> Cause after all he did most of the writing, he probably has the most explanation to this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/priest-soulcatcher-paladin-lore-idea/360/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/priest-soulcatcher-paladin-lore-idea/360/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-360-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/priest-soulcatcher-paladin-lore-idea/360.rss">Priest/Soulcatcher/Paladin Lore Idea</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
