<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596</link>
    <description>**Hi There!**

Obviously, you cant just add the same gamemode and change the name to **&quot;Ranked Mode&quot;.**

I know you need to change the game to make it more competitive in a gamemode like this.

In my opinion, this classes needs to be changed if we get a Ranked mode.

**Cult Leader And Mastermind**
-
- Now they Start at full house (4 cult members or 3 Unseen members)
- Conversion is removed

- Mastermind new ability: **Corrupt path:** If somebody visits you at night, the Assassin will know who. **Infinite uses**

- Cult Leader new ability: **Mithras Will:** Target a player, he will think he got attacked by a cultist, he will not be able to talk in court or vote, the effect will dissapear at night. **3 Uses**

**Mercenary**
-
- Now she can pick her first contract. She has until Day 4.

**Alchemist**
-
- Removed **Crimson Potion**
- Added **Smoke Potion**: If your target leaves the room, he gets occupied no matter the immunities. **3 Uses**</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 13:53:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dude if there was a Ranked of course you’d balance the game for that mode</p>
<p>That would be the entire point</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 13:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First of all, let me be clear, on the whole I’m opposed to a ranked mode in general. Even with all of the suggestions it’s going to make, I don’t have a solution for the elo hell problem. My key problem with ranked, is that while I would absolutely preffer a veterans mode where experienced players can play with other experienced players, seperate from newer players, inevitably as people are set appart from eachother, the playing field is never even. (IE a great player that was misfiled into lower ranks, will lose more games than a mediocre player that was misfiled into mid/higher ranks).</p>
<p>That being said, if a ranked system “Must” be attempted. IMO to do it as close to not horrible as possible. There would have to be an invisible score system (Invisible as in you do not see any results until after the game, as in some cases score going up at certain times could reveal hints as to what certain individuals are).</p>
<p>1/4th of those points would come from individual accomplishments. Say if you are a an investigative, and an evil you just found (other than fool obviously), is executed, you earn points. If you are a butler and you block an evil that earns points. If you are a jailor or knight and kill an evil that earns points etc…</p>
<p>1/2 of the points would be team points. IE you earn team points whenever sides that cannot win with you are executed, you lose points when people in your faction are executed (non-k neutrals don’t fall into this equasion). Basically you earn these points as things go in favor of the team you are on WHILE you are on that team.</p>
<p>only 1/4th or less should be based on the factor of which team you happened to be on at the end of the game. IE if unseen breezed through the game, and you were BD until the last night, that should be a very low scoring victory for you. LIkewise if you kicked total ass as BD, but got sucked into a cult that was in a royally fucked cannot possibly win scenerio at the last second, you should still earn more points than the oposite case I just mentioned, as the majority of the game you were helping the team win, that eventually won.</p>
<p>A system like that also would most heavilly reward say a player that was an amazing asset for BD, giving them a very strong lead mid game, but then gets converted, and after being converted flips the script and carries his new allies to victory.</p>
<p>Again though all that being said, IMO at the very least I would say a leveling style of system (IE your rank only can go up, it can go up faster or slower based on how well you played, but it doesn’t go down when games go bad), over the style of ranked where score goes up and down. Nothings more frustrating and futile than getting paired up with a bad team… explaining on a pure logic basis exactly who the evils are, being able to demonstrate it, but the other players don’t know the mechanics well enough to understand what you are saying, and execute you or other BDs even after you explain who the evils are and how you know it, and that futile loss causes your rank to drop, making you have even more games with players that don’t know how to play and the cycle continues.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 13:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crimson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If Ranked mode is added i think player must have a standard names (like Ivo Bardolf and other…) to avoid some edgy or oppressing names <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is one of the reasons I was against Ranked mode in the first place.  As soon as you introduce it you’re going to get people pushing to either make changes to the entire game centered solely around Ranked, or do things that separate the two mechanically (and <span class="bbcode-i">then</span> they’ll suggest things that only work in Ranked without regard for whether it ruins gameplay elsewhere.)</p>
<p>I don’t think it’s a good idea to split the playerbase this way, and it’s definitely not a good idea to have separate modes with different mechanics - it’s hard enough to balance one mode, now every mode will have to be balanced for both.  (Or, worse, we’ll have people arguing that only Ranked matters because it’s the “serious” mode.  Come on.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 09:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey I replied to that <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I’d be interested in seeing a ToL gamemode balanced around no conversions, but first we need a ton more players. Once we have that, any competitive mode would need some major changes from the current setup. While these tweaks could potentially be a part of that, it would almost certainly need a lot more work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeathReaperRH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/cuatrolan">@Cuatrolan</a> read this lengthy thread about why ranked would not be good for ToL<br>
<a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/please-do-not-add-a-ranked-mode/33151</a><br>
Look if you really want a ranked mode that is your opinion that I’m sure hundreds also want.Thing is this game isn’t really designed to be competitive it’s just supposed to be a fun game that you can get on and join for a fun time. I like winning I really do but adding this ranked mode would need a multitude of things in ToL. Really more classes to fake claim.Right now you can’t really claim that much as evils which others have brought up <a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422" class="inline-onebox-loading">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422</a> of course skill and other things are a factor but in general it is harder for evils to win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeathReaperRH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dude you’re literally making ToL ToS with different names .<br>
And Yes I do agree with you that it would be unfair if you got converted while doing a good job as BD or Mercenary in a ranked mode but thats what makes this game unique and fun.That is the sole reason that ranked mode wouldn’t work for ToL.The reason it works for ToS is because ToS is more simple more rigid-easier some would say.MM and CL in these states would become neigh useless.<br>
Sure you start with 4 cult or 3 unseen but with no ability to restock your faction once you’re found you’re dead.That makes this game ToS but with unseen instead of mafia and slightly different abilities and names.<br>
Mercenary is a class which I feel like is fine as it is but of course some people say its too easy to confirm. Of course that is their opinion.Also for alchemists <a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/claiming-d1-as-alchemist/45394" class="inline-onebox-loading">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/claiming-d1-as-alchemist/45394</a> read my post and see why I think it is one of the easist classes to win as.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cuatrolan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi orangeblack5!</p>
<p>This post was just a Idea I wanted to share with you, since Ranked ToL would be a gamemode that I would play almost 100% of my freetime since I love the game but I donr have a real progression system.</p>
<p>So I thinked a way to change a basic mechanic of the game and translate it into a competitive form.</p>
<p>Thats it <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d be against this.</p>
<p>Removing the conversions from ToL just makes it a shitty Mafia game (unless you start to rebalance everything).</p>
<p>Granted, you could argue it already is shitty <em>because</em> of its focus on conversions, but in general I feel that these bring enough variety to the table for the game to be fun to play without bringing in a competitive gamemode.</p>
<p>That being said, would you mind explaining the thought process behind these suggestions?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cuatrolan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also I want to say: <strong>its just a suggestion from a player</strong>, dont take it to serious, its just what I would like to see in the game, try to not be so rude with me. Thank you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If I wanted to play Town of Salem, I’d play Town of Salem. I don’t want to play Town of Salem (because Throne of Lies is better), I want to play Throne of Lies.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cuatrolan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only “Big thing” I change is the conversions.</p>
<p>I know it sounds really painful on paper, but Im sure you would love to play ToL like this, It would add a “Serious” mode to play the game instead of just getting converted by random reasons.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is not ToL. Its a different game with a similar theme and classes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cuatrolan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ToL but with competitive changes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So basically you want us to play a more complicated standard mafia.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cuatrolan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would feel really unfair if you get converted while doing a nice job as Blue Dragon/Mercenary in a Ranked mode.</p>
<p>Alchemist needs another survival ability, because now she has to <strong>Survive</strong> and not decide what faction she picks to win with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why the hell should Ranked not be about conversion? It’s one of the main points that distinguishes this game. This just makes this more like traditional Mafia and Town of Salem.</p>
<p>Mercenary change just should be added, and remove the second contract.</p>
<p>Why change Alchemist?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cuatrolan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Hi There!</strong></p>
<p>Obviously, you cant just add the same gamemode and change the name to <strong>“Ranked Mode”.</strong></p>
<p>I know you need to change the game to make it more competitive in a gamemode like this.</p>
<p>In my opinion, this classes needs to be changed if we get a Ranked mode.</p>
<h2><strong>Cult Leader And Mastermind</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Now they Start at full house (4 cult members or 3 Unseen members)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Conversion is removed</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Mastermind new ability: <strong>Corrupt path:</strong> If somebody visits you at night, the Assassin will know who. <strong>Infinite uses</strong></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cult Leader new ability: <strong>Mithras Will:</strong> Target a player, he will think he got attacked by a cultist, he will not be able to talk in court or vote, the effect will dissapear at night. <strong>3 Uses</strong></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Mercenary</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>Now she can pick her first contract. She has until Day 4.</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Alchemist</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>Removed <strong>Crimson Potion</strong>
</li>
<li>Added <strong>Smoke Potion</strong>: If your target leaves the room, he gets occupied no matter the immunities. <strong>3 Uses</strong>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 02:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47596-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/my-suggestions-if-ranked-mode-is-added/47596.rss">My suggestions if Ranked mode is added</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
