<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181</link>
    <description>The people of Ravenswood Bluff gathered in the town square to see that which they always dreaded; the specter of Tangeld, returned once more, which could only mean that horror was drawing near to their home.

“Folks, I know you’re alarmed, but I need you all to listen.” Tangeld tried to gather the crowd.

“We don’t need you here, you psychotic poltergeist!”

“The phrase you’re looking for is ‘ravishing revenant’, and I’m afraid you do. This Demon is more dangerous than any Ravenswood Bluff has faced before.”

“You’re joking, right? Do you have any idea what sort of demonic incursions we’ve had to battle back?”

Tan smirked. “I remember that the last one didn’t go so well. And so does he.” Tan jerked her thumb to the side, where the townsfolk saw the ghost of… Marshal?

“Wait, weren’t you the last Demon we had to kill?”

“Yeah, and you couldn’t quite get the job done. But this one… This one was too much even for me.”

Tan turned back to the town. “So, are we willing to play along and hopefully not all die horribly?”

“… I’ll take those grumbles as a ‘yes’. Let’s get on with it.”

# Day 1 has begun, and the nomination phase will open in twelve hours.

# Player List:
1. N.1 (Died N4)
2. ~~Winterfall~~ Leafia (Died D3)
3. an_gorta_pratai (Died N4)
4. Magnus (Died D4)
5. SirDerpsALot (Died N2)
6. Clonedcheese
7. TheBlueElixir
8. Apprentice (Died N2)
9. KyoDaz (Died D2)
10. Zone_Q11 (Died D4)
11. Italy (Died N4)
12. Amelia (Died N5)
13. Arete (Died D1)
14. oB_L1ght

# As always, a refresher on the rules and regulations of this game can be found in the OP of the signup thread, conveniently linked here for you.
https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-signups-14-15-signups-closed/82055?u=tangeld

# Now featuring by popular demand... Fast-travel to important points in the game!
Day 1 - Opening of Nominations: https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-day-4-nominations-closed-6-14-replacements-needed/82181/500?u=tangeld
Day 2 - SoD: https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-day-4-nominations-closed-6-14-replacements-needed/82181/906?u=tangeld
Day 2 - Opening of Nominations: https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-day-4-nominations-closed-6-14-replacements-needed/82181/1121?u=tangeld
Day 3 - SoD: https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-day-4-nominations-closed-6-14-replacements-needed/82181/1812?u=tangeld
Day 3 - Opening of Nominations: 
https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-day-4-nominations-closed-6-14-replacements-needed/82181/2021?u=tangeld
Day 4 - SoD: https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-day-4-nominations-closed-6-14-replacements-needed/82181/3094?u=tangeld
Day 4 - Opening of Nominations: https://forum.imperium42.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-day-4-nominations-closed-6-14-replacements-needed/82181/3653?u=tangeld</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 03:07:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Completed</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheBlueElixir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>few notes coming from the Demon - kinda want to explain what ive been thinking through the game</p>
<details>
<summary>
Theres no scumchat to look at, gonna walk through some of my thoughts through the game. I mainly am rewriting what I wrote in my classcard</summary>
<details>
<summary>
Early game</summary>
<p>D1/N1/N2 - got my card, was hyped, and I was thinking that i would be able to fake perspective well but not tone. I believe I was wrong, I think I got my tone well but perspective worse</p>
<p>I had my plan to single kill -&gt; no kill -&gt; triple kill all the way back this earlier to avoid courtiers. I, unfortunately, did not hit Amelia during any of this. I also(to go with my Sailor claim) intended to push whoever I claimed to occ because I was gonna say ‘there was a nokill, mustve been a malfunction’</p>
<p>Also, when i looked back at myself even ~2h in I considered myself incredibly scummy. As I put it in classcard - I felt boxed in, and nobody even remotely SRd me.</p>
<p>I did some planning with numbers, but then ditched them when I felt like I wanted to bus Magnus. Magnus was only whispering scum and I was afraid to get caught in that web, and there were a few posts I knew I could push on. I just kinda have an urge to bus and Magnus was the perfect candidate for me. I never did this till later. though.</p>
<p>I killed App n2 because he was really obviously town and I feared his reads. I tried to signal to oB to kill N so then we could take his read on Amelia and push it, but oB feared protectives and went to SDA, which still got us a mislynch.</p>
<p>also I actually didnt know how the voting system worked and alot of the game worked - that was legit</p>
</details>
<hr>
<details>
<summary>
Full N2 thought process and where from there</summary>
<p>During the first half of the game but kinda in, I intended to make a readslist. I then wondered where Id put the people I knew were town and the people that I knew were scum</p>
<p>Turns out thats a bit of a problem when I want to pocket a mass amount of people at the same time as bussing scum - my reads are probably better when Im scum</p>
<p>Winterfall was MM though, so I wanted them around. oB I would rather to be with, but I could more or less go either way and Magnus wouldnt be a bad bus, particularly if they targeted themself</p>
<p>there was an absurd amount of lowposters aswell, so it would be gamer if I just kept pushing those and pocketing everyone that posts alot</p>
<p>So here we had it. Lets make a PoE of people to push. Just put it together and let it do the work for you.</p>
<p>Amelia/gorta/Magnus</p>
<p>I woulda actually went through with it if it wasnt for Arete - SFoL 61.5, Arete said CRich did ‘the rule of threes’ and I was about to walk into that trap. So gamer plan? Just make the 3 man PoE all town</p>
<p>gorta/Amelia/SDA(this particularly was N2), my plan was to take a card out of Ans’ book - push alot of town, claim to not like PoE, push it anyway, win</p>
<p>thanks to SDA nothing went like that but w/e</p>
<p>I wanted to pocket N and Amelia both aswell so I was gonna call em TvT at one point</p>
<p>Also, sometimes I was around when thread was dead. I let it stay that way. At first I would revive it, thinking like Marshal in ToS 2 but then I decided ‘ya know what, im not doing this’ and made the conscious choice to deepwolf instead of powerwolf.</p>
<p>This was the single worst strategic decision I made all game, though it made the game easier for me.</p>
<p>its why I was top of Po PoE, not Amelia. Because if I had that thread control I very well mightve been able to shove my way out of it.</p>
<p>besides that, I wanted to tunnel Italy. If they claimed literally anything besides Innkeeper, I wouldve really pushed for their death, but I think most people just kinda accepted it, so bruh. I literally - here lemme grab this</p>
<details>
<summary>
Perfect foolproof way to win</summary>
<p>nom Italy tomorrow and we that good</p>
<p>wow</p>
<p>alright</p>
<ul>
<li>Tinker</li>
<li>Good</li>
<li>Good</li>
<li>Good</li>
<li>Good</li>
<li>Good</li>
<li>Minion</li>
<li>Minion</li>
<li>Minion</li>
<li>Demon</li>
</ul>
<p>Gossip kill tonight -&gt; mislynch -&gt; triple kill -&gt; Grandmother dies</p>
<ul>
<li>Minion</li>
<li>Minion</li>
<li>Minion</li>
<li>Demon</li>
</ul>
<p>gg, perfect game</p>
<p>this assumes Tinker doesnt die(which would also trigger GF), nobody is successfully protected, Gossip kills a Good, Good is lynched tomorrow and I dont malfunction.</p>
</details>
<p>See, almost every gossip statement was false so I expected a nightkill. Unfortunately, I happened to kill the gossip n1, so that went wrong and so did alot of the rest of it.</p>
</details>
<hr>
<details>
<summary>
From Leafia's death till the end</summary>
<p>I didn’t realize Leafia would actually die, so it was a hard hitter for me</p>
<p>like, I legitimately thought we had game in the bag there and then it started slipping, getting farther from just out of reach…</p>
<p>So now time to pick who to kill. Since a minion died, I effectively have to decide whether I want to prove oB or not. I was thinking ‘just no action and triple the night after’ but that wasnt an option. I could kill 3 dead players and make it look like that, but it would still take another night of charging.</p>
<p>so I made a few more gamer plans that the courtier messed up - I wont keep going into those</p>
<p>I killed Italy, obviously, but my other two targets were legitimately unsure for me. I guessed Italy would sit on the same people again(I was right) so I attacked N(Nobody bothered to look back on their read on Amelia, and turned out not to matter) and gorta because who else(also chance of being a power role)</p>
<p>Then Arete whispers me - see, to support my Sailor claim, I claimed Professor to Arete. Now I went to claim Sailor - only to not realize Sailor acts n1. So then I scumslip p hard, my chest beats at the speed of light, I then whisper Zone, <em>claim that I told him my n1 action earlier when I didnt, so if he went back and checked it woulda been gg right there,</em> and then Zone and Arete whisper a bunch and I thought Zone really checked</p>
<p>he didnt</p>
<p>At this point, or maybe a bit earlier, I forget, Zone calls me a sheep. Thats not my normal playstyle at all though - im usually tunneling towncore. So there I was, knowing I had to flip my reads, but, uh, there was no towncore to tunnel. N was more or less out of towncore at this point, Zone was obvious town and so I didnt think I had any good tunnel targets, so I just kinda dropped this, but I was hyper aware</p>
<p>Anyway I wanted to hard bus Magnus, wrote up a big wallpost, then all the sudden everyone just kinda wants Magnus dead. Like, nobody needed any convincing this game, alot of people just kinda accepted lynches</p>
<p>Anyway, the Leafia death meant I was going to have to make it to endgame and Magnus’ meant that I wasnt going anywhere but to kil off minions</p>
<p>then the game got mech solved so that wasnt great(nearly mech solved, only me/amelia were the only non-proven). What I didnt realize is that when the courtier dies I can attack again. This fact is literally why I didnt just throw everything on the floor right there. I thought Id have to survive 3 days, which would be p much impossible, but when I realized if they got lynched I won <em>that</em> was pog.</p>
<p>then oB killed Amelia</p>
<p>I kinda died inside when that happened. Like, enough time was wearing on me and that really nailed the coffin. Not much to say about it, the game ended how it did.</p>
</details>
<hr>
<p>also shoutout to oB for being a pog teamate</p>
<p>MVP of scum</p>
<p>(that isnt meant to be ironic, besides that kill at the end he was legitimately the best of us)</p>
</details>
<p>I think thats all I wanted to say</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5911">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5911</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 17:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5911</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh yeah</p>
<p>With it being revealed now that <a class="mention" href="/u/tangeld">@Tangeld</a>  is stepping down as head host of the Blood on the Forums Franchise, I want to offer the following heartfelt gratitude to her.</p>
<p>I’m unimaginably grateful that you brought BotF here last November. That alerted me to the existence of clocktower (which I wasn’t aware of before), which in turn led me to 1) Pre-order the official game, which I’m excited for, 2) Learn about DeceptaCon, which was affiliated with Clocktower and in the same city that I was living in at the time, helping me to develop a bunch of new friendships I never would have had without clocktower, 3) Learn about the existence of Airlock, which was run at DeceptaCon and I never would have known about without that event, and 4) Inspired me to spend ~50 hours designing elements for and crafting a comprehensive homebrewed grimoire (including all released scripts / roles and all unreleased roles that were known in early March of this year) to give to a great friend from marching band in a sub-group of the marching band that loved social deduction games, that will hopefully help me to stay connected to that group for a very long time.</p>
<p>Again, thank you so much for deciding to bring clocktower here to the forums. I never would have otherwise known about it, or several other really positive things that resulted from the knowledge of its existence, and I’m really, really happy about that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5910">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5910</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 22:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5910</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am no fool, don’t you think I know that?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5909">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5909</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 17:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5909</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>Like Boomdandy, the best role to ever exist</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5908">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5908</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5908</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, doing that is extremely difficult to balance. Maybe it’s possible but idk where to begin</p>
<p>The real botf roles were in development for over five years.</p>
<p>I was referring to mixing and matching real roles (both released and unreleased, there are many unreleased roles that were not in BotF IV) to make a new, custom script.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5907">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5907</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5907</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d help with that if that’s what we would do</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5906">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5906</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5906</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be cool if we made entirely custom roles</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5905">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5905</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5905</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah</p>
<p>I hate teensyvilles<br>
That’s also the most shit one</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5904">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5904</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5904</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>run We’re the Bad Guys</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5903">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5903</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5903</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All three official ones have now been run on the site.</p>
<p>BotF IV was a custom setup made up of only leaked unreleased roles. For a new full-size BotF experience, we’d have to make a new custom setup; probably would be one that combined both released and unreleased roles. Many of the roles are not compatible with each other tho based on some mechanical properties.</p>
<p>PM me if you’d like to help with that process for BotF V. Since it’s semi-open, you of course can still play if u help. This applies to anyone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5902">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5902</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5902</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is my least favourite BotF setup tbh, DA is absurdly broken and Goon forces town into a double mislynch<br>
What other ones are there</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5901">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5901</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5901</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Poor wazza</p>
<p>Italy is the only player to win all four BotF’s<br>
Wazza is the only player to lose all four BotF’s</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5900">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5900</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 15:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5900</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah clearly my night actions won us the game</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5899">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5899</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 14:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5899</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My night actions won us the game wdym</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5898">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5898</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5898</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheBlueElixir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you sound like you dont know that your night actions won the game</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5897">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5897</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 14:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5897</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do feel bad for not being more active in the main thread, but at least I did some good stuff behind the scenes. The problem is that I felt out of place not knowing the mechanics as well and spoke up on the stuff I knew and could confirm</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5896">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5896</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 10:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5896</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[an_gorta_pratai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Arete" data-post="5736" data-topic="82181">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/arete/40/30476_2.png" class="avatar"> Arete:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and everyone accepted me as locktown, and I won the game</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I only went from tunneling you to accepting your claim because it made sense with my half asleep night action</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TheBlueElixir" data-post="5762" data-topic="82181">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/theblueelixir/40/29077_2.png" class="avatar"> TheBlueElixir:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gorta literally strolling into d3 and voting exe on L1ght when nobody else suspected them</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Kyo was assumed scum and trusted light (and also others cast doubts on that claim in whispers). Don’t think I am some good player here, even though I have a habit of catching scum on some bs reason that no one else would understand.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TheBlueElixir" data-post="5807" data-topic="82181">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/theblueelixir/40/29077_2.png" class="avatar"> TheBlueElixir:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>gorta starts solving in literally his first 10 posts</p>
<p>if I was town id white knight it</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>something something gorta has bad reads and gut reads are bad</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Arete" data-post="5809" data-topic="82181">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/arete/40/30476_2.png" class="avatar"> Arete:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I trusted Gorta because he didn’t understand the implications of his ability but was nevertheless feeding me accurate info (or accurate-barring-lolGoon)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>only because I trusted you</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Leafia" data-post="5869" data-topic="82181" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/leafia/40/25929_2.png" class="avatar"> Leafia:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you had accepted the whisper, you could’ve told me. Also, what does everyone think of my attempt to get people to think I was really town after my scumslip?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>fool was the worst claim here because if you don’t die then you are sus as crap</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5895">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5895</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 10:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5895</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vulgard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel bad for Leafia.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5894">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5894</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 09:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5894</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve never randed scum in BotF, can that change</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5893">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5893</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 09:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5893</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wazza" data-post="5889" data-topic="82181">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/wazza/40/41244_2.png" class="avatar"> Wazza:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hah, I was just vibing in this game but couldn’t keep up with FoL 28 as well so I had to replace out. Sadly I lost anyway.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah-ha! I thought something was up with Winter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5892">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5892</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 09:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5892</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This game was a circus. LOL</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5891">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5891</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 08:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5891</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh yeah winterfall was wazza.</p>
<p>that was a thing</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5890">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5890</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 06:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5890</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hah, I was just vibing in this game but couldn’t keep up with FoL 28 as well so I had to replace out. Sadly I lost anyway.<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/winterfall">@Winterfall</a>, bye nerrrd.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5889">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5889</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 06:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5889</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t realize that a GF or demon attacking the goon would fail to kill them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5888">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5888</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5888</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leafia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah. I see. I was under the impression that if a goon dies at night, they become evil since evil killed them. If I had realized it wasn’t like that, I never would’ve been fooled by App.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5887">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181/5887</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 01:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-82181-5887</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-blood-on-the-forums-iii-moonlight-badness-good-wins/82181.rss">(Misc) Blood on the Forums III: Moonlight Badness (Good Wins)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
