<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208</link>
    <description>*The year is 20XX, corrupt governments fight and seize each other for power and wealth across the globe. In the midst of this chaos, government officials, backed up by the influence of certain factions, strategically try to eliminate opposing governments in an attempt to ensure their government to be the last one standing...*

# Welcome to Coup, a card/board game based around lying, deceit and bluffing, hosted by @Intensify

You will be pitted up against 1 to 7 other players, in a race to be the last one standing. However along the way, you must find a way to trick others into believing your lies, while at the same time ensuring that others do not manipulate you into believing their lies.

This version of Coup is basically the original version, with 2 cards I made that are based off of Kickstarters exclusives, to spice things up a little for those familiar with the game. 

[details=&quot;Setup + The Deck&quot;]
Each player starts with 2 Influence Cards drawn from the deck and 2 coins.

The Influence Cards will be only visible to you and nobody else.

The deck consists of 3 copies of each unique card.

So the deck would look like this:

3 **[color=steblue]Duke[/color]** cards
3 **[color=purple]Assassin[/color]** cards
3 **[color=darkblue]Captain[/color]** cards
3 **[color=orange]Ambassador[/color]** cards
3 **[color=yellow]Contessa[/color]** cards
3 **[color=grey]Graverobber[/color]** cards
3 **Inquisitor** cards

The deck will contain in total 21 cards.

Setup can be modified and expanded if for some reason more than 8 players want to play. 
[/details]

[details=&quot;Cards/Characters&quot;]
The cards you draw at the start of game (your Influence Cards) will allow you to perform special actions during your turn and possibly block other actions. You may declare to have one of these cards in order to perform the corresponding actions. These cards are:

**[color=steblue]Duke[/color]** - Gain 3 coins. Block **Foreign Aid**.
**[color=purple]Assassin[/color]** - Pay 3 coins to make a player of your choice lose an Influence Card.
**[color=darkblue]Captain[/color]** - Steal 2 coins from another player. Block stealing against you.
**[color=orange]Ambassador[/color]** - Draw 2 cards from the top of the deck. You may exchange any of your alive cards with the cards drawn. Return 2 cards back at the end to the bottom of the deck.
**[color=yellow]Contessa[/color]** - Block an assassination attempt or stealing against you.
**[color=grey]Graverobber[/color]** - When a player loses and has no more cards, you may claim **[color=grey]Graverobber[/color]**. After claims and challenging, the coins are split among **[color=grey]Graverobber[/color]** claim(s) (rounded down). 
**Inquisitor** - Gain 2 coins. Look at the top and bottom cards of the deck. 
[/details]

[details=&quot;Gameplay&quot;]
Turns will take place in the order of the player list from top to bottom.

During your turn, state your action and the character claimed (if applicable) with a :exclamation: or putting it in green.

For example:

[quote]
:exclamation: I want to do income and gain 1 coin this turn.
:exclamation: I claim Duke and gain 3 coins this turn.
[color=green]I want to do income and gain 1 coin this turn.[/color]
[color=green]I claim Duke and gain 3 coins this turn.[/color]
[/quote]

You are allowed to bluff to have any card in the game and you may claim to have that card in order to do the card&#39;s special action. You may also bluff to have any card as well for blocking an action. However, there is a risk to bluffing any card known as challenging (which will be explained later on).

For example:
[quote]
Player 1 has a Duke, but doesn&#39;t like Player 2.
Player 1 decides to claim Captain and steals 2 coins from Player 2 despite having a Duke.
Player 2 loses 2 coins and is now sad.
[/quote]

Certain actions can be blocked by other cards. For example, a **[color=darkblue]Captain[/color]** may block a steal from another **[color=darkblue]Captain[/color]** attempting to steal 2 coins from them. When you wish to block an action, state whichever card you claim and the block with a :shield: or in red. 

[quote]
:shield: I claim Captain and I block your steal.
[color=red]I claim Captain and I block your steal.[/color]
[/quote]

Each player is attempting to eliminate the Influence Cards of all the other players. These cards are unknown to the other players, and players may bluff on their claims.

When a player loses an Influence Card, they choose which card to reveal. It no longer provides any use to the player and does not return to the court deck.

When a player loses all their Influence Cards, they are exiled and removed from the game.

The last player standing is the winner.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Challenging&quot;]
Whenever a player claims to have a card along with its action or block, you may challenge the claim. When a player challenges another player, they are basically telling the other player that they don&#39;t believe their claim and think that they are bluffing.

Anyone may challenge a claim made by a player during that player&#39;s turn.

To challenge someone, post whoever you want to challenge with a :crossed_swords: or in blue.

For example:

[quote]
:crossed_swords: I challenge your Duke claim!
[color=blue]I challenge your Duke claim![/color]
[/quote]

When a claim is challenged, the challenge process will happen.
During this process, there are 2 different players, [color=orange]The Challenger[/color] and [color=red]The Accused[/color]. 
[color=orange]The Challenger[/color] is the person who is accusing the person of lying and [color=red]The Accused[/color] is the person who is.. well being accused of lying. 
[color=red]The Accused[/color] beings by revealing a card.
If the card is the correct card they claimed to have, [color=orange]The Challenger[/color] loses a card and the action goes through. [color=red]The Accused[/color] shuffles the card they revealed to the deck and draws a new one from the top of the deck.
If the card is the wrong card they claimed to have, [color=red]The Accused[/color] loses a card and the action is negated and does not happen.

For example:
[quote]
There are 2 players, player 1 and player 2.
Player 1 has a **[color=steblue]Duke[/color]** and a **[color=darkblue]Captain[/color]**.
Player 2 has a **[color=yellow]Contessa[/color]** and a **[color=yellow]Contessa[/color]**.
Player 2 isn&#39;t doing so great right now, so he decides to claim to have an Assassin and makes an assassination attempt against player 1. 
Player 1 does not like this, and instead of losing one of his cards to an assassination attempt, he claims to have a [color=yellow]**Contessa**[/color] and blocks the assassination attempt.
Player 2 does not believe the claim and challenges the claim.
Player 1 cries like a nerd.
Player 1 reveals a [color=steblue]**Duke**[/color] and turns out he did not have a **[color=yellow]Contessa[/color]**.
Player 1 decides to lose his **[color=steblue]Duke[/color]** after revealing it.
[/quote]

Keep in mind that any claim of beholding a certain card can be challenged by anyone. This includes claims during blocks.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Actions and Blocks&quot;]
Here is the list of all actions you may claim on your turn. Notice that there are 3 actions that do not require you to claim a specific card in order to perform. These are **Income**, **Foreign Aid** and **Coup**. These are actions that may be performed by anyone as long as the requirements are met and can not be challenged since no claim of having a certain card is presented. 

Keep in mind that you must perform an action during your turn and you cannot no-action. 

**Income** - Gain 1 coin.
**Foreign Aid** - Gain 2 coins.
**Coup** - Pay 7 coins to host a coup against a player, making them lose an Influence Card. This cannot be stopped. You are forced to **Coup** at 10 coins.
**[color=steblue]Duke[/color]** - Gain 3 coins.
**[color=purple]Assassin[/color]** - Pay 3 coins to make a player of your choice lose an Influence Card.
**[color=darkblue]Captain[/color]** - Steal 2 coins from another player.
**[color=orange]Ambassador[/color]** - Draw 2 cards from the top of the deck. You may exchange any of your alive cards with the cards drawn. Return 2 cards back at the end to the bottom of the deck.
**Inquisitor** - Gain 2 coins. Look at the top and bottom cards of the deck. 

Cards can also of course block other actions.

**[color=steblue]Duke[/color]** - Block **Foreign Aid**.
**[color=darkblue]Captain[/color]** - Block stealing against you.
**[color=yellow]Contessa[/color]** - Block an assassination attempt or stealing against you.

When a player dies, you may claim **[color=grey]Graverobber[/color]**. After claims and challenging, the coins is split among the **[color=grey]Graverobber[/color]** claims.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Discussion and Deals&quot;]
Anytime during the game, you may talk in the thread unless otherwise specified by the host to shut up. You are allowed to talk about anything as long as it follows the guidelines and general rules.  bluffing, talking about food, questioning other claims (but not actually challenging them with a :crossed_swords: or in blue), cat pics, making alliances and self voting + ateing, those are all allowed, so have fun.

All discussion must be held in the game thread. You are not allowed to create private PMs to make deals or talk privately to another player.

You may also not show cards, give cards, give coins or anything else similar to this to other players. All your possessions are yours and cannot be given away for free. 
[/details]

[details=&quot;Time Limit&quot;]
The time limit for your turn to perform an action is 24 hours. If you do not perform an action by the end of this, I will automatically default your action to **Income**. If you have 10 coins, it will be defaulted to **Coup** on a random player instead.

When an action is declared, there will also be a 24 hour period where players may challenge the claim, block it or pass into the next turn. By the end of this 24 hour period, the action will pass through unless otherwise proven to be fake via a challenge. 

For whatever reason, if you wish to expand this time limit for a specific action, ping me and I will do so

In order to pass, post **/pass** in the game thread.

When a player dies, there will be a free 24 hour period for players to claim **[color=grey]Graverobber[/color]** or to pass. 
[/details]

Feel free to ask any questions, I will answer them.

# Playerlist A

1. Whysper
2. PokemonKidRyan
3. Apprentice
4. Jane
5. Solic 

# Playerlist B

1. EliThePsycho
2. BlueStorm
3. Twil1ght
4. Nerbins
5. Wazza
6. Gorta

# Threadmarks

[Signups Begin](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-pre-game-5-5/87208/2?u=intensify)
[Round 1 Begins](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-whyspers-turn-5-5/87208/153?u=intensify)
[Round 2 Begins](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-whysper-s-turn-5-5/87208/227?u=intensify)
[Round 3 Begins](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-pkr-s-turn-5-5/87208/299?u=intensify)
[Round 4 Begins](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-round-4-begins-with-whysper-5-5/87208/417?u=intensify)
[Round 5 Begins](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-s-turn-4-5/87208/518?u=intensify)
[Round 6 Begins](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-s-turn-3-5/87208/593?u=intensify)
[Round 7 Begins](https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-round-8-go-brr-3-5/87208/607?u=intensify)

&lt;small&gt; psst thx @whysper for letting me ~~steal~~ borrow your OP thread : D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 03:35:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Completed</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Whysper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ahhh okay, nice attempt <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Congrats on the win!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/697">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/697</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 03:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-697</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exciting until the very end at least, GG.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/696">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/696</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-696</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That was good fun.<br>
Apologies Solic to put you on the spot like that but I had to make things interesting.</p>
<p>So I had 2 choices.<br>
Claim Graverobber or Captain.</p>
<p>I figured with guessing you had a captain, that you would be more unlikely to think I had a captain.</p>
<p>Also if you had let me get the money I could’ve contessa’d the assassination by you. So it was a last second plan. Haha.</p>
<p>GG</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/695">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/695</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 21:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-695</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Chloe wins yet again</p>
<p>how does she always do it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/694">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/694</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-694</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/whysper">@Whysper</a> the alliance talk was a ploy to try and trap Apprentice into calling my Captain since I knew they had seen 2 in the deck per my Inquisitor info. I tried to make it seem like a signal for them to not call me on it, because I was faking it in order to hopefully get them to call me on it anyways and lose a card as a result.</p>
<p>I would have gone less explicit otherwise too probably.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/693">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/693</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-693</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh yeah sure.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/692">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/692</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-692</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for hosting Intensify! Can we get access to death chat?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/691">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/691</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-691</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EliThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ez clap<br>
now we wait for the trees to fade from coup B</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/690">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/690</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-690</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Solic’s last card was an <font color="purple">Assassin</font>.</h1>
<p>GGs everyone</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/689">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/689</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-689</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Solic has won…</h1>
<p>: )</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/688">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/688</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-688</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>And with that… PKR loses a card, and he dies from a heart attack after Solic makes amongus reference.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/687">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/687</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-687</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>The revealed card was a</h1>
<details>
<summary>
</summary>
<p><font color="yellow"><strong>Contessa</strong></font>!</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/686">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/686</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 20:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-686</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Drumrolls please…</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/685">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/685</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 19:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-685</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>PKR reveals a card</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/684">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/684</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-684</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Solic challenges PKR’s claim…</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/683">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/683</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 19:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-683</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crossed_swords.png?v=9" title=":crossed_swords:" class="emoji" alt=":crossed_swords:"> I challenge PKR’s Graverobber claim!</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/intensify">@Intensify</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/682">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/682</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 19:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-682</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have to guess whether you have a Contessa or a Graverobber now.</p>
<p>Graverobber is lower odds considering the flipped cards.</p>
<p>I think you would have taken Jane’s bearings otherwise, because you could coup again after that… we both had low coins, except App could assassinate potentially. I and maybe you already guessed App would keep a Contessa around to ward off attacks when he was gathering information, so there was less of a need to be scared of that. Then there is annoying Captain math. I believe that you believed I had one when we made our wager, so that paranoia can be real enough. I could steal once from you before you could coup me and you’d just earn your money back. You would start at 11, even with 2 Captain claims, would be able to coup again, and then have 6 coins. It’s true, that option is a possibility for not claiming a Graverobber… It’d require you to think that Apprentice had a Duke and a Captain though, which is an unlikely pairing to want to keep in endgame. There is also the fact you didn’t say Graverobber, but gravedigger supporting that you don’t have one.</p>
<p>Overall you are more likely to not hold one I believe… and if not, well gg and at least the game is over already then <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/man_shrugging.png?v=9" title=":man_shrugging:" class="emoji" alt=":man_shrugging:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/681">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/681</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 19:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-681</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>nah… you can idk lolcat in here or something though I guess</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/680">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/680</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-680</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>can I communicate anything game relevant in here now though?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/679">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/679</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 18:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-679</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Uhh yeah sure. I have a dead chat if you want to be invited there</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/678">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/678</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 18:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-678</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>can we still talker?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/677">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/677</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 18:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-677</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>PKR claims to have a <font color="grey">Graverobber</font>.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/676">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/676</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 17:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-676</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intensify]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <div class="md-table">
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Player</th>
<th>Card 1</th>
<th>Card 2</th>
<th>Coins</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><s>Whysper</s></td>
<td><font color="grey"><strong>Graverobber</strong></font></td>
<td><font color="purple"><strong>Assassin</strong></font></td>
<td>Mugged by Jane</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>PKR</td>
<td><font color="steblue"><strong>Duke</strong></font></td>
<td>???</td>
<td>0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><s>Apprentice</s></td>
<td><font color="yellow"><strong>Contessa</strong></font></td>
<td><strong><font color="steblue">Duke</font></strong></td>
<td>7</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><s>Jane</s></td>
<td><font color="grey"><strong>Graverobber</strong></font></td>
<td><strong><font color="steblue">Duke</font></strong></td>
<td>7</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Solic</td>
<td><strong><font color="darkblue">Captain</font></strong></td>
<td>???</td>
<td>6</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/675">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/675</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 17:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-675</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or graverobber owo</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/674">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/674</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-674</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong><font color="green">I claim Gravedigger</font></strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/673">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208/673</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 17:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-87208-673</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-coup-thread-a-solic-wins-1-5/87208.rss">[MISC] Coup Thread A - Solic Wins! (1/5)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
