<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How the Unseen Convert people</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547</link>
    <description>**How the unseen convert**

_**In game - N1) Delivering mail to 15. Redirected to themself**_
**Mastermind coming back from 15&#39;s room**: Ahhhh... Now 15, whoever they are will join us. We&#39;ll get another member, isn&#39;t that right Assassin?
**Assassin**: Sure is boss!
**Mastermind entering the unseen room**: Now we wait for them to show up

**3 hours later**
**Mastermind**: What the crap? Where are they?
_Assassin walks in the unseen&#39;s door_
**Assassin**: Hey boss! Where&#39;s our new member?
**Mastermind**: I have no idea. You didn&#39;t kill them did you?
**Assassin**: No! They must have lost their way or something
**Mastermind**: *sigh* I guess we just wait more.
_Mastermind puts their hand in their pockets and feels a letter_
**Mastermind**: Wait.... What is this??
_*Holds up letter_
**Assassin**: That looks like your letter... Did you forget to give them it? Wow... Truly, your intellect is showing
**Mastermind**: SHUDDUP!! -.-

**_In game - N2) Delivering mail to 15... Again. Redirected to the Assassin_**
**Mastermind coming back from 15&#39;s room**: There, I made SURE my letter left my pockets! Without any interruptions, this should be our newest member!
_The hallways of the castle_
**Assassin, making their way back slowly from their kill**: I wonder who will be our newest member? _snickers_ Or did he forget to deliver his own mail again? He truly is high IQ.
_A letter comes flying out of nowhere into their face_
**Assassin**: Ow! What the f-. Hey, isn&#39;t this the Mastermind&#39;s letter? What does he want with me?
_Opens it_
**Assassin**: Ummmmm... This is 6D chess...... But the only thing I recognize is the &quot;unseen room&quot; part... Does the Mastermind want me for something? I&#39;d better hurry back
**In the unseen room, 30 mins later**
**Mastermind**: Got any 5&#39;s?
**Sheriff**: Go fish. Got any 7&#39;s?
**Mastermind**: Curses! *hands over his 7*. Got any-
_Unseen room door bursts open_
**Assassin**: Hey Master- _sees the Sheriff and quickly shuts up_
**Sheriff**: Master? _puts cards down and sits up straight_ Is there something going on here?
**Mastermind (in their head)**: F*CK THAT INCOMPETENT NITWIT!!
**Mastermind (out loud)**: It&#39;s nothing. *grins in a very forced manner* We are just into role-playing, that&#39;s all
_Sheriff glares at the Mastermind_
_Mastermind glares back at the Sheriff_
**Tension escalating**
**Sheriff shrugs**: Okay, you got your own kinks and whatever. Just don&#39;t involve me. Have a nice night! _leaves_
**Mastermind**: YOU FOOL!!! YOU ALMOST EXPOSED US!! *deep breaths to calm down* At least we&#39;ll be getting our newest member
**Assassin**: Ummmm yeah.... About that. _Holds up the letter._ You never told me you played 6D chess
**An enraged howl could be heard from the dungeons of the castle**

**_In game - N3) Delivering mail to the Prince... We all know how that will end up_**
**Mastermind walking back to their room again**: Ohhhhh... Please, please, PLEASE let this work. _stumbles into the room and collapses onto a chair_
**Prince&#39;s dungeon**
**Prince**: night claim 2019 lul. no. u die
**Jailed Person**: Ummmm.... I claimed Noble, I twinned D3 and gossiped the King, exposing the NK. When did I ever claim KNIGHT?
**Prince**: u did. u siad d3 &quot;def 1&quot;. me going too exe u
**Jailed Person (Noble)**: NO STOP! DON&#39;T THROW!!!! SCROLL UP AND READ THE CHAT AGAIN YOU IDIOT!!!
**Prince**: shut up exe
_Prince holds up axe_
**Noble**: Report Prince for throwing. What a retard
_A letter flutters down onto the Prince&#39;s head_
**Prince**: _puts down axe._ what dis?
_Prince opens letter and stares at contents_
**Prince**: kek. me cant reed. i see address.... hmmm... sender must hv lost their letter. i am prince. i am good boi. i return to sender

**Unseen room, 2.5 hours later**
**Assassin**: So when will the newest recruit arrive?
**Mastermind**: Soon I hope
_knocking on the door_
**Mastermind**: Must be them! _gets up and opens the door_
**Mastermind**: Hello, we&#39;ve been expecting you... Welcome to the - HHRRK!!
**Assassin**: Hey hey, what&#39;s wrong? _gets up and looks at the door_ Who&#39;s ther- GRRRK
**Prince standing at the door**: _smiles goofily_ hi doods. u lost ur letter. im returning it to it&#39;s owner
**Mastermind**: _sweating heavily_ U-U-Ummm... Tha-That&#39;s not ours. It&#39;s someone else&#39;s, I swear!
**Prince**: oh? but ur address is here at the bottom
_points to the address_
**Prince**: _frowns_ y u lie to meh? :(
**Mastermind and Assassin**: ... ... _sweating like a waterfall_
**Prince**: _happy again_ ahhh. u testing my iq. my iq very high, i know you too are guud bd. have a nice night! i got to kill that fake night claim. bai bai. _closes door and leaves_
_Mastermind and Assassin collpase onto the floor_
**Assassin**: Ummmm....... What just happened?
**Mastermind**: I.... I.... I have no clue....
**Assassin**: _gets up and pours a glass of whiskey_ Is the prince really.... That stupid??
**Mastermind**: _grabs a bottle of vodka and starts chugging it down_ Apparently so..... 
_Mastermind looks at the letter in his hand_
**Mastermind**: You know what? I don&#39;t even care anymore. I&#39;m done. _chucks the letter out the door and into the waterway_
**Sheriff&#39;s room**
**Sheriff**: This person is NS! He&#39;s fine! For now...
_letter washes up beside him_
**Sheriff**: Oh? What&#39;s this?
_Opens letter and reads it_
**Marshal**: Hmmmm... _eyes glint evilly_ I see what must be done......
**Unseen room**
**Assassin (drunk)**: **Hic** welp, aiiiim off 2 beddd.. **Hic**
**Mastermind**: Go... Just go....
_sudden knocking on the door_
**Mastermind**: Door&#39;s unlocked! 
_door opens and &quot;sheriff&quot; walks in_
**Mastermind**: Hello again sh-
**Assassin**: HAI BUDDY!!! WELCOME 2 DE UNSEEN!!!! WE GOTZ COOKIEEEEEES
**Mastermind**: OH FOR THE LOVE OF F*CK!!! CAN&#39;T YOU SEE THE SHERIFF STANDING THERE??? YOU JUST GAVE US AWAY!
**&quot;Sheriff&quot;**: Actually, I came here for a different reason... I&#39;m now no longer BD
**Mastermind**: Wat O.O
**Marshal**: I saw your letter. It made a lot of sense to me
**Mastermind**: I literally just wrote &quot;You were converted into the Unseen&quot; and the address... How does that make any sense?
**Marshal**: That is the point. I too, play 6D chess. I understand fully what you said
**Mastermind**: ... ... ... ... Why is this castle full of idiots???</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 13:50:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How the Unseen Convert people</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="LOLZ1337" data-post="1" data-topic="75547">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> LOLZ1337:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>NO STOP! DON’T THROW!!! SCROLL UP AND READ THE CHAT AGAIN YOU IDIOT!!!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I love this</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 13:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75547-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547.rss">How the Unseen Convert people</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How the Unseen Convert people</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 08:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75547-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547.rss">How the Unseen Convert people</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How the Unseen Convert people</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LOLZ1337]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>How the unseen convert</strong></p>
<p><em><strong>In game - N1) Delivering mail to 15. Redirected to themself</strong></em><br>
<strong>Mastermind coming back from 15’s room</strong>: Ahhhh… Now 15, whoever they are will join us. We’ll get another member, isn’t that right Assassin?<br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Sure is boss!<br>
<strong>Mastermind entering the unseen room</strong>: Now we wait for them to show up</p>
<p><strong>3 hours later</strong><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: What the crap? Where are they?<br>
<em>Assassin walks in the unseen’s door</em><br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Hey boss! Where’s our new member?<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: I have no idea. You didn’t kill them did you?<br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: No! They must have lost their way or something<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: <em>sigh</em> I guess we just wait more.<br>
<em>Mastermind puts their hand in their pockets and feels a letter</em><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Wait… What is this??<br>
<em>*Holds up letter</em><br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: That looks like your letter… Did you forget to give them it? Wow… Truly, your intellect is showing<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: SHUDDUP!! -.-</p>
<p><strong><em>In game - N2) Delivering mail to 15… Again. Redirected to the Assassin</em></strong><br>
<strong>Mastermind coming back from 15’s room</strong>: There, I made SURE my letter left my pockets! Without any interruptions, this should be our newest member!<br>
<em>The hallways of the castle</em><br>
<strong>Assassin, making their way back slowly from their kill</strong>: I wonder who will be our newest member? <em>snickers</em> Or did he forget to deliver his own mail again? He truly is high IQ.<br>
<em>A letter comes flying out of nowhere into their face</em><br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Ow! What the f-. Hey, isn’t this the Mastermind’s letter? What does he want with me?<br>
<em>Opens it</em><br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Ummmmm… This is 6D chess… But the only thing I recognize is the “unseen room” part… Does the Mastermind want me for something? I’d better hurry back<br>
<strong>In the unseen room, 30 mins later</strong><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Got any 5’s?<br>
<strong>Sheriff</strong>: Go fish. Got any 7’s?<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Curses! <em>hands over his 7</em>. Got any-<br>
<em>Unseen room door bursts open</em><br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Hey Master- <em>sees the Sheriff and quickly shuts up</em><br>
<strong>Sheriff</strong>: Master? <em>puts cards down and sits up straight</em> Is there something going on here?<br>
<strong>Mastermind (in their head)</strong>: F*CK THAT INCOMPETENT NITWIT!!<br>
<strong>Mastermind (out loud)</strong>: It’s nothing. <em>grins in a very forced manner</em> We are just into role-playing, that’s all<br>
<em>Sheriff glares at the Mastermind</em><br>
<em>Mastermind glares back at the Sheriff</em><br>
<strong>Tension escalating</strong><br>
<strong>Sheriff shrugs</strong>: Okay, you got your own kinks and whatever. Just don’t involve me. Have a nice night! <em>leaves</em><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: YOU FOOL!!! YOU ALMOST EXPOSED US!! <em>deep breaths to calm down</em> At least we’ll be getting our newest member<br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Ummmm yeah… About that. <em>Holds up the letter.</em> You never told me you played 6D chess<br>
<strong>An enraged howl could be heard from the dungeons of the castle</strong></p>
<p><strong><em>In game - N3) Delivering mail to the Prince… We all know how that will end up</em></strong><br>
<strong>Mastermind walking back to their room again</strong>: Ohhhhh… Please, please, PLEASE let this work. <em>stumbles into the room and collapses onto a chair</em><br>
<strong>Prince’s dungeon</strong><br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: night claim 2019 lul. no. u die<br>
<strong>Jailed Person</strong>: Ummmm… I claimed Noble, I twinned D3 and gossiped the King, exposing the NK. When did I ever claim KNIGHT?<br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: u did. u siad d3 “def 1”. me going too exe u<br>
<strong>Jailed Person (Noble)</strong>: NO STOP! DON’T THROW!!! SCROLL UP AND READ THE CHAT AGAIN YOU IDIOT!!!<br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: shut up exe<br>
<em>Prince holds up axe</em><br>
<strong>Noble</strong>: Report Prince for throwing. What a retard<br>
<em>A letter flutters down onto the Prince’s head</em><br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: <em>puts down axe.</em> what dis?<br>
<em>Prince opens letter and stares at contents</em><br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: kek. me cant reed. i see address… hmmm… sender must hv lost their letter. i am prince. i am good boi. i return to sender</p>
<p><strong>Unseen room, 2.5 hours later</strong><br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: So when will the newest recruit arrive?<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Soon I hope<br>
<em>knocking on the door</em><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Must be them! <em>gets up and opens the door</em><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Hello, we’ve been expecting you… Welcome to the - HHRRK!!<br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Hey hey, what’s wrong? <em>gets up and looks at the door</em> Who’s ther- GRRRK<br>
<strong>Prince standing at the door</strong>: <em>smiles goofily</em> hi doods. u lost ur letter. im returning it to it’s owner<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: <em>sweating heavily</em> U-U-Ummm… Tha-That’s not ours. It’s someone else’s, I swear!<br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: oh? but ur address is here at the bottom<br>
<em>points to the address</em><br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: <em>frowns</em> y u lie to meh? <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
<strong>Mastermind and Assassin</strong>: … … <em>sweating like a waterfall</em><br>
<strong>Prince</strong>: <em>happy again</em> ahhh. u testing my iq. my iq very high, i know you too are guud bd. have a nice night! i got to kill that fake night claim. bai bai. <em>closes door and leaves</em><br>
<em>Mastermind and Assassin collpase onto the floor</em><br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: Ummmm… What just happened?<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: I… I… I have no clue…<br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: <em>gets up and pours a glass of whiskey</em> Is the prince really… That stupid??<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: <em>grabs a bottle of vodka and starts chugging it down</em> Apparently so…<br>
<em>Mastermind looks at the letter in his hand</em><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: You know what? I don’t even care anymore. I’m done. <em>chucks the letter out the door and into the waterway</em><br>
<strong>Sheriff’s room</strong><br>
<strong>Sheriff</strong>: This person is NS! He’s fine! For now…<br>
<em>letter washes up beside him</em><br>
<strong>Sheriff</strong>: Oh? What’s this?<br>
<em>Opens letter and reads it</em><br>
<strong>Marshal</strong>: Hmmmm… <em>eyes glint evilly</em> I see what must be done…<br>
<strong>Unseen room</strong><br>
<strong>Assassin (drunk)</strong>: <strong>Hic</strong> welp, aiiiim off 2 beddd… <strong>Hic</strong><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Go… Just go…<br>
<em>sudden knocking on the door</em><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Door’s unlocked!<br>
<em>door opens and “sheriff” walks in</em><br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Hello again sh-<br>
<strong>Assassin</strong>: HAI BUDDY!!! WELCOME 2 DE UNSEEN!!! WE GOTZ COOKIEEEEEES<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: OH FOR THE LOVE OF F*CK!!! CAN’T YOU SEE THE SHERIFF STANDING THERE??? YOU JUST GAVE US AWAY!<br>
<strong>"Sheriff"</strong>: Actually, I came here for a different reason… I’m now no longer BD<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: Wat O.O<br>
<strong>Marshal</strong>: I saw your letter. It made a lot of sense to me<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: I literally just wrote “You were converted into the Unseen” and the address… How does that make any sense?<br>
<strong>Marshal</strong>: That is the point. I too, play 6D chess. I understand fully what you said<br>
<strong>Mastermind</strong>: … … … … Why is this castle full of idiots???</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 07:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75547-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/how-the-unseen-convert-people/75547.rss">How the Unseen Convert people</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
