<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775</link>
    <description>The consept behind this faction is a more mafia style faction that keeps that still has meny of a conversion game.

Faction leader
&gt;The Trainer - Resistance Special
Passive 1: Skilled - Night and Occupy immune
.
Night Ability 1: Retrain - Attempt to convert someone. If it succeeds a Resistance member dies. This cannot be healed. You select 2 targets for this, 1 is a Resistance member and 1 isn&#39;t. (Unlimited)
Night Ability 2: Train - Convert the target into the Resistance. If this fails it will not consume a use. (2 uses)

Faction killer - Will be replaced by the oldest non trainer resistance member if he dies. 
&gt;The Activist - Resistance Killer
Passive: Driven - Night immune once
.
Night ability 1: Eliminate - Kill the target (unlimited)
Night Ability 2: Rampage - Kill the target and all visitors. Peirces night Immunity. Uses transfer between Activists (2 uses)

&gt;The Planner - Resistanc Support (CW and Merc convert)
.
Night Ability 1: Misdirect - Swap all visitors of 2 targets. Resolves before other redirects (5 uses)
Night Ability 2: Zeal - Prevent anyone from visiting the Resistance tonight. (2 uses)

&gt;The Sabateor - Resistance Offensive (converted from butler and drunk)
Passive: Mischievous - Occupy immune
.
Night Ability 1: Sabatoge - Occupy the target (4 uses)
Night Ability 2: Misslead - Your first target targets your second Target. (3 uses)

&gt;The Kamakazy - Resistance Killer (converted from hunter and Knight)
Passive: expendable - If you die by any means other than replace then the trainer gets another use of train
.
Day Ability: Mark - Set a mark on your target. They will be informed. The mark lasts 1 night(Unlimited)
.
Night Ability 1: Revenge - if your target attacks or occupys someone then attack them. (3 uses)
Night Ability 2: Suicide - Attack the marked target. You and them will both die. Neither of them can be healed. (1 use)

&gt;The Informat - Resistance Investigative (converted from Princess and Observer)
.
Day Ability: Bug - You will know who your target visits tonight. (5 uses)
.
Night Ability 1: Stalk - You know who visits your target. Can target self. (3 uses)
Night Ability 2: Profile - Learn the targets class type and faction. (2 uses)

&gt;The Mystic - Resistance Social (Converted from Psychic and probably Priest later)
Passive: Call the dead - The dead resistance members can speak to the living members
.
Day Ability: Psychic message - Same as Psychic (2 uses)
.
Night Ability 1: Private matter - Hide whispers to and from you the next day (4 uses)
Night Ability 2: Mind read - Read your targets journal (4 uses)

&gt;The Medic - Resistance Support (converted from Physician)
Passive: Med kit - You will heal yourself the first time you would die at night
.
Night Ability 1: Heal - Heal the target (4 uses)
Night Ability 2: Escort - Give the target Occupy immunity if don&#39;t they have it. Remove it if they do. They will only be notified if they are occupied. (3 uses)

&gt;The Flagbearer - Resistance Social (Converted from Noble)
Passive 1: Royal blood
Passive 2: People&#39;s trust - Will always auto win a 1 on 1 with any class. Your guilty or pardon votes count for 2.
.
Day Ability 1: Power play - Force a player to vote target player. He cannot revoke the vote. If you target the king he will double vote. (2 uses)
.
Night Ability 1: Petition - Target player loses the ability to vote. The next day your first vote for treason counts for 2. (2 uses)
Night Ability 2: Dedication - If the trainer is dead then become a trainer with 1 use of train. You will not lose Royal blood. (Unlimited)

&gt;Scout - Resistance Investigative (converted from spy)
.
Night Ability 1: Search - Learn your targets class (4 uses)
Night Ability 2: Scan - check what classes visit your target. (4 uses)

And now for the hardcounter

&gt;Spy - Blue Dragon Investigator
.
Day Ability: Forestall - Prevent the trainer from using retrain or train tonight. (2 uses)
.
Night Ability 1: Tag - You know who the Resistance visits this night. (Unlimited)
Night Ability 2: Scan - You know what classes visit your target. (Unlimited)

Something I would like to point out:

Unseen KPN: 2 + 4 + 1
Cult KPN: 2 + 4 - 1/4
Resistance KPN: 2 + 2 + 2</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:26:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="12" data-topic="24775">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>nonono. The Unseen has a MAX of 3 members AT A TIME!. The Resistance has a max of 4 members TOTAL! As in no regenerating members if one dies.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ooooooh! NOW I GET IT!!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="12" data-topic="24775">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Btw I made the activists night immunity like the inquisitor’s. It only works once</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like that change! <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>nonono. The Unseen has a MAX of 3 members AT A TIME!. The Resistance has a max of 4 members TOTAL! As in no regenerating members if one dies.</p>
<p>Btw I made the activists night immunity like the inquisitor’s. It only works once</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="10" data-topic="24775">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Medic removing occupy immunity is totally the job of the support. It’s not like you are using it on the other resistance members if they are occ immune</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The problem with that skill is not the ability to remove an occupy but the fact that it both removes and adds. I think that makes it more powerful than it should be. That’s why I suggested focusing on the most supportive part.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="10" data-topic="24775">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Scout is there to reward converting the spy rather than killing him. Also the things the scout finds are different or more powerful (depending on ability) than the informant.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I see. That makes sense.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="10" data-topic="24775">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As for the Spy… Your Forestall suggestion is fine but I’m not sure you get why Spy isn’t anything like Sheriff or Paladin. Unlike with the Unseen or Cult the Resistance has a strictly limited number of members. If you could easily point at someone and say if they are a Resistance member it wouldn’t work. I should however probably say that he doesn’t see the trainer’s visits.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The Unseen is also limited to 3 members. I would prefer if it didn’t show the trainer, yeah. I’d use my Forestall suggestion though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>KPN stands for Kills per night btw.</p>
<p>Rampage does in fact kill the targets visitors.</p>
<p>All of the naming things are because of either flavor or the different number of uses.</p>
<p>Power play does not work quite like any of the existing equivalents as it can force a king’s double vote. Dedication is a night ability so that it would take a night to use instead of happening immediately.</p>
<p>Medic removing occupy immunity is totally the job of the support. Its not like you are using it on the other resistance members if they are occ immune</p>
<p>The Scout is there to reward converting the spy rather than killing him. Also the things the scout finds are different or more powerful (depending on ability) than the informant.</p>
<p>As for the Spy… Your Forestall suggestion is fine but I’m not sure you get why Spy isn’t anything like Sheriff or Paladin. Unlike with the Unseen or Cult the Resistance has a strictly limited number of members. If you could easily point at someone and say if they are a Resistance member it wouldn’t work. I should however probably say that he doesn’t see the trainer’s visits.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is my first response to a faction suggestion so, sorry if it sucks! I think this will be really long. Hope you have the patience for this.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Vive la Resistance!! Please make it green!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I’m not really fond of the leader being called “The Trainer”. It kinda sounds less powerful than I think it should.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Can you explain to me how Retrain is really supposed to work? The way I understood it is that you choose a Resistance member an someone who isn’t Resistance. The Resistance member dies and the other take his place as Resistance. If this is how it works, I like it! Also train not losing a use after failing is awesome.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I say let the Activist be killable. I would strongly recommend it even. Does Rampage kill your visitors or the targets visitors? I believe it’s the target’s.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Regarding the Planner, why not just Tornado on night ability 1? No problem with Zeal.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Saboteur? Occupy immunity is ok. I think you meant Sabotage as well and it sounds good to me. Also Mislead only has one s. Both of the night abilities effects already exist. I’d use the existing ones instead, since they share the same effect you intend here.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kamikaze*. I think regardless of Expendable, the Trainer should always get another use of train if a Resistance member dies from other means than Retrain. I like his night abiities.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Informant*, missing an n there. Nothing to add to this class, simple and nice. The same applies to Mystic, I’d just have less uses of Mind read and use Marshall’s existing ability instead.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Medic has a cool passive. Heal should be infinite. Escort should give occupy immunity and nothing else. Removing should not be the job of a suppot class.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Flagbearer’s passives are what they need to be. I believe there is already an ability such as his day ability. I know the last part is different, but I still suggest sticking to the existing ones.Petition would kinda give the Flagbearer away on the next vote.Dedication should be a passive.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Scout and Informant are basically the same. I’d make spy become Informant and get rid of scout.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>As for the Spy, I like Forestall but maybe it should also work for Train, making Trainer unable to convert at all. Tag is too powerful, it should be replaced with something else. Scan is okay. Make it so the Spy can discover the faction of a target instead of Tag.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>No idea what KPN is.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Now regarding what has been told after the post…</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>In my opinion Private Matter can be either a night ability or a day. I don’t mind either option, it’s your choice.</li>
</ol>
<p>That’s it for my feedback! See you around!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 15:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just realized that kinda like the cult sacrafice the Trainers retrain means that the faction members have a short lifespan. As a result I lowered all the classes with unlimited use ability’s down to 5-8 nights of use. I would do 4 or less like the cult but the Trainer is not replaceable without the Flag bearer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 19:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Does anyone have any suggestions? Feedback? Things I missed? Ect?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 19:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I added something for the converted noble. Depending on what they do with him later I might change it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 06:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I cleared it up. I also changed mind read to the marshals snoop with more uses.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 00:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeathReaperRH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ahhh ok the wording just sounds like its a useless ability as you can only whisper during the day and this says</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="1" data-topic="24775">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night Ability 1: Private matter - Hide whispers to and from you (Unlimited)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This just makes it sound to me at least that you would have hidden whispers until the end of th night.<br>
Thanks for clearing it up!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 00:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1: You choose it is not a passive.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>It works like the old noble. This way you can use this and the day ability but you can’t use mind warp if you do. I am not trying to clone illusionist completely here.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 00:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeathReaperRH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you mean to make the night ability 1 on Spy a passive or no it is a choice between follow and spy?<br>
Also night ability 1 on the Mystic should be a day ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 00:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The consept behind this faction is a more mafia style faction that keeps that still has meny of a conversion game.</p>
<p>Faction leader</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The Trainer - Resistance Special<br>
Passive 1: Skilled - Night and Occupy immune<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Retrain - Attempt to convert someone. If it succeeds a Resistance member dies. This cannot be healed. You select 2 targets for this, 1 is a Resistance member and 1 isn’t. (Unlimited)<br>
Night Ability 2: Train - Convert the target into the Resistance. If this fails it will not consume a use. (2 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Faction killer - Will be replaced by the oldest non trainer resistance member if he dies.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The Activist - Resistance Killer<br>
Passive: Driven - Night immune once<br>
.<br>
Night ability 1: Eliminate - Kill the target (unlimited)<br>
Night Ability 2: Rampage - Kill the target and all visitors. Peirces night Immunity. Uses transfer between Activists (2 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Planner - Resistanc Support (CW and Merc convert)<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Misdirect - Swap all visitors of 2 targets. Resolves before other redirects (5 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Zeal - Prevent anyone from visiting the Resistance tonight. (2 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Sabateor - Resistance Offensive (converted from butler and drunk)<br>
Passive: Mischievous - Occupy immune<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Sabatoge - Occupy the target (4 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Misslead - Your first target targets your second Target. (3 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Kamakazy - Resistance Killer (converted from hunter and Knight)<br>
Passive: expendable - If you die by any means other than replace then the trainer gets another use of train<br>
.<br>
Day Ability: Mark - Set a mark on your target. They will be informed. The mark lasts 1 night(Unlimited)<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Revenge - if your target attacks or occupys someone then attack them. (3 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Suicide - Attack the marked target. You and them will both die. Neither of them can be healed. (1 use)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Informat - Resistance Investigative (converted from Princess and Observer)<br>
.<br>
Day Ability: Bug - You will know who your target visits tonight. (5 uses)<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Stalk - You know who visits your target. Can target self. (3 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Profile - Learn the targets class type and faction. (2 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Mystic - Resistance Social (Converted from Psychic and probably Priest later)<br>
Passive: Call the dead - The dead resistance members can speak to the living members<br>
.<br>
Day Ability: Psychic message - Same as Psychic (2 uses)<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Private matter - Hide whispers to and from you the next day (4 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Mind read - Read your targets journal (4 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Medic - Resistance Support (converted from Physician)<br>
Passive: Med kit - You will heal yourself the first time you would die at night<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Heal - Heal the target (4 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Escort - Give the target Occupy immunity if don’t they have it. Remove it if they do. They will only be notified if they are occupied. (3 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Flagbearer - Resistance Social (Converted from Noble)<br>
Passive 1: Royal blood<br>
Passive 2: People’s trust - Will always auto win a 1 on 1 with any class. Your guilty or pardon votes count for 2.<br>
.<br>
Day Ability 1: Power play - Force a player to vote target player. He cannot revoke the vote. If you target the king he will double vote. (2 uses)<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Petition - Target player loses the ability to vote. The next day your first vote for treason counts for 2. (2 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Dedication - If the trainer is dead then become a trainer with 1 use of train. You will not lose Royal blood. (Unlimited)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Scout - Resistance Investigative (converted from spy)<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Search - Learn your targets class (4 uses)<br>
Night Ability 2: Scan - check what classes visit your target. (4 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And now for the hardcounter</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Spy - Blue Dragon Investigator<br>
.<br>
Day Ability: Forestall - Prevent the trainer from using retrain or train tonight. (2 uses)<br>
.<br>
Night Ability 1: Tag - You know who the Resistance visits this night. (Unlimited)<br>
Night Ability 2: Scan - You know what classes visit your target. (Unlimited)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Something I would like to point out:</p>
<p>Unseen KPN: 2 + 4 + 1<br>
Cult KPN: 2 + 4 - 1/4<br>
Resistance KPN: 2 + 2 + 2</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 19:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-24775-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/faction-suggestion-the-resistance/24775.rss">[Faction Suggestion] The Resistance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
