<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391</link>
    <description>![image|650x750](upload://jl5sTM1QH7LYJejzlbPfCRPJzEp.jpg)

---------

## What would this mean for ToL? What is Throne&#39;o&#39;ween?

Well, I&#39;m glad you asked- basically it&#39;s ToL&#39;s version of Halloween, or All Hallows Eve. During which time Castle Adiart is decorated with pumpkins and jackolanterns, and all that kind of stuff. 

Decorated? Why would a kingdom back then be decorated? Well, actually- did you know jackolanterns were used to ward off evil spirits? *looks towards the ToL cemetery*. Because during Halloween (Throne&#39;o&#39;ween), darkness was at it&#39;s greatest power. The ghosts would rise, and haunt. and so the townsfolk put jackolanterns around the kingdom and it stopped. Bye ghosts :) stay in the cemetery where you belong ;) 

It would also, in my opinion just be cool to have these sorts of events once in a while. Keeping the community involved and active. Perhaps this would be a great time, for maybe 2 days, the day before and the day of Halloween to do a 2x GP boost or something of that sort, to bring everyone online and together. Heck, I was even thinking of something kind of cool but it might be impossible to do, maybe a Halloween outfit that would be sold for a limited time in the store, like a seasonal outfit. Only purchasable during Halloween-time, but not just this year- next year and so on, seasonal. The outfit I was thinking would have a jackolantern as the head and a viney-sort of body, hey! We need more cool armor! We have these awesome weapons, but somewhat bland outfits :(  and this shouldn&#39;t just be limited to Halloween! Maybe during like Christmas time Santa outfits, and maybe elf outfits could be sold seasonally too! :D but yeah, what do you think- Halloween in ToL? Any ways you can think of to make this a better suggestion? Let me know below in the comments section, thanks for your time reading this, and as always- stay frosty my friends.

___
and yes, this may be hard to implement this year on such short notice, but maybe it would be something cool for next year. :unknown:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 22:20:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://snag.gy/hQnYCz.jpg" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://snag.gy/hQnYCz.jpg</a></p>
<p>My god they managed to implement my suggestion!!! &lt;3 my dream come true, or am I asleep? ;( I better not be asleep and wake up and this all gone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 21:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3391-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391.rss">🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, agreed. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3391-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391.rss">🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nazle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Next year definitely, or something in the future before that with the same concept and mind [Christmas, easter - you know what I mean <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Right now I don’t think they have the time, and I don’t think its something they should focus a lot on, something you did mention which I like a lot is that they on christmas, easter, halloween and so on - make a little event where people get rewards for playing. Just a thought :))</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 22:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3391-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391.rss">🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/8/878b8f8fe14c2e2f484695bdbca32cce9dd6007d.jpg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="jl5sTM1QH7LYJejzlbPfCRPJzEp" width="650" height="750"></p>
<hr>
<h2>What would this mean for ToL? What is Throne’o’ween?</h2>
<p>Well, I’m glad you asked- basically it’s ToL’s version of Halloween, or All Hallows Eve. During which time Castle Adiart is decorated with pumpkins and jackolanterns, and all that kind of stuff.</p>
<p>Decorated? Why would a kingdom back then be decorated? Well, actually- did you know jackolanterns were used to ward off evil spirits? <em>looks towards the ToL cemetery</em>. Because during Halloween (Throne’o’ween), darkness was at it’s greatest power. The ghosts would rise, and haunt. and so the townsfolk put jackolanterns around the kingdom and it stopped. Bye ghosts <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> stay in the cemetery where you belong <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>It would also, in my opinion just be cool to have these sorts of events once in a while. Keeping the community involved and active. Perhaps this would be a great time, for maybe 2 days, the day before and the day of Halloween to do a 2x GP boost or something of that sort, to bring everyone online and together. Heck, I was even thinking of something kind of cool but it might be impossible to do, maybe a Halloween outfit that would be sold for a limited time in the store, like a seasonal outfit. Only purchasable during Halloween-time, but not just this year- next year and so on, seasonal. The outfit I was thinking would have a jackolantern as the head and a viney-sort of body, hey! We need more cool armor! We have these awesome weapons, but somewhat bland outfits <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  and this shouldn’t just be limited to Halloween! Maybe during like Christmas time Santa outfits, and maybe elf outfits could be sold seasonally too! <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> but yeah, what do you think- Halloween in ToL? Any ways you can think of to make this a better suggestion? Let me know below in the comments section, thanks for your time reading this, and as always- stay frosty my friends.</p>
<hr>
<p>and yes, this may be hard to implement this year on such short notice, but maybe it would be something cool for next year. <img src="/uploads/default/original/1X/b8d89f4cdc5d55da23b6ae120a3caa94ff342e6c.png?v=9" title=":unknown:" class="emoji emoji-custom" alt=":unknown:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 01:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3391-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/throneoween-a-throne-of-lies-halloween/3391.rss">🎃 Throne&#39;o&#39;ween 🎃 A Throne of Lies Halloween</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
