<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Inquisitor</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585</link>
    <description>
&quot;Ah!&quot; said the befuddled Brakuren. &quot;I have finally found some mythos on the Inquisitor. That bastard always burning up his past to save it from the sorcerer, makes my life a whole lot harder.&quot; Brakuren began to wander around his room in a Mobius strip-like pattern, for the myth on the Inquisitor was complex, or so to speak. He was befuddled at the fact that the myth actually contained no relevant information on the Inquisitor that he was searching for, but instead contained something about a &quot;SSOM&quot; and a &quot;MLE&quot;. &quot;How is this going to help me? How is this &quot;SSOM&quot; and &quot;MLE&quot; have any relevance to the Inquisitor&quot; what Brakuren didn&#39;t know was that &quot;SSOM&quot; stood for &quot;Secret Society of Magic&quot; which is where it all begins. 

You see, the secret society of magic was not the type of individuals to be classified as &quot;Nice&quot; they were the type of people who would rob you at any given moment in time. Leave at that some might be nice, but most of the people there only desired one thing, to rule to the kingdom of Adiart. The Sorcerer had gone to the Secret Society of Magic and studied there under some of the higher leaders there. She learned everything she could from any scrapbook she could find. The Sorcerer found all of her notes about casting from a near-by court wizard who left his notes out in his house. Every day she snuck in and read the notes, then she learned from The Secret Societ of Magic to curse things which would cause death. So, she began casting her magic that she had learned from the Court Wizard and then cursing it. 

Now you might ask &quot;How does this relate to the Inquisitor?&quot; Let me answer that question. The MLE stands (stood) for &quot;Magic Law Enforcement&quot;. Magic Law Enforcement was a small group of individuals unified under a banner that &quot;Magic is the Devil&#39;s Work&quot;. What you can infer from this is that all of the individuals were religious, and your answer would be correct. These men were very religious but they were all old. They were not fond of the new practices, so they persecuted any magic users. The men in the &quot;Magic Law Enforcement&quot; all knew of the way to tell if there was a magic user, &quot;If they had magical insignias on them&quot;. 

So, on a day like any other, the sun was gone in the skies of Adiart. The clouds rained darkness upon the peaceful town. The Sorcerer was attending her daily death lessons when suddenly... 
## _BOOM_

The wall of the facility collapsed and to reveal three old men and knights all with spears and swords, ready to kill or capture the magic user. It was total chaos, the criminals began casting spells onto the knights, not knowing who the old men were, but the clear winner was the knights. But during the chaos, a inquisitor was killed by a little adolescent who cast a fireball of death unto him. She quickly escaped and was unseen seeing as though she was wearing a hood. It turns out that the inquisitor that was killed was a friend of the inquisitor that Brakuren was researching.

After the dust swept the battlefield the Inquisitor grieved over his friend&#39;s death, and swore to god &quot;I will destroy this foul beast of the Devil! Rid this world of the evil in which they have created!&quot; The inquisitor vowed to get their revenge on that girl, that girl the Sorcerer. He vowed to avenge his friend&#39;s death. No matter the costs.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 01:33:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Inquisitor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Helpful advice</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 01:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58585-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Inquisitor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Inquisitor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s fine tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 21:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58585-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Inquisitor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Inquisitor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Ah!” said the befuddled Brakuren. “I have finally found some mythos on the Inquisitor. That bastard always burning up his past to save it from the sorcerer, makes my life a whole lot harder.” Brakuren began to wander around his room in a Mobius strip-like pattern, for the myth on the Inquisitor was complex, or so to speak. He was befuddled at the fact that the myth actually contained no relevant information on the Inquisitor that he was searching for, but instead contained something about a “SSOM” and a “MLE”. “How is this going to help me? How is this “SSOM” and “MLE” have any relevance to the Inquisitor” what Brakuren didn’t know was that “SSOM” stood for “Secret Society of Magic” which is where it all begins.</p>
<p>You see, the secret society of magic was not the type of individuals to be classified as “Nice” they were the type of people who would rob you at any given moment in time. Leave at that some might be nice, but most of the people there only desired one thing, to rule to the kingdom of Adiart. The Sorcerer had gone to the Secret Society of Magic and studied there under some of the higher leaders there. She learned everything she could from any scrapbook she could find. The Sorcerer found all of her notes about casting from a near-by court wizard who left his notes out in his house. Every day she snuck in and read the notes, then she learned from The Secret Societ of Magic to curse things which would cause death. So, she began casting her magic that she had learned from the Court Wizard and then cursing it.</p>
<p>Now you might ask “How does this relate to the Inquisitor?” Let me answer that question. The MLE stands (stood) for “Magic Law Enforcement”. Magic Law Enforcement was a small group of individuals unified under a banner that “Magic is the Devil’s Work”. What you can infer from this is that all of the individuals were religious, and your answer would be correct. These men were very religious but they were all old. They were not fond of the new practices, so they persecuted any magic users. The men in the “Magic Law Enforcement” all knew of the way to tell if there was a magic user, “If they had magical insignias on them”.</p>
<p>So, on a day like any other, the sun was gone in the skies of Adiart. The clouds rained darkness upon the peaceful town. The Sorcerer was attending her daily death lessons when suddenly…</p>
<h2><em>BOOM</em></h2>
<p>The wall of the facility collapsed and to reveal three old men and knights all with spears and swords, ready to kill or capture the magic user. It was total chaos, the criminals began casting spells onto the knights, not knowing who the old men were, but the clear winner was the knights. But during the chaos, a inquisitor was killed by a little adolescent who cast a fireball of death unto him. She quickly escaped and was unseen seeing as though she was wearing a hood. It turns out that the inquisitor that was killed was a friend of the inquisitor that Brakuren was researching.</p>
<p>After the dust swept the battlefield the Inquisitor grieved over his friend’s death, and swore to god “I will destroy this foul beast of the Devil! Rid this world of the evil in which they have created!” The inquisitor vowed to get their revenge on that girl, that girl the Sorcerer. He vowed to avenge his friend’s death. No matter the costs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 21:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58585-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-inquisitor/58585.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Inquisitor</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
