<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Possessor (There&#39;s a post with the normal title so I&#39;m putting this here)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor-theres-a-post-with-the-normal-title-so-im-putting-this-here/1361</link>
    <description>**Location:** Either http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/Lore  or  http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Possessor



**Subject:**  Myths And Legends: An Encounter With The Possessor

**A Note Taken in The Sheriff’s Journal:** Scouts have recently returned from a confidential reconnaissance mission to nearby territory outside Castle Adiart. One scout, to be accurate. The scout returned in terrible shape, tattered clothes and slashed skin. For days, this scout was constantly questioned about the events that had transpired on their journey. He would only scream and cry… a mere shadow of his confident, maybe even brash, self.

Days later, the scout seemed to regain what was left of his senses. When The Court Wizard took it upon himself to give the scout another questioning, the scout shakily looked at the Court Wizard. It seemed to terrify him to even speak of the event.

**“**We had just finished eating lunch… we were about a mile away from the castle. There was nobody… for miles. We were loading up our horses once more; food rations and the like. Rillard had disappeared behind a large boulder to grab some of his things he left when ‘relieving himself’. I was hooking some bags onto a saddle, when I heard a loud yell, and the jarring sound of smashing glass. I drew my sword, as I never let it leave my side. However, the other men had left their weapons leaned up against the mountain, or the large boulder. When I dashed to the sound, I found Rillard and one of our men locked in brutal combat. The victim… didn’t last very long. Rillard soon ran him through with his blade. As I shouted to the men to stop him, they all gazed at me in confusion. All of our weapons had disappeared. I felt my blood turn cold… I drew my blade, but I was distracted by… what seemed to be a pair of blue, glowing eyes near the boulder a ways away. A blue shimmering light surrounded a very... unkempt-looking man. I could feel the hair rising on my neck. I wanted to deal with the issue at hand, but I couldn’t seem to look away… not until Rillard was upon me, hacking at my armor. I shoved him away, and got a glimpse of my surroundings. Everyone else… had been killed. As I finally struck Rillard down with my blade, I looked back over at the rock, and jumped when the man was still there. He smiled at me… and I felt my vision grow cloudy. Afraid, I fell backwards, causing the sensation to dissipate, but I could still feel his eyes on me as I fled. I… I can still feel them on me now! No! NO!**”** 

The scout began to mutter nonsense, and was to be taken away for treatment by Castle Adiart doctors. We sent more scouts to see if there are connections between the “unkempt-looking man” and Corax. We are still awaiting their return.


**Comments:** I wrote this lore (in contrast to Magna&#39;s previous lore post for The Possessor- I had no idea there was lore suggestions for it other than mine) to emphasize the myth-like nature of The Possessor, and show him as something to be wary of when travelling. I also decided to make The Possessor a single entity, not a species of magical origin. His motives are often unclear, but it&#39;s indisputable that it&#39;s dangerous, and is required to be studied in attempts to learn if it&#39;s a real danger to Castle Adiart. Who knows what could happen if it managed to enter the Castle gates?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 14:12:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor-theres-a-post-with-the-normal-title-so-im-putting-this-here/1361.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Possessor (There&#39;s a post with the normal title so I&#39;m putting this here)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlueZed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Location:</strong> Either <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/Lore" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/Lore</a>  or  <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Possessor" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Possessor</a></p>
<p><strong>Subject:</strong>  Myths And Legends: An Encounter With The Possessor</p>
<p><strong>A Note Taken in The Sheriff’s Journal:</strong> Scouts have recently returned from a confidential reconnaissance mission to nearby territory outside Castle Adiart. One scout, to be accurate. The scout returned in terrible shape, tattered clothes and slashed skin. For days, this scout was constantly questioned about the events that had transpired on their journey. He would only scream and cry… a mere shadow of his confident, maybe even brash, self.</p>
<p>Days later, the scout seemed to regain what was left of his senses. When The Court Wizard took it upon himself to give the scout another questioning, the scout shakily looked at the Court Wizard. It seemed to terrify him to even speak of the event.</p>
<p><strong>“<strong>We had just finished eating lunch… we were about a mile away from the castle. There was nobody… for miles. We were loading up our horses once more; food rations and the like. Rillard had disappeared behind a large boulder to grab some of his things he left when ‘relieving himself’. I was hooking some bags onto a saddle, when I heard a loud yell, and the jarring sound of smashing glass. I drew my sword, as I never let it leave my side. However, the other men had left their weapons leaned up against the mountain, or the large boulder. When I dashed to the sound, I found Rillard and one of our men locked in brutal combat. The victim… didn’t last very long. Rillard soon ran him through with his blade. As I shouted to the men to stop him, they all gazed at me in confusion. All of our weapons had disappeared. I felt my blood turn cold… I drew my blade, but I was distracted by… what seemed to be a pair of blue, glowing eyes near the boulder a ways away. A blue shimmering light surrounded a very… unkempt-looking man. I could feel the hair rising on my neck. I wanted to deal with the issue at hand, but I couldn’t seem to look away… not until Rillard was upon me, hacking at my armor. I shoved him away, and got a glimpse of my surroundings. Everyone else… had been killed. As I finally struck Rillard down with my blade, I looked back over at the rock, and jumped when the man was still there. He smiled at me… and I felt my vision grow cloudy. Afraid, I fell backwards, causing the sensation to dissipate, but I could still feel his eyes on me as I fled. I… I can still feel them on me now! No! NO!</strong>”</strong></p>
<p>The scout began to mutter nonsense, and was to be taken away for treatment by Castle Adiart doctors. We sent more scouts to see if there are connections between the “unkempt-looking man” and Corax. We are still awaiting their return.</p>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong> I wrote this lore (in contrast to Magna’s previous lore post for The Possessor- I had no idea there was lore suggestions for it other than mine) to emphasize the myth-like nature of The Possessor, and show him as something to be wary of when travelling. I also decided to make The Possessor a single entity, not a species of magical origin. His motives are often unclear, but it’s indisputable that it’s dangerous, and is required to be studied in attempts to learn if it’s a real danger to Castle Adiart. Who knows what could happen if it managed to enter the Castle gates?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor-theres-a-post-with-the-normal-title-so-im-putting-this-here/1361/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor-theres-a-post-with-the-normal-title-so-im-putting-this-here/1361/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 14:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1361-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-possessor-theres-a-post-with-the-normal-title-so-im-putting-this-here/1361.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Possessor (There&#39;s a post with the normal title so I&#39;m putting this here)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
