<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ongoing games notification</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679</link>
    <description>Please add a message to lobbies about the number of ongoing games

If a player joins a lobby while there is one ongoing game, it should say something like
&quot;There is currently 1 game in progress - people will likely join when it ends.&quot;
If a player joins a lobby while there is no ongoing games, prompt them to join the Discord and get a game started. (that&#39;s how most games are started now, and new players should be **told** that)

If there are games going, the thing which stops people from leaving when they see only a few players in the lobby is someone saying &quot;hey there is a game going, just wait for it to end and people will join&quot;. 
If someone doesn&#39;t know that and sees like 3/16 people in a lobby and they&#39;re not on the discord they&#39;ll just go &quot;oh nobody is online i&#39;ll leave&quot;

New players who join without being on the discord should know how to get a game started.

This change would likely improve player retention which is obviously needed right now</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 02:09:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ongoing games notification</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_torino]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please add a message to lobbies about the number of ongoing games</p>
<p>If a player joins a lobby while there is one ongoing game, it should say something like<br>
“There is currently 1 game in progress - people will likely join when it ends.”<br>
If a player joins a lobby while there is no ongoing games, prompt them to join the Discord and get a game started. (that’s how most games are started now, and new players should be <strong>told</strong> that)</p>
<p>If there are games going, the thing which stops people from leaving when they see only a few players in the lobby is someone saying “hey there is a game going, just wait for it to end and people will join”.<br>
If someone doesn’t know that and sees like 3/16 people in a lobby and they’re not on the discord they’ll just go “oh nobody is online i’ll leave”</p>
<p>New players who join without being on the discord should know how to get a game started.</p>
<p>This change would likely improve player retention which is obviously needed right now</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 05:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88679-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679.rss">Ongoing games notification</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
