<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424</link>
    <description>**If Revived somebody as Priest: Soulcatcher (Investigative):** 

**Consume Soul (Passive):** If you die at night with at least one soul, you will consume it and come back to life. (Does NOT work if executed by The Prince)
**Soul Splice (Day):** Choose a target - Use a Soul and they become Immune to death this upcoming night. ∞ use (must have at least 1 soul).
**Collect Soul (Night):** Capture a dying player&#39;s soul. - ∞ use.
**Unleash Souls (Night):** Unleash all the souls you currently have in your possession each targets a random player and reveals the target&#39;s class to you. - ∞ use.


**If Revive wasn&#39;t used: Soulcatcher (Support):**

**Consume Soul (Passive):** If you die at night with at least one soul, you will consume it and come back to life. (Does NOT work if executed by The Prince)
**Soul Splice (Day):** Choose a target - Use a Soul and they become Immune to death this upcoming night. ∞ use (must have at least 1 soul).
**Collect Soul (Night):** Capture a dying player&#39;s soul. - ∞ use.
**Re-animate (Night):** Use all of your souls, including your own, to bring back a dead Blue Dragon, they will be revived as their Unseen Class. You will show up as Priest. - 1 use (you will die, must have at least 3 souls)


**Reasons why I think this would benefit the game:** 

With this revision, you&#39;re able to keep your Priest claim when Soulcatcher.

I always thought it was strange that the Priest would be converted into an investigating monk type figure. Why would Souls be giving you someone&#39;s class? I know logic isn&#39;t always played out in Throne of Lies, but my ideas fit the Soulcatcher much better.

Granted, it&#39;s essentially a MastermindPriest but I don&#39;t think this is a bad thing right here.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 22:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nazle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good concept, I have some problems tho:</p>
<ul>
<li>How would this work when there can only be 3 unseen members at the same time?</li>
</ul>
<p>And I think the restriction on having 3 souls on reviving is to much, which also brings in another problem that is explained in my long text under.</p>
<p>If you are converted mid game, I’d rather have my invest Soulcatcher which I think is very strong. You are nerfing the Soulcatcher a bit too hard imo with having them dying when they revive with 0 souls as this pretty much mean you have to wait 3 nights before you can revive. I’d also not give my life for someone who is dead as I’d rather trust on myself to win with the Unseen, what I am trying to say is that wouldn’t I hand over the responsibility to the revived member since I would die the same time when I have 0 souls, waiting 3 nights for you to be able to revive in the first place for the Unseen  is too long imo, then you also get the [3 unseen only member problem] and on that here is another problem: I do not know what you would change because taking away the “souls” part in the kit would mean you take away a part in the kit. - and name.</p>
<p>Having the Soulcatcher not being able to revive someone is good my opinion as this brings more deduction in the game, and lying is super fun when it comes down to ToL.</p>
<p>Scenario example:</p>
<ul>
<li>Why have you not revived someone yet Priest…</li>
<li>ehmmm I was occupied, etc…</li>
</ul>
<p>If you manage to play along with the lie you are telling, and you win the game, you get such a good feeling, so please don’t remove that.</p>
<p>The changes I would like for Soulcatcher would be to reconstruct the Unleash Souls into something a bit less over powered, tho I do not have anything on my mind yet, but I am thinking <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 22:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3424-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424.rss">[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm, seems good</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 20:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3424-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424.rss">[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know! I missed something out when copy pasting my notes! (I added it in)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 19:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3424-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424.rss">[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But if you re-animate and die, showing as Soulcatcher and someone gets revived, won’t everyone instantly know they are unseen? Edit: Now it’s neat. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 19:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3424-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424.rss">[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>If Revived somebody as Priest: Soulcatcher (Investigative):</strong></p>
<p><strong>Consume Soul (Passive):</strong> If you die at night with at least one soul, you will consume it and come back to life. (Does NOT work if executed by The Prince)<br>
<strong>Soul Splice (Day):</strong> Choose a target - Use a Soul and they become Immune to death this upcoming night. ∞ use (must have at least 1 soul).<br>
<strong>Collect Soul (Night):</strong> Capture a dying player’s soul. - ∞ use.<br>
<strong>Unleash Souls (Night):</strong> Unleash all the souls you currently have in your possession each targets a random player and reveals the target’s class to you. - ∞ use.</p>
<p><strong>If Revive wasn’t used: Soulcatcher (Support):</strong></p>
<p><strong>Consume Soul (Passive):</strong> If you die at night with at least one soul, you will consume it and come back to life. (Does NOT work if executed by The Prince)<br>
<strong>Soul Splice (Day):</strong> Choose a target - Use a Soul and they become Immune to death this upcoming night. ∞ use (must have at least 1 soul).<br>
<strong>Collect Soul (Night):</strong> Capture a dying player’s soul. - ∞ use.<br>
<strong>Re-animate (Night):</strong> Use all of your souls, including your own, to bring back a dead Blue Dragon, they will be revived as their Unseen Class. You will show up as Priest. - 1 use (you will die, must have at least 3 souls)</p>
<p><strong>Reasons why I think this would benefit the game:</strong></p>
<p>With this revision, you’re able to keep your Priest claim when Soulcatcher.</p>
<p>I always thought it was strange that the Priest would be converted into an investigating monk type figure. Why would Souls be giving you someone’s class? I know logic isn’t always played out in Throne of Lies, but my ideas fit the Soulcatcher much better.</p>
<p>Granted, it’s essentially a MastermindPriest but I don’t think this is a bad thing right here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 19:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3424-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-revision-the-soulcatcher/3424.rss">[Class Revision] The Soulcatcher</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
