<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520</link>
    <description>&gt; # [color = &quot;brown&quot;] The Occultist [/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Killer [/color]** 
**Corrupting Energy (Passive)** - Any player that visits the Occultist will be corrupted. For each player that is alive and corrupted, the Occultist’s Corruption Rating increases by 3% per night and caps at 100%. The user will known their corruption rating at the start of each night and their gains at the end of it.
**Shield of Corruption (Passive)** - Gives the Occultist defensive bonuses depending on their Corruption Rating.
&gt;5%+: The Occultist will be immune to death at night.
&gt;15%+: The Occultist will be immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt;25%+: The Occultist will be immune to Bleeding and Poison.
&gt;65%+: The Occultist will automatically kill all incoming attackers.
&gt;90%+: The Occultist will be immune to Order Execution, Frenzy, and execution by the Prince and will instead kill the Prince when jailed.
**Mental Corruption (Day)** - If the target uses an ability the coming night, they will receive incorrect feedback. Only usable if the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 40% or higher. Able to use it against two players at once if the Occultists Corruption Rating is at 75% or higher. Gains an additional charge per 30% corruption. - 1 use 
**Eternal Night (Day)** - Skips a day phase and causes two night phases to happen in a row. Can only be used when the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 90% or higher. - 1 use 
**Burst of Corruption (Night)** - Only usable if the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 5% rating or higher. Kills a player. Gains the following bonuses depending on the Occultist’s Corruption Rating: - 
&gt;20%+: The first attack does not count as a visit.
&gt;35%+: The first attack bypasses night immunity and healing.
&gt;55%+: The Occultist is able to select a second target.
&gt;65%+: The second attack does not count as a visit.
&gt;70%+: The second attack bypasses night immunity and healing.
&gt;75%+: The first attack kills all players who visits the first target.
&gt;85%+: The second attack kills all players who visit the second target.
&gt;Infinite uses 
**Beacon of Corruption (Night)** - Increases the Occultist’s Corruption Rating by 5% and causes Corrupting Energy to trigger against anyone visiting the Occultist’s target along with the target themselves. Allows selecting two targets if the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 50% or higher. - Infinite uses 
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*

Theme: A neutral killer that becomes stronger as the game goes on.
Survivability: Shield of Corrupt can save the Occultist from pretty much anything, even the Prince, provided the Occultist&#39;s corruption rating is high enough.
Late-game: Once the Occultist&#39;s corruption rating goes over 90% it&#39;s essentially an instant win due to the KPN potential of double Burst of Corruption via Eternal Night.

Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:18:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>me gusta, the double night would be epic!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70520-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Provided he used Beacon of Corrupt n1, then no as then he’ll instantly gain death immunity. He basically needs to be occupied and attacked the same night in order for him to dying n1.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70520-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So it can die N1?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70520-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="brown"> The Occultist </font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Corrupting Energy (Passive)</strong> - Any player that visits the Occultist will be corrupted. For each player that is alive and corrupted, the Occultist’s Corruption Rating increases by 3% per night and caps at 100%. The user will known their corruption rating at the start of each night and their gains at the end of it.<br>
<strong>Shield of Corruption (Passive)</strong> - Gives the Occultist defensive bonuses depending on their Corruption Rating.<br>
5%+: The Occultist will be immune to death at night.<br>
15%+: The Occultist will be immune to occupation and target changing.<br>
25%+: The Occultist will be immune to Bleeding and Poison.<br>
65%+: The Occultist will automatically kill all incoming attackers.<br>
90%+: The Occultist will be immune to Order Execution, Frenzy, and execution by the Prince and will instead kill the Prince when jailed.<br>
<strong>Mental Corruption (Day)</strong> - If the target uses an ability the coming night, they will receive incorrect feedback. Only usable if the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 40% or higher. Able to use it against two players at once if the Occultists Corruption Rating is at 75% or higher. Gains an additional charge per 30% corruption. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Eternal Night (Day)</strong> - Skips a day phase and causes two night phases to happen in a row. Can only be used when the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 90% or higher. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Burst of Corruption (Night)</strong> - Only usable if the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 5% rating or higher. Kills a player. Gains the following bonuses depending on the Occultist’s Corruption Rating: -<br>
20%+: The first attack does not count as a visit.<br>
35%+: The first attack bypasses night immunity and healing.<br>
55%+: The Occultist is able to select a second target.<br>
65%+: The second attack does not count as a visit.<br>
70%+: The second attack bypasses night immunity and healing.<br>
75%+: The first attack kills all players who visits the first target.<br>
85%+: The second attack kills all players who visit the second target.<br>
Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Beacon of Corruption (Night)</strong> - Increases the Occultist’s Corruption Rating by 5% and causes Corrupting Energy to trigger against anyone visiting the Occultist’s target along with the target themselves. Allows selecting two targets if the Occultist’s Corruption Rating is at 50% or higher. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Theme: A neutral killer that becomes stronger as the game goes on.<br>
Survivability: Shield of Corrupt can save the Occultist from pretty much anything, even the Prince, provided the Occultist’s corruption rating is high enough.<br>
Late-game: Once the Occultist’s corruption rating goes over 90% it’s essentially an instant win due to the KPN potential of double Burst of Corruption via Eternal Night.</p>
<p>Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70520-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-occultist-nk/70520.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Occultist (NK)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
