<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reaper Buff ideas</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080</link>
    <description>Note: Im only asking for one of these. Both might be OP

Reaper&#39;s main problem are that he lacks ways of deflecting claims. Chilling someone can help but they can just put you in thier will and your screwed. The Possessor can just Possess when under suspension and thus set everyone else back to square one. 

Here is my solution:
A second night ability 

Soul Shatter (1-3 uses) - Kill your target, remove his journal and defile him. Cost&#39;s 3 soul&#39;s. Reveals their real Class to the Reaper

Now a second solution to this is upping his kill power. This doesn&#39;t sound like it addresses the issue but a higher KPN means less time to find you.

Second solution:

Gather darkness (same as now) - The attack on the target can&#39;t fail (bypasses night immunity, Healing, occupation, ect) Also attacks visitors (Normal attack. Doesn&#39;t bypass night immunity/healing) Visitor kills will die immediately and you won&#39;t get thier soul&#39;s.

This is basically a combo if the ritualist and Enforcer&#39;s main ability. In addition to Upping KPN it also lets you defend yourself vs roleblockers. Right now I rarely use gather darkness except to kill the king. The mastermind is usually not found by me as Reaper before everyone else.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 13:19:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reaper Buff ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Should Soul Shatter tell the reaper the true role and journal of the target?</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-type="regular" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="a602e160ae8b1572fc141f717d520d46">Soul Shatter should tell reaper the real role and journal</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="a6505f6ad514c1e20cd9b871623acb0f">Soul Shatter should tell reaper the real role but not the journal</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="822a34d1eaf42c47bf15d7549e3a4a32">Soul Shatter shouldn’t tell the reaper anything about the target</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 13:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3080-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080.rss">Reaper Buff ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reaper Buff ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s why it was my first suggestion. I find that it adds more. The reason behind the second solution is that it isn’t very useful right now.</p>
<p>Btw how meny uses should it have?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3080-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080.rss">Reaper Buff ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reaper Buff ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like soul shatter better</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 11:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3080-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080.rss">Reaper Buff ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reaper Buff ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Note: Im only asking for one of these. Both might be OP</p>
<p>Reaper’s main problem are that he lacks ways of deflecting claims. Chilling someone can help but they can just put you in thier will and your screwed. The Possessor can just Possess when under suspension and thus set everyone else back to square one.</p>
<p>Here is my solution:<br>
A second night ability</p>
<p>Soul Shatter (1-3 uses) - Kill your target, remove his journal and defile him. Cost’s 3 soul’s. Reveals their real Class to the Reaper</p>
<p>Now a second solution to this is upping his kill power. This doesn’t sound like it addresses the issue but a higher KPN means less time to find you.</p>
<p>Second solution:</p>
<p>Gather darkness (same as now) - The attack on the target can’t fail (bypasses night immunity, Healing, occupation, ect) Also attacks visitors (Normal attack. Doesn’t bypass night immunity/healing) Visitor kills will die immediately and you won’t get thier soul’s.</p>
<p>This is basically a combo if the ritualist and Enforcer’s main ability. In addition to Upping KPN it also lets you defend yourself vs roleblockers. Right now I rarely use gather darkness except to kill the king. The mastermind is usually not found by me as Reaper before everyone else.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 01:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3080-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/reaper-buff-ideas/3080.rss">Reaper Buff ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
