<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882</link>
    <description># [color=Green]VLDR 3: Experiments[/color]

[color=(color)]   [/color]

Hosted by TrustworthyLiberal 
Co-Host(s): Kyo, Solic
# Important Notes

**As a notice this game will run Wed through Saturday and be on pause sunday through Tusday.**
**The hosts may or may not utilize WOTM to prohibit players from joining.**
In addition i am looking for 1/2 co-hosts to make action processing as smooth as possible 

Hope to start on Wednesday Augest 18th maw allow disscusion to start slightly before this time. 
Likely close this thread sometime before that to rand roles and allow any questions to form.

### How to Play

The game will shift through three cycles, Discussion, Roaming, and Ambidex, until it is over. Note that this game is complex and has many elements and factors. Please read all of the below before signing up.


[details=&quot;Discussion&quot;]
During Discussion all players can speak in the main thread. All players will be in the same room, so actions can be performed on other players during this time. You can also choose to end Discussion early by leaving the room. After you have left you can no longer talk in the main thread, and players can no longer perform actions on you.

Discussion will last for 24 hours, or until 3/4 of the total players have left the room.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Roaming&quot;]
During roaming all players can move about and perform actions, search for items, attack other players, and explore in a pre-made map via PMs. If two or more people are in the same place they will be added to a PM in which they can talk privately.

There will likely be different puzzles you can solve to get better and upgraded gear and to unlock other areas of the map.

Roaming lasts 48 hours or until all players say in their PM that they would like Roaming to end.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Ambidex&quot;]
During Ambidex all players will return to the room Discussion takes place. However, no actions can be performed at this time. Players will publicly vote on 1 of 3 lists that say which players will be paired with whom during the Ambidex Games.

After pairings have been voted on, the main thread will be closed and all players must decide whether to ally or betray their partner in their PM. If a player doesn’t cast a vote they will ally by default. If both partners don’t cast a vote they will both betray by default.

**Ally vs. Ally:** Both players gain 2 Ambidex Points.
**Ally vs. Betray:** The person who allied will lose 3 points, and the betrayer will gain 4.
**Betray vs. Betray:** Both players will earn zero Amdidex Points.

Ambidex Phase will last 48 hours, 24 for voting, 24 to submit Ally or Betray.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Stats&quot;]

If an action a player performs has a chance to fail, a 1d20 will be rolled with discobot. Depending on the action, the player will have one or more of their stats added to the roll. This will determine how successful it is. There are five different stats that can be applied to actions.

**Strength (STR):** Lifting or pushing heavy things, pulling things, attacking with melee-based weapons, etc.
**Precision (PRC):** Throwing items, attacking with ranged weapons, doing actions with items that are hard to maneuver, etc.
**Endurance (END):** How much hits you can, how much you can withstand harmful effects, etc.
**Intelligence (INT):** Searching rooms, gaining information, healing, building things, etc.
**Agility (AGI):** Dodging hits, running, attacking with melee weapons, etc.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Inventory and Items&quot;]

During the game, players may find useful items they want to keep with them, or take them from other players.

Players have a limited inventory space. They have 5 public inventory slots that can be seen by anyone looking into their inventory, and 1 private slot that no one can see unless the player is unconscious or specifically shows it to someone.

In addition, some players may start with an addition private role slot, in which a role item can be stored.

[/details]


[details=&quot;Roles&quot;]

Before the game starts, players will be assigned a role via PM. Roles will dictate unique abilities, stats, your alignment, and your win condition. Roles are custom.

Claiming anything on your rolecard is allowed. Players can make fake rolecards, abilities, stats, alignments or wincons. Speculating on the above is also allowed.

The four alignments are Good, Evil, Wildcard and Neutral.

**Good** players need to help others, and help as many people escape as possible.
**Neutral** players need to escape at all costs, and may have other side goals.
**Wildcard** players have a more flexible win condition and can end up being any of the other three alignments.
**Evil** players are there to sabotage others, cause chaos, and cause conflict and potentially death.
There is no role list.

**Roles and alignments will not be flipped upon death.**
[/details]

[details=&quot;Actions&quot;]

Players submit actions to the moderator in order to interact with other players and the map. These can be anything; picking up an item, punching another player, doing a backflip, investigate a part of the room.

To perform an action, type **/action,** for example **/Investigate the Couches.** Actions can be submitted in your PM, in chats with other players, or in the main thread during discussion. You can submit actions anytime except during the Ambidex phase.

Players can set automatic actions for when they are AFK in case something happens to them while they are gone. If they have nothing set I will generally do something for them. *I’m not just going to let someone get stabbed because they were AFK*.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Combat&quot;]

All weapons will have a certain damage amount. When a player attacks another, I will take the weapons damage amount and add it to the attacks strength. For example, if a player with a strength stat of 4 attacks a player with a weapon that does four damage, they will do eight damage.

If a player attempts to dodge an attack I will roll a 1d20 and choose a number depending on how the player is attacked. If the number rolled is more than that number the player will successfully dodge.

I am flexible processing combat actions and might award more damage points for creativity.

Health is calculated by 20+(5*END stat). If a player takes more damage than this they will be knocked out. If a player is hit after that they will die.

Medical items will have a flat healing amount, and extra healing will be added on by the INT stat*2.
[/details]

[details=&quot;Ambidex Points and Winning&quot;]

Every player will start with 4 Ambidex Points. Ambidex Point totals will be visible at all times in the OP. If a player ever has less than one Ambidex Point they will immediately die.

If a player has more than or equal to 11 Ambidex Points, they can access the Door Number 11 that is located in the map. When the door is opened, it will remain open for 11 seconds, then it will close forever and the game will end. Only players with 11 points or more can exit the door.

**The Ambidex Game is the only way to earn Ambidex Points, and the Door Number 11 is the only way to escape.**
[/details]
### Game Maps And Room Descriptions

## [color=Cyan]Facility Map [/color] 
![Facilitiy Map|494x432, 75%](upload://hLs7fdZ9KkfcVhtTn1mtdSCUvVe.png)


[details=&quot;Door Bay&quot;]
This is the main room where the doors await the ambidex game and everyone wakes up in.
[/details]
[details=&quot;Lobby&quot;]
Comfy looking lobby with a pair of couchs and a few tables with chairs setup with a carpet.
[/details]
[details=&quot;Cabin&quot;]
A simple navy style cabin that holds a thin layer of dust over it. 
[/details]
[details=&quot;Kitchen&quot;]
Stocked kitchen with some nice food to pair with it mostly stainless steel.
[/details]
[details=&quot;Laundry Room&quot;]
Beat down room with old machinery and table to bat has a weird clicking sound.
[/details]
[details=&quot;Art Room&quot;]
Narrow room with some nice art to go to it though seems almost more like a hallway then a room though.
[/details]
[details=&quot;???&quot;]
Wouldn&#39;t you like to know.
[/details]
[details=&quot;Stroage Room&quot;]
Boxs scattered around the flooring with no real set order a tower of which has formed in the back corner
[/details]
[details=&quot;Elevator Room&quot;]
Room with a pair of elevators
[/details]







### Rules

Breaking any of the below will first give you a warning, and breaking them again will result in a force replacement or a modkill.

1. Follow all Global Forum Rules
2. Do not discuss the game outside this thread or in your PM(s)
3. Do not copy and paste, directly quote, or screenshot anything sent by me.
4. Do not game throw, or go directly against your win condition.
5. Do not angleshoot.
6. Do not edit or delete any posts in the main thread or in any PMs.
7. Do your best to be active, doing actions and posting every phase, getting Ambidex actions in.
8. Mod has the right to add, change, or remove rules.

### Signing Up

To sign up, do /in, /join, just express interest in joining in the thread.
**The hosts may or may not utilize WOTM to prohibit players from joining.**

1: EliThePsycho: 8
2: DatBird: 8
3: Amelia: 1
4: Icibalus: 10
5: Geyde: 1
6: Aelin: 8
7: Atlas: 1
8: Apprentice: 10
9: Wazza: 8
10: Jane: 3
11: Marluxion: 6
12: ~~Silviu200530~~ Whysper: 8

**Back-Up**
1: Whysper
2: Nightingale
3: thepigeonnyc
4: WindwardAway

**Spec**
1: Sulit 
2: Min</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 15:42:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Completed</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Whysper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Atlas was giving away weapons like candy <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=10" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I got the Magnum and blowtorch from him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2974">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2974</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 15:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2974</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean nobody else tried</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2973">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2973</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2973</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightingale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>windex was the only weapon that could harm trustworthy<br>
whos the real winner here <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/sunglasses.png?v=10" title=":sunglasses:" class="emoji" alt=":sunglasses:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2972">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2972</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2972</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sorry to say but I don’t think windex counts as a weapon</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2971">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2971</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2971</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightingale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>but what you didnt touch was<br>
<strong>WINDEX</strong></p>
<p>also i touched the blowtorch if you count the flame part of it</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2970">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2970</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2970</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightingale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wincon: touch the most weapons out of all players</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2969">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2969</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2969</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scythe, sickle, Blowtorch, Magnum, spade, something I forgot the name of but I gave it to Eli</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2968">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2968</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2968</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/flushed.png?v=10" title=":flushed:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":flushed:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2967">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2967</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2967</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pretty sure I was the person who touched the most weapons</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2966">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2966</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2966</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightingale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i only took 1 hit the entre game<br>
thats how gamer i am</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2965">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2965</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2965</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TrustworthyLiberal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t write down the health’s at base cause it was all 20 +5 per END</p>
<p>So you could easily math it but if asked reminded people</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2964">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2964</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2964</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You had 40</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2963">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2963</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2963</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>40</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2962">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2962</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2962</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DatBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dont even know how much HP I even had the whole game. Luckily I never took a hit</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2961">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2961</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2961</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A single shot would’ve knocked me</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2960">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2960</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2960</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also btw during that entire fight I only had 4 hp</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2959">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2959</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2959</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Atlas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The two semi-big fights were probably the best part of the game</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2958">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2958</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2958</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DatBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cause if everything wasnt opening at once is it really fol</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2957">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2957</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2957</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the fucking SCREWS were STOLEN</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2956">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2956</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2956</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Best and most funny part in this game was Icibalus thinking there was a conspiracy with screws<br>
I am not going to elaborate</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2955">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2955</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2955</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arctic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>both mafia games and both misc games all finished around the same time</p>
<p>why does this always happen</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2954">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2954</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 10:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2954</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Silviu200530]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Game design</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2953">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2953</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 08:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2953</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>something something why the FUCK was one of my only abilities the ability to make my wincon harder</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2952">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2952</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 08:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2952</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TrustworthyLiberal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Naw you did fine wish I could actually remember names and help forfill that Rp part but all my hosting but the last two fights scenes was phone and omg I was having enough trouble with the site crashing never mind remembering names.</p>
<p>Sorry will do better next time on that part lol.</p>
<p>Dat wins best RP obviously.</p>
<p>Edit: Also amense thanks to both Whysper and Night for subbing in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2951">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2951</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 06:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2951</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks, but I didn’t really contribute that much beyond chapter 1. Really learned hosting a game like this takes a lot. I apologize for my low investment and won’t join again unless I’m more certain I am able to contribute meaningfully.</p>
<p>It seems that most players enjoyed the game though, so mission accomplished on that one! I personally lived for Birdo’s roleplay. <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/smile.png?v=10" title=":smile:" class="emoji" alt=":smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2950">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882/2950</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 06:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-88882-2950</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/misc-gamethread-vldr-3-experiments-4-12-whysper-apprentice-eli-datbird-wins/88882.rss">[MISC] [GAMETHREAD] VLDR 3 Experiments 4/12 - Whysper, Apprentice, Eli, Datbird WINS</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
