<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Neutral Killer suggestions</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622</link>
    <description>**Reaper**

**Gather Darkness** - Make the Reaper&#39;s next attack almost completely unstoppable; bypassing Ice Ward/Hide/Mercenaries Guard and also gaining temporary occupation immunity for the night. The only thing that can block Reap when Gather Darkness is used is if the target is jailed. Should the Reaper be jailed the night following the use of Gather Darkness, the Reaper will automatically reap the Prince.

**Summary** - Reaper gets some of Serial Killer&#39;s attributes (if they use Gather Darkness) from Towns of Salem for a moderate buff. Many of this classes weaknesses are strengthened at the expense of souls. 

--------

**Sorcerer**

**Passive:** Circe&#39;s Shawl
Description: Immune to occupation and death at night. Players attempting to occupy will think they succeeded. The Sorcerer&#39;s visits at night are also now hidden.

**Summary**: The passive rework helps the Sorcerer blend in with other classes much more while also making it difficult for Observer&#39;s to find them. I also never really liked the old passives name either; it felt too generic. Inquisitor is now MUCH more important for hunting down the Sorcerer, too.

**Day abilities:** 

**Magic Dust**: Make two targets appear as a magic user to the Inquisitor tonight.
Uses: 3

**Summary**: Magic Dust is way too powerful right now, making an Inquisitor&#39;s Find Magic ability almost useless early game. Limiting it to just two players will keep it useful while balancing it a bit. 

**Femme Fatale**: Charm a target, temporarily preventing them from speaking (much like an Assassin&#39;s Distract) and also from voting for the remainder of the day. The night after, any Magic Missile that the Sorcerer casts will be mirrored to the player they charmed, too.
Uses: 1

**Summary**: Gives the Sorcerer a limited Two for One and also the means to make someone shush if they&#39;re too talkative. =p Side note: The charmed target won&#39;t know that they can&#39;t vote until they try to vote.

----

I&#39;ve no suggestions for Possessor right now. Honestly, I think it&#39;s balanced fine compared to the other two right now.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:56:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="grahfite" data-post="1" data-topic="25622">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/grahfite/40/1999_2.png" class="avatar"> grahfite:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Day abilities:</p>
<p>Magic Dust: Make two targets appear as a magic user to the Inquisitor tonight.</p>
<p>Uses: 3</p>
<p>Summary: Magic Dust is way too powerful right now, making an Inquisitor’s Find Magic ability almost useless early game. Limiting it to just two players will keep it useful while balancing it a bit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is the only thing which I disagree with.  Inquisitor is OP enough as is, it doesn’t need any nerfs.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Moleland" data-post="2" data-topic="25622" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/moleland/40/5104_2.png" class="avatar"> Moleland:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m not against the whole idea of the sorcerer magic dust being nerfed, it the reaper ability ideas, but TBH I feel that sorcerer circle of death should be self targetable too</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed, it also should be usable at any time.  I understand kills having a “warmup”  time for Blue Dragon killing classes but not for evil or neutral classes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25622-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622.rss">Neutral Killer suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not against the whole idea of the sorcerer magic dust being nerfed, it the reaper ability ideas, but TBH I feel that sorcerer circle of death should be self targetable too</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 10:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25622-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622.rss">Neutral Killer suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[grahfite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Reaper</strong></p>
<p><strong>Gather Darkness</strong> - Make the Reaper’s next attack almost completely unstoppable; bypassing Ice Ward/Hide/Mercenaries Guard and also gaining temporary occupation immunity for the night. The only thing that can block Reap when Gather Darkness is used is if the target is jailed. Should the Reaper be jailed the night following the use of Gather Darkness, the Reaper will automatically reap the Prince.</p>
<p><strong>Summary</strong> - Reaper gets some of Serial Killer’s attributes (if they use Gather Darkness) from Towns of Salem for a moderate buff. Many of this classes weaknesses are strengthened at the expense of souls.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Sorcerer</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive:</strong> Circe’s Shawl<br>
Description: Immune to occupation and death at night. Players attempting to occupy will think they succeeded. The Sorcerer’s visits at night are also now hidden.</p>
<p><strong>Summary</strong>: The passive rework helps the Sorcerer blend in with other classes much more while also making it difficult for Observer’s to find them. I also never really liked the old passives name either; it felt too generic. Inquisitor is now MUCH more important for hunting down the Sorcerer, too.</p>
<p><strong>Day abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Magic Dust</strong>: Make two targets appear as a magic user to the Inquisitor tonight.<br>
Uses: 3</p>
<p><strong>Summary</strong>: Magic Dust is way too powerful right now, making an Inquisitor’s Find Magic ability almost useless early game. Limiting it to just two players will keep it useful while balancing it a bit.</p>
<p><strong>Femme Fatale</strong>: Charm a target, temporarily preventing them from speaking (much like an Assassin’s Distract) and also from voting for the remainder of the day. The night after, any Magic Missile that the Sorcerer casts will be mirrored to the player they charmed, too.<br>
Uses: 1</p>
<p><strong>Summary</strong>: Gives the Sorcerer a limited Two for One and also the means to make someone shush if they’re too talkative. =p Side note: The charmed target won’t know that they can’t vote until they try to vote.</p>
<hr>
<p>I’ve no suggestions for Possessor right now. Honestly, I think it’s balanced fine compared to the other two right now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25622-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-killer-suggestions/25622.rss">Neutral Killer suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
