<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Hunter&#39;s Fury (Polished)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446</link>
    <description>A lone man in a tattered hood and robe walked through Adiart&#39;s Courtyard. You couldn&#39;t ever see his face but you could see a long brown beard and a polished sword sheathed hanging on his waist. Upon closer inspection of the sword you could see the inscription &quot;The Dragon will not fall as long as a knight carries me.&quot; 

This sword marked him as a knight and faded on the back of his robe a faint dragon with its wings spread could be seen. To a normal servant he was just an old man thinking of his old glory days and they would leave him alone.

The only thing the servants got wrong about him that he is not in fact a knight anymore, but the legendary Hunter that is rumored to live in the woods around Adiart. It was said that he speaks with the wisps, hunted with wolves and bears alike, and defended great threats that lived in the woods. Now whether or not these are just tales or truth is up to each citizen of Adiart and has sparked much debate in the halls of the castle. 

Not everyone was as negligent as the servants and the old Hunter felt a pair of eyes on him, as he scanned his surroundings he saw the King looking down at him. He had once known the king and served under him in the past wars, but this king looked old and tired as he had been dealing with this new threat of the Unseen that threatened to overthrow him everyday.

He waved and The King did not respond and just simply walked away, and as the Hunter once again went into his thoughts he saw a black robed figure out of the corner of his eye. He quickly turned towards him, but the shadow was already walking away. He ran towards where he saw the shadowy figure and saw nothing but a single rose on the ground. He picked it up and on closer inspection it had a single black petal.

After the close encounter to what the Hunter believe was The Assassin from the Unseen, he rushed back to his shack in a hurry and planned for the many nights to come. Many days and nights came and went, but the old man didn&#39;t waste a minute. He was one with nature and his home and forest would not be corrupted by the Unseen. He thought to himself *&quot;I have survived wars, plagues, fanatic cultist from far off regions, and even The Court in my younger days. I will not fall to Assassins and their masters.&quot;*

Months had past now and the man sat one night by his fire cooking his dinner for him and his loyal wolves. He heard a rustling outside and three knocks on the door, and as he approached the door he knew The Assassin had finally come for him. He picked up his sword, he opened the door and a slim figure in a black robe whispered five words to him *&quot;Join us Hunter, or Die.&quot;*

He replied with *&quot;Child leave this place or I will be forced to fight you, and then return to Court and stop all of you.&quot;* The Assassin laughed at him as she couldn&#39;t see how this old man could help or even stop the Unseen and she was only there because of the Mastermind ordering her to come here.


She raised her daggers, he just glanced and held his sword still sheathed and looked at her sadly. She made her first step towards him, but before she could make a single swipe both of his wolves lunged at her tackling to the ground and ending her life. He buried her the next day and mourned the loss of another young soul in another war that was not needed.

The old knight stared off to into the distance petting his wolves, and he knew he had to put an end to this fighting. He read the Inscription written on his sword once more and started on his journey back to The Court. He knew that he could defeat them as he was a myth, a legend, the man that scares the monsters, he was The Hunter...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:26:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Hunter&#39;s Fury (Polished)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thunder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Really good stuff here, Ace. I love the description and the exposition. It’s a nice, slow burn that has a nice satisfying ending and great details along the way.</p>
<p>Great job!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69446-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Hunter&#39;s Fury (Polished)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Hunter&#39;s Fury (Polished)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Silent_Ace1778]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Any feedback would be appreciated and don’t forget to like it <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 21:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69446-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Hunter&#39;s Fury (Polished)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Hunter&#39;s Fury (Polished)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Silent_Ace1778]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A lone man in a tattered hood and robe walked through Adiart’s Courtyard. You couldn’t ever see his face but you could see a long brown beard and a polished sword sheathed hanging on his waist. Upon closer inspection of the sword you could see the inscription “The Dragon will not fall as long as a knight carries me.”</p>
<p>This sword marked him as a knight and faded on the back of his robe a faint dragon with its wings spread could be seen. To a normal servant he was just an old man thinking of his old glory days and they would leave him alone.</p>
<p>The only thing the servants got wrong about him that he is not in fact a knight anymore, but the legendary Hunter that is rumored to live in the woods around Adiart. It was said that he speaks with the wisps, hunted with wolves and bears alike, and defended great threats that lived in the woods. Now whether or not these are just tales or truth is up to each citizen of Adiart and has sparked much debate in the halls of the castle.</p>
<p>Not everyone was as negligent as the servants and the old Hunter felt a pair of eyes on him, as he scanned his surroundings he saw the King looking down at him. He had once known the king and served under him in the past wars, but this king looked old and tired as he had been dealing with this new threat of the Unseen that threatened to overthrow him everyday.</p>
<p>He waved and The King did not respond and just simply walked away, and as the Hunter once again went into his thoughts he saw a black robed figure out of the corner of his eye. He quickly turned towards him, but the shadow was already walking away. He ran towards where he saw the shadowy figure and saw nothing but a single rose on the ground. He picked it up and on closer inspection it had a single black petal.</p>
<p>After the close encounter to what the Hunter believe was The Assassin from the Unseen, he rushed back to his shack in a hurry and planned for the many nights to come. Many days and nights came and went, but the old man didn’t waste a minute. He was one with nature and his home and forest would not be corrupted by the Unseen. He thought to himself <em>“I have survived wars, plagues, fanatic cultist from far off regions, and even The Court in my younger days. I will not fall to Assassins and their masters.”</em></p>
<p>Months had past now and the man sat one night by his fire cooking his dinner for him and his loyal wolves. He heard a rustling outside and three knocks on the door, and as he approached the door he knew The Assassin had finally come for him. He picked up his sword, he opened the door and a slim figure in a black robe whispered five words to him <em>“Join us Hunter, or Die.”</em></p>
<p>He replied with <em>“Child leave this place or I will be forced to fight you, and then return to Court and stop all of you.”</em> The Assassin laughed at him as she couldn’t see how this old man could help or even stop the Unseen and she was only there because of the Mastermind ordering her to come here.</p>
<p>She raised her daggers, he just glanced and held his sword still sheathed and looked at her sadly. She made her first step towards him, but before she could make a single swipe both of his wolves lunged at her tackling to the ground and ending her life. He buried her the next day and mourned the loss of another young soul in another war that was not needed.</p>
<p>The old knight stared off to into the distance petting his wolves, and he knew he had to put an end to this fighting. He read the Inscription written on his sword once more and started on his journey back to The Court. He knew that he could defeat them as he was a myth, a legend, the man that scares the monsters, he was The Hunter…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 19:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69446-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-hunters-fury-polished/69446.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Hunter&#39;s Fury (Polished)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
