<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458</link>
    <description>![image|600x450](upload://p8B86a54keIvBfCjuTtpRaai7rY.jpeg) 


# [color]The Alternative Universe[/color]
*This game is part of 2nd anniversary event.*

### Game information:
&gt; **Start date:** 29/09
&gt; **Phases:** 72 / 24
&gt; **Night actions:** 1 hour before day start.
&gt;
&gt; Everything else same as in standard FoL match.

### Rules:
[details=&quot;Rules&quot;]
&gt; 1. Follow the Global Forum Rules
&gt; 2. If you haven’t posted content in 36 hours, you’ll be prodded for inactivity. If you don’t respond to that prod in 12 hours, you will be force replaced.
&gt; 3. No private messaging others in the game about the game.
&gt; 4. Do not quote private host messages
&gt; 5. Don’t throw the game. This includes any form of intent to make you or your faction lose
&gt; 6. Refrain from posting so many times in a row.
&gt; 7. Players are not allowed to use big letters. These are reserved for the host.
&gt; 9. Lets all have fun and play together!
&gt; 10. Do not edit or delete made posts.
&gt; 11. Do not like posts in a thread if you are dead in that game.
[/details]


### Mechanics:
&gt; Every player before gamestart will be asked to design 1-2 classes which they think would be cool to have in standard FoL match.
&gt;
&gt; You are not allowed to discuss class you create with anyone else, until all classes are created.
&gt;
&gt; After that all classes will be revealed and SFoL game with classic ToL rules, but using only roles designed by you will comence.
&gt;
&gt; After match ends FoL team will review created roles and how well they worked in the game, and consider adding them to standard FoL setup.
&gt; So... do your best!

### Roles:

[details=&quot;Kings (called Tsars in this game)&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:368, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # Heroic Tsar :shield: :crossed_swords: :fire:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon Special**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Authority (Passive)** - Once per day, you may choose to make a player unable to be voted, and another to be added to your imperial chat at the start of the night. Players in your private chat cannot use abilities with limited uses, but will have votes for them during elections count as double. Twice per game, if you did not use any night abilities, you will be death immune for the night. If you die by any means, an election will be held to determine the next Tsar.
&gt; **Will of the People (Passive)** - If you are lynched or otherwise killed by Blue Dragon, all following Tsars will lose their Authority passive, no matter their alignment. Additionally, your abilities do not count as visits.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Subdue (Day)** - Occupy a player today. If you are an elected Tsar, this will instead prevent the target from using day abilities, regardless of any immunities. - 2 Uses
&gt; **Blessing of Might (Day)** - Give a player that is not in your chat immunity to conversion tonight. If you are an elected Tsar, this will instead add them to your imperial chat at the start of the night. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Vigilanteism (Night)** - Kill a player. - 1 Use
&gt; **Denounce (Night)** - Target a player and guess their alignment. If that player is lynched tomorrow and is that alignment, all players on their wagon will gain one use in any limited use abilities. If incorrect and they are lynched tomorrow, all players on their wagon will instead lose one use in any limited abilities. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # Corrupt Tsar :shield: :crossed_swords: :fire:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Special**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Authority (Passive)** - Once per day, you may choose to make a player unable to be voted, and another to be added to your imperial chat at the start of the night. Players in your imperial chat cannot use abilities with limited uses, but will have votes for them during elections count as double. Once per game, if you did not use any night abilities, you will be death immune for the night. If you die by any means, an election will be held to determine the next Tsar.
&gt; **Quisler (Passive)** - Should all members of your imperial chat by night 3 or afterward be members of the Unseen, you will join their chat permanently. If you were elected, instead a copy of all your messages in the imperial chat will be sent to the Unseen chat at the end of each night. Additionally, your abilities do not count as visits.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Subdue (Day)** - Occupy a player today. If you are an elected Tsar, this will instead prevent the target from using day abilities, regardless of any immunities. - 2 Uses
&gt; **U’kir Spirit (Day)** - Make a player appear as Blue Dragon to investigative abilities tonight. If you are an elected Tsar, this will instead add them to your imperial chat at the start of the night. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Vigilanteism (Night)** - Kill a player. - 1 Use
&gt; **Denounce (Night)** - Target a player and guess their alignment. If that player is lynched tomorrow and is that alignment, all players on their wagon will gain one use in any limited use abilities. If incorrect and they are lynched tomorrow, all players on their wagon will instead lose one use in any limited abilities. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that would stand in your way.*

&gt; # Devout Tsar :shield: :crossed_swords: :fire:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Cult Special**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Authority (Passive)** - Once per day, you may choose to make a player unable to be voted, and another to be added to your imperial chat at the start of the night. Players in your imperial chat cannot use abilities with limited uses, but will have votes for them during elections count as double. Once per game, if you did not use any night abilities, you will be death immune for the night. If you die by any means, an election will be held to determine the next Tsar.
&gt; **Among Friends (Passive)** - Should all members of your imperial chat by night 3 or afterward be members of the Cult, you will join their chat permanently. If you were elected, instead a copy of all your messages in the imperial chat will be sent to the Cult chat at the end of each night. Additionally, your abilities do not count as visits.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Subdue (Day)** - Occupy a player today. If you are an elected Tsar, this will instead prevent the target from using day abilities, regardless of any immunities. - 2 Uses
&gt; **U’kir Spirit (Day)** - Make a player appear as Blue Dragon to investigative abilities tonight. If you are an elected Tsar, this will instead add them to your imperial chat at the start of the night. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Vigilanteism (Night)** - Kill a player. - 1 Use
&gt; **Denounce (Night)** - Target a player and guess their alignment. If that player is lynched tomorrow and is that alignment, all players on their wagon will gain one use in any limited use abilities. If incorrect and they are lynched tomorrow, all players on their wagon will instead lose one use in any limited abilities. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that would stand in your way.*

&gt; # Mad Tsar :shield: :fire:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Authority (Passive)** - Once per day, you may choose to make a player unable to be voted, and another to be added to your imperial chat at the start of the night. Players in your private chat cannot use abilities with limited uses, but will have votes for them during elections count as double. Once per game, if you did not use any night abilities, you will be death immune for the night. If you die by any means, an election will be held to determine the next Tsar. Additionally, you abilities do not count as visits.
&gt; **Witness (Passive)** - Placeholder for wincon related passives
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Subdue (Day)** - Prevent the target from using day abilities, regardless of any immunities. - 2 Uses
&gt; **Blessing of Might (Day)** - Add the target to your imperial chat at the start of the night. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Vigilanteism (Night)** - Kill a player. - 1 Use
&gt; **Denounce (Night)** - Target a player and guess their alignment. If that player is lynched tomorrow and is that alignment, all players on their wagon will gain one use in any limited use abilities. If incorrect and they are lynched tomorrow, all players on their wagon will instead lose one use in any limited abilities. - 2 Uses
&gt; **Embrace Futility (Night)** - Placeholder for wincon related abilities
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; *Your previous wincondition.*

&gt; # Psychopathic Tsar :shield: :fire:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Authority (Passive)** - Once per day, you may choose to make a player unable to be voted, and another to be added to your imperial chat at the start of the night. Players in your private chat cannot use abilities with limited uses, but will have votes for them during elections count as double. If you die by any means, an election will be held to determine the next Tsar.
&gt; **Abomination (Passive)** - You are immune to everything other than lynches. Every night, you may choose to kill a player. If you are alive in the last 5 players, the game will end with you as the victor. Additionally, your abilities do not count as visits.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Subdue (Day)** - Prevent the target from using day abilities, regardless of any immunities. - 2 Uses
&gt; **Blessing of Might (Day)** - Add the target to your imperial chat at the start of the night. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Denounce (Night)** - Target a player and guess their alignment. If that player is lynched tomorrow and is that alignment, all players on their wagon will gain one use in any limited use abilities. If incorrect and they are lynched tomorrow, all players on their wagon will instead lose one use in any limited abilities. - 2 Uses
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; *Defeat all members of both main factions.*
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;BD Special and Converts&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:380, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; &lt;big&gt; **Enchantress** &lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **BD Special**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Hexed Emblem (Passive)** - You carry around the Hexed Emblem and will gain 1 curse stack on every even night is able to hold up to 5 curses at once. You start the game with 1 curse. If you out or hint yourself as BD Special, then you will lose 2 curse stacks (can go into negatives).
&gt; **Cursed Bloodline (Passive)** - If you are lynched, you may choose to bleed one person for every two curse stacks you have tonight, causing them to die in 1 night if not healed. If you are killed at night you may target a player to lose 1 of their limited use abilities.
&gt; **Bless (Day)** - Use 1 curse stack to mark a target with your *Blessing,* secretly making them take 1 more vote to lynch and making them immune to roleblocks/redirction tonight. You may target yourself. [3 Uses]
&gt; **Karmic Balance (Day)** - Gain 2 curse stacks but inflict bleeding on yourself, causing you to die in 2 nights if not healed. [2 uses, 1 Night Cooldown]
&gt; **Exiled’s Oath (Day)** - Use 5 curse stacks to bind someone’s soul, killing them through immunity and healing if they kill someone. They will be notified of this effect and you cannot be prevented from using this. [1 Use]
&gt; **Jinx (Night)** - Choose 2 players to be marked with the *Jinxed* status. If a jinxed player is the target of another jinxed player, then you will gain a curse stack. You will be informed on which *Jinxed* player was visited and this ability will not count as a visit. [Infinite]
&gt; **Bane of the Moon (Night)** - Use 3 curse stacks to gain night immunity and roleblock and bleed anyone attacking you tonight. [2 uses]
&gt; **Channel Soul (Night)** - Use 2 curse stacks to use a dead player’s support/social/offensive ability or 3 to use a killer/investigative ability. You cannot do this more than once per dead player. However, this will make them unable to speak to the living in any way, shape, or form. [Infinite]
&gt; *Win condition: Defeat all threats to the Blue Dragon.*
[/quote]

&gt; &lt;big&gt;**[color=purple]The Shaman[/color]**&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen[/color] Special**
&gt; **Hexed Emblem (Passive)** - You carry around the Hexed Emblem and have 2 curse stacks or however many you had when you were converted, whichever is more.
&gt; **Cursed Bloodline (Passive)** - You can choose to not become **The Assassin** or **The Hitman** if there is another eligible player that can become it.
&gt; **Karmic Balance (Day)** - Bleed yourself to gain 1 curse stack, causing yourself to die in 2 nights if not healed. You may spend a curse stack instead to bleed a target and yourself, causing them to die in 1 night if not healed. This will fail and not go on cooldown or take a use if your target is unable to be bled but you will not be able to use it for the rest of the day but may use a different day ability. [2 Uses, 1 night cooldown]
&gt; **Bless (Day)** - Make your target immune to roleblocks and redirection tonight. You may spend curse stacks to gain additional effects. [4 Uses]
&gt; - **(COST - DESCRIPTION)**
&gt; - 1 stack - Make your target secretly take 1 more vote to lynch.
&gt; - 1 stack - Your target will bypass visit prevention tonight.
&gt; - 1 stack - Remove all negative effects from a target.
&gt; - 2 stacks - Your target will occupy everyone visiting their target(s) tonight.
&gt; - 2 stacks - Your target&#39;s abilities will bypass immunities tonight if they do not target the Neutral Killer.
&gt; - 3 stacks - Your target will not consume uses of limited use abilities tonight.
&gt; 
&gt; **Jinx (Night)** - Target 2 players to mark with *Jinx* for 2 nights. If a *Jinxed* player dies from a source that isn&#39;t from **The Assassin&#39;s** or ** The Hitman&#39;s** night abilities, then you will gain 1 curse stack. You may spend a curse stack to cause the players you *Jinx* tonight to be mindwarped bypassing passives and for *Jinxed* to last an additional night. [Infinite]
&gt; **Burn Soul (Night)** - Use 1 curse stack to use a dead player&#39;s infinite use ability and prevent them from speaking to the living or the dead. You can consume 3 stacks to use a limited use ability. [3 Uses]
&gt; *Win condition: Defeat all threats to the Unseen.*


&gt; &lt;big&gt;**[color=darkred]The Adept[/color]**&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **[color=darkred]Cult[/color] Special**
&gt; 
&gt; **Voodoo Doll (Passive)** - At any point, the **Cult Leader** may target an additional member to *Eradicate* once at the cost of bleeding you if he does. This cannot be activated if you are already bled.
&gt; **Cursed Bloodline (Passive)** - If you die at night, you may target 1 person to have protection not work on for 1 cycle, not counting passives. You may also choose to have more than 2 day/night abilities and use up to 3 abilities per cycle.
&gt; **Soul Read (Night)** - Guess a player&#39;s class. If you are correct, then you will occupy them tonight and can give a cult member a usage of a limited use ability. [3 Uses]
&gt; *Win condition: Defeat all threats to the Cult.*


## Inherits 3 of theirs choice:
&gt; **Bless** -&gt; **Corax&#39;s Guidance (Day)** - Your target will be immune to roleblocks and redirections tonight. If they are not cult, then they will receive incorrect feedback on their abilities today and tonight. [2 Uses]
&gt; **Karmic Balance (Day)** - Bleed a target and yourself or heal a non-cult and yourself. You cannot bleed someone if you are already bled and this will fail and not take a use if your target is unable to be bled but you will not be able to use it for the rest of the day but may use a different day ability. [1 Use]
&gt; **Corrupt Intervention (Day)** - Prevent non-cult visits to target player tonight and learn who try to visit them. [2 Uses]
&gt; **Jinx (Night)** - Disable all limited use abilities of your target tonight and tomorrow. [3 Uses]
&gt; **Bane of the Moon** -&gt; **Blood Moon&#39;s Scourge (Night)** -&gt; All non-cult will receive incorrect feedback tonight, bypassing passives. If any non-cult use a limited use ability tonight, it will lose an additional use if possible. [1 Use]

[/details]

[details=&quot;BD Offensive and Unseen Converts&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:407, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # [The](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The) [Wikipedist ](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Main_Page)
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ![image|231x217](upload://AfW6GOMlQYYL94sCU9C7a6z7Pqx)
&gt; **[Blue](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue) [Dragon](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dragon) [Offensive](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Offensive_(military))**
&gt; **[Featured Article](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Featured_articles) (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing. However, if someone attempts to convert you, they will do so bypassing any occupation or redirection they may have or protections you have.
&gt; **[Wikieditor](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Introduction) (Passive)** - All Wikipedia mentions in this class reffer to the English Wikipedia (en). Disambiguations also count as articles for this purpose.
&gt; **[Getting to Philosophy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Getting_to_Philosophy) (Day)** - Enter a [wikipedia race ](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Wiki_Game) with your target. The host sorts a [random article](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Special:Random) and sends to both of you. The destination article is always [Philosophy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philosophy). If the target is part of a scum faction, this notification is sent in the scum chat and all players in that chat can help the target complete the race. The wikirace lasts for 24 hours and may be finished at night if the day ended before 24 hours has passed. Both players may send a sequence of steps (an input) they have taken from the initial page to the destiny page. Whoever finishes the race with less steps wins. Before the race ends, both players may edit their input. In the case of a draw, the race is nullified as if it never existed. If the Wikipedist wins the race, the target loses their immunities for the night. - 4 uses.
&gt; **[Wikipedia Charades](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Wikipedia_Charades) (Day)** - Start a Wikipedia Charade in which the charade master is the game host. The Charade and the tips are given out publicly. The first person to send the right answer becomes occupation and redirection immune for this night. - 4 uses.
&gt; **[Detect Vandalism](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Vandalism#How_to_spot_vandalism) (Night)** - If your target is from a killing, offensive or special class, occupy them this night bypassing immunities. - 3 uses.
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen, Cult, and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **Converts into What Wikipedia is Not or Cult Offensive**
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:410, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # [What Wikipedia is Not ](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:What_Wikipedia_is_not)
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ![image|230x232](upload://rrBgCsr6ilzMGQTRe0XdwvIaUKy)
&gt; **[Unseen](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unseen_(organization)) [Investigative](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Investigative_journalism)**
&gt; **[Edit War](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Edit_warring) (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt; **[Self-Published Source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Verifiability#Self-published_sources) (Passive)** - You can’t be targeted by people whose nickname is the name of a Wikipedia article created before the announcement of the classlist. Disambiguations also count as articles for this purpose. All Wikipedia mentions in this class reffer to the English Wikipedia (en).
&gt; **[Biased Viewpoint](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Neutral_point_of_view) (Day)** - Start a corrupted wikirace to Philosophy with your target. You may choose who wins and who loses the race. In both cases, you will frame your target as a class of your choosing to investigatives tonight. - 4 uses.
&gt; **[Disrupting to Demonstrate a Point](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Do_not_disrupt_Wikipedia_to_illustrate_a_point) (Day)** - Start a Wikipedia Charade in which the charade master is the game host. The Charade and the tips are given out publicly. The first person to send the right answer has their class type revealed to the Unseen. - 4 uses.
&gt; **[Fringe Theory](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Fringe_theories) (Night)** - If your target was previously affected by either Biased Viewpoint or Disrupting to Demonstrate a Point, investigate them tonight to discover their alignment, bypassing framing. - Infinite Uses.
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:417, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; # The Tavern Keeper (Unofficial Class)
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon Offensive**
&gt; **Steadfast (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt; **Dose (Day)** - Target player is occupied for this day. - 1 Use
&gt; **Mix Rooms (Night)** - Target 2 players. Redirect all players targeting either of your targets to the other. You will be seen visiting your first target only. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Serve Ale (Night)** - Target player will be redirected to themselves this night bypassing redirection immunity. - 2 Uses
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **Converts into The Wench or Cult Offensive.**

&gt; # The Wench (Unofficial Class)
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Offensive**
&gt; **Steadfast (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
&gt; **Dose (Day)** - Target player is occupied for this day. - 2 Uses
&gt; **Mix Rooms (Night)** - Target 2 players. Redirect all players targeting either of your targets to the other. You will be seen visiting your first target only. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Serve Ale (Night)** - Target player will be redirected to themselves this night bypassing redirection immunity. - 2 Uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:435, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; # The Brewer
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; BD Offensive
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Passive] **Hard-working:** Immune to occupation and redirection
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Day] **Product Tracking:** Learn who your target of *sell drink* last night gives the drink to tonight at the end of the night *(2 use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **Sell drink:** Give a player a 1-shot occupation that can be used the next night alongside their other night abilities. They will be informed you have done so at the beginning of the next night. *(inf use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **Discounted drink:** Give a player a 1-shot redirection that can be used the next night alongside their other night abilities. They will be informed you have done so at the beginning of the next night *(2 use)*

&gt; # The Moonshiner
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; Unseen Offensive
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Passive] **Addicted:** Immune to occupation and redirection
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Day] **Stalk Customer:** Learn who your target of *sell drink* last night gives the drink to tonight at the end of the night *(2 use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **Sell drink:** Give a player a 1-shot occupation that can be used the next night alongside their other night abilities. They will be informed you have done so at the beginning of the next night. *(inf use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **Cheap drink:** Give a player a 1-shot redirection that can be used the next night alongside their other night abilities. They will be informed you have done so at the beginning of the next night. *(2 use)*
[/quote]
[/details]

[details=&quot;BD Social and Unseen Converts&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:120, topic:78353&quot;]
### Peasant
Blue Dragon Social

Your abilities are that you can speak and vote.
[/quote]

&gt; ### [color=purple]Angry Peasant[/color]
&gt; Unseen Social
&gt; 
&gt; Your abilities are that you can speak and vote angrily.

Scribe A (Scribe with Calligrapher)

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:664, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # The Scribe
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon Social**
&gt; **Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become Tsar count as two for you.
&gt; **Reply (Day)** - Reply to a player’s parchment message with the same selected words. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Send Parchment (Night)** - Give parchment to a player. Choose 30 words for them to use the next day phase. The words cannot be longer than 15 characters. The player may re-order the words to send a message to you. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Patriotic Poetry (Night)** - Select a player. If they have Royal Blood, a vote for them will be negated silently. You may target yourself. - 2 uses :crown:
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # The Calligrapher
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Social**
&gt; **Royal Blood (Passive)** - Votes to become Tsar count as two for you.
&gt; **Reply (Day)** - Reply to a player’s parchment message with the same selected words. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Slip Parchment (Night)** - Give parchment to a player and frame them. Choose 30 words for them to use the next day phase. The words cannot be longer than 15 characters. The player may re-order the words to send a message to you. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Patriotic Poetry (Night)** - Select a player. If they have Royal Blood, a vote for them will be negated silently. You may target yourself. - 2 uses :crown:
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]

Scribe B (Scribe with Scrivener):

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:669, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # The Scribe
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon Social**
&gt; **Dedication (Passive) -** Immune to occupation.
&gt; **Messenger (Day) -** Target two players, they will be able to send each other a single 1000-character message through the host tonight. – 1 use
&gt; **Secret Letter (Day) -** Anonymously send a single 1000-character message through the host to a player. They will receive the message at the start of the night. – 2 uses
&gt; **Copy (Night) -** You will receive target player’s logs at the end of the night unless they have Royal Blood or their Class Type is Special. If the player did not have logs, you will not receive any feedback. Not usable until N3. – 3 uses
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **Converts into The Scrivener or The Partisan.**

&gt; # The Scrivener
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Social**
&gt; **Obstinacy (Passive) -** Immune to occupation.
&gt; **Man In The Middle (Day) -** Target two players, they will be able to send each other a single 1000-character message through the host tonight. You will also receive both messages. – 1 use
&gt; **Secret Orders (Day) -** Anonymously send a single 1000-character message through the host to a player. They will receive the message at the start of the night. – 3 uses
&gt; **Scrape Off (Night) -** If target player dies tonight, they will appear to not have any logs. – 2 uses :crown:
&gt; *Your objective is to Eliminate the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals who stand against you.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:702, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; ## The Runecaster
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon Social**
&gt; **Rune of Invocation (Passive)** : The power of runic incantation cannot be stifled. You are immune to all effects which may attempt to silence your speech. You keep this passive upon class change.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Rune of Alteration (Day)** : Using the power of incantation, alter the perspective of others. Force a player to accuse another specific player and lock them out of the ability to change their vote for up to 2 hours (2 uses).
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Rune of Revelation (Day)** : The power of runes gives you influence over the airwaves. Send a message of up to 250 characters to the court anonymously through the host (2 uses).
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Rune of Communication (Night)** : Establish a vocal link with another player. You and that player now share a chat where you can speak to one another for specifically this and only this night phase (Infinite uses).
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Rune of Creation (Night)** : Unleash the runic power of creation to summon a portal to the afterlife. You may utilize this portal to temporarily enter the afterlife and establish a vocal connection with the dead residing there, gaining access to dead chat. You may only stay in this realm for a maximum of 6 hours; you must return to reality by then or the portal will close and you will be trapped there forever (2 uses).

&gt; ## The Sealer
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Social**
&gt; Converted from: **The Runecaster**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Seal of Dominance (Passive)** : You are immune to all effects that may attempt to silence your speech. In addition, if someone attempts to silence you, they themselves will experience that effect instead. You keep this passive upon class change.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Seal of Petrification (Day)** : Force a player to accuse another specific player and lock them out of the ability to change their vote for up to 2 hours (2 Uses).
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Seal of Lies (Day)** : Send a message of up to 250 characters to the court anonymously through the host (2 uses).
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Seal of Sabotage (Night)** : Establish a vocal link with another player. You and that player now share a chat where you can speak to one another for specifically this and only this night phase. The rest of the unseen will receive all messages sent in this chat as they appear, but the linked player will not be aware of this (Infinite uses).
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Seal of Armogeddon (Night)** : Upon activating this ability, the result is, tomorrow during the trial, once someone has reveived enough votes to be hammered, sacrifice yourself in order to irrevocably transfer all the votes on the hammer to someone else and hammer the alternate person instead. Action is irrevocable (if someone is hammered tomorrow, you may choose to transfer the hammer to someone else, but you will die), but will not have an effect and will be refunded if there is no hammer the following day (1 use).
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;BD Killer and Unseen Converts&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:752, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; # The Insane Brawler
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; Blue Dragon Killer
&gt; “Killing is fun! Being accurate… That’s not my speciality”
&gt; **Throwing the gauntlet (Passive)** - If you die, your killer will gain a 1-shot silent dayvig. This must be used in their classcard and it will not be announced who used it when it is used.
&gt; **Fight to the death (Day)** - Target player will be attacked. If they are a Killing class you will die instead. This does not bypass immunities. If you kill a Blue Dragon player you will be unable to use ‘Baile de la muerte’ again. - 1 use
&gt; **Baile de la muerte (Night)** - Target 2 players. If they are from the same faction, attack them both. Neutral Killers count as a separate faction for the sake of this. This does not bypass immunities. - Infinite use, 1 night cooldown upon successful use.
&gt; **Last Stand Saloon (Night)** - Gladiate a player, only one of you two may be lynched the following day. If you are lynched, the other player gets your ‘Throwing the gauntlet’ trigger for defeating you in combat. - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm*

&gt; # The Combattant
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; Unseen Killer
&gt; “I fight for what is right. As the Hitman’s friend and Mastermind’s right hand.”
&gt; **Seasoned Fighter (Passive)** - You will not become The Hitman upon the Hitman’s death. Instead you will gain 4 uses of ‘dastardly dagger’.
&gt; **Dealing in Death (Passive)** - If you die, your killer will gain a bonus dependent on their class type (As listed under ‘Class buffs’). If you die to a lynch, this will be given to the first person to vote to you on the current wagon.
&gt; **Dastardly Dagger (Day)** - Attack someone. Does not bypass immunities. - 0 use.
&gt; **Gifted with Death (Day)** - Give someone a gift, they may choose to open it or leave it. If they open the gift and they are a killer this gives them a 1-shot dayvig, if they are not a killer they die. If they choose to leave it, they will bleed causing them to die in 2 days if not healed. - Infinite uses, 1 day cooldown.
&gt; **Champion of the Arena (Night)** - Choose 2 people. If they are from the same faction attack both. Bypasses immunities, Neutral Killers count as Neutral for this ability. - Infinite Uses (Only usable after Hitman dies)
&gt; **Underhanded Blow (Night)** - Gladiate a player, only one of you two may be lynched the following day. If you are lynched, the other player gets your ‘Throwing the gauntlet’ trigger for defeating you in combat. - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; Class Buffs:
&gt; Killer - Gains a 1-shot dayvig. This kills anyone who hits a member of the Unseen.
&gt; Offensive - Gain a 1-shot immunity bypassing redictor.
&gt; Social - Gain a 1-shot matchmake, this is usable alongside any other night abilities.
&gt; Support - Gain a 1-shot heal, this heal succeeds even against any heal-bypassing abilities.
&gt; Investigative - Gain a 1-shot class check usable during night.
&gt; Special - Gain a day ability which instantly reduces cooldowns on your abilities to 0 and gain a use of any limited use abilities you have. (Has a 1 day cooldown for use).
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:778, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; # The Royal Guard [Blue Dragon Killer]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ## Passives:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Royal Blood** - Votes for you to become Tsar will be doubled. This passive will stay with you even if your class changes.
&gt; **Guilty Mind** - The 2nd time you would kill a Blue Dragon member, you will also commit suicide.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ## Day Abilities:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Revenge** - If the player that was executed was Blue Dragon, targeting one of their voters with **Kill the Guilty** will be unhealable. (2 uses)
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ## Night Abilities:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Royal Safeguard** - Defend target player. If a player visiting them would occupy, redirect, or kill them, you will instead kill the offending player. (Inf use)
&gt; **Kill the Guilty** - Kill target player, as well as occupying them. If you are redirected into killing a Blue Dragon member, it will not count against **Guilty Mind** . (Inf use)
&gt; **Goal:** Defeat The Cult, Unseen, and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.

Converts to:

&gt; # The Bastard Safeguard [Unseen Killer]
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ## Passives:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Royal Blood** - Votes for you to become Tsar will be doubled. This passive will stay with you even if your class changes.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ## Day Abilities:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; None!
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; ## Night Abilities
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Hideout Defender** - Kill anyone visiting Target Unseen member tonight. (3 uses)
&gt; * **Does not count as an attack**
&gt; **Secondary Killer** - Kill target player. If you target the same person as the Hitman, target player will be guaranteed to die. (2 uses)
&gt; * **You will be the attacker if you attack the same person as the Hitman.**
&gt; **Goal:** Defeat the Blue Dragon, Cult, and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:784, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # The Platypus
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **BD Killing**
&gt; ![image|287x310](upload://a17UgU5l4IekQPrK6rQDEvse1LY)
&gt; **Grkgkrkgrkgk (Passive)** : You must add a grkgrkgkrgk into every single one of your posts or else
&gt; **Platypus Slap (Night)** : You slap someone with you waffle tail! They will die the next night if they aren’t healed! (2 Uses)
&gt; **Where’s Perry? (Day)** : Disappear. You will not be able to be killed the following night but you can’t perform actions. (2 uses)
&gt; **Literally a Platypus (Day)** Put a curse on someone. They must also include a grkgkgrgkk in their posts for the rest of the phase. (2 Uses)
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # The EVIL Platypus
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Killing**
&gt; ![image|287x310](upload://a17UgU5l4IekQPrK6rQDEvse1LY)
&gt; **Grkgkrkgrkgk (Passive)** : You must add a grkgrkgkrgk into every single one of your posts or else
&gt; **Platypus Slap (Night)** : You slap someone with you waffle tail! They will die the next night if they aren’t healed! (1 Use)
&gt; **Where’s Perry? (Day)** : Disappear. You will not be able to be killed the following night but you can’t perform actions. (1 use)
&gt; **Literally a Platypus (Day)** Put a curse on someone. They must also include a grkgkgrgkk in their posts for the rest of the phase. (1 Use)
&gt; **EVIL PLATYPUS (Day)** Let your dominance be known. Your strength immeasurable. Choose a player, and their action will bypass player immunity, occupation, and protecting. (1 Use)
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:798, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; ## Executioner
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **BD Killer**
&gt; **Self-Defense (Passive) -** You are immune to the first attack directed at you. You lose this passive after use.
&gt; **Dungeon (Day Ability) -** Cause a player to start bleeding. They will die in three nights if not healed. They will not be alerted **- 1 use.**
&gt; **Clean Blade (Day Ability) -** Gain a use of *Dagger.* **- 1 use.**
&gt; **Dagger (Night Ability) -** Attack a player, bypassing Death Immunity. If they are not aligned with the Blue Dragon, you will gain a use of *Clean Blade.* Cannot be used the night after using *Clean Blade* **- 0 use.**
&gt; **Last Resort (Night Ability) -** Select a player. If they attack anyone that night, you will kill the attacker. Doesn’t take effect if the attacked player survives for any reason **- 1 use.**
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; ## Headsman
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Killer**
&gt; **Out of Knives (Day Ability) -** Cause a player to believe that they are bleeding **- 1 use**
&gt; **Cutthroat (Night Ability) -** Select two players. You will send the first player to kill the second. They will believe that they were redirected. If the Hitman attempts to carry out a kill, they will kill the Hitmans target instead **- 3 uses**
&gt; **Dirty Business (Night Ability) -** If the Mitochondrium conversion fails for any reason, you will kill their target for them instead. Does not count as a visit **- 2 uses.**
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;BD Investigative and Unseen Converts&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:823, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # The Cartographer
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon Investigative**
&gt; **Incomplete Atlas (Passive)** - You will be informed upon circumnavigating the court. Any players who visit a player with a trading post established or have a trading post established will be added to the Atlas. You are automatically added to the Atlas. Visiting a player adds them to the Atlas. You are informed of how many players have been added to the Atlas however you are not informed of who.
&gt; **Complete Atlas (Gained Passive)** - Your abilities are guaranteed to be successful. You no longer need to visit yourself to gain the information of trading posts. You may still use your abilities while imprisoned.
&gt; **Trace (Day)** - Trace the last day ability used on your target back to a player. - 2 uses
&gt; **Trade Post (Night)** - Setup a trading post on the target monitoring all players visiting them. This will collect how many night actions have been used on that player in total and determine whether they are positive, negative or neutral. Visiting yourself will give you the information the trading post has gathered. This ability persists forever. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Plan Route (Night)** - Learn a player’s class type if they visit a player on the Atlas. - 3 uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **Trading Post Indications**
&gt; Positive - Supportive and social abilities. (Ice ward, heal, bounty ect.)
&gt; Negative - Killer and offensive abilities. (2 for 1, emerald potion, timesnatch ect.)
&gt; Neutral - Special and investigative abilities. (Conversion, surveillance, test faith ect.)

&gt; # The Topographer
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Investigative**
&gt; **Assisted Atlas (Passive)** - You will be informed upon circumnavigating the court. Any players who visit a player with a boundary established or have a boundary established will be added to the Atlas. Unseen members are automatically added to the Atlas. Any member of the Unseen that visits a player will add them to the Atlas. You are informed of who needs to be added to the Atlas.
&gt; **Complete Atlas (Gained Passive)** - Your abilities are guaranteed to be successful. You no longer need to visit yourself to gain the information of trading posts. You may still use your abilities while imprisoned.
&gt; **Footprint (Day)** - Follow the last day ability used on a player. You will learn who they used it on. - 2 uses
&gt; **Boundary Tax (Night)** - Setup a boundary on the target monitoring all players visiting them. This will collect how many night actions have been used on that player in total and determine whether they are positive, negative or neutral and who used them. Visiting yourself will give you the information the boundary has gathered. This ability persists forever. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Divert Route (Night)** - Learn a player’s exact class if they visit a player on the Atlas. - 3 uses
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **Trading Post Indications**
&gt; Positive - Supportive and social abilities. (Ice ward, heal, bounty ect.)
&gt; Negative - Killer and offensive abilities. (2 for 1, emerald potion, timesnatch ect.)
&gt; Neutral - Special and investigative abilities. (Conversion, surveillance, test faith ect.)
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:843, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; ## Clothing Tailor
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; bd invest
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Passive** - eye for detail - your results are immune to tampering. In addition, if you are target the same person more than once, you will not be given repeat info where possible.
&gt; (i.e. frame/tailor/god father immune, not occ/redirect)
&gt; **Day 1** - The stains tell a story - at the end of the day, you will be told whether the target used a day ability today, and if so, its target.- 3 uses
&gt; (i.e. day observer)
&gt; **Day 2** - fresh out of the dryer - tonight, your night abilities will instead target the last word of the descriptions of abilities/passives- 2 uses
&gt; **Night 1** - take a peek in them drawers - You learn the first word of the description of one of the abilities or passives the target had, as well as whether it was on a day abil, night abil, or passive - inf
&gt; **Night 2** - a rigorous wash - you will learn the first word of the description of a passive, day abil, *and* night abil the target has, assuming they have at least one of each. you will *not* be told which is from what - 1 use
&gt; [bd wincon]

&gt; ## Tailor
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; Unseen Support
&gt; **Day 1** - The Stains Are Hiding Something - at the end of the day, you will be told whether the target used a day ability today, and if so, its target. in addition, if they targeted another member of the unseen, they will also be told this information at the start of the night - 2 uses**
&gt; **Night 1** - A cross-stich is *much* more sturdy - heal the target of bleeding/poison. in addition, if they are attacked 2 or more times tonight, give them night immunity tonight. - infinite, 1 day cooldown if secondary effect triggers, you will *not* be told when the ability is on cooldown
&gt; **Night 2** - Costume swap! - target a member of the unseen. if they were not one of the starting unseen, tonight all investigatives will receive results on them as if they were their original class. otherwise, all investigatives will receive results on them as if they were a Clothing Tailor - 1 use
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:879, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; ## **The Astromancer**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **BD Investigative**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Passive:**
&gt; **Star Map:** You will always get correct investigative results.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Day:**
&gt; **Comet’s Trail (2 use):** You will be notified if you visit the same player as your Target tonight.
&gt; **Inner Cosmos (1 use):** Choose 2 players. They will receive correct feedback tonight.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Night:**
&gt; **Stargazing (inf use):** You will receive all class types that visited your target tonight. Doesn’t show repeated class types. Cannot target King or self. Special classes show as Investigative.
&gt; **Galaxy Cross (2 use):** Choose 2 players. You will be notified if they visit the other players class type tonight.

&gt; ## **The Zodiac**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Social**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Day:**
&gt; **Outer Void (2 use):** Numb a players senses, delaying any bleeding feedback by 1 in-game day.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Night:**
&gt; **Constellation (3 use):** Frame a player. If they get executed the next day they will appear as their converted class or assassin if they are convert immune. If you succesfully disguise someone you will lose all charges of this ability.
&gt; **Celestial Object (2 use):** Make an Unseen member appear as a Class of your chosing to players investigating them tonight.
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;BD Support and Unseen Converts&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:919, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; # The Alchemist
&gt; 
&gt; Blue Dragon Support
&gt; **Coagulate (Passive)** - Immune to infection and bleeding.
&gt; **Brew Potion (Day)** - Brew a potion, each potion must be brewed once before you can brew the others again. [Infinite Uses]
&gt; **Apply Potion (Night)** - Use the potion you have brewed. You may save it if you wish. [Infinite Uses]
&gt; **Potions:**
&gt; 
&gt; * Truth Potion: Discover whether a player is a member of the Unseen/Cult or not.
&gt; * Tar Potion: Occupy a player, you will be occupy and redirection immune while using this.
&gt; * Health Potion: Heal a player, preventing their death tonight and curing bleeding.
&gt; * Poison Potion: Attack a player, if they are a member of the Blue Dragon, you will commit suicide instead.

&gt; # [color=purple]The Potion Master[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]Unseen[/color] Support
&gt; **Coagulate (Passive)** - Immune to bleeding. 
&gt; **Brew Potion (Day)** - Brew a potion, each potion must be brewed once before you can brew the others again. [Infinite Uses]
&gt; **Apply Potion (Night)** - Use the potion you have brewed. You may save it if you wish. [Infinite Uses]
&gt; **Potions:**
&gt;* Truth Potion: Discover a player&amp;rsquo;s class, if they are a member of the Blue Dragon.
&gt;* Tar Potion: Occupy a player, you will be occupy and redirection immune while using this.
&gt;* Health Potion: Heal a player, preventing their death tonight and curing bleed.
&gt;* Hemorrhage Potion: Cause a player to begin to bleed sometime tomorrow.
&gt;
&gt;*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals who may stand in your way.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:924, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; # The Nurse
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; BD Support
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Passive] **Medical Knowledge:** Immune to bleed/poison/all similar effects
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Day] **Nurse’s calling:** Learn who your target of *Give bandage* last night heals tonight at the end of the night *(2 use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **Give bandage:** Give a player a 1-shot Heal that can be used the next night alongside their other night abilities. They will be informed you have done so at the beginning of the next night. *(inf use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **Taste of your own medicine:** Using this ability heals you tommorow night *(2 use)*

&gt; # The Drug Dealer
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; Unseen Support
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Passive] **Thick skin:** Immune to bleed/poison/all similar effects
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Day] **Stalker:** Learn who your target of *Deal drugs* last night heals tonight at the end of the night *(2 use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **Deal drugs:** Give a player a 1-shot heal that can be used the next night alongside their other night abilities. This heal, however, causes their target to be bled the next day. They will be informed you have done so at the beginning of the next night. *(inf use)*
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; [Night] **High on your own supply:** Heal the entire unseen tonight *(2 use)*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:928, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
&gt; # **The Heiress**
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **BD Support**
&gt; **Would you like some tea? (Day)** : Hand someone a cup of tea. They will be unable to be occupied the following night. (Inf Uses)
&gt; **Tea Party! (Night)** : Give two players an invite to a tea party. The next night phase, they will be put into a private chat with you. They will also be occupied and protected. (3 uses)
&gt; *Defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **Converts into The Poisoner or Cult Support**

&gt; # The Poisoner
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Support**
&gt; **Would you like some tea? (Day)** : Hand someone a cup of tea. They will be unable to be occupied the following night. (2 Uses)
&gt; **Poison Party! (Night)** : Give two players an invite to a tea party. The next night phase, they will be put into a private chat with you. They will also be occupied and protected. You can choose one of the players to poison. They will start to bleed. (2 uses)
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Unseen Main Killer&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:734, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
# The Hitman [Unseen Killer]

## Passives:

**Trained Killer** - If you fail to get a night kill, your next attack will gain a one-time tiered buff, in this order:
1: You become occupy immune
2: You bypass healing
3: You bypass death immunity

**Promotion** - If (Unseen Special) dies, you will become the (Unseen Special).
* **Starting Hitman only**

## Day Abilities

**Cyanide Poisoning** - Target player dies during the day, bypassing immunity. (0 uses, shared)
*This ability fails if target is immune to bleeding
**Blade Slice** - *Bleed* target player. They will die in 2 nights unless healed (2 uses, shared)

## Night Abilities

**Suffocate** - *Kill* target player. (Inf use)
**Restock** - Gain a use of either **Cyanide Poisoning** or **Blade Slice** (2 uses, 1 use for promoted Hitmen)
**Goal:** Defeat the Blue Dragon, Cult, and any Neutrals that seek to do your harm.
[/quote]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Unseen Special&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:459, topic:78353&quot;]
# The Mitochondrion :shield: :fire:

**Unseen Special**

**Powerhouse of the Cell (Passive)** - Immune to death at night and occupation (although not target changing). You may at any time before your death pick another Unseen member to become the new *Mitochondrion* , swapping your class with theirs. Doing so wastes 1 use from *Mitochondrial Biogenesis* and theirs limited-use abilities. Any limited uses of abilities you or they wasted won’t be regained. You can’t pick your sucessor if you don’t have uses of *Mitochondrial Biogenesis* .
**Kiss-and-run Exocytosis (Passive)** - If, at any time, the Unseen finds themselves without a *Mitochondrion* , the faction is renamed to Monocercomonoides.
**Supravital Staining (Passive)** - You know, at the start of the game, how many factions there are.
**Celular Differentiation (Night)** - Change target player into the Unseen version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown
**Mitochondrial Biogenesis (Night)** - Make all actions from the Unseen bypass occupation and healing tonight - 3 uses.

*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, the other scum factions and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;Cult Offensive&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:954, topic:78353&quot;]
## The Trickster

**Cult Offensive**
Warlock Magic (Passive) - Immune to occupation and redirection
Trace Barrier (Day) - Redirect a player’s day action if targeting [Target] to themselves - 2 Uses.
Rune Mark (Night) - Redirect the players to self if one tries to visit the other, You’ll only be seen visiting the first - 3 Uses.
Blind Sight (Night) - Redirect a player to Self - 1 Use.
[/quote]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Cult Investigative&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:954, topic:78353&quot;]
## The Bishop

**Cult Investigative**
Dark Crown (Day) - Upon being elected for king you’ll have 1 vote extra.
Peer Gaze (Day) - At the end of the night, learn if a flip has been tampered with and by which class - 1 Use.
Eye of the Gods (Night) - Select a Class type and player if that player is that class type you’ll learn their class - 2 Uses.
Interrogate (Night) - Target any number of players and declare a class name. You will learn if any of those players are that class (but not whom) - 2 Uses.
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;Cult Killer&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:954, topic:78353&quot;]
## The Crusader

**Cult Killer**
Blood-lust (Passive) - You’ll visit for the [Cult special] Instead if they decide to kill, if there are two the oldest will visit.
Sacrifice (Night) - You will guard the target player tonight, giving your life to kill their attacker - 3 Uses.
Spite (Night) - Kill target player, Killing you in the process, this will bypass occupation and redirection - 1 Use.
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;Cult Social&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:679, topic:78353&quot;]
# The Partisan :crossed_swords:

**Cult Social**
**Specious Reasoning (Day)** - Your target will receive incorrect results from investigations tonight. - 2 uses
**Subterfuge (Day)** - You will appear to be BD tonight. - 1 use
**Expose (Night)** - You will receive target player’s logs at the end of the night. If the player did not have logs, you will not receive any feedback. Not usable until N3. - 2 uses
**Forge (Night)** - Select a target and send fake logs for them. If target player dies tonight and is Blue Dragon, their logs will be the logs you sent. - 2 uses
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that oppose you.*
[/quote]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Cult Support&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:972, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
## **Mithras Ritualist**

**Cult Support**

**Passive:**
**Mithras’ Protection:** If your Cult Leader is attacked tonight, you will be given the option to give up your life in order to keep them alive. **Healable if the attack is, other than that similar to a Knight defend but won’t kill the attacker**

**Day:**
**Mithras’ Will:** (1 Use) Chose a player and mark them for one night, if they are converted this night your Cult leader can decide what class type they will convert into. **Not usable D1**

**Copy(sorry for shot names):** (3 Use) Select target dead BD and copy a random non-killer ability

**Night:**
**Blood swap:** (1 Use) Swap or alter any invest results on target cult player. **Can target self**
**Mithras’ Strength:** (1 Use) The Cult is occupy and redirect immune tonight
**((Name is whatever ability last copied):** (Has 1-0 uses) Use your copied ability **Can only hold one ability at a time, copied abilities are one shot use, start the game with random abilitie**
[/quote]
[/details]

[details=&quot;Cult Special&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:484, topic:78353&quot;]
# The Infiltrator

Cult Special
“This place should have plenty to join my cause. Time to recruit some followers for the ethereal beings I hear.”
**Hidden Weapon (Day)** - Cause a player to bleed. They will bleed and die in two nights if not healed. - 1 use :crown:
**Secret Training (Day)** - Retrain a member of the cult, you may choose what original BD class that member would originate from, giving them different ability inheritance - Infinite use
**Outside Influence (Night)** - Change target player into the Cult version of their class. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. This may target a dead player, bringing them back to life - Infinite uses, 1 night cooldown
**Cloak and Dagger (Night)** - Attack 2 players at once, bypassing immunity, this can still be healed. Alternatively you may attack 1 player bypassing all forms of healing and immunity. :crown:
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that oppose you.*
[/quote]

## [color=orange]For converted Enchantress, check &quot;BD Special and Converts&quot;[/color]
[/details]


[details=&quot;Neutral Social&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:501, topic:78353&quot;]
The Balance Dev
Neutral Social

Passive:
Community Feedback: You will see the feedback of all abilities that target you.
Contracted: You are death immune and must use at least one of your abilities every day/night cycle starting d2.

Day:
#feedback-discuss (3 use): You will have a private chat tonight with your chosen player.
Release Patch (inf use): Make all the changes public. The rest of the players will vote if they want to keep them or not. If they vote Yes, all abilities will be updated to your suggested ones.

Night:
Rework Ability (inf use): Change an ability that targeted you into another one.
Private Test Realm (inf use): Use an ability you created on another player.

Win condition: Release a patch with at least 3 changes that the majority of players will like.
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:981, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
# Jeff Probst

*Neutral Social*
*”The Tribe Has Spoken”*
**The Tribe Has Spoken (Passive)** -If you are the hammer vote on a player, you get a vig during the twilight phase. This counts as snuffing a torch
**Digging Deep (Passive)** -Immune to redirection and occupation
**Tonight, That’s Enough (Day Ability)** -If a player is at the point where there are not enough votes to hammer them if no votes are placed or switched to them. You can snuff their torch, lynching them and ending the day (1 use)
**If anybody has a hidden immunity idol…(Night)** -Plant a hidden immunity, it is up to the hosts to decide how it is gotten. The idol functions as a standard night vest.
*Snuff 3 torches through the course of the game*
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;Neutral Support&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:988, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
## **The Seraph**

**Neutral Support**

**Watchful Protector (Passive)** : At the start of the game, you will be given the names of two players in the game. These two players are your divine disciples and they could be any classes or alignments that are ***NOT* a part of the Blue Dragon faction.**

**Transcendent (Passive)** : All of your limited use abilities can also be used while dead. In addition, you gain an additional use of each ability upon your own death.

**Purge (Day)** : Remove any negative status ailments affecting one of your divine disciples (2 uses).

**Martyr (Day)** : Sacrifice yourself to be lynched in place of a divine disciple. (1 use). Upon your death, you gain 1 use of an alternate version of this ability which will lynch an alternative target of your choosing in place of a divine disciple when a divine disciple is set to die via lynch, in exchange for losing all uses of the rest of your abilities.

**Holy Protectorate (Night)** : Prevent any visits to a divine disciple that incur any kind of negative effect on the disciple, with the visit (2 uses).

**Sacred Intervention (Night)** : Provide unstoppable death immunity to all divine disciples alive for the night (1 use).

*Win condition: Conclude the game with at least one divine disciple alive.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:1003, topic:78353&quot;]
&gt; ## Chemist
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; Neutral “Good”/Support
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; Passive - by the skin of your teeth - you are night immune the first time you are attacked* and are not otherwise protected. you *will* be told when this activates, and it can activate only once.
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; day 1 - make your [night 1’s name] night ability swap from protecting against occupy to being against redirection, or vice versa - inf
&gt; day 2 - Only for this SFoL! - give yourself night immunity tonight. you will not be told if this blocks an attack. will trigger before your passive if both are active - 2 uses****
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; night 1 - [name tbd] - target player will have ~~redirection~~ occupy immunity tonight - inf
&gt; night 2 - Scarlet Potion - Heal a player, protecting them from dying tonight, and curing any poison and bleeding they were suffering from. can only be used while your passive has not triggered*****- 3 uses :crown:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; *Survive or see the unseen/cult fail*

&gt; ## Notes:
&gt;
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; (unconvertable)
&gt; *i just mean a one-time death immunity like i think mm has. i just forget how thats worded.
&gt; ****the purpose of this ability is to give them some survivability. normally their survivability would come from scum thinking they’re an alch they can work with.
&gt; *****to go along with that, i dont want to make them too strong with town, as that would make them an easy target for scum, so i made the fake-claim heal work only before they’re found out, or for not long after. if timed right, they can use their day ability to extend the time frame for which it works
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;Neutral Offensive&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:998, topic:78353&quot;]
# Chad Valakhad

![ChadValakhad|256x256](upload://AczegJrqJw3LmBcfusXzOoFB0Am)
**Neutral Offensive**

*“The name’s Chaaaad Valakhaaaad and I know what you’re thinking. How the hell did the divines bless one man with such beauty? Well, I couldn’t tell you. But what I can do is allow you to bask in my glorious presence. Go ahead! It’s all free for you, my adoring fans.”*

**Asshole (Passive) -** All heals and protections on you from other players will fail.

**Perfume of Bewitching (Day) -** Spray copious amounts of perfume on yourself, guaranteeing that people will visit you tonight. [2 uses]

**Charm Person (Night) -** Redirect a target to yourself. [∞ uses]
**Dissonant Whispers (Night) -** Target a player, if they attack you tonight, it will fail. [1 use]
*Be visited by 5 different players over the course of the game.*
[/quote]
[/details]
[details=&quot;Neutral Killer&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:531, topic:78353&quot;]
# Arabellus

![Arabellus|256x256](upload://ppxTdju5djc0cCkSPF03n2NRREX)
**Neutral Killer**

*“It is not enough that the people must know of my vast intelligence and knowledge of the workings of the world, no… they must experience my relentless power firsthand.”*

**Dragon Scales (Passive) -** You will survive the first attack on you.

**Benign Transposition (Day) -** Switch places with a player tonight - everything targeting you that night will target them, and vice versa. If this player dies tonight, you will gain a use of **Disintegrate.** [∞ use, one day cooldown]

**Catapult (Night) -** Launch a box at a target at an incredible velocity, killing them. [∞ use]
**Disintegrate (Night) -** Turn a target to ash with a blast of force energy, killing them. This cannot be healed or prevented. [1 uses]
*Destroy all who stand against you.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:542, topic:78353, full:true&quot;]
# Kai

*Neutral Killer*
*”Anrgey noises”*
**Homosexual-(Passive)** -Immune to occupation and redirection to and from female players.
**Theatre Kid-(Passive)** -Immune to all forms of death sans the lynch
**”DONT FUCKING MASS CLAIM”** (Day Abilty)-Silently strongman dayvig a player provided they have softed or hard claimed their *ACTUAL* class or its mechanics. Provide the quote with the guess their class is for it to go off. You may use thise twice per day (Infinite use)
**”Angrey noises”** -Kill a player, it will strongman if they have claimed their class or given mechanics (provide a quote with guess of class for strongman to take effect)-(Infinite use)
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:564, topic:78353&quot;]
# The Mind Flayer :shield: :crossed_swords:

Neutral Killer
**Insanity (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night, occupation and redirection.
**Mindstorm (Passive)** - Once per night you may guess a player’s class. If you are correct you will empower your attack via **Mind Read** . You will gain a one-night buff depending on who you kill with this passive. This passive will be disabled if you guess incorrectly twice. Cannot Target the King.
**Insight (Day)** - Gain a clue to your target’s class type. You receive the same results as princess. [4 Uses]
**Mind Read (Day)** - You will see who your target visits tonight. [4 Uses]
**Brain Destruction (Night)** - Kill a player. You will be able to choose who they target tonight, bypassing redirection immunity. You may not redirect the King. [Infinite Uses]
**Whispers of Insanity (Night)** - Cause a player to commit suicide, destroying their logs and allowing you to determine what they flip as the next day. You will receive their real class and their logs. [1 Use, Cannot Target the King]
**Possible Buffs Gained:**

&gt; * Killer: Gain an addition use of Whispers of Insanity.
&gt; * Offensive: You will occupy everyone visiting you, bypassing occupy immunity.
&gt; * Support: You will heal yourself tomorrow night, curing infection and bleed.
&gt; * Social: You will be guaranteed to visit your target.
&gt; * Investigative: All uses of Insight and Mind Read will be replenished. Your visits will be hidden from Investigators.
&gt; * Special: You will appear as the class of your choice to investigators.

*Goal: Destroy both the major factions and any neutrals who may stand in your way.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:580, topic:78353&quot;]
&lt;big&gt; **Jack the Ripper** &lt;/big&gt;
**Neutral Killer**

**One With The Fog (Passive)** - You will be immune to death and will gain additional powers for every successful kill.

* 1 kill - Your visits will be hidden and will be prevented from visiting anyone that would lead to your death. You may also target 2 people with **Stalk** .
* 2 kills - You will be immune to redirection and occupation. Additionally, gain a use of an ability of your choice.
* 3 kills - You will be immune to all forms of delayed death and **Eviscerate** now bypasses immunity and healing and cleans the flip for other players. You will secretly receive their real classcard in your PM.
* 4 kills - You can no longer die at night and **Leer** also prevents your target from voting.
* 5 kills - Day abilities no longer take any uses and you will secretly have a double vote or take 1 more vote to lynch. You may switch between the double vote/loved passive at any time.
* 6+ kills - You may use 2 day abilities every day.

**Leer (Day)** - Prevent a player from using day abilities today and occupying them tonight. [3 Uses]
**Stalk (Day)** - Learn who your target(s) visit tonight. [3 Uses]
**Cutthroat Tactics (Day)** - Your target will be bled at the end of the night, killing them in 1 night if not healed. [1 Use]
**Eviscerate (Night)** - Kill your target. This will bypass all forms of protection and prevention if your target has claimed at least one ability that they have. [Infinite]
**Ambush (Night)** - You will attack all players visiting your target tonight. [1 Use]
*Win Condition: Survive to the final 3 or defeat all that would stand in your way.*
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:647, topic:78353&quot;]
# Shar Pei

**Neutral Killer**
**Chinese Fighting Dog (Passive)** - When you are attacked, you will not die but instead become Injured. Injuries can be healed, if you are attacked while you have an Injury you will die.
**Puppy Eyes (Day)** - If Target Player targets you with a day ability for the rest of the day, it will be redirected to a player of your choice. You can select your target twice. - 2 uses.
**Rabid Wolf Bite (Day)** - Dive at a player and bite them, making them bleed. If they are not healed in 2 nights, they will die. - 2 uses.
**Neck Slice (Night)** - Stab your claws into a player. Killing them. - Infinite Uses.
**Bite Marks (Night)** - Bite a player. They will become marked. If you kill a player who is marked, it will bypass death immunity.
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult, any Neutrals that dare stand in your way and any other main faction.*
[/quote]
[/details]


[details=&quot;Memesky Special&quot;]
[quote=&quot;eevee-sama, post:609, topic:78353&quot;]
# Memesky

![image|256x256](upload://dsbyzjUH3tf7LChpTYDK6XXffJl)
**Memesky Special**

**No U (Passive)** - You count as a harmful neutral for the purposes of the Blue Dragon and Unseen/Cult win conditions. Any neutral killers must make sure you are dead in order to win.
**God of the Forum (Passive)** - You will be provided a list of one shot abilities with no description at the start of the game. These do not target players, but count as actions for the purposes of limits. You are 1-shot bulletproof and will appear as Blue Dragon Investigative to investigative results. If you become Tsar, your conversion ability is kept and is no longer conditional.

**Memesky Carry (Day)** - Imitate an ability present in the class cards, then use it on a person of your choice. - 3 Uses

**Recruit (Night)** - Recruit a neutral or player from a faction with only one player remaining to match your wincon. They will lose all other abilities should they have any and will become the new Memesky should you die. This ability bypasses conversion immunity. - Infinite Uses

*Defeat all players that are not present in Memesky’s Cult.*
[/quote]
[/details]

### 2nd anniversary:
&gt; This game is part  of 2nd anniversary event.
&gt;
&gt; Participants will be awarded lottery tickets for 2nd anniversary lottery.
&gt; In case of replacements, tickets will be split betwen players up to host discretion.
&gt;
&gt; People who will design 3 best roles (most enjoyable, balanced and innovative) will receive bonus tickets. Those roles will also be considered by FoL team for adding them in the standard FoL classcards. 

## Playerlist:
1. ~~Soulshade55r~~ - [color=ligblue]The Royal Guard[/color] - Lynched D2
2. Sulit
3. Jake
4. ~~Mercenary~~ - [color=ligblue]Cartographer[/color] - Dead D3
5. Maximus
6. ~~Derps~~ - [color=ligblue]The Scribe[/color] - Dead N1
7. Jgoes
8. ~~Wazza~~ - [color=ligblue]The Insane Brawler[/color] - Dead N2
9. ~~Marshal~~ - [color=ligblue]The Astromancer[/color] - Dead D2
10. Kai
11. Luxy
12. ~~Geyde~~ - [color=red]The Trickster[/color] - Dead D2
13. ~~BlueStorm~~ -&gt; KyoDaz
14. Maxwell :ru:
15. Simon
16. ~~PKR~~ - [color=ligblue]The Alchemist[/color] - Dead N2

## Backups:
1. Magnus
2. KyoDaz
3. Solic</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 15:50:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Completed</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SirDerpsAlot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean paint technically finished</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4138">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4138</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 15:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4138</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yep</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4137">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4137</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4137</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…is this the <em>only</em> anniversary game that actually finished?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4136">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4136</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 15:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4136</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think so</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4135">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4135</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 23:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4135</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SirDerpsAlot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did they pick the classes that won or whatever</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4134">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4134</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 22:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4134</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oof. Mine was BD killer. It had low confirmability</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4133">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4133</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4133</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not all classes were guaranteed to roll.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4132">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4132</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 21:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4132</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Who got Executioner/Headhunter?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4131</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 21:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4131</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="eevee-sama" data-post="4126" data-topic="78458" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 eevee-sama:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a></p>
<p>Alchemist + Enchantress as BD Special (after rewoks)<br>
Prince as BD Special</p>
<p>Only one BD Special can roll per game.</p>
<p>Prove me wrong.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>bet</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4130</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 15:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4130</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>eevee is back</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4129</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 15:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4129</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eevee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Obviously with adjustments.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4128</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 12:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4128</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="eevee-sama" data-post="4126" data-topic="78458">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 eevee-sama:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Alchemist + Enchantress as BD Special (after rewoks)<br>
Prince as BD Special</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Alchemist and Enchantress are not as strong as the Prince.</p>
<p>You’d need to buff the other two if this was implemented imo</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4127</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 12:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4127</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eevee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a></p>
<p>Alchemist + Enchantress as BD Special (after rewoks)<br>
Prince as BD Special</p>
<p>Only one BD Special can roll per game.</p>
<p>Prove me wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4126</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 12:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4126</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s certainly workable since it’s main ability, while having upside, has equal part downside</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4125</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4125</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s how I’d implement it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4124</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4124</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And I would make it so if the heiress dies the people they invited won’t be added to the chat</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4123</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4123</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean it basically does the same thing as both alignments, you just can’t reeeally fake claim it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4122</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4122</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sulit" data-post="4119" data-topic="78458" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/sulit/40/32765_2.png" class="avatar"> sulit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How could you make it less confirmable though</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It can’t<br>
That’s what makes it a possible problem</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4121</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4121</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sulit" data-post="4118" data-topic="78458" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/sulit/40/32765_2.png" class="avatar"> sulit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Heiress was stolen from my home forum it’s a custom role we made</p>
<p>I tweaked it a bit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4120</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4120</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How could you make it less confirmable though</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4119</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4119</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Heiress was stolen from my home forum it’s a custom role we made</p>
<p>I tweaked it a bit</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4118</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4118</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Geyde" data-post="4108" data-topic="78458">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/geyde/40/32764_2.png" class="avatar"> Geyde:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Brain Destruction (Night)</strong> - Kill a player. You will be able to choose who they target tonight, bypassing redirection immunity. You may not redirect the King. [Infinite Uses]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Supposed to empower this</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4117</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4117</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually wtf thats wrong</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4116</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4116</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was under the idea that it just gives the buff to the sk shot and the class type buff</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4115</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4115</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Geyde" data-post="4108" data-topic="78458">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/geyde/40/32764_2.png" class="avatar"> Geyde:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Mindstorm (Passive)</strong> - Once per night you may guess a player’s class. If you are correct you will empower your attack via <strong>Mind Read</strong> .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mind Read is a day ability<br>
How does that affect this</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458/4114</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-78458-4114</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-sfol-00-the-alternative-universe-game-thread-cult-wins/78458.rss">[SFoL] SFoL 00: The Alternative Universe - Game Thread - Cult Wins</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
