<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155</link>
    <description>Hey all, just got this game, and loving it so far,
at least on one computer that I have in my workplace. On my personal laptop, which is effectively a potato, I can&#39;t run the game.

One thing that I&#39;ve noted, is like similar games in the genre, actually playing the game, more or less everything that is in 3-D, is completely un-needed for gameplay. Playing the game at full capacity, involves being able to read the text in the chat boxes, wills, and the interface buttons. Everything else while nice, and perhaps enhances the experience for most players, isn&#39;t actually necessary or even advantageous to see to play the game.

In theory it would seem to be plausible to make an option, or possibly even a slimmed alternate client, that doesn&#39;t bother to render the tables/rooms/models etc... Which would expand the amount of systems that could run the game (and may even be preferred by some of the more hardcore type of players who would rather have less distractions from the game itself).

Again would like to emphasize that this isn&#39;t a request to take the graphics away from any players who want them, I can see no reason why players who have graphics disabled would have any complications playing with those who do, it would simply be an option for those who can&#39;t or don&#39;t want to render the graphics.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 12:55:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Necromancy is the new trend</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 12:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah, the new necro?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 12:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…bump?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 11:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah static images would work great. To me I was thinking just solid black. but pictures would be a good compromise for those who do need something to see.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 21:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh wait, I know! Static images only. It can even be well-done art over screencaps of the game. It won’t be as exciting, but who cares?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 03:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hamsterdams]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would like this too. I think it’s a good idea.</p>
<p>My laptop can run it, but the fan is constantly on and I can tell my computer is working pretty hard for it. Granted, I have a 2015 Macbook Pro but as we all know, the gameplay is much more important than graphics.</p>
<p>I was going to return it, but I do like the game and will want to play it, so I decided to keep it. However, I’d spend a lot more time playing ToL if there was a “basic” version of the game or something similar.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would like this too, by default if everything was on, but if there was this option- because my pc is potato too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 01:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zero graphics mode</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey all, just got this game, and loving it so far,<br>
at least on one computer that I have in my workplace. On my personal laptop, which is effectively a potato, I can’t run the game.</p>
<p>One thing that I’ve noted, is like similar games in the genre, actually playing the game, more or less everything that is in 3-D, is completely un-needed for gameplay. Playing the game at full capacity, involves being able to read the text in the chat boxes, wills, and the interface buttons. Everything else while nice, and perhaps enhances the experience for most players, isn’t actually necessary or even advantageous to see to play the game.</p>
<p>In theory it would seem to be plausible to make an option, or possibly even a slimmed alternate client, that doesn’t bother to render the tables/rooms/models etc… Which would expand the amount of systems that could run the game (and may even be preferred by some of the more hardcore type of players who would rather have less distractions from the game itself).</p>
<p>Again would like to emphasize that this isn’t a request to take the graphics away from any players who want them, I can see no reason why players who have graphics disabled would have any complications playing with those who do, it would simply be an option for those who can’t or don’t want to render the graphics.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 01:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4155-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/zero-graphics-mode/4155.rss">Zero graphics mode</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
