<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Ritualist (The Shadow of the Gods)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-ritualist-the-shadow-of-the-gods/1370</link>
    <description>Lore Link: 
https://tol.wikia.com/The_Ritualist

Lore Subject: 
The Shadow of the Gods (Ritualist Lore)

Lore:
The newly trained Court Wizard had lots of tricks and magic up his sleeve...until last night. He remembers that night as the darkest night of his life when the Cult Leader approached him, and demanded the Wizard&#39;s initiation into the Cult. Now he was different, whole. Stronger. Darker. Tonight would be his first meeting with the Cult. He stepped into the room where the Cult Leader had instructed him to go, and found a table there soaking in blood and marked with ancient signs. As he sat down on the blood-soaked chair, it felt natural to him. He would get his revenge on the Blue Dragon once and for all! The Cult Leader began chanting anciently, and two more creatures appeared. He recognized the huge red one as Mithras, the god of blood, and the large bat-like winged one with one purple eye as Corax, the god of darkness. They didn&#39;t speak as the Cult Leader recited his orders, but they did speak to the new Cultist as if it were a dream cloaked in shadows. Corax said, &quot;You and our worshipper here will wipe out the Blue Dragon in the name of the gods and we shall take over Castle Adiart and enjoy it&#39;s riches for ourselves.&quot; Mithras said, &quot;Yeah. We shall kill EVERY LAST person here. Don&#39;t think you&#39;re alone, we will recruit more members. It&#39;s just a matter of time.&quot; The two gods laughed maniacally, and disappeared. He nodded to the Cult Leader, for he was the Ritualist, the shadow of the gods, and the bane of Castle Adiart!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 13:44:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-ritualist-the-shadow-of-the-gods/1370.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Ritualist (The Shadow of the Gods)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore Link:<br>
<a href="https://tol.wikia.com/The_Ritualist" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://tol.wikia.com/The_Ritualist</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject:<br>
The Shadow of the Gods (Ritualist Lore)</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
The newly trained Court Wizard had lots of tricks and magic up his sleeve…until last night. He remembers that night as the darkest night of his life when the Cult Leader approached him, and demanded the Wizard’s initiation into the Cult. Now he was different, whole. Stronger. Darker. Tonight would be his first meeting with the Cult. He stepped into the room where the Cult Leader had instructed him to go, and found a table there soaking in blood and marked with ancient signs. As he sat down on the blood-soaked chair, it felt natural to him. He would get his revenge on the Blue Dragon once and for all! The Cult Leader began chanting anciently, and two more creatures appeared. He recognized the huge red one as Mithras, the god of blood, and the large bat-like winged one with one purple eye as Corax, the god of darkness. They didn’t speak as the Cult Leader recited his orders, but they did speak to the new Cultist as if it were a dream cloaked in shadows. Corax said, “You and our worshipper here will wipe out the Blue Dragon in the name of the gods and we shall take over Castle Adiart and enjoy it’s riches for ourselves.” Mithras said, “Yeah. We shall kill EVERY LAST person here. Don’t think you’re alone, we will recruit more members. It’s just a matter of time.” The two gods laughed maniacally, and disappeared. He nodded to the Cult Leader, for he was the Ritualist, the shadow of the gods, and the bane of Castle Adiart!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-ritualist-the-shadow-of-the-gods/1370/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-ritualist-the-shadow-of-the-gods/1370/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 13:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1370-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-ritualist-the-shadow-of-the-gods/1370.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Ritualist (The Shadow of the Gods)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
