<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415</link>
    <description>**Fortune Teller** (Neutral) - A cryptic, twisted seer who manipulates the fates.

Passive:
**Reveal Fool** - If there is a Fool in the round, you will be told who they are, and will automatically gain 1 toward your kill count (See: Goal) if they are executed under any circumstances.

Day Ability:
**Death Card** - Your target will kill the person they use any night ability on that night. Target player is notified that someone has done this to them. IE: &quot;You have been given a death card! The player you use any ability on tonight will die!&quot; (4 uses.)

_^ Has 4 uses because non-evil players who don&#39;t have any information on the bad guys will likely not do anything that night. Unless they&#39;re dumb and reckless._

Night Ability 1:
**Wheel of Fortune** - Select two players. If either one visits the other for any reason, they will kill them. (4 uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**The Hanged Man** - If you correctly select the player who will be put on trial the next day, your vote to execute will count for three. Everyone will be notified &quot;A Fortune Teller has added additional votes!&quot; (Unlimited use.)

_^ It could just count as two, but I wanted to give this class some strength above the existing vote-based classes. It&#39;s a reward for correctly predicting the next day&#39;s trial._

----

Goal: Cause 3 deaths with any of your abilities, including &quot;The Hanged Man&quot;.

Comments: Please note this is NOT a Neutral Killing class. You&#39;re more like a Scorned, trying to cause people to die rather than directly killing them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 21:25:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chocolate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tormental" data-post="1" data-topic="39415">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/tormental/40/1695_2.png" class="avatar"> Tormental:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Passive:</p>
<p>Reveal Fool - If there is a Fool in the round, you will be told who they are, and will automatically gain 1 toward your kill count (See: Goal) if they are executed under any circumstances.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How about replacing it with something like this</p>
<p><strong>Reveal Darkness</strong>- If there is a Fool or a Scorned, you are told who they want to see executed (Fool or the Scorned Targets), and will gain one toward the kill count if any of these neutrals win the game.</p>
<p>and adding something like this</p>
<p><strong>Skeleton’s bait</strong>- Death immune twice only. Conversion immune.  If someone attempts to kill or convert you, You will be shown as immune and one point towards the kill count will be gained. (This can only happen once)</p>
<p>Then increasing the goal would work well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 21:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39415-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss">[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/noble1">@NOBLE1</a> - Yup, Hanged Man executions count as a kill. Thanks for the kind words, I’ve seen some things (like making two visitors kill each other) done in various ways, so I can’t claim total originality since I’m sure someone has at some point done SOMEthing similar. XD Maybe for another game, even. I dunno.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/vandalay">@Vandalay</a> - I agree that giving the Death Card to someone who previously used it will be a very very good idea/tactic. Mitigating factors would of course be your target getting blocked, having them get caught killing the previous victim, or even just not knowing who to kill next, etc. etc. They also may have limited night abilities and don’t want to spam them just to kill people.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/nuclearburrito">@NuclearBurrito</a> - I’m sure you would. XD</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/tinydeer">@TinyDeer</a> - I have to read that over a few times and consider everything.</p>
<p><em>Would it be improper to ask what the other commenters think about TinyDeer’s points? I don’t necessarily disagree with anything, yet, but again I have to consider it for a while.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 21:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39415-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss">[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TinyDeer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Very interesting suggestion. Some thoughts:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>In General</strong>, this feels like a new NK since the Fortune Teller causes so much death. I’d say we should go further with that, and set their goal death count to 4 or 5. This would help eliminate the Inquisitor issue of winning early and then just doing whatever the player feels like until the game ends, since the Fortune Teller would be dangerous for a longer period of time.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>The Hanged Man</strong> seems really, really strong. The King himself only has one additional vote with Finger, and with the readdition of the Noble/Aristocrat, there would be the potential for a TON of vote manipulation, which as BD I might find very frustrating. Put together, that’s an extra <em>three votes</em> toward who is on the stand (two players counting as five) in addition to the King’s extra vote to put the player up. Interesting and relevant prediction mechanic, though.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Death Card</strong> - this seems like the core of the class, but feels very powerful and easy to win, since, as others have said, if someone actually acts on the death card, you’d be incentivized to use it on the same player again. I fear this would run into the Sorcerer issue - for the BD, finding the Fortune Teller would be a priority, since they can’t depend on their abilities to not kill important players, which is a <em>huge</em> disadvantage.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Wheel of Fortune</strong> - An interesting ability that could cause chaos. To me, it feels natural and a good fit for the game, particularly from a Neut.</p>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 20:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39415-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss">[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gives death card to a lone MM early game<br>
( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 16:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39415-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss">[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>honestly I wouldn’t say the good BD would never use the death card… it depends if the prince is still in play, but once you remove that… it’s potential is pretty high up there… just because there’s more BD, doesn’t eliminate that usually a good portion of them can be crossed off the suspect list. If you can eliminate enough bd’s to give yourself a 50/50 shot you should usually take it.</p>
<p>That’s of course before factoring in that say if you are doing that, and your guy uses the card, you probably just need to re-use the card on him 2 more times and victory is quite likely. (IE you give it to the converted, or MM, they sure as heck are going to love it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 16:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39415-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss">[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like this class. Escpically the death card because that’s a new cool concept that no one has thought of yet. My only concern is that it might be to easy to win as him. Also does the hanged man Ability count as a kill?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 14:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39415-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss">[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Fortune Teller</strong> (Neutral) - A cryptic, twisted seer who manipulates the fates.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Reveal Fool</strong> - If there is a Fool in the round, you will be told who they are, and will automatically gain 1 toward your kill count (See: Goal) if they are executed under any circumstances.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Death Card</strong> - Your target will kill the person they use any night ability on that night. Target player is notified that someone has done this to them. IE: “You have been given a death card! The player you use any ability on tonight will die!” (4 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ Has 4 uses because non-evil players who don’t have any information on the bad guys will likely not do anything that night. Unless they’re dumb and reckless.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Wheel of Fortune</strong> - Select two players. If either one visits the other for any reason, they will kill them. (4 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>The Hanged Man</strong> - If you correctly select the player who will be put on trial the next day, your vote to execute will count for three. Everyone will be notified “A Fortune Teller has added additional votes!” (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p><em>^ It could just count as two, but I wanted to give this class some strength above the existing vote-based classes. It’s a reward for correctly predicting the next day’s trial.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Goal: Cause 3 deaths with any of your abilities, including “The Hanged Man”.</p>
<p>Comments: Please note this is NOT a Neutral Killing class. You’re more like a Scorned, trying to cause people to die rather than directly killing them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 07:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39415-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-fortune-teller-neutral/39415.rss">[Class Suggestion] Fortune Teller (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
