<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Doppelgänger (NK)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518</link>
    <description>&gt; # [color = &quot;silver&quot;] The Doppelgänger [/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Killer [/color]** 
**Sadism (Passive)** - The Doppelgänger is immune to occupation, target changing, and has self-healing for the first two nights. The Doppelgänger gains an additional three nights of self-healing for every Blue Dragon-aligned player executed during the day.
**Trollbox (Day)** - 	Choose a target player and Whisper a short phrase into the troll box. It will appear as if that player said it. - Infinite uses 
**Scapegoat (Day)** - If the player is voted to be executed in the day, including the Doppelgänger, then they will swap their position with another chosen player. The King cannot be the target. - 1 use 
**Impersonate (Night)** - Takes the form of one player and kills another one. Any investigative results a player will have on the Doppelgänger will instead reflect on the player they impersonated. If the impersonated target has Royal Blood, then the Doppelgänger shall also have Royal Blood for the next day. If the Doppelgänger attacks a player who is being followed, then the feedback will show the impersonated player being the visitor. The impersonated player will be framed for the night and Will o’ Wisp will only show the target attacked if used on the impersonated player. - Infinite uses 
**Crushing Guilt (Night)** - If a Blue Dragon-aligned player was executed the previous day, then the Doppelgänger can select two players who’ve voted to execute and cause them to commit suicide by guilt, bypassing healing, night immunity, and not counting as visits. - Infinite uses 
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*

Theme: A neutral killer with a focus on framing and mislynches.
Survivability: Self-heal against poisoning/bleed and in the event they get attacked by a Knight/Bearing hunter then they can still survive providing Sadism is active.
Late-game: Can survive the late-game via Scapegoat then finalizing with Crushing Guilt.



Posting my NKs by Firekitten&#39;s requests.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:07:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Doppelgänger (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Does he really need Crushing Guilt on top of Impersonate and Scapegoat?  Other than that, I really like this class.  Actually all of your suggestions seem to introduce some very original concepts (at least, original to me)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70518-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Doppelgänger (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Doppelgänger (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>stupid firekitten</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70518-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Doppelgänger (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Doppelgänger (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="silver"> The Doppelgänger </font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Sadism (Passive)</strong> - The Doppelgänger is immune to occupation, target changing, and has self-healing for the first two nights. The Doppelgänger gains an additional three nights of self-healing for every Blue Dragon-aligned player executed during the day.<br>
<strong>Trollbox (Day)</strong> - 	Choose a target player and Whisper a short phrase into the troll box. It will appear as if that player said it. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Scapegoat (Day)</strong> - If the player is voted to be executed in the day, including the Doppelgänger, then they will swap their position with another chosen player. The King cannot be the target. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Impersonate (Night)</strong> - Takes the form of one player and kills another one. Any investigative results a player will have on the Doppelgänger will instead reflect on the player they impersonated. If the impersonated target has Royal Blood, then the Doppelgänger shall also have Royal Blood for the next day. If the Doppelgänger attacks a player who is being followed, then the feedback will show the impersonated player being the visitor. The impersonated player will be framed for the night and Will o’ Wisp will only show the target attacked if used on the impersonated player. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Crushing Guilt (Night)</strong> - If a Blue Dragon-aligned player was executed the previous day, then the Doppelgänger can select two players who’ve voted to execute and cause them to commit suicide by guilt, bypassing healing, night immunity, and not counting as visits. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Theme: A neutral killer with a focus on framing and mislynches.<br>
Survivability: Self-heal against poisoning/bleed and in the event they get attacked by a Knight/Bearing hunter then they can still survive providing Sadism is active.<br>
Late-game: Can survive the late-game via Scapegoat then finalizing with Crushing Guilt.</p>
<p>Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70518-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-doppelganger-nk/70518.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Doppelgänger (NK)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
