<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051</link>
    <description>_For the longest of times I&#39;ve been pondering on a way to preserve the King&#39;s leading position but remove his omnicient investigative ability. I think I&#39;ve found a solution however its quite controversial._ 

**King rework suggestion:**

**Removal of his Allies ability:** The King shouldnt be some kind of omnicient detective he has an entire court to do that for him. Besides that it gets neutrals easily spotted and executed as creating an alibi is near impossible. 

**Combine Royal Finger with Decide Fate:** Its a common annoyance to me. A certain faction managed to gain a slight voting majority. You use Royal Finger to work around this and still put an enemy up the stand. However now you cannot use your Decide Fate, the accused gets pardoned and you get hanged. With this merger of the two abilities you now get to have both the 2 votes onto someone and you can decide their fate. The amount of uses is still 1x per King however. 

**Move Imprison  from the Prince to the King but allow only 1 execute:** This is where the controversy begins, I can already hear you think &#39;&#39;But what if the King is Evil?!&#39;&#39;. Before I get to that however I&#39;d like to point out a few key features of this suggestion. 

This would make it more attractive for both factions to make a play for the King role. Right now the King position for the evil faction is just about an extra vote. There is too little incentive for them to go after the King to try and gain a position of power. 

Second of all the King would still have his leading role. He gets to investigate and question those he imprisoned with the benefit of a potential execution. It would also make it extra tense because if he is evil high value Blue Dragon members may have to lie to avoid the headsmans axe. However the king no longer has an omnicient ability to just know who is who. 

The Execute itself cannot be used until night 3 just like it is now. This is in line with the end of the Loyalty passive the King has. This way the court can hang the king immediately after a wrong execution if they so desire.

Finally the King is less likely to just die night 1 like some Princes seem to do these days. People know who the king is and knights and healers can start defending him from the moment they get into the game. 

**The Imprison Day Ability can be used along side the new Royal Finger Ability:** You dont have to choose you can use both on the same day. 

**Removal of the Guards! ability:** The King gains some incredible power with my suggestion, Royal Finger combined with Decide Fate, Imprison with a 1x execute. Without guards however he is becomes a target for other forces to try and take him out. Knights and healers have their work cut out for them, protect the King or the Council?

**Let the Butler&#39;s Nightshade ability kill the King in one night instead of two:** When you succesfully identify an evil King, poison him but then allow him to rule 2 more days (if not healed) isnt very rewarding. Since the King would be able to imprison people it&#39;d be prudent to make it so he dies in 1 night if not healed. 

**Removal of the Neutral King at start:** As there have been a few topics floating around I&#39;d support the idea of removing the neutral King at the start and replacing it with a 50/50 chance of Blue Dragon or Evil King spawn. 
Non-neutral killers stepping up can still become a neutral king as is now. 

**Implement the Reaper/Possessor King:** A neutral King that maintains its original killing ability and goal of removing everyone in their path. There is other great suggestions on this like the Psychopathic King. 


**The Prince Rework (The Leader of the Blue Dragon):** 

_By now you are probably appalled by the idea of being Blue Dragon while the King is Evil with the ability to both use Royal Finger, Decide Fate, Imprison and Execute someone for good measure. How would you stand a chance? Well this is where my Prince rework comes in._ 

**Prince changes from Killer class to Special.**
**Unique**
**Guaranteed**
**Conversion Immune**
**Blue Dragon.**

**Passives:** 

**Diligent:** You will stop at nothing to accomplish your goal, you are occupy immune. 
**The Illusive Prince:** Nobody can visit you Night 1 and 2. They will be prevented. 

**Day abilities:** 

**Royal Pardon:** Pardon someone from the stand immediately, they cannot be voted back up the rest of the day. Cannot be used if the King uses his new Royal Finger/Decide Fate. Cannot be used on self. (2x uses) 

**Night abilities:** 

**Order execution:** You decide to kill someone. This bypasses night immunity, cannot be occupied, redirected or prevented otherwise. You can no longer use this if you execute a Blue Dragon with it. 
Cannot be used until night 3. Cannot be used on the King. (3x Uses)

**Persuasion:** The target of your choice is conversion immune this night. (Infinite uses) 

**Strategy:**

My suggested Prince is the true leader of the Blue Dragon and extremely powerful to counter a potential Evil King (which now occurs 50% of the time). His order execution ability is the same as his current execute however he no longer has to imprison the target first. With persuasion he can ensure a high priority target cannot be converted. Royal Pardon is extremely powerful and can prevent the Blue Dragon from making a major mistake. Due to the Prince&#39;s passive the Blue Dragon will have their leader at least 3 nights.. which means there is always sufficient time to launch one ordered execution. The downside is however that deduction for the Prince is much more reliant on teamplay and coordination since he lost his ability to jail. 


_I realize this is quite the wall of text but if you made it this far I&#39;d love to know what you think._
_All constructive criticism and feedback is encouraged and appreciated._</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 13:13:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>as far as i know its intentional that you cant use both decide fate and royal finger in one day</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 13:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27051-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051.rss">Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spotshooter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think prince change isn’t good because it remove his ability to talk and get claim at night. It’s important for blue dragon to be able to trust someone and work together. If this change is implemented, blue dragon must talk openly during day(evil then will see everything) or use psychic which doesn’t guarantee to spawn.<br>
Also king change, blue dragon still won’t have a way to remove king without butler(which don’t guarantee to spawn).<br>
Voting king waste a day which is very valuable late game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 11:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27051-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051.rss">Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like some of your ideas here, but the radically Prince change is not for me personally.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 10:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27051-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051.rss">Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cleanfear]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>For the longest of times I’ve been pondering on a way to preserve the King’s leading position but remove his omnicient investigative ability. I think I’ve found a solution however its quite controversial.</em></p>
<p><strong>King rework suggestion:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Removal of his Allies ability:</strong> The King shouldnt be some kind of omnicient detective he has an entire court to do that for him. Besides that it gets neutrals easily spotted and executed as creating an alibi is near impossible.</p>
<p><strong>Combine Royal Finger with Decide Fate:</strong> Its a common annoyance to me. A certain faction managed to gain a slight voting majority. You use Royal Finger to work around this and still put an enemy up the stand. However now you cannot use your Decide Fate, the accused gets pardoned and you get hanged. With this merger of the two abilities you now get to have both the 2 votes onto someone and you can decide their fate. The amount of uses is still 1x per King however.</p>
<p><strong>Move Imprison  from the Prince to the King but allow only 1 execute:</strong> This is where the controversy begins, I can already hear you think ‘‘But what if the King is Evil?!’’. Before I get to that however I’d like to point out a few key features of this suggestion.</p>
<p>This would make it more attractive for both factions to make a play for the King role. Right now the King position for the evil faction is just about an extra vote. There is too little incentive for them to go after the King to try and gain a position of power.</p>
<p>Second of all the King would still have his leading role. He gets to investigate and question those he imprisoned with the benefit of a potential execution. It would also make it extra tense because if he is evil high value Blue Dragon members may have to lie to avoid the headsmans axe. However the king no longer has an omnicient ability to just know who is who.</p>
<p>The Execute itself cannot be used until night 3 just like it is now. This is in line with the end of the Loyalty passive the King has. This way the court can hang the king immediately after a wrong execution if they so desire.</p>
<p>Finally the King is less likely to just die night 1 like some Princes seem to do these days. People know who the king is and knights and healers can start defending him from the moment they get into the game.</p>
<p><strong>The Imprison Day Ability can be used along side the new Royal Finger Ability:</strong> You dont have to choose you can use both on the same day.</p>
<p><strong>Removal of the Guards! ability:</strong> The King gains some incredible power with my suggestion, Royal Finger combined with Decide Fate, Imprison with a 1x execute. Without guards however he is becomes a target for other forces to try and take him out. Knights and healers have their work cut out for them, protect the King or the Council?</p>
<p><strong>Let the Butler’s Nightshade ability kill the King in one night instead of two:</strong> When you succesfully identify an evil King, poison him but then allow him to rule 2 more days (if not healed) isnt very rewarding. Since the King would be able to imprison people it’d be prudent to make it so he dies in 1 night if not healed.</p>
<p><strong>Removal of the Neutral King at start:</strong> As there have been a few topics floating around I’d support the idea of removing the neutral King at the start and replacing it with a 50/50 chance of Blue Dragon or Evil King spawn.<br>
Non-neutral killers stepping up can still become a neutral king as is now.</p>
<p><strong>Implement the Reaper/Possessor King:</strong> A neutral King that maintains its original killing ability and goal of removing everyone in their path. There is other great suggestions on this like the Psychopathic King.</p>
<p><strong>The Prince Rework (The Leader of the Blue Dragon):</strong></p>
<p><em>By now you are probably appalled by the idea of being Blue Dragon while the King is Evil with the ability to both use Royal Finger, Decide Fate, Imprison and Execute someone for good measure. How would you stand a chance? Well this is where my Prince rework comes in.</em></p>
<p><strong>Prince changes from Killer class to Special.</strong><br>
<strong>Unique</strong><br>
<strong>Guaranteed</strong><br>
<strong>Conversion Immune</strong><br>
<strong>Blue Dragon.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Diligent:</strong> You will stop at nothing to accomplish your goal, you are occupy immune.<br>
<strong>The Illusive Prince:</strong> Nobody can visit you Night 1 and 2. They will be prevented.</p>
<p><strong>Day abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Royal Pardon:</strong> Pardon someone from the stand immediately, they cannot be voted back up the rest of the day. Cannot be used if the King uses his new Royal Finger/Decide Fate. Cannot be used on self. (2x uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Order execution:</strong> You decide to kill someone. This bypasses night immunity, cannot be occupied, redirected or prevented otherwise. You can no longer use this if you execute a Blue Dragon with it.<br>
Cannot be used until night 3. Cannot be used on the King. (3x Uses)</p>
<p><strong>Persuasion:</strong> The target of your choice is conversion immune this night. (Infinite uses)</p>
<p><strong>Strategy:</strong></p>
<p>My suggested Prince is the true leader of the Blue Dragon and extremely powerful to counter a potential Evil King (which now occurs 50% of the time). His order execution ability is the same as his current execute however he no longer has to imprison the target first. With persuasion he can ensure a high priority target cannot be converted. Royal Pardon is extremely powerful and can prevent the Blue Dragon from making a major mistake. Due to the Prince’s passive the Blue Dragon will have their leader at least 3 nights… which means there is always sufficient time to launch one ordered execution. The downside is however that deduction for the Prince is much more reliant on teamplay and coordination since he lost his ability to jail.</p>
<p><em>I realize this is quite the wall of text but if you made it this far I’d love to know what you think.</em><br>
<em>All constructive criticism and feedback is encouraged and appreciated.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27051-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/controversial-king-prince-rework-class-suggestion-must-read/27051.rss">Controversial King &amp; Prince rework [Class Suggestion] [Must read!]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
