<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003</link>
    <description># Class Cards for SFOL Echoes

All classes are in sections below.

Warning: There are some spoilers.

[details=&quot;Kings&quot;]

[quote]

![Rudolf|256x255](upload://o5uJ1HErYHqu8wP9trLSPt4jVgI.png) 

# [color=green]**Emperor Rudolf**[/color]
[color=green]Deliverance Special[/color]

Ruler of the Rigelian Empire, Stalwart Conquerer, there is little you have not done during your reign to increase the might of your people. Though you lead a kingdom of iron-willed men, your priority was, is, and always will be towards your only son, Albein Alm Rudolf. You may pretend to wear a façade on your seat, but your heart and hope is still with that of the Deliverance, so that they may rise up and become the heroes that the prophecy demands. 



**Inheritance (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, [color=green]**Alm**[/color] has the priority on becoming King.
**Maker of Prophecy (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two. If you target a member of the Deliverance at night, from that point on you will be added to the Deliverance Members’ chat if not already in it.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose another player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Royal Might (Night)** - Choose a player and make them appear NS to all checks. Your target will have a 10% increased chance of a successful day attack. - oo uses
_Your objective is to subdue the Rigelian Army and the Mad Lord Duma._
[/quote]

[quote]

![Desaix|255x233](upload://hY1vMkCj75DNxNMY9CsinYLMpdZ.png) 

# [color=brown]**Chancellor Desaix**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Special[/color]

Former chancellor of the Zofian Kingdom, you traded away your soul and honor to the Rigelian Empire in exchange for absolute ruin. You and your second-in-command, Slayde, joined the ranks of the Rigelian army when the Deliverance so badly humiliated both of you. There is no hesitation in seeking revenge.

**Dynastic Fall (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, all [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] will lose their Nobility status for the next election.
**Valentian Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose another player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Blackmail (Night)** - Choose a player. They will be conversion immune until you choose another player with this ability. - oo uses 
_Your objective is to crush the Deliverance alongside the Mad Lord Duma._
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=green]**Saint King Alm**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Special[/color]
(From [color=green]Alm[/color])

**The True Heir (Passive)** - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, all [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] will lose their Nobility status for the next election, and the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] chooses who will become the next [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**The Saint King (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two, and you will continue to be in the chat of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color], but will not add to their member cap.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Falchion (Night)** - Choose any two players. They will be immune to death tonight. If you target [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color], he will instead be killed, bypassing all immunities, occupation, redirection and visit prevention. - 4 uses
**Valentia’s Hero (Night)** - Choose a player and convert them to the [color=green]Deliverance[/color].  - oo uses
_Your objective is to subdue the Rigelian Army and the Mad Lord Duma._
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=gray]**King Lima**[/color]
[color=gray]Neutral Special[/color]
(From [color=gray]Brigand[/color])

**Lavish (Passive)** - If anyone visits you, you use up an extra use of the night ability being used that night. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. 
**Valentian Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose any player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 4 uses
**Hide (Night)** - Prevent all visits to you tonight. - 2 uses
_Your objective is to survive no matter the costs._
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=gray]**Acolyte Jedah**[/color] :fire: 
[color=gray]Neutral Special[/color]
(From [color=gray]Jedah[/color])

**Devoted Acolyte (Passive)** - You share a direct chat with the [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color]. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. 
**Valentian Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two.
**Royal Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Guard! (Night)** - Choose any player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses
**Offer Soul (Night)** - Guarantee that [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma&#39;s**[/color] actions are successful tonight. - 2 uses
Your objective is to ensure that Mad Lord Duma destroys the world.
[/quote]

[quote]

![NK%20Duma|245x256](upload://nWFuJ2MKK19j6xE57ess9nmlY41.png) 

# **D[color=red]U[/color]M[color=blue]A[/color] [color=brown]A[/color][color=gray]W[/color]A[color=red]K[/color][color=gold]E[/color]N[color=gray]E[/color][color=orange]D[/color]** :fire:
[color=gray]Neutral Special[/color]

With the sealing of Mila, you have risen up as the dark god, cast away your old physical body, and become the embodiment of chaos. Your mission is now only one: destroy the world.

**God Status (Passive)** - You are immune to death, bleeding, occupation, and redirection. You are able to use both day abilities and night abilities in the same phase.
**Destroyed Throne (Passive)** - Your vote counts as two. When there are no members of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] left, your vote will count as six. If you are lynched, there will be no more Kings except for [color=green]**Saint King Alm**[/color].
**Divine Pardon (Day)** - Make another player unable to be voted today.  - 2 uses
**Decide Fate (Day)** - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use
**Upheaval (Night)** - All players except you will gain the wrong feedback from their results, if they would get any, and be randomly redirected to any player except you. - oo uses
**Ocular Beam (Night)** - Kill 2 players. - oo uses
_Your objective is to ensure that you destroy the world._
[/quote]

[/details]

[details=&quot;Rigelians&quot;]

[details=&quot;Unique Classes&quot;]

[quote]

![Berkut|250x250](upload://A8DOHO3Pcn3C9uzUGZxZTiPZsun.png) 

# [color=brown]**Berkut**[/color] :shield: :crown: :crossed_swords: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Special[/color]

Nephew to King Rudolf, you were the heir to the throne of Rigel. You spent your life being the pinnacle of Rigelian model, showing off your confidence in waves to the people, but your inner mind was plagued with thoughts of doubt and insecurity as you tried to please your uncle. A staunch believer of the caste system, you looked down upon the peasant who lead the Deliverance, until it was revealed that Alm was not peasant but the son of Emperor Rudolf, meaning heir to the throne, and your only cousin. You grew up with such faith that the throne was yours, but now you will not tolerate anyone who dares to challenge you, even family. 

**Phantasm (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. Immune to any attacks from [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color] as long as Starting [color=green]**King Rudolf**[/color] is alive. 
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Lock and Order (Day)** - Choose a player and lock them up in the dungeon. You and your prisoner can send a single 1000 character message to one another over the course of the night. - oo uses.
**Kriemhild (Night)** - Exact justice upon your prisoner and kill them, bypassing all immunities. If you kill a Rigelian, you will lose the rest of your uses. If you kill [color=brown]**Fernand**[/color] or [color=brown]**Rinea**[/color], you will die alongside them. - 2 uses
**Cease Thy March (Night)** - Default the [color=brown]Rigelian&#39;s[/color] weapon choice to match that of the [color=green]Deliverance&#39;s[/color] tomorrow, regardless of the vote. - 1 use

[/quote]

[quote]

![Slayde|256x256](upload://mvAGk8QgGYtJOSXnVUBkDj9wN7T.png) 

# [color=brown]**Slayde**[/color] :shield: :crown: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Killer[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Sir Mycen[/color]

Second in command to Chancellor Desaix, you are part of his inner circle. Acting in accordance with the chancellor to stage a coup, and kill those of the royal family. After a failed defense of the Zofian Capital, you have joined the Rigelian army seeking vengeance for what the Deliverance has done. 

**Vengeful Turncoat (Passive)** - When you are lynched, you will occupy all of your accusers that night.
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Coup (Day)** - Place a mark of death on the King for the next two nights that causes any visit to the King to kill him, bypassing all immunities. If the King turns out to be [color=brown]**Chancellor Desaix**[/color], you will be killed for treason the following night. - 1 use
**Quick Assault (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 2 use
**Elite Vanguard (Night)** - Summon your elite fighters to protect you, granting you death immunity for the night. You will kill any attackers bypassing immunity. - 3 uses
**Garrison (Night)** - Grant a player death immunity. They gain 10% accuracy for all Day Attacks tomorrow.  - 2 use
[/quote]

[quote]

![Nuibaba|218x256](upload://cm6wC5HKhuvbR559kiLw31gVYy.png) 

# [color=brown]**Nuibaba**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Social[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Delthea[/color]

A witch in high leadership of a cult, the Duma Faithful, you are in a strategic position at the Rigelian court. While Emperor Rudolf is out of your control, you still try to manipulate the young Prince Berkut, heir to the throne. Although you will help out the Rigelians in their time of need, your loyalty is first to Duma, second to Jedah, and third to those pesky warmongers.

**Mental Link (Passive)** - All players hypnotized by you will be added to your private neighborhood. You will be able to talk at night. If converted, your neighborhood will not change.
**Hypnotize (Day)** - Bring a player’s mind under your control at the start of tonight. - oo uses 
**Arcane Power (Day)** - Remove cooldown from Mire. - 2 uses
**Mire (Night)** - Remove a player from your control at the end of the night. They will lose all protections from Day Attacks tomorrow if they have any. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]

[quote]

![Fernand|256x256](upload://tx7uKAfJb8dEeOzFJLEcGHnGbld.png) 

# [color=brown]**Fernand**[/color] :shield: :crown: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]

Once the deputy of the Deliverance, and Clive&#39;s best friend, you turned your back on the Deliverance and its idealistic dreams when Clive appointed Alm to the leadership of the army. Unforgiving of peasants after your family was slaughtered by a whole pack of them, you refused to submit to the boy from Ram and joined Berkut&#39;s calling of honor and upholding of the caste system. And due to your knowledge of the Deliverance and its members, you are valuable to the Rigelian cause. More than you give yourself credit.

**Trusted Commander (Passive)** - When jailed by [color=brown]**Berkut**[/color], he will know that you are [color=brown]**Fernand**[/color]. Gain 1 use of all limited abilities each time the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] win a battle using Axes.
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Traitor’s Sight (Night)** - Check a player. Determine if they are part of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. - oo uses
**Bane of Deliverance (Night)** - Choose two players. Protect them from conversion to the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. If both players are not Nobility, this is ineffective. Cannot be used Night 1 and does not count as visiting.  - 1 use
[/quote]

[quote]

![Rinea|256x256](upload://tuwt8t9B52QnD7gn4cKcGO1HQaT.png) 

# [color=brown]**Rinea**[/color] :shield: :fire: :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Social[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Tatiana[/color]

A reserved, Rigelian noble and fiancée of Berkut, you desired only his love but  never had any ambition to take the throne as your own. You may disagree with your betrothed on the views of war and the caste system, but you still love Berkut more than enough to follow him to the ends of the world.

**Empathetic Noble (Passive)** - You will be able to communicate with fallen soldiers at night. If you are visited by any member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color], you will be converted and not count towards the member cap. 
**By His Side (Passive)** - You cannot step up to be King, as your only wish is to spend your days at [color=brown]**Berkut&#39;s**[/color] side.
**Message of Mercy (Day)** - Send a private message to a player anonymously. They may not reply back. - 2 uses
**Resurrection (Night)** - Bring a dead player back to life. - 1 use
[/quote] 

[/details]

[details=&quot;Common Classes&quot;]

[quote]

![Paladin|226x256](upload://8NevegpuAVxxPs6EmXO0aOJASbz.png) 

# [color=brown]**Paladin**[/color] :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Ezekiel[/color]

A veteran cavalier, you are the vanguard and pride of the Rigelian army. Your mounts are quick, and your lances are sharp. At the head of every battalion, your battlecry brings morale to your troops. And until the Emperor himself tells you to lay down your arms, you will continue to lead the charge and fight for the glory of Rigel.

**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Commander’s Presence (Day)** - Your vote during today&#39;s battle will secretly count as 2 when totaling the end result. - 2 uses
**Bolster (Day)** - Choose a player. Their Day Attacks will be 20% more accurate today. - 1 uses
**Triad Check (Night)** - Choose two weapons, designating one as the fake and real choice of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. If both match the choices of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color], you will be notified. If matched, gain 1 use of Bolster. - oo uses
**Veteran Lancer (Night)** - For tomorrow&#39;s battle, if the [color=brown]Rigelian&#39;s[/color] weapon is Lances, you will win the battle even if you tie. - 2 uses

[/quote]

[quote]

![Baron|505x479](upload://nmeC88jtislc8JqQPfXRi2RxFTO.png) 

# [color=brown]**Baron**[/color] :crown: 
[color=brown]Rigelian Killer[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Lukas[/color]

You are the wall. The best line of defense. Your immense shields and body armor are the reason Rigel stands today, and will continue to stand for eternity. And every Deliverance soldier that rushes at you will find themselves against an immovable object.

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Ridersbane (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Mounted** passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them. 
**Javelin Toss (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance of killing them. Increases by 5% if the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] win a battle today using Lances. - 2 uses
**Defend (Night)** - Watch over a player, and sacrifice your life to kill their attackers. Bypasses death immunity. - oo uses
**Heavy Armor (Night)** - Choose a player. You will redirect any attacks from them, bypassing redirection immunity, and gain death immunity tonight. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Cavalier|154x256](upload://h27oWaQmTf0OBvOwCyd6qLT7aCA.png) 

# [color=brown]**Cavalier**[/color] :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Mathilda[/color]

Though you may be new and unskilled, your quick mounts justify you as a worthy scout of Rigel. You travel through day and night, to search for the enemies of the empire and obliterate them. At least, that&#39;s your goal.

**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Expedition (Night)** - Choose a player. Determine if that player is the same alignment as the previous player you checked. [color=gray]Neutrals[/color] and [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] will be considered NS. - oo uses
**Interrogate (Night)** - Choose a player. Determine the most recent night they have been  visited by a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Arcanist|245x256](upload://aUhEE1vPVyBHday6nYo93EJvTgl.png) 

# [color=brown]**Arcanist**[/color] :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Kliff[/color]

Members of the Duma Faithful, you align yourself with the Rigelians to get rid of the boy of the prophecy, Alm. Though the empire may see you as an ally, your first goal is to only see all enemies of the all-powerful lord Duma. And to know where they&#39;re headed.

**Dark Aura (Passive)** - If you are lynched, your accuser and hammerer will be occupied the following night, bypassing immunities. 
**Faint Wisp (Night)** -  Choose a player and light their path. You will see who they visit first tonight. - oo uses
**Ghastly Eyes (Night)** -  Choose a player and watch their surroundings. You will discover who visits them. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Sky_Knight|167x237](upload://zK3MctzGLzCev3xXHL8vmd6abYl.png) 

# [color=brown]**Sky Knight**[/color] :crown:
[color=brown]Rigelian Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Clair[/color]

No walls or citadels have enough height to stop your search. And though you could just as easily hurl javelins down onto the soldiers below, you and your pegasus are trained to find the nobles of Rigel and Zofia, the ones who believe in the old caste system, and to recruit them to your aid, against the Deliverance.

**Airborne (Passive)** - You bypass visit prevention and all players who target you with Day Attacks have 10% less chance to hit. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] used Bows during today&#39;s battle, this passive is disabled until the next day.
**Blue Bloods (Night)** - Determine if a player is of Valentian Nobility. - oo uses 
**Aerial Spy (Night)** - Choose a player and discover their faction. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Mercenary|181x247](upload://mH36gAVsJu792WY9cvN9olFcaCA.png) 

# [color=brown]**Mercenary**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Offensive[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Gray[/color]

The hired sword of Rigel, you don&#39;t care about morals and righteous acts; as long as you get paid, you&#39;re fine. And with a little bit of money, you&#39;re more than willing to knock some foes out for more time than they want to be.

**Swordsmanship (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] win a battle with Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.
**Subdue (Day)** - Disable a player&#39;s immunities tonight. - 3 use
**Parry (Night)** - Occupy a player. - oo use
**Sweeping Blow (Night)** - Choose a player and occupy all players who visit them. - 2 use
[/quote]

[quote]

![Myrmidon|167x254](upload://4Au3gSgGyvuYHpR1bUdxUZPbO6j.png) 

# [color=brown]**Myrmidon**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Offensive[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Python[/color]

Elite swordsmen of the Rigelian Empire, you are adept with all types of swords. Small blades, longswords, and even knives. And aided by the threat of your sharp edges, none of the lower ranks in the army would dare disobey your orders. They go only where you tell them to go.

**Swordsmanship (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] win a battle with Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.
**Crosswise Cut (Day)** - Attack 2 players. You will have a 10% chance to individually kill them. - 2 use
**Enforce (Night)** - Choose a player and redirect them to a target. - oo use
**Harsh Battlecry (Night)** - Choose a player. You will make all of their day attacks miss tomorrow. - 2 use
[/quote]

[quote]

![Mage|147x229](upload://ixuzL4mvAYHVfoKYYsrho7YjETV.png) 

# [color=brown]**Mage**[/color] :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Luthier[/color]

Rigel&#39;s army, though it may be filled with iron-willed and hardened soldiers, also has room for those gifted with magical powers. Spellcasters who wield powerful fire magic, shocking lightning magic, and unstable wind magic, are most desired among all soldiers to make the enemy&#39;s day even more worse. And you have plenty up your sleeve for the Deliverance to take.

**Firewall (Day)** - Prevent all visits to a player tonight. You may not target them tomorrow. - 2 use 
**Empower (Night)** - Choose a player and guarantee their night ability is successful and bypasses immunities and protections. - oo uses
**Excalibur (Night)** - Choose two players and swap their positions. Bypasses redirection immunity. - 3 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Cleric|123x233](upload://jEL4WQHIjiwVCEx8m6jCk27aA6x.png) 

# [color=brown]**Cleric**[/color] :fire:
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Silque[/color]

Advocates of pacifism, you desire no war nor bloodshed on any country&#39;s soil. However, forced into servitude of Rigel by the fall of your goddess, Mila, you find that it may be easier to deal with the suffering if you can save as many lives as possible on the battlefield.

**Warp (Day)** - Teleport a player and bring them to you today. For the rest of today, any day attacks and abilities that target them will be ineffective, but they will die alongside you if you die to a day attack. - 3 uses
**Recover (Night)** - Choose a player and heal their wounds. - oo uses
**Physic (Night)** - Choose a player and heal their wounds, bypassing visit prevention. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Archer|247x256](upload://pVk67GhSWo8eHFqG0BxkYkEv3vc.png) 

# [color=brown]**Archer**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Killer[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Tobin[/color]

Armed to the brim with arrows and your trusty bow, you are the long arm of the Rigelian Empire. There&#39;s no need to lose your lives in hasty close combat when you could shoot them from far away. And you will bring this war to an end faster than it would without you. Provided you&#39;re not shot, of course.

**Anti-Air (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Airborne** passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them. 
**Loose Barrage (Passive)** - If you kill a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] with your attacks, you will be unable to use any abilities the following day.
**Snipe (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a -10% chance to hit them with 0 uses. Each use you have on Snipe increases your chances of hitting your target by 20%. Expends all uses after a successful hit. - 0 uses
**Curved Shot (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 0 uses
**Precision Firing (Night)** - Gain 1 use of a Day Ability of your choice. - oo uses
**Warding Arrow (Night)** - You will gain 10% accuracy for any day attack tomorrow that targets a magic user. - 3 uses

[/quote]

[quote]

![Soldier|226x256](upload://aQdcTpYPyQi40d2QvIEOlbW5Gmv.png) 

# [color=brown]**Soldier**[/color]
[color=brown]Rigelian Support[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Forsyth[/color]

The newest recruits of the Rigelian army, you came from poor villages to earn some gold for your family back home. You may be inexperienced, but with each battle, your strength will only continue to grow.

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Promote (Night)** - Choose a dead non-Unique [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] class and gain its passives and abilities. You will not gain Nobility status from becoming a class that does have it. - oo uses
**Shieldbearer (Night)** - Choose another player and make them and you immune to death tonight. - 1 use

[/quote]

[/details]

[/details]


[details=&quot;Deliverance&quot;]

[quote]

![Clive|250x250](upload://1zN4vRfqMoUqIl1gUuULaAxyhhL.png) 

# [color=green]**Clive**[/color] :shield: :crown: :crossed_swords:
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

Captain of the Knights of Zofia and the founder of the Deliverance, you put loyalty and honor above all else to defend your country and your people. Put under immense stress, you worry every day for the lives of your soldiers and your friends. And you become more anxious in knowing your sister, Clair, and your fiancée, Mathilda, also joins you on the battlefield every day. But you sent Lukas out to bring a hero to the Deliverance, and you have faith in Alm that he will be that hero.

**Iron-Clad (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you. Any day attack targeting you will have 10% less chance of killing you. 
**Ridersbane (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Mounted** passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them. 
**Hit and Run (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 30% chance of killing them. - oo uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Sharpened Lance (Night)** - Attack a player. - oo uses
**Lunge (Night)** - Attack a player, bypassing death immunity. Swaps all targeting actions between you and the player you&#39;re attacking except for you. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Alm|256x256](upload://4ObiDMIfzvoxnKBmKyKGYuSCNnx.png) 

# [color=green]**Alm**[/color] :shield: :crown: :crossed_swords:
[color=green]Deliverance Special[/color]

The bearer of the brand, and the prophesied hero, you were born the Crown Prince of Rigel but knew no home other than the small village of Ram, under the care of the former Zofian General, Sir Mycen. Accepting Lukas&#39; invitation, and setting out from Ram with most of your childhood friends, you hold a heart for those who suffer, and you will continue to persevere through the fight in the toughest of times. You know that there are many who hate you, and seek to kill you, but you still have hope that maybe they&#39;ll see justice, and come to terms with the truth, that all humans are equal and can stand together. And maybe someday, the love of your life, Celica, can also see the same way as you do.

**Hero&#39;s Brand (Passive)** - Immune to death at night, occupation, and redirection. Cannot die to any attacks from Duma even if they bypass immunity while there is a living [color=green]**King Rudolf**[/color].
**Rigel&#39;s Heir (Passive)** - If Starting [color=green]**Alm**[/color], you will appear as a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] to all checks on you and the day after a [color=green]**King Rudolf**[/color] dies at night, you will have the priority ascension to the throne. All day attacks targetting you will have 20% less accuracy. 
**Commandeering (Day)** - If [color=green]**Clive**[/color] is dead, choose another [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member. They will become [color=green]**Clive**[/color] at the start of tonight. - 2 use (Shared)
**True Sacrifice (Day)** - Your conversion will bypass conversion protection and **Hero&#39;s Brand** will be disabled tonight. - 1 use (Shared)
**Recall to Light (Night)** - Choose a player. You will convert them to the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
**Double Lion (Night)** - For tomorrow&#39;s battle, if the [color=green]Deliverance&#39;s[/color] weapon is Swords, you will win the battle even if you tie. - 3 uses (Shared)

[/quote]

[quote]

![Sir%20Mycen|256x256](upload://gxjJim0j4SId2E1oVY0ROhP5azc.png) 

# [color=green]**Sir Mycen**[/color] :shield: :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

Former general of Zofia, you lost your job when the manipulation of Chancellor Desaix sent you far away from the Zofian court, to the tiny village of Ram. But even there, you continued to be Emperor Rudolf&#39;s support and friend, accepting his request to raise his own son to be the hero of Valentia. Though you have aged, you still haven&#39;t lost your skill with lance or sword, and is the guardian for your adopted child, Alm, even on the battlefield.

**Military Hero (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you. If [color=green]**Alm**[/color] uses **Commandeering** on you, they will not lose a use of its ability.
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Veteran Knight (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance of killing them. - 2 uses
**Hero of Yore (Night)** - Prevent all visits to a [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member. The first time you successfully block a visit, gain 1 use of **Piercing Blow**. - 3 uses
**Piercing Blow (Night)** - Kill a player. Bypasses healing. - 0 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Gray|256x256](upload://47UFiJw7stf7D3vb5EB33Bb9pJM.png) 

# [color=green]**Gray**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Offensive[/color]

One of Alm&#39;s childhood friends from Ram, you were the most eager to set out on this journey with him, setting your life and sword on the line so that you can stay with your friends. You&#39;re quite flirtatious as well, although your skill with a sword speaks more than your tongue. And you don&#39;t set out on things alone, the least you could do was convince your best friend, Tobin, to come along with you.

**Swordsmanship (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] wins a battle using Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.
**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Subdue (Day)** - Disable a player&#39;s immunities tonight. - 3 uses
**Sunder (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. Increases by 10% if you voted Swords in today&#39;s battle. - 3 uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Parry (Night)** - Occupy a player. - oo use
**Windsweep (Night)** - Occupy a player and all players who visit them. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Tobin|250x250](upload://fa9bYbgAUivydsaYZGW38eZwLA4.png) 

# [color=green]**Tobin**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

One of Alm&#39;s childhood friends from Ram, you agreed to join him and Gray on this journey in exchange for coin so that your family could eat during the hard times brought on by the war. Though you lack strength, your skill with a bow and strategic mindset has done much to aid your friends on the journey. However, you won&#39;t give a moment&#39;s hesitation if the opportunity to get something... shiny... comes up.

**Anti-Air (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Airborne** passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them. 
**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Snipe (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a -10% chance to hit them with 0 uses. Each use you have on Snipe increases your chances of hitting your target by 20%. Expends all uses after a successful hit. - 1 use
**Curved Shot (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 2 uses
**Precision Firing (Night)** - Gain 1 use of a Day Ability of your choice. - oo uses
**Ranged Charge (Night)** - Allow for the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] to choose Bows in tomorrow&#39;s battle. - 3 uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]

[quote]

![Kliff|250x250](upload://kFwDWhWJycDpHi5Rhuooc3jxa5a.png) 

# [color=green]**Kliff**[/color] :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Investigative[/color]

One of Alm&#39;s childhood friends from Ram, you eventually agreed to Alm, Gray, and Tobin&#39;s requests to journey with them to the Deliverance so that you could fulfill your dream of seeing the world. Out of all of your friends, you are a gifted mage with raw arcane power. You may seem sharp and prickly, but your friends don&#39;t underestimate your skill on the battlefield, as well as reconnaissance.

**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Sagittae (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance to kill them. If they are Magical, you will lose 25% accuracy. If they have the **Armored** passive, you will gain 25% accuracy. Disables the **Armored** passive&#39;s effect when targeting a player with it. - 2 uses
**Sense Aura (Day)** - Choose a player and determine if they are Magical at the start of tonight. - 3 uses
**Bright Wisp (Night)** - Choose a player and see who they visit and who visits them. - oo uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Faye|250x250](upload://jOuWf2Xd2ZDHgn9a9A5HMGhrdZR.png) 

# [color=green]**Faye**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

One of Alm&#39;s childhood friends from Ram, you had a major crush on him when you were young, and have grown up with it too, although your love for him gives you strength to let him go and instead fight with him at his side. You have a caring personality, although Kliff and Gray continue to mention that you are also very obsessive when it comes to anything involving Alm. You still try your best to let Alm go, as he asked of you.

**Ram&#39;s Banner (Passive)** - When you replace [color=green]**Alm**[/color], refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming [color=green]**Alm**[/color].
**Unwavering Love (Passive)** - You will not count towards the member cap of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] and can use both day abilities in the same day.
**Anew (Day)** - Choose a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. They are able to use one Day Attack twice today, and will only count as using it once. - 2 uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Rescue (Day)** - Choose a player and prevent all visits to them tonight. They will be targeted by any non-Investigative abilities that target you as well tonight. - 3 uses
**Bright Wisp (Night)** - Choose a player and see who they visit and who visits them. - oo uses
**Imbue (Night)** - Choose a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] and guarantee their action is successful tonight, bypassing immunities and protections. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Lukas|256x256](upload://n8uIasnWpyamy5db9BVzMA4Cfxh.png) 

# [color=green]**Lukas**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Killer[/color]

The backwater noble of the Deliverance, you serve as Clive&#39;s cold and calculating tactician. Although you do your best to help those in need, and be sympathetic to those who ask of your help, you can&#39;t let emotions get in the way of being the best that the Deliverance has to offer. You served Clive well before, and you&#39;re more than ready to give Alm all the assistance he needs to lead the Deliverance.

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Ridersbane (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Mounted** passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them. 
**Javelin Toss (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance of killing them. Increases by 5% if the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] won a battle with Lances. - 2 uses
**Zofian Shield (Night)** - Prevent all visits to a player.  - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
**Rallying Cry (Night)** - Choose a [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member and guarantee their action is successful tonight, bypassing all protections and immunities. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Silque|250x250](upload://c2Wgtr5qpfuirnsgVRRjwVYLDWZ.png) 

# [color=green]**Silque**[/color] :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

A cleric from a monastery in Novis, you came to the aid of Alm at the request of his love, Celica, although sidetracked by brigands along the way. Reserved and pious, you heal the wounds of the broken and revitalize the spirit of the Deliverance, using the way of the goddess Mila.

**Invoke (Day)** - Summon soldiers to protect the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. The first successful day attack targeted at any member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] will not kill them. - 3 uses
**Recover (Night)** - Heal a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. Their day attacks will gain 10% accuracy tomorrow. - oo uses
**Nosferatu (Night)** - Choose a player and a class. If that player dies tonight or tomorrow during a Day Attack, they will be revealed as the class you chose. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Clair|250x250](upload://A1CaSUlrcDUytulLwa0IB0vvAEb.png) 

# [color=green]**Clair**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Investigative[/color]

The energetic and headstrong younger sister of Clive, you saw yourself in total admiration of your brother since you were kids. He is everything you want to find in a man for your future, someone good with words, strong, kind, gifted in music, and well versed in poetry and literature. You even followed him to the Deliverance and joined as a Sky Knight. However, you know that it&#39;s near impossible to find anyone who can come close to the likes of Clive, and that it&#39;s hard to resist the flirting from Gray and Tobin for too long. 

**Airborne (Passive)** - You bypass visit prevention and all players who target you with Day Attacks have 10% less chance to hit. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] used Bows during today&#39;s battle, this passive is disabled until the next day.
**Expose (Day)** - At the start of tonight, discover who [color=brown]**Berkut**[/color] has in his jail. - 2 uses
**Blue Bloods (Night)** - Choose two players and determine whether each are Valentian Nobility. - oo uses 
**Winged Guard (Night)** - Make all members of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] appear as [color=brown]Rigelians[/color] tonight. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Forsyth|250x250](upload://blT4EuiAqdgksnPuVIGNbi8qKMV.png) 

# [color=green]**Forsyth**[/color] 
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

Born as a scholar, you came from a small town with your best friend Python to enlist in the Deliverance. Although Python continued to discourage you, you persevered and rose through the ranks, eventually becoming Clive&#39;s second-in-command. You are the example of meritocracy and evidence that hard work does yield results. 

**Armored (Passive)** - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Lieutenant by Merit (Passive)** - If [color=green]**Alm**[/color] uses Commandeering on you, they will not lose a use of its ability. You will keep this passive even after you change classes from being [color=green]**Forsyth**[/color] or a [color=brown]**Soldier**[/color].
**Promote (Night)** - Choose a dead non-Unique [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] or [color=green]Deliverance[/color] class and gain its passives and abilities tonight. You will become the convert form if you choose a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] class. You will not gain Nobility status from becoming a class that does have it. - oo uses
**Shieldbearer (Night)** - Choose another player and make them and you immune to death tonight. - 2 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Python|250x250](upload://1GR0aNRnpXxkX8unYsnEBmPZtsq.png) 

# [color=green]**Python**[/color]
[color=green]Deliverance Offensive[/color]

You were dragged into the mess that Forsyth calls the Deliverance, as you were just too eager to escape your small town and the harsh overseer, Dunderhead. Skeptical of the nobility, you put up an edgy façade to deal with uninviting conversation. However, as much as your laziness shows to your best friend, your skill with archery shows just as much, too. 

**Anti-Air (Passive)** - If targeting a player with the **Airborne** passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them. 
**Stubborn (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. Each time someone tries to occupy or redirect you unsuccessfully, gain 1 use of any limited ability. 
**Double Shot (Day)** - Attack 2 players. You will have a 20% chance to individually kill them. - 2 use
**Hunter&#39;s Volley (Day)** - Force a player to use their top night ability tonight, if they have uses left. - 1 use
**Notched Threat (Night)** - Choose a player and redirect them to a target. - oo use
**Smoke Arrow (Night)** - Choose a player. You will make all of their day attacks miss tomorrow. - 3 use
[/quote]

[quote]

![Mathilda|250x250](upload://cTJCc4v3zsp6G9PpFtt2LDUDCSV.png) 

# [color=green]**Mathilda**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Investigative[/color]

Once a legend for young boys, you went from a beauty of martial skill on the battlefield to the sole affection of your fiancée, Clive. As he founded and continued to lead the Deliverance until Alm&#39;s ascendance, you were his constant support and foundation throughout his hard times. And although Clive is the man in the relationship, everyone, even Clive himself, knows that you are the stronger force to be wagered with.

**The Betrothed (Passive)** - If [color=green]**Alm**[/color] uses Commandeering on you, they will not lose a use of its ability.
**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Pinpoint (Night)** - Discover a player&#39;s exact class if they are a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color]. - oo uses
**Warding Guard (Night)** - Choose a player and determine if they are Magical. - 3 uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Luthier|250x250](upload://qXL1l8vigxfzAcpru9YLlZ1UgrW.png) 

# [color=green]**Luthier**[/color] :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

A mage from a Zofian village, you asked Alm for help in saving your sister, Delthea, from the influence of the Duma Faithful. As a humble yet anti-social person, you try your best to make friends, although the only person you&#39;ve ever been comfortable talking to is your sister. Your spells are powerful, and the Deliverance would be lacking without your efforts. 

**Firewall (Day)** - Prevent all non-[color=green]Deliverance[/color] visits to a player tonight.  - 2 use 
**Thunder (Night)** - Stun a player. They will get incorrect feedback from their abilities tonight. - oo uses
**Excalibur (Night)** - Choose two players and swap their positions. Bypasses redirection immunity. - oo uses
[/quote]

[quote]

![Delthea|250x250](upload://5b2izlsAFv522763VyxUwj7yyVI.png) 

# [color=green]**Delthea**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=green]Deliverance Social[/color]

You hold more energy and potent magic aura than anyone could ever give you credit for. And that&#39;s why the Duma Faithful took you and put you under their influence as a mindless puppet to kill the Deliverance, until Alm saved you and reunited you with your brother, Luthier. You are the antithesis to your brother. You are the social bunny of the army, but never cease bragging about yourself or your powerful magic. Luthier tells you to not wave your power around too much though.

**Mental Link (Passive)** - All players stunned by you will be added to your private neighborhood. You will be able to talk at night. Your neighborhood will not change if you are converted.
**Aura (Day)** - Stun a player, bringing them under your control at the start of tonight. - oo uses 
**Hasten (Day)** - Remove cooldown from Ragnarok. - 2 uses
**Ragnarok (Night)** - Remove a player from your control at the end of the night. If they are not a [color=green]Deliverance[/color] member, all Day Attacks targeting them will be 30% more accurate tomorrow. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]

[quote]

![Tatiana|250x250](upload://jkyZrXJSe4xO1AVw5aMowlhF1Fx.png) 

# [color=green]**Tatiana**[/color] :shield: :fire: :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Social[/color]

A Rigelian Saint, you came to love the man you once found washed ashore on the beaches of Rigel. Although the whole land is about strength and power, you know that there&#39;s something more to life than just domination and war. And when the Deliverance saved you from Nuibaba&#39;s prison, you committed your staff to their cause, as well as your fiancée&#39;s lance. Zeke would have done the same thing in your position.

**By His Side (Passive)** - You cannot step up to be King, as your only wish is to spend your days at [color=green]**Ezekiel&#39;s**[/color] side.
**Saintful Words (Passive)** - While you are alive, dead members of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] may talk directly in the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] chat. You will not count towards the member cap.
**Outcry of Rebellion (Day)** - Send a private message to a player anonymously. They may not reply back. - 2 uses
**Mind Warp (Night)** - Make any player gain incorrect feedback from their abilities tonight. - oo uses
**Revival (Night)** - Bring a dead member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] back to life as their first [color=green]Deliverance[/color] class. If [color=green]**Starting Alm**[/color] or [color=green]**Starting Clive**[/color] is revived, the player holding their position will revert to their previous class. - 1 use
[/quote]

[quote]

![Ezekiel|256x256](upload://4tPDoRyDJa4ISZWu3z96ZanlCaz.png) 

# [color=green]**Ezekiel**[/color] :crown:
[color=green]Deliverance Support[/color]

Although you once had another name, you are known in Rigel as Ezekiel, and Zeke to your fiancée, Tatiana. Your lance is the extension of Emperor Rudolf&#39;s hand, and just as he puts his trust in his son Alm, you have done the same, and joined the Deliverance with Tatiana. Although a powerful military commander, you are sensitive and empathetic to the people of Rigel and Zofia.

**Mounted (Passive)** - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.
**Commander’s Presence (Day)** - Your vote during today&#39;s battle will secretly count as 2 when totaling the end result. - 2 uses
**Gradivus (Day)** - Attack a player. You have a 15% chance to kill them. If the [color=green]Deliverance[/color] chose Lances the previous night, gain 20% accuracy. - 3 uses (1-Day Cooldown)
**Lancer&#39;s Poise (Night)** - For tomorrow’s battle, if the [color=green]Deliverance’s[/color] weapon is Lances, you will win the battle even if you tie. Overrides Veteran Lancer. - 2 uses 
**Rallying Cry (Night)** - Choose a member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. All of their Day Attacks will gain 20% accuracy tomorrow. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)
[/quote]


[/details]

[details=&quot;Neutrals&quot;]

[quote]

![Lover%20Faye|250x250](upload://kZPHGXrsM6m8V5bzHP0R7pEvjAi.png) 

# [color=gray]**Lover Faye**[/color] :shield:
[color=gray]Neutral Investigative[/color]
Converts to [color=green]Faye[/color]

One of Alm&#39;s childhood friends from Ram, you are the most worried about this war. All of the boys seem ready to be up in arms for Zofia, but all you can think about is keeping Alm safe, and away from the fighting. Alm did ask you to try to let go of him a little, for your benefit, but it will take a lot of persuasion and time for that to happen.

**Lovestruck (Passive)** - Once you visit [color=green]**Alm**[/color], you will know their identity. If you visit 2 members in the same turn, or are visited/tried to be killed by any member of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color], you will be converted and not count towards the member cap. If you become King, you will become Emperor Rudolf. 
**Whisper (Day)** - Send a single 1000 character message to a player. They cannot send a message back. - 1 use
**Stalking Eyes (Night)** - Watch over two players. You will know who they visit and who visited them. - oo uses
**Love&#39;s Sacrifice (Night)** - Guard a player. If they would die from any cause, prevent their death, and you canot use this again. Stays on the player until moved to someone else. - oo uses
_Your objective is to ensure that your love, Starting Alm, survives the destruction of the world or that you join the Deliverance and gain its objective._
[/quote]

[quote]

![Jedah|233x256](upload://kCTLS5pOVdAfY4iGx5jQtzTQha.png) 

# [color=gray]**Jedah**[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=gray]Neutral Offensive[/color]

You are the high priest of the Duma Faithful. The mastermind behind the doomsday of Valentia, your goal is to awaken your lord Duma and bring upon the destruction of the world. You sent your witch, Nuibaba, to deal with the Rigelian court, as you wait for the demise of the Deliverance and the doom of the second prophesied one, Celica.

**Duma’s Servant (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection. If [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color] targets you, they will be prevented from visiting instead.
**Rigel&#39;s Conjuring (Day)** - Choose a player, you will make them appear a member of the Deliverance tonight. If you target Mad Lord Duma, you will know their identity. - oo uses
**Telepathy (Day)** - Choose a player. You may send a single 1000 character message to that player, and they may send one back as well. - 2 uses
**Incarnation (Night)** - Choose two players. You will swap their positions tonight. Bypasses redirection immunity. - 2 uses
**Hand of Duma (Night)** - Choose one of your targets. Force them to target another player of your choice. - 3 uses
_Your objective is to see at least 3 Rigelians and 1 Deliverance lynched or to ensure that Mad Lord Duma destroys the world._
[/quote]

[quote]

![Brigand_1|241x256](upload://1MzBfNrSPBcSt5HHA7vvdMvA948.png) 

# [color=gray]**Brigand**[/color]
[color=gray]Neutral Support[/color]

Thanks to the war between Zofia and Rigel, power has been vacuumed out from the local countryside, and mischievous individuals have risen up to secure power and wealth from the sudden loss of authority. That is you. A brigand. You are no more than obstacles to the Deliverance, yet you fight against them due to your greed for more wealth and more power. In the end though, all you want is to live a good life.

**Plunderer (Passive)** - Each time either side votes for Axes in a battle, you will gain 1 use of your choice ability.
**Wanted! (Passive)** - If you are lynched or killed, the player who accused or killed you will gain death immunity that night and be healed that night. Your killer/accuser will also be conversion immune that night if a [color=brown]Rigelian[/color] or reset 1 cooldown for any member of the faction if part of the [color=green]Deliverance[/color]. 
**Reap the Spoils (Night)** - Heal any player, including yourself. - 2 uses
**Trusty Axe (Night)** - Kill a player. - 0 use
_Your objective is to survive no matter the cost._
[/quote]

[quote]

![Duma|482x500](upload://45NrfE4bQiCGwX8XRXEzGBk2hcc.png) 

# [color=gray]**Mad Lord Duma**[/color] :shield: :crossed_swords: :fire:
[color=gray]Neutral Killer[/color]

The brother of Mila, a 1000 years ago, you and Mila split the continent of Valentia in two like some sibling territorial struggle. Mila raised the people of Zofia with riches and plentitude, while you hammered the humans of Rigel into hard and iron-willed soldiers. But due to time, your sanity has completely vanished, and now all you await is the day when you can bring about the end of the world. 

**The Power of Madness (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection when there is no King. You are immune to death at night and will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.
**Spread Darkness (Day)** - You will be able to choose two targets tonight. Only able to be used after Starting [color=green]**Alm**[/color] is dead.  - 2 uses
**Discard Soul (Day)** - Your attacks will bypass death immunity tonight. - 2 uses
**Ocular Beam (Night)** - Attack a player. - oo uses
**Mad Wrath (Night)** - Attack a player and occupy them. - 3 use
_Your objective is to destroy the world and those who are not your servants._
[/quote]

[/details]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 18:04:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lightsin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
<p>I think what Ici says is tomorrow<br>
But what he means never</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 18:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>where’s this real review</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 17:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll add Celica’s group after the first one coming up</p>
<p>it was hard enough coming up with 34 ish custom classes and add pictures and flavor text</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>also because the Rigelian flag is brown and gray while the Zofian flag, aka Deliverance, is green and white</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>haha funny review of the setup: 0/10 no valbar bad pls delet<br>
real review: it looks super detaield so I’ll do it tommorow.png</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>okay that’s in the actual game</p>
<p>but still it’s from his support convos with Forsyth</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it dosen’t matter Livi<br>
you’re neglecting the point that he’s a sniper who can’t hit anything for shit</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just used color=brown</p>
<p>and he has innate skill</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>also <a class="mention" href="/u/livicus">@Livicus</a>  what’s the hex code for the Rigelian red because I’m stealing it to use for the wovles in every future game I make</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Livicus" data-post="1" data-topic="72003">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/livicus/40/9286_2.png" class="avatar"> Livicus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>skill with archery</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>skill?<br>
what skill?</p>
<p><em>PYTHONDOESN’THAVEANYFUCKINGSKILL</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>because the Deliverance are the good guys in Fire Emblem Echoes<br>
so even though  they’re the wolves they deserve green</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why is town brown-red and why is scums green? Pretty misleading</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No random posting on this thread please.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 07:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Class Cards for SFOL Echoes</h1>
<p>All classes are in sections below.</p>
<p>Warning: There are some spoilers.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Kings</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a8d335446bd5b60e807fbd5280fa46b92e94abb8.jpg" alt="Rudolf" data-base62-sha1="o5uJ1HErYHqu8wP9trLSPt4jVgI" width="256" height="255"></p>
<h1><font color="green"><strong>Emperor Rudolf</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Special</font></p>
<p>Ruler of the Rigelian Empire, Stalwart Conquerer, there is little you have not done during your reign to increase the might of your people. Though you lead a kingdom of iron-willed men, your priority was, is, and always will be towards your only son, Albein Alm Rudolf. You may pretend to wear a façade on your seat, but your heart and hope is still with that of the Deliverance, so that they may rise up and become the heroes that the prophecy demands.</p>
<p><strong>Inheritance (Passive)</strong> - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font> has the priority on becoming King.<br>
<strong>Maker of Prophecy (Passive)</strong> - Your vote counts as two. If you target a member of the Deliverance at night, from that point on you will be added to the Deliverance Members’ chat if not already in it.<br>
<strong>Royal Pardon (Day)</strong> - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Guard! (Night)</strong> - Choose another player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Royal Might (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and make them appear NS to all checks. Your target will have a 10% increased chance of a successful day attack. - oo uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to subdue the Rigelian Army and the Mad Lord Duma.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7dedf5fa30d24837b92a863e5f4354b19ee67d77.png" alt="Desaix" data-base62-sha1="hY1vMkCj75DNxNMY9CsinYLMpdZ" width="255" height="233"></p>
<h1><font color="brown"><strong>Chancellor Desaix</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Special</font></p>
<p>Former chancellor of the Zofian Kingdom, you traded away your soul and honor to the Rigelian Empire in exchange for absolute ruin. You and your second-in-command, Slayde, joined the ranks of the Rigelian army when the Deliverance so badly humiliated both of you. There is no hesitation in seeking revenge.</p>
<p><strong>Dynastic Fall (Passive)</strong> - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, all <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> will lose their Nobility status for the next election.<br>
<strong>Valentian Throne (Passive)</strong> - Your vote counts as two.<br>
<strong>Royal Pardon (Day)</strong> - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Guard! (Night)</strong> - Choose another player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Blackmail (Night)</strong> - Choose a player. They will be conversion immune until you choose another player with this ability. - oo uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to crush the Deliverance alongside the Mad Lord Duma.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="green"><strong>Saint King Alm</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Special</font><br>
(From <font color="green">Alm</font>)</p>
<p><strong>The True Heir (Passive)</strong> - If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King. If you are lynched, all <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> will lose their Nobility status for the next election, and the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> chooses who will become the next <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>The Saint King (Passive)</strong> - Your vote counts as two, and you will continue to be in the chat of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>, but will not add to their member cap.<br>
<strong>Royal Pardon (Day)</strong> - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Falchion (Night)</strong> - Choose any two players. They will be immune to death tonight. If you target <font color="gray"><strong>Mad Lord Duma</strong></font>, he will instead be killed, bypassing all immunities, occupation, redirection and visit prevention. - 4 uses<br>
<strong>Valentia’s Hero (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and convert them to the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>.  - oo uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to subdue the Rigelian Army and the Mad Lord Duma.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="gray"><strong>King Lima</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="gray">Neutral Special</font><br>
(From <font color="gray">Brigand</font>)</p>
<p><strong>Lavish (Passive)</strong> - If anyone visits you, you use up an extra use of the night ability being used that night. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King.<br>
<strong>Valentian Throne (Passive)</strong> - Your vote counts as two.<br>
<strong>Royal Pardon (Day)</strong> - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Guard! (Night)</strong> - Choose any player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 4 uses<br>
<strong>Hide (Night)</strong> - Prevent all visits to you tonight. - 2 uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to survive no matter the costs.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="gray"><strong>Acolyte Jedah</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="gray">Neutral Special</font><br>
(From <font color="gray">Jedah</font>)</p>
<p><strong>Devoted Acolyte (Passive)</strong> - You share a direct chat with the <font color="gray"><strong>Mad Lord Duma</strong></font>. If you die, there will be a vote held to crown the next King.<br>
<strong>Valentian Throne (Passive)</strong> - Your vote counts as two.<br>
<strong>Royal Pardon (Day)</strong> - Make another player unable to be voted today. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Guard! (Night)</strong> - Choose any player. They will be immune to death tonight. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Offer Soul (Night)</strong> - Guarantee that <font color="gray"><strong>Mad Lord Duma’s</strong></font> actions are successful tonight. - 2 uses<br>
Your objective is to ensure that Mad Lord Duma destroys the world.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a7d3ca3eb8ffb21cb8bb8f93b2c8fc29cca95701.png" alt="NK%20Duma" data-base62-sha1="nWFuJ2MKK19j6xE57ess9nmlY41" width="245" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<strong>D<font color="red">U</font>M<font color="blue">A</font> <font color="brown">A</font><font color="gray">W</font>A<font color="red">K</font><font color="gold">E</font>N<font color="gray">E</font><font color="orange">D</font></strong> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="gray">Neutral Special</font></p>
<p>With the sealing of Mila, you have risen up as the dark god, cast away your old physical body, and become the embodiment of chaos. Your mission is now only one: destroy the world.</p>
<p><strong>God Status (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to death, bleeding, occupation, and redirection. You are able to use both day abilities and night abilities in the same phase.<br>
<strong>Destroyed Throne (Passive)</strong> - Your vote counts as two. When there are no members of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> left, your vote will count as six. If you are lynched, there will be no more Kings except for <font color="green"><strong>Saint King Alm</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>Divine Pardon (Day)</strong> - Make another player unable to be voted today.  - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - You may choose the whether the player on trial will be executed or pardoned. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Upheaval (Night)</strong> - All players except you will gain the wrong feedback from their results, if they would get any, and be randomly redirected to any player except you. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Ocular Beam (Night)</strong> - Kill 2 players. - oo uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to ensure that you destroy the world.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Rigelians</summary>
<details>
<summary>
Unique Classes</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fd485aa2a08ba79e0affe68be0dd56bd81f0a013.jpg" alt="Berkut" data-base62-sha1="A8DOHO3Pcn3C9uzUGZxZTiPZsun" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Berkut</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crossed_swords.png?v=9" title=":crossed_swords:" class="emoji" alt=":crossed_swords:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Special</font></p>
<p>Nephew to King Rudolf, you were the heir to the throne of Rigel. You spent your life being the pinnacle of Rigelian model, showing off your confidence in waves to the people, but your inner mind was plagued with thoughts of doubt and insecurity as you tried to please your uncle. A staunch believer of the caste system, you looked down upon the peasant who lead the Deliverance, until it was revealed that Alm was not peasant but the son of Emperor Rudolf, meaning heir to the throne, and your only cousin. You grew up with such faith that the throne was yours, but now you will not tolerate anyone who dares to challenge you, even family.</p>
<p><strong>Phantasm (Passive)</strong> - Immune to occupation and redirection. Immune to any attacks from <font color="gray"><strong>Mad Lord Duma</strong></font> as long as Starting <font color="green"><strong>King Rudolf</strong></font> is alive.<br>
<strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Lock and Order (Day)</strong> - Choose a player and lock them up in the dungeon. You and your prisoner can send a single 1000 character message to one another over the course of the night. - oo uses.<br>
<strong>Kriemhild (Night)</strong> - Exact justice upon your prisoner and kill them, bypassing all immunities. If you kill a Rigelian, you will lose the rest of your uses. If you kill <font color="brown"><strong>Fernand</strong></font> or <font color="brown"><strong>Rinea</strong></font>, you will die alongside them. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Cease Thy March (Night)</strong> - Default the <font color="brown">Rigelian’s</font> weapon choice to match that of the <font color="green">Deliverance’s</font> tomorrow, regardless of the vote. - 1 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9dc2092aa30f10533a4963a1d738c7cf7e42339d.png" alt="Slayde" data-base62-sha1="mvAGk8QgGYtJOSXnVUBkDj9wN7T" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Slayde</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Killer</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Sir Mycen</font></p>
<p>Second in command to Chancellor Desaix, you are part of his inner circle. Acting in accordance with the chancellor to stage a coup, and kill those of the royal family. After a failed defense of the Zofian Capital, you have joined the Rigelian army seeking vengeance for what the Deliverance has done.</p>
<p><strong>Vengeful Turncoat (Passive)</strong> - When you are lynched, you will occupy all of your accusers that night.<br>
<strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Coup (Day)</strong> - Place a mark of death on the King for the next two nights that causes any visit to the King to kill him, bypassing all immunities. If the King turns out to be <font color="brown"><strong>Chancellor Desaix</strong></font>, you will be killed for treason the following night. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Quick Assault (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 2 use<br>
<strong>Elite Vanguard (Night)</strong> - Summon your elite fighters to protect you, granting you death immunity for the night. You will kill any attackers bypassing immunity. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Garrison (Night)</strong> - Grant a player death immunity. They gain 10% accuracy for all Day Attacks tomorrow.  - 2 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/0/016593b8654712dba40dca14aa0d335d0102a03e.png" alt="Nuibaba" data-base62-sha1="cm6wC5HKhuvbR559kiLw31gVYy" width="218" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Nuibaba</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Social</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Delthea</font></p>
<p>A witch in high leadership of a cult, the Duma Faithful, you are in a strategic position at the Rigelian court. While Emperor Rudolf is out of your control, you still try to manipulate the young Prince Berkut, heir to the throne. Although you will help out the Rigelians in their time of need, your loyalty is first to Duma, second to Jedah, and third to those pesky warmongers.</p>
<p><strong>Mental Link (Passive)</strong> - All players hypnotized by you will be added to your private neighborhood. You will be able to talk at night. If converted, your neighborhood will not change.<br>
<strong>Hypnotize (Day)</strong> - Bring a player’s mind under your control at the start of tonight. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Arcane Power (Day)</strong> - Remove cooldown from Mire. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Mire (Night)</strong> - Remove a player from your control at the end of the night. They will lose all protections from Day Attacks tomorrow if they have any. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/c/cefd81e448cadf251e91784196db1c08b432518f.png" alt="Fernand" data-base62-sha1="tx7uKAfJb8dEeOzFJLEcGHnGbld" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Fernand</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Investigative</font></p>
<p>Once the deputy of the Deliverance, and Clive’s best friend, you turned your back on the Deliverance and its idealistic dreams when Clive appointed Alm to the leadership of the army. Unforgiving of peasants after your family was slaughtered by a whole pack of them, you refused to submit to the boy from Ram and joined Berkut’s calling of honor and upholding of the caste system. And due to your knowledge of the Deliverance and its members, you are valuable to the Rigelian cause. More than you give yourself credit.</p>
<p><strong>Trusted Commander (Passive)</strong> - When jailed by <font color="brown"><strong>Berkut</strong></font>, he will know that you are <font color="brown"><strong>Fernand</strong></font>. Gain 1 use of all limited abilities each time the <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> win a battle using Axes.<br>
<strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Traitor’s Sight (Night)</strong> - Check a player. Determine if they are part of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Bane of Deliverance (Night)</strong> - Choose two players. Protect them from conversion to the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. If both players are not Nobility, this is ineffective. Cannot be used Night 1 and does not count as visiting.  - 1 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/c/ceb25959fb65a805723ab6087ee7e9d81d51fb6b.png" alt="Rinea" data-base62-sha1="tuwt8t9B52QnD7gn4cKcGO1HQaT" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Rinea</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Social</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Tatiana</font></p>
<p>A reserved, Rigelian noble and fiancée of Berkut, you desired only his love but  never had any ambition to take the throne as your own. You may disagree with your betrothed on the views of war and the caste system, but you still love Berkut more than enough to follow him to the ends of the world.</p>
<p><strong>Empathetic Noble (Passive)</strong> - You will be able to communicate with fallen soldiers at night. If you are visited by any member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>, you will be converted and not count towards the member cap.<br>
<strong>By His Side (Passive)</strong> - You cannot step up to be King, as your only wish is to spend your days at <font color="brown"><strong>Berkut’s</strong></font> side.<br>
<strong>Message of Mercy (Day)</strong> - Send a private message to a player anonymously. They may not reply back. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Resurrection (Night)</strong> - Bring a dead player back to life. - 1 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Common Classes</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3da22333de4733fc03f712d5b7ea2b38bed9eb95.jpg" alt="Paladin" data-base62-sha1="8NevegpuAVxxPs6EmXO0aOJASbz" width="226" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Paladin</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Support</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Ezekiel</font></p>
<p>A veteran cavalier, you are the vanguard and pride of the Rigelian army. Your mounts are quick, and your lances are sharp. At the head of every battalion, your battlecry brings morale to your troops. And until the Emperor himself tells you to lay down your arms, you will continue to lead the charge and fight for the glory of Rigel.</p>
<p><strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Commander’s Presence (Day)</strong> - Your vote during today’s battle will secretly count as 2 when totaling the end result. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Bolster (Day)</strong> - Choose a player. Their Day Attacks will be 20% more accurate today. - 1 uses<br>
<strong>Triad Check (Night)</strong> - Choose two weapons, designating one as the fake and real choice of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. If both match the choices of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>, you will be notified. If matched, gain 1 use of Bolster. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Veteran Lancer (Night)</strong> - For tomorrow’s battle, if the <font color="brown">Rigelian’s</font> weapon is Lances, you will win the battle even if you tie. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a3b57715748b8d4e47b4a388f2a5a4f7aa6a3d30.png" alt="Baron" data-base62-sha1="nmeC88jtislc8JqQPfXRi2RxFTO" width="505" height="479"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Baron</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Killer</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Lukas</font></p>
<p>You are the wall. The best line of defense. Your immense shields and body armor are the reason Rigel stands today, and will continue to stand for eternity. And every Deliverance soldier that rushes at you will find themselves against an immovable object.</p>
<p><strong>Armored (Passive)</strong> - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.<br>
<strong>Ridersbane (Passive)</strong> - If targeting a player with the <strong>Mounted</strong> passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them.<br>
<strong>Javelin Toss (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance of killing them. Increases by 5% if the <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> win a battle today using Lances. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Defend (Night)</strong> - Watch over a player, and sacrifice your life to kill their attackers. Bypasses death immunity. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Heavy Armor (Night)</strong> - Choose a player. You will redirect any attacks from them, bypassing redirection immunity, and gain death immunity tonight. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/7/776249fd013e15aaad4fde4b0b1f82e9b7c5aa58.png" alt="Cavalier" data-base62-sha1="h27oWaQmTf0OBvOwCyd6qLT7aCA" width="154" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Cavalier</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Investigative</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Mathilda</font></p>
<p>Though you may be new and unskilled, your quick mounts justify you as a worthy scout of Rigel. You travel through day and night, to search for the enemies of the empire and obliterate them. At least, that’s your goal.</p>
<p><strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Expedition (Night)</strong> - Choose a player. Determine if that player is the same alignment as the previous player you checked. <font color="gray">Neutrals</font> and <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> will be considered NS. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Interrogate (Night)</strong> - Choose a player. Determine the most recent night they have been  visited by a member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4c72864c0bff0da41b73516e7f1d60a0a8d8f7e9.png" alt="Arcanist" data-base62-sha1="aUhEE1vPVyBHday6nYo93EJvTgl" width="245" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Arcanist</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Investigative</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Kliff</font></p>
<p>Members of the Duma Faithful, you align yourself with the Rigelians to get rid of the boy of the prophecy, Alm. Though the empire may see you as an ally, your first goal is to only see all enemies of the all-powerful lord Duma. And to know where they’re headed.</p>
<p><strong>Dark Aura (Passive)</strong> - If you are lynched, your accuser and hammerer will be occupied the following night, bypassing immunities.<br>
<strong>Faint Wisp (Night)</strong> -  Choose a player and light their path. You will see who they visit first tonight. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Ghastly Eyes (Night)</strong> -  Choose a player and watch their surroundings. You will discover who visits them. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fa81036ae4419ef0b939dc1545219f22f4fff839.png" alt="Sky_Knight" data-base62-sha1="zK3MctzGLzCev3xXHL8vmd6abYl" width="167" height="237"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Sky Knight</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Investigative</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Clair</font></p>
<p>No walls or citadels have enough height to stop your search. And though you could just as easily hurl javelins down onto the soldiers below, you and your pegasus are trained to find the nobles of Rigel and Zofia, the ones who believe in the old caste system, and to recruit them to your aid, against the Deliverance.</p>
<p><strong>Airborne (Passive)</strong> - You bypass visit prevention and all players who target you with Day Attacks have 10% less chance to hit. If the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> used Bows during today’s battle, this passive is disabled until the next day.<br>
<strong>Blue Bloods (Night)</strong> - Determine if a player is of Valentian Nobility. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Aerial Spy (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and discover their faction. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9f0d9f0713399967bdb7a7e92cdd923ecb39ab90.png" alt="Mercenary" data-base62-sha1="mH36gAVsJu792WY9cvN9olFcaCA" width="181" height="247"></p>
<h1><font color="brown"><strong>Mercenary</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Offensive</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Gray</font></p>
<p>The hired sword of Rigel, you don’t care about morals and righteous acts; as long as you get paid, you’re fine. And with a little bit of money, you’re more than willing to knock some foes out for more time than they want to be.</p>
<p><strong>Swordsmanship (Passive)</strong> - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> win a battle with Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.<br>
<strong>Subdue (Day)</strong> - Disable a player’s immunities tonight. - 3 use<br>
<strong>Parry (Night)</strong> - Occupy a player. - oo use<br>
<strong>Sweeping Blow (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and occupy all players who visit them. - 2 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/2/20288057e13943c267fe221bbec6d3cf91413707.png" alt="Myrmidon" data-base62-sha1="4Au3gSgGyvuYHpR1bUdxUZPbO6j" width="167" height="254"></p>
<h1><font color="brown"><strong>Myrmidon</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Offensive</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Python</font></p>
<p>Elite swordsmen of the Rigelian Empire, you are adept with all types of swords. Small blades, longswords, and even knives. And aided by the threat of your sharp edges, none of the lower ranks in the army would dare disobey your orders. They go only where you tell them to go.</p>
<p><strong>Swordsmanship (Passive)</strong> - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> win a battle with Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.<br>
<strong>Crosswise Cut (Day)</strong> - Attack 2 players. You will have a 10% chance to individually kill them. - 2 use<br>
<strong>Enforce (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and redirect them to a target. - oo use<br>
<strong>Harsh Battlecry (Night)</strong> - Choose a player. You will make all of their day attacks miss tomorrow. - 2 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/8/81f05dd9bd7ee56592ac1534a9b77bbe1a9b2df3.png" alt="Mage" data-base62-sha1="ixuzL4mvAYHVfoKYYsrho7YjETV" width="147" height="229"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Mage</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Support</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Luthier</font></p>
<p>Rigel’s army, though it may be filled with iron-willed and hardened soldiers, also has room for those gifted with magical powers. Spellcasters who wield powerful fire magic, shocking lightning magic, and unstable wind magic, are most desired among all soldiers to make the enemy’s day even more worse. And you have plenty up your sleeve for the Deliverance to take.</p>
<p><strong>Firewall (Day)</strong> - Prevent all visits to a player tonight. You may not target them tomorrow. - 2 use<br>
<strong>Empower (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and guarantee their night ability is successful and bypasses immunities and protections. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Excalibur (Night)</strong> - Choose two players and swap their positions. Bypasses redirection immunity. - 3 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/8/89c4cfb4ae3488bff8c4823d24ea268147b26d05.png" alt="Cleric" data-base62-sha1="jEL4WQHIjiwVCEx8m6jCk27aA6x" width="123" height="233"></p>
<h1>
<font color="brown"><strong>Cleric</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Support</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Silque</font></p>
<p>Advocates of pacifism, you desire no war nor bloodshed on any country’s soil. However, forced into servitude of Rigel by the fall of your goddess, Mila, you find that it may be easier to deal with the suffering if you can save as many lives as possible on the battlefield.</p>
<p><strong>Warp (Day)</strong> - Teleport a player and bring them to you today. For the rest of today, any day attacks and abilities that target them will be ineffective, but they will die alongside you if you die to a day attack. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Recover (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and heal their wounds. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Physic (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and heal their wounds, bypassing visit prevention. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b5b136787bae1379edf8edf3f1f56ce99fe5cca2.png" alt="Archer" data-base62-sha1="pVk67GhSWo8eHFqG0BxkYkEv3vc" width="247" height="256"></p>
<h1><font color="brown"><strong>Archer</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Killer</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Tobin</font></p>
<p>Armed to the brim with arrows and your trusty bow, you are the long arm of the Rigelian Empire. There’s no need to lose your lives in hasty close combat when you could shoot them from far away. And you will bring this war to an end faster than it would without you. Provided you’re not shot, of course.</p>
<p><strong>Anti-Air (Passive)</strong> - If targeting a player with the <strong>Airborne</strong> passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them.<br>
<strong>Loose Barrage (Passive)</strong> - If you kill a <font color="brown">Rigelian</font> with your attacks, you will be unable to use any abilities the following day.<br>
<strong>Snipe (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a -10% chance to hit them with 0 uses. Each use you have on Snipe increases your chances of hitting your target by 20%. Expends all uses after a successful hit. - 0 uses<br>
<strong>Curved Shot (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 0 uses<br>
<strong>Precision Firing (Night)</strong> - Gain 1 use of a Day Ability of your choice. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Warding Arrow (Night)</strong> - You will gain 10% accuracy for any day attack tomorrow that targets a magic user. - 3 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4bfcb20e6cf7e80fc2114185b9594fc451a1c173.png" alt="Soldier" data-base62-sha1="aQdcTpYPyQi40d2QvIEOlbW5Gmv" width="226" height="256"></p>
<h1><font color="brown"><strong>Soldier</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="brown">Rigelian Support</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Forsyth</font></p>
<p>The newest recruits of the Rigelian army, you came from poor villages to earn some gold for your family back home. You may be inexperienced, but with each battle, your strength will only continue to grow.</p>
<p><strong>Armored (Passive)</strong> - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.<br>
<strong>Promote (Night)</strong> - Choose a dead non-Unique <font color="brown">Rigelian</font> class and gain its passives and abilities. You will not gain Nobility status from becoming a class that does have it. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Shieldbearer (Night)</strong> - Choose another player and make them and you immune to death tonight. - 1 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</details>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Deliverance</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0b0deb2e73cac181ae00b9583e8f37ebaa41d511.jpg" alt="Clive" data-base62-sha1="1zN4vRfqMoUqIl1gUuULaAxyhhL" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Clive</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crossed_swords.png?v=9" title=":crossed_swords:" class="emoji" alt=":crossed_swords:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Killer</font></p>
<p>Captain of the Knights of Zofia and the founder of the Deliverance, you put loyalty and honor above all else to defend your country and your people. Put under immense stress, you worry every day for the lives of your soldiers and your friends. And you become more anxious in knowing your sister, Clair, and your fiancée, Mathilda, also joins you on the battlefield every day. But you sent Lukas out to bring a hero to the Deliverance, and you have faith in Alm that he will be that hero.</p>
<p><strong>Iron-Clad (Passive)</strong> - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you. Any day attack targeting you will have 10% less chance of killing you.<br>
<strong>Ridersbane (Passive)</strong> - If targeting a player with the <strong>Mounted</strong> passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them.<br>
<strong>Hit and Run (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 30% chance of killing them. - oo uses (1-Day Cooldown)<br>
<strong>Sharpened Lance (Night)</strong> - Attack a player. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Lunge (Night)</strong> - Attack a player, bypassing death immunity. Swaps all targeting actions between you and the player you’re attacking except for you. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/2/21b4e289ef9784e98a83169a313dc8183cfa19e7.png" alt="Alm" data-base62-sha1="4ObiDMIfzvoxnKBmKyKGYuSCNnx" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crossed_swords.png?v=9" title=":crossed_swords:" class="emoji" alt=":crossed_swords:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Special</font></p>
<p>The bearer of the brand, and the prophesied hero, you were born the Crown Prince of Rigel but knew no home other than the small village of Ram, under the care of the former Zofian General, Sir Mycen. Accepting Lukas’ invitation, and setting out from Ram with most of your childhood friends, you hold a heart for those who suffer, and you will continue to persevere through the fight in the toughest of times. You know that there are many who hate you, and seek to kill you, but you still have hope that maybe they’ll see justice, and come to terms with the truth, that all humans are equal and can stand together. And maybe someday, the love of your life, Celica, can also see the same way as you do.</p>
<p><strong>Hero’s Brand (Passive)</strong> - Immune to death at night, occupation, and redirection. Cannot die to any attacks from Duma even if they bypass immunity while there is a living <font color="green"><strong>King Rudolf</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>Rigel’s Heir (Passive)</strong> - If Starting <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>, you will appear as a <font color="brown">Rigelian</font> to all checks on you and the day after a <font color="green"><strong>King Rudolf</strong></font> dies at night, you will have the priority ascension to the throne. All day attacks targetting you will have 20% less accuracy.<br>
<strong>Commandeering (Day)</strong> - If <font color="green"><strong>Clive</strong></font> is dead, choose another <font color="green">Deliverance</font> member. They will become <font color="green"><strong>Clive</strong></font> at the start of tonight. - 2 use (Shared)<br>
<strong>True Sacrifice (Day)</strong> - Your conversion will bypass conversion protection and <strong>Hero’s Brand</strong> will be disabled tonight. - 1 use (Shared)<br>
<strong>Recall to Light (Night)</strong> - Choose a player. You will convert them to the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)<br>
<strong>Double Lion (Night)</strong> - For tomorrow’s battle, if the <font color="green">Deliverance’s</font> weapon is Swords, you will win the battle even if you tie. - 3 uses (Shared)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/7/73e6f4ccaf486207e7459ecf1dceb96de05a8896.png" alt="Sir%20Mycen" data-base62-sha1="gxjJim0j4SId2E1oVY0ROhP5azc" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Sir Mycen</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Killer</font></p>
<p>Former general of Zofia, you lost your job when the manipulation of Chancellor Desaix sent you far away from the Zofian court, to the tiny village of Ram. But even there, you continued to be Emperor Rudolf’s support and friend, accepting his request to raise his own son to be the hero of Valentia. Though you have aged, you still haven’t lost your skill with lance or sword, and is the guardian for your adopted child, Alm, even on the battlefield.</p>
<p><strong>Military Hero (Passive)</strong> - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you. If <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font> uses <strong>Commandeering</strong> on you, they will not lose a use of its ability.<br>
<strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Veteran Knight (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance of killing them. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Hero of Yore (Night)</strong> - Prevent all visits to a <font color="green">Deliverance</font> member. The first time you successfully block a visit, gain 1 use of <strong>Piercing Blow</strong>. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Piercing Blow (Night)</strong> - Kill a player. Bypasses healing. - 0 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1cedb66fd9c9e2a9e5437f32915fa2ec30496582.png" alt="Gray" data-base62-sha1="47UFiJw7stf7D3vb5EB33Bb9pJM" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1><font color="green"><strong>Gray</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Offensive</font></p>
<p>One of Alm’s childhood friends from Ram, you were the most eager to set out on this journey with him, setting your life and sword on the line so that you can stay with your friends. You’re quite flirtatious as well, although your skill with a sword speaks more than your tongue. And you don’t set out on things alone, the least you could do was convince your best friend, Tobin, to come along with you.</p>
<p><strong>Swordsmanship (Passive)</strong> - Immune to occupation and redirection. If the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> wins a battle using Swords, gain 1 use of any limited ability.<br>
<strong>Ram’s Banner (Passive)</strong> - When you replace <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>, refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>Subdue (Day)</strong> - Disable a player’s immunities tonight. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Sunder (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. Increases by 10% if you voted Swords in today’s battle. - 3 uses (1-Day Cooldown)<br>
<strong>Parry (Night)</strong> - Occupy a player. - oo use<br>
<strong>Windsweep (Night)</strong> - Occupy a player and all players who visit them. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6a46488444c8f7a4834ccc6da9c3e5323ed68608.png" alt="Tobin" data-base62-sha1="fa9bYbgAUivydsaYZGW38eZwLA4" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1><font color="green"><strong>Tobin</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Killer</font></p>
<p>One of Alm’s childhood friends from Ram, you agreed to join him and Gray on this journey in exchange for coin so that your family could eat during the hard times brought on by the war. Though you lack strength, your skill with a bow and strategic mindset has done much to aid your friends on the journey. However, you won’t give a moment’s hesitation if the opportunity to get something… shiny… comes up.</p>
<p><strong>Anti-Air (Passive)</strong> - If targeting a player with the <strong>Airborne</strong> passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them.<br>
<strong>Ram’s Banner (Passive)</strong> - When you replace <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>, refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>Snipe (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a -10% chance to hit them with 0 uses. Each use you have on Snipe increases your chances of hitting your target by 20%. Expends all uses after a successful hit. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Curved Shot (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 20% chance to kill them. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Precision Firing (Night)</strong> - Gain 1 use of a Day Ability of your choice. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Ranged Charge (Night)</strong> - Allow for the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> to choose Bows in tomorrow’s battle. - 3 uses (1-Night Cooldown)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/9/90dd2f926fb3167a948fc57823762a9d0b193d30.png" alt="Kliff" data-base62-sha1="kFwDWhWJycDpHi5Rhuooc3jxa5a" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Kliff</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Investigative</font></p>
<p>One of Alm’s childhood friends from Ram, you eventually agreed to Alm, Gray, and Tobin’s requests to journey with them to the Deliverance so that you could fulfill your dream of seeing the world. Out of all of your friends, you are a gifted mage with raw arcane power. You may seem sharp and prickly, but your friends don’t underestimate your skill on the battlefield, as well as reconnaissance.</p>
<p><strong>Ram’s Banner (Passive)</strong> - When you replace <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>, refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>Sagittae (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance to kill them. If they are Magical, you will lose 25% accuracy. If they have the <strong>Armored</strong> passive, you will gain 25% accuracy. Disables the <strong>Armored</strong> passive’s effect when targeting a player with it. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Sense Aura (Day)</strong> - Choose a player and determine if they are Magical at the start of tonight. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Bright Wisp (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and see who they visit and who visits them. - oo uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8adea92784022deb29dccdab74edeb7a2ff2c5a7.png" alt="Faye" data-base62-sha1="jOuWf2Xd2ZDHgn9a9A5HMGhrdZR" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Faye</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Support</font></p>
<p>One of Alm’s childhood friends from Ram, you had a major crush on him when you were young, and have grown up with it too, although your love for him gives you strength to let him go and instead fight with him at his side. You have a caring personality, although Kliff and Gray continue to mention that you are also very obsessive when it comes to anything involving Alm. You still try your best to let Alm go, as he asked of you.</p>
<p><strong>Ram’s Banner (Passive)</strong> - When you replace <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>, refresh all uses of all of your abilities. You will have priority on becoming <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>Unwavering Love (Passive)</strong> - You will not count towards the member cap of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> and can use both day abilities in the same day.<br>
<strong>Anew (Day)</strong> - Choose a member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. They are able to use one Day Attack twice today, and will only count as using it once. - 2 uses (1-Day Cooldown)<br>
<strong>Rescue (Day)</strong> - Choose a player and prevent all visits to them tonight. They will be targeted by any non-Investigative abilities that target you as well tonight. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Bright Wisp (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and see who they visit and who visits them. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Imbue (Night)</strong> - Choose a member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> and guarantee their action is successful tonight, bypassing immunities and protections. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a227d7aec602cf41917f2daf32fdb18bf9f1bb5b.png" alt="Lukas" data-base62-sha1="n8uIasnWpyamy5db9BVzMA4Cfxh" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Lukas</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Killer</font></p>
<p>The backwater noble of the Deliverance, you serve as Clive’s cold and calculating tactician. Although you do your best to help those in need, and be sympathetic to those who ask of your help, you can’t let emotions get in the way of being the best that the Deliverance has to offer. You served Clive well before, and you’re more than ready to give Alm all the assistance he needs to lead the Deliverance.</p>
<p><strong>Armored (Passive)</strong> - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.<br>
<strong>Ridersbane (Passive)</strong> - If targeting a player with the <strong>Mounted</strong> passive during the day, you will have 40% more chance to kill them.<br>
<strong>Javelin Toss (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 25% chance of killing them. Increases by 5% if the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> won a battle with Lances. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Zofian Shield (Night)</strong> - Prevent all visits to a player.  - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)<br>
<strong>Rallying Cry (Night)</strong> - Choose a <font color="green">Deliverance</font> member and guarantee their action is successful tonight, bypassing all protections and immunities. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/5/546f28d743c6e40a95a964ede6b80e68b063318d.png" alt="Silque" data-base62-sha1="c2Wgtr5qpfuirnsgVRRjwVYLDWZ" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Silque</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Support</font></p>
<p>A cleric from a monastery in Novis, you came to the aid of Alm at the request of his love, Celica, although sidetracked by brigands along the way. Reserved and pious, you heal the wounds of the broken and revitalize the spirit of the Deliverance, using the way of the goddess Mila.</p>
<p><strong>Invoke (Day)</strong> - Summon soldiers to protect the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. The first successful day attack targeted at any member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> will not kill them. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Recover (Night)</strong> - Heal a member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. Their day attacks will gain 10% accuracy tomorrow. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Nosferatu (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and a class. If that player dies tonight or tomorrow during a Day Attack, they will be revealed as the class you chose. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fc7d04fd47a0479144b1b6538eda79b56beff383.png" alt="Clair" data-base62-sha1="A1CaSUlrcDUytulLwa0IB0vvAEb" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Clair</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Investigative</font></p>
<p>The energetic and headstrong younger sister of Clive, you saw yourself in total admiration of your brother since you were kids. He is everything you want to find in a man for your future, someone good with words, strong, kind, gifted in music, and well versed in poetry and literature. You even followed him to the Deliverance and joined as a Sky Knight. However, you know that it’s near impossible to find anyone who can come close to the likes of Clive, and that it’s hard to resist the flirting from Gray and Tobin for too long.</p>
<p><strong>Airborne (Passive)</strong> - You bypass visit prevention and all players who target you with Day Attacks have 10% less chance to hit. If the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> used Bows during today’s battle, this passive is disabled until the next day.<br>
<strong>Expose (Day)</strong> - At the start of tonight, discover who <font color="brown"><strong>Berkut</strong></font> has in his jail. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Blue Bloods (Night)</strong> - Choose two players and determine whether each are Valentian Nobility. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Winged Guard (Night)</strong> - Make all members of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> appear as <font color="brown">Rigelians</font> tonight. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4f9152e6f1e03ad2da38728f162158687157d241.png" alt="Forsyth" data-base62-sha1="blT4EuiAqdgksnPuVIGNbi8qKMV" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1><font color="green"><strong>Forsyth</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Support</font></p>
<p>Born as a scholar, you came from a small town with your best friend Python to enlist in the Deliverance. Although Python continued to discourage you, you persevered and rose through the ranks, eventually becoming Clive’s second-in-command. You are the example of meritocracy and evidence that hard work does yield results.</p>
<p><strong>Armored (Passive)</strong> - You will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.<br>
<strong>Lieutenant by Merit (Passive)</strong> - If <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font> uses Commandeering on you, they will not lose a use of its ability. You will keep this passive even after you change classes from being <font color="green"><strong>Forsyth</strong></font> or a <font color="brown"><strong>Soldier</strong></font>.<br>
<strong>Promote (Night)</strong> - Choose a dead non-Unique <font color="brown">Rigelian</font> or <font color="green">Deliverance</font> class and gain its passives and abilities tonight. You will become the convert form if you choose a <font color="brown">Rigelian</font> class. You will not gain Nobility status from becoming a class that does have it. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Shieldbearer (Night)</strong> - Choose another player and make them and you immune to death tonight. - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0bda522e998f9e6b476133e1c4a4d75881f96c1e.png" alt="Python" data-base62-sha1="1GR0aNRnpXxkX8unYsnEBmPZtsq" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1><font color="green"><strong>Python</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Offensive</font></p>
<p>You were dragged into the mess that Forsyth calls the Deliverance, as you were just too eager to escape your small town and the harsh overseer, Dunderhead. Skeptical of the nobility, you put up an edgy façade to deal with uninviting conversation. However, as much as your laziness shows to your best friend, your skill with archery shows just as much, too.</p>
<p><strong>Anti-Air (Passive)</strong> - If targeting a player with the <strong>Airborne</strong> passive, you will have 50% more chance to kill them.<br>
<strong>Stubborn (Passive)</strong> - Immune to occupation and redirection. Each time someone tries to occupy or redirect you unsuccessfully, gain 1 use of any limited ability.<br>
<strong>Double Shot (Day)</strong> - Attack 2 players. You will have a 20% chance to individually kill them. - 2 use<br>
<strong>Hunter’s Volley (Day)</strong> - Force a player to use their top night ability tonight, if they have uses left. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Notched Threat (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and redirect them to a target. - oo use<br>
<strong>Smoke Arrow (Night)</strong> - Choose a player. You will make all of their day attacks miss tomorrow. - 3 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/5/5a66fc1556b7666fc055d72bb17675d5ee6c100d.png" alt="Mathilda" data-base62-sha1="cTJCc4v3zsp6G9PpFtt2LDUDCSV" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Mathilda</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Investigative</font></p>
<p>Once a legend for young boys, you went from a beauty of martial skill on the battlefield to the sole affection of your fiancée, Clive. As he founded and continued to lead the Deliverance until Alm’s ascendance, you were his constant support and foundation throughout his hard times. And although Clive is the man in the relationship, everyone, even Clive himself, knows that you are the stronger force to be wagered with.</p>
<p><strong>The Betrothed (Passive)</strong> - If <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font> uses Commandeering on you, they will not lose a use of its ability.<br>
<strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Pinpoint (Night)</strong> - Discover a player’s exact class if they are a <font color="brown">Rigelian</font>. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Warding Guard (Night)</strong> - Choose a player and determine if they are Magical. - 3 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bcf9d45886eba9e11acf4e52a0cd1b40864ef974.png" alt="Luthier" data-base62-sha1="qXL1l8vigxfzAcpru9YLlZ1UgrW" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Luthier</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Support</font></p>
<p>A mage from a Zofian village, you asked Alm for help in saving your sister, Delthea, from the influence of the Duma Faithful. As a humble yet anti-social person, you try your best to make friends, although the only person you’ve ever been comfortable talking to is your sister. Your spells are powerful, and the Deliverance would be lacking without your efforts.</p>
<p><strong>Firewall (Day)</strong> - Prevent all non-<font color="green">Deliverance</font> visits to a player tonight.  - 2 use<br>
<strong>Thunder (Night)</strong> - Stun a player. They will get incorrect feedback from their abilities tonight. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Excalibur (Night)</strong> - Choose two players and swap their positions. Bypasses redirection immunity. - oo uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/2/244a43aac64235136553b741355909954ec30882.png" alt="Delthea" data-base62-sha1="5b2izlsAFv522763VyxUwj7yyVI" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Delthea</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Social</font></p>
<p>You hold more energy and potent magic aura than anyone could ever give you credit for. And that’s why the Duma Faithful took you and put you under their influence as a mindless puppet to kill the Deliverance, until Alm saved you and reunited you with your brother, Luthier. You are the antithesis to your brother. You are the social bunny of the army, but never cease bragging about yourself or your powerful magic. Luthier tells you to not wave your power around too much though.</p>
<p><strong>Mental Link (Passive)</strong> - All players stunned by you will be added to your private neighborhood. You will be able to talk at night. Your neighborhood will not change if you are converted.<br>
<strong>Aura (Day)</strong> - Stun a player, bringing them under your control at the start of tonight. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Hasten (Day)</strong> - Remove cooldown from Ragnarok. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Ragnarok (Night)</strong> - Remove a player from your control at the end of the night. If they are not a <font color="green">Deliverance</font> member, all Day Attacks targeting them will be 30% more accurate tomorrow. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/8/877c67385d859f5ca0d80d974992fc55a657493b.png" alt="Tatiana" data-base62-sha1="jkyZrXJSe4xO1AVw5aMowlhF1Fx" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Tatiana</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Social</font></p>
<p>A Rigelian Saint, you came to love the man you once found washed ashore on the beaches of Rigel. Although the whole land is about strength and power, you know that there’s something more to life than just domination and war. And when the Deliverance saved you from Nuibaba’s prison, you committed your staff to their cause, as well as your fiancée’s lance. Zeke would have done the same thing in your position.</p>
<p><strong>By His Side (Passive)</strong> - You cannot step up to be King, as your only wish is to spend your days at <font color="green"><strong>Ezekiel’s</strong></font> side.<br>
<strong>Saintful Words (Passive)</strong> - While you are alive, dead members of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> may talk directly in the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> chat. You will not count towards the member cap.<br>
<strong>Outcry of Rebellion (Day)</strong> - Send a private message to a player anonymously. They may not reply back. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Mind Warp (Night)</strong> - Make any player gain incorrect feedback from their abilities tonight. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Revival (Night)</strong> - Bring a dead member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> back to life as their first <font color="green">Deliverance</font> class. If <font color="green"><strong>Starting Alm</strong></font> or <font color="green"><strong>Starting Clive</strong></font> is revived, the player holding their position will revert to their previous class. - 1 use</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f6801c91f9ad3565d2c03f8a51cae4c92e086ef.png" alt="Ezekiel" data-base62-sha1="4tPDoRyDJa4ISZWu3z96ZanlCaz" width="256" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="green"><strong>Ezekiel</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<p><font color="green">Deliverance Support</font></p>
<p>Although you once had another name, you are known in Rigel as Ezekiel, and Zeke to your fiancée, Tatiana. Your lance is the extension of Emperor Rudolf’s hand, and just as he puts his trust in his son Alm, you have done the same, and joined the Deliverance with Tatiana. Although a powerful military commander, you are sensitive and empathetic to the people of Rigel and Zofia.</p>
<p><strong>Mounted (Passive)</strong> - You are able to use both night abilities in the same night.<br>
<strong>Commander’s Presence (Day)</strong> - Your vote during today’s battle will secretly count as 2 when totaling the end result. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Gradivus (Day)</strong> - Attack a player. You have a 15% chance to kill them. If the <font color="green">Deliverance</font> chose Lances the previous night, gain 20% accuracy. - 3 uses (1-Day Cooldown)<br>
<strong>Lancer’s Poise (Night)</strong> - For tomorrow’s battle, if the <font color="green">Deliverance’s</font> weapon is Lances, you will win the battle even if you tie. Overrides Veteran Lancer. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Rallying Cry (Night)</strong> - Choose a member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>. All of their Day Attacks will gain 20% accuracy tomorrow. - oo uses (1-Night Cooldown)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</details>
<details>
<summary>
Neutrals</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9328d91a8d2a4725befbd8a58ca2897b44ba9abe.jpg" alt="Lover%20Faye" data-base62-sha1="kZPHGXrsM6m8V5bzHP0R7pEvjAi" width="250" height="250"></p>
<h1>
<font color="gray"><strong>Lover Faye</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><font color="gray">Neutral Investigative</font><br>
Converts to <font color="green">Faye</font></p>
<p>One of Alm’s childhood friends from Ram, you are the most worried about this war. All of the boys seem ready to be up in arms for Zofia, but all you can think about is keeping Alm safe, and away from the fighting. Alm did ask you to try to let go of him a little, for your benefit, but it will take a lot of persuasion and time for that to happen.</p>
<p><strong>Lovestruck (Passive)</strong> - Once you visit <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font>, you will know their identity. If you visit 2 members in the same turn, or are visited/tried to be killed by any member of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>, you will be converted and not count towards the member cap. If you become King, you will become Emperor Rudolf.<br>
<strong>Whisper (Day)</strong> - Send a single 1000 character message to a player. They cannot send a message back. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Stalking Eyes (Night)</strong> - Watch over two players. You will know who they visit and who visited them. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Love’s Sacrifice (Night)</strong> - Guard a player. If they would die from any cause, prevent their death, and you canot use this again. Stays on the player until moved to someone else. - oo uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to ensure that your love, Starting Alm, survives the destruction of the world or that you join the Deliverance and gain its objective.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0254ec0a24a719623673236fb21afffb9d9aed50.png" alt="Jedah" data-base62-sha1="kCTLS5pOVdAfY4iGx5jQtzTQha" width="233" height="256"></p>
<h1>
<font color="gray"><strong>Jedah</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="gray">Neutral Offensive</font></p>
<p>You are the high priest of the Duma Faithful. The mastermind behind the doomsday of Valentia, your goal is to awaken your lord Duma and bring upon the destruction of the world. You sent your witch, Nuibaba, to deal with the Rigelian court, as you wait for the demise of the Deliverance and the doom of the second prophesied one, Celica.</p>
<p><strong>Duma’s Servant (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to occupation and redirection. If <font color="gray"><strong>Mad Lord Duma</strong></font> targets you, they will be prevented from visiting instead.<br>
<strong>Rigel’s Conjuring (Day)</strong> - Choose a player, you will make them appear a member of the Deliverance tonight. If you target Mad Lord Duma, you will know their identity. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Telepathy (Day)</strong> - Choose a player. You may send a single 1000 character message to that player, and they may send one back as well. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Incarnation (Night)</strong> - Choose two players. You will swap their positions tonight. Bypasses redirection immunity. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Hand of Duma (Night)</strong> - Choose one of your targets. Force them to target another player of your choice. - 3 uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to see at least 3 Rigelians and 1 Deliverance lynched or to ensure that Mad Lord Duma destroys the world.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0c7fd416c004b5cf58712078ff7d826a530a23b4.png" alt="Brigand_1" data-base62-sha1="1MzBfNrSPBcSt5HHA7vvdMvA948" width="241" height="256"></p>
<h1><font color="gray"><strong>Brigand</strong></font></h1>
<p><font color="gray">Neutral Support</font></p>
<p>Thanks to the war between Zofia and Rigel, power has been vacuumed out from the local countryside, and mischievous individuals have risen up to secure power and wealth from the sudden loss of authority. That is you. A brigand. You are no more than obstacles to the Deliverance, yet you fight against them due to your greed for more wealth and more power. In the end though, all you want is to live a good life.</p>
<p><strong>Plunderer (Passive)</strong> - Each time either side votes for Axes in a battle, you will gain 1 use of your choice ability.<br>
<strong>Wanted! (Passive)</strong> - If you are lynched or killed, the player who accused or killed you will gain death immunity that night and be healed that night. Your killer/accuser will also be conversion immune that night if a <font color="brown">Rigelian</font> or reset 1 cooldown for any member of the faction if part of the <font color="green">Deliverance</font>.<br>
<strong>Reap the Spoils (Night)</strong> - Heal any player, including yourself. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Trusty Axe (Night)</strong> - Kill a player. - 0 use<br>
<em>Your objective is to survive no matter the cost.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1cb0768baff1aff26f6960d768dded24c27c7fc8.png" alt="Duma" data-base62-sha1="45NrfE4bQiCGwX8XRXEzGBk2hcc" width="482" height="500"></p>
<h1>
<font color="gray"><strong>Mad Lord Duma</strong></font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/crossed_swords.png?v=9" title=":crossed_swords:" class="emoji" alt=":crossed_swords:"> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:">
</h1>
<p><font color="gray">Neutral Killer</font></p>
<p>The brother of Mila, a 1000 years ago, you and Mila split the continent of Valentia in two like some sibling territorial struggle. Mila raised the people of Zofia with riches and plentitude, while you hammered the humans of Rigel into hard and iron-willed soldiers. But due to time, your sanity has completely vanished, and now all you await is the day when you can bring about the end of the world.</p>
<p><strong>The Power of Madness (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to occupation and redirection when there is no King. You are immune to death at night and will survive the first successful day attack that targets you.<br>
<strong>Spread Darkness (Day)</strong> - You will be able to choose two targets tonight. Only able to be used after Starting <font color="green"><strong>Alm</strong></font> is dead.  - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Discard Soul (Day)</strong> - Your attacks will bypass death immunity tonight. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Ocular Beam (Night)</strong> - Attack a player. - oo uses<br>
<strong>Mad Wrath (Night)</strong> - Attack a player and occupy them. - 3 use<br>
<em>Your objective is to destroy the world and those who are not your servants.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 07:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72003-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sfol-echoes-class-cards-for-echoes-1/72003.rss">SFOL Echoes - Class Cards for Echoes 1</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
