<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621</link>
    <description>[Cult Lore] _Baptism by Blood_

The following excerpt was taken from a journal found among the belongings of a suspected Mithras cultist. While portions of the writing were rendered illegible due to the blood stains on the pages, it quickly became apparent that the individual in question was in fact the Cult’s leader, the self-appointed shepherd to the profane masses.

“Ever since my days at Castle Demwir, I [illegible] way to make others hear him. The [illegible] Mithras is not a god of malice, but he does not accept as worshippers [illegible] have not sacrificed. If I am to show to them the glory of Mithras, I must [illegible] sacrifice by taking that which they hold most dear. Only then [illegible] accepted into his flock. But [illegible] bond with their new god, they [illegible] taste of blood consecrated by Him. Where could [illegible] be found?
Mine…of course! [Illegible] serves as a conduit for his [illegible] always has! And surely Mithras [illegible] my own sacrifice to spread his glory! I must [illegible] and when they are broken shells of themselves, Mithras [illegible] through my gift of blood. They shall [illegible] in His embrace…”


[Apostle Lore] _Words of Power_

Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is gifted with their words, and holds the power to turn the people away from Mithras’ embrace. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and their words hold great power indeed.
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is bound and gagged, unable to use the words upon which they so have so relied. The Cult Leader fills the chalice, preparing for the Baptism of Blood. When all is in place, before the followers of Mithras, the Cult Leader takes hold of the ceremonial dagger. He removes the gag from the chosen, and in one smooth motion, cuts out their tongue, thereby silencing their words forever.
Next comes the Baptism of Blood. The Cult Leader takes the chalice, filled with his own blood, and dips in one finger. With this blood, he draws the symbol of Mithras on the chosen’s forehead, before abruptly tilting back their head and forcing the rest of the chalice down the chosen’s throat. As the chosen sputters and chokes on blood, Mithras himself speaks to them, just as he speaks to the Cult Leader. Mithras offers the chosen the power to speak without words, using their newfound gifts to speak directly to their victims’ minds. The offer of power is tempting…the deal is consecrated in blood. The Apostle has risen.

[Invoker Lore] _Strength of Will_

Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is renowned for their strength, and has the power to serve as a shield against Mithras’ faithful. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and strength is valuable to whoever controls it.
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is bound before Mithras’ altar, iron chains wrapped around their arms, chest and legs. The scent of old blood mingles horridly with the rusted chains as the followers of Mithras begin their invocation. The chains begin to glow red with otherworldly heat as the chosen screams in searing pain. Their flesh is seared by the hot metal as the Cult leader baptizes them, and as the ritual ends and the chains are removed, the brands still glow with dark magic. Their strength is now bound to the will of Mithras. The Invoker has risen.

[Ritualist Lore] _Terrible to Waste_

Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is quick-witted, and could outsmart the Cult’s well-laid plan to bring the glory of Mithras to Castle Adiart. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and a mind is a terrible thing to waste.
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is secured to the altar, kneeling and bound before the carving of the Blood God. With hoarse breath, they cry out for their god to save them, but their new god is saving them. The Cult leader readies a ceremonial weapon, a short but thick spike with a fine point. 
As the followers began the incantation, the cult leader gives the chosen their baptism of blood, then punches the spike through the back of the chosen’s skull. They are limp for but a moment, before the statue of Mithras glows bright red. The energy released is absorbed by the spike, and the chosen is animated once again…but they are not as they once were. Their mind, so cunning, is no longer their own. They belong to Mithras now. The Ritualist has risen.

[Seeker Lore] _Seeing Is Believing_

Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is a watchful one, and their gaze seeks to root out the worshippers of Mithras. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and their gaze reveals many things.
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is bound atop the altar, unable to free themselves from their bindings as the Cult Leader performs the baptism of blood. Now, the chosen must know sacrifice. The Cult Leader has sharpened his nails to points, and he uses these weapons with ruthless efficiency, as he reaches down and effortlessly plucks out the chosen’s eyes. 
Blinded and in agony, they scream in the darkness, until they see once again. Their agony has earned an audience with Mithras himself, and he offers to return their sight if they will only serve him and his followers. Desperate for any sort of return, they accept the terms, and the deal is struck. The Seeker has risen.

_From the Author:_ I decided to combine these all into a single thread, rather than creating five separate threads for these. For each lore, I was trying to focus on the ritual of conversion, which comes across to me as the most striking part of the converted roles. Each conversion ritual is based around a simple concept; destroy what the person holds most valuable to break down their sense of self, then rebuild them in the image of a loyal cultist. Beyond that, I tried simply to create a compelling narrative that fit a dark theme (it&#39;s a blood cult, after all) and could also tie in to the existing lore. Feel free to reply with constructive criticism or requests for more details into my lore.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:54:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tangeld]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d imagine that Corax plays more of a role in Unseen conversion, and when and if I start writing Unseen conversion lore, Corax would likely appear there. That’s not to say that he doesn’t have a place with the Cult, but I feel like Mithras takes the place of Honor with the cult that worships him as their god. Silly, I know…</p>
<p>As for the conversion rituals, I tried to avoid the idea of torture or forced servitude because to me, that doesn’t explain why the brainwashed Cultists would continue to faithfully serve Mithras. My idea behind this conversion lore (at least for the Apostle and Seeker) was that Mithras tempts the convert to pledge themselves to him by offering them something they value greatly. And besides, the existing lore for Cult King and Cult Leader portray Mithras as demonstrating a strange form of benevolence to those who follow him. But perhaps you’re right, in that the Blood God should be a bit more forceful and cruel in his actions. Corax seems more likely to be the one to use temptation and guile in his destruction of Castle Adiart…</p>
<p>I’m curious to hear feedback for the Invoker and Ritualist. The Invoker lore sounds rather torturous in my opinion, and I feel like you didn’t give the Ritualist a fair shake in its darkness. The passage you chose from their lore describes Mithras invading their mind and destroying their old self. I think of it as a form of psychological torture that also ties in with the Cult’s profane magics.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean I personally think that you did well with explains your thoughts on the lore, but the lore it’s self from what I have read so far doesn’t fit my vision of the brainwashings. Seeker one fits my vision someone what but not completely. Most of these are based on the “Magic” principle. What I mean by that is there is little explanation as to why this occurred, but they show the prep work. I feel like you are leaving to much of the lore to mithras himself rather then to the cult. You know what I mean? Like ill show it,</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tangeld" data-post="1" data-topic="32621">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/tangeld/40/15969_2.png" class="avatar"> Tangeld:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Mithras offers the chosen the power to speak without words, using their newfound gifts to speak directly to their victims’ minds. The offer of power is tempting…the deal is consecrated in blood. The Apostle has risen.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mithras offers something.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tangeld" data-post="1" data-topic="32621">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/tangeld/40/15969_2.png" class="avatar"> Tangeld:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Blinded and in agony, they scream in the darkness, until they see once again. Their agony has earned an audience with Mithras himself, and he offers to return their sight if they will only serve him and his followers. Desperate for any sort of return, they accept the terms, and the deal is struck. The Seeker has risen.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mithras does the work.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tangeld" data-post="1" data-topic="32621">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/tangeld/40/15969_2.png" class="avatar"> Tangeld:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They are limp for but a moment, before the statue of Mithras glows bright red. The energy released is absorbed by the spike, and the chosen is animated once again</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Implied mithras does something.</p>
<p>But that is my opinion, I like to imagine cult brainwash people via torture rather then extremely complicated rituals that are highly dependent on wether mithras is in a good mood or not.</p>
<p>But what makes me really sad is you didn’t even mention the corax! You had like perfect opportunities to, and that would have solved a portion of my problem with the lore by making it not so reliant on mithras!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tangeld]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why would I fight you? There is no need to kill you. You have your part to play…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fight me</p>
<details>
<summary>
o_O</summary>
<p><a href="https://forum.imperium42.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856" class="inline-onebox-loading">https://forum.imperium42.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856</a></p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tangeld]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Quiet, heathen. Do not ask how I know the sacred rituals of Lord Mithras.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cult icons responding to cult lore? Coincidence? <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Coatsman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is really cool. Though much is not known about him, maybe you could implement something about Corax with the Apostle and Ritualist?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 14:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tangeld]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[Cult Lore] <em>Baptism by Blood</em></p>
<p>The following excerpt was taken from a journal found among the belongings of a suspected Mithras cultist. While portions of the writing were rendered illegible due to the blood stains on the pages, it quickly became apparent that the individual in question was in fact the Cult’s leader, the self-appointed shepherd to the profane masses.</p>
<p>“Ever since my days at Castle Demwir, I [illegible] way to make others hear him. The [illegible] Mithras is not a god of malice, but he does not accept as worshippers [illegible] have not sacrificed. If I am to show to them the glory of Mithras, I must [illegible] sacrifice by taking that which they hold most dear. Only then [illegible] accepted into his flock. But [illegible] bond with their new god, they [illegible] taste of blood consecrated by Him. Where could [illegible] be found?<br>
Mine…of course! [Illegible] serves as a conduit for his [illegible] always has! And surely Mithras [illegible] my own sacrifice to spread his glory! I must [illegible] and when they are broken shells of themselves, Mithras [illegible] through my gift of blood. They shall [illegible] in His embrace…”</p>
<p>[Apostle Lore] <em>Words of Power</em></p>
<p>Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is gifted with their words, and holds the power to turn the people away from Mithras’ embrace. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and their words hold great power indeed.<br>
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is bound and gagged, unable to use the words upon which they so have so relied. The Cult Leader fills the chalice, preparing for the Baptism of Blood. When all is in place, before the followers of Mithras, the Cult Leader takes hold of the ceremonial dagger. He removes the gag from the chosen, and in one smooth motion, cuts out their tongue, thereby silencing their words forever.<br>
Next comes the Baptism of Blood. The Cult Leader takes the chalice, filled with his own blood, and dips in one finger. With this blood, he draws the symbol of Mithras on the chosen’s forehead, before abruptly tilting back their head and forcing the rest of the chalice down the chosen’s throat. As the chosen sputters and chokes on blood, Mithras himself speaks to them, just as he speaks to the Cult Leader. Mithras offers the chosen the power to speak without words, using their newfound gifts to speak directly to their victims’ minds. The offer of power is tempting…the deal is consecrated in blood. The Apostle has risen.</p>
<p>[Invoker Lore] <em>Strength of Will</em></p>
<p>Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is renowned for their strength, and has the power to serve as a shield against Mithras’ faithful. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and strength is valuable to whoever controls it.<br>
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is bound before Mithras’ altar, iron chains wrapped around their arms, chest and legs. The scent of old blood mingles horridly with the rusted chains as the followers of Mithras begin their invocation. The chains begin to glow red with otherworldly heat as the chosen screams in searing pain. Their flesh is seared by the hot metal as the Cult leader baptizes them, and as the ritual ends and the chains are removed, the brands still glow with dark magic. Their strength is now bound to the will of Mithras. The Invoker has risen.</p>
<p>[Ritualist Lore] <em>Terrible to Waste</em></p>
<p>Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is quick-witted, and could outsmart the Cult’s well-laid plan to bring the glory of Mithras to Castle Adiart. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and a mind is a terrible thing to waste.<br>
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is secured to the altar, kneeling and bound before the carving of the Blood God. With hoarse breath, they cry out for their god to save them, but their new god is saving them. The Cult leader readies a ceremonial weapon, a short but thick spike with a fine point.<br>
As the followers began the incantation, the cult leader gives the chosen their baptism of blood, then punches the spike through the back of the chosen’s skull. They are limp for but a moment, before the statue of Mithras glows bright red. The energy released is absorbed by the spike, and the chosen is animated once again…but they are not as they once were. Their mind, so cunning, is no longer their own. They belong to Mithras now. The Ritualist has risen.</p>
<p>[Seeker Lore] <em>Seeing Is Believing</em></p>
<p>Deep within the halls of the castle, in the meeting chamber of Mithras’ loyal followers, the Cult Leader gathers the faithful. Their god has called for another to enter the fold. This devotee of the court is a watchful one, and their gaze seeks to root out the worshippers of Mithras. They must be dealt with…but there is no need to kill them. They have their part to play, and their gaze reveals many things.<br>
Under cover of night, the chosen is brought to the profaned halls of Mithras’ faithful. The ritual is ready to commence. The chosen is bound atop the altar, unable to free themselves from their bindings as the Cult Leader performs the baptism of blood. Now, the chosen must know sacrifice. The Cult Leader has sharpened his nails to points, and he uses these weapons with ruthless efficiency, as he reaches down and effortlessly plucks out the chosen’s eyes.<br>
Blinded and in agony, they scream in the darkness, until they see once again. Their agony has earned an audience with Mithras himself, and he offers to return their sight if they will only serve him and his followers. Desperate for any sort of return, they accept the terms, and the deal is struck. The Seeker has risen.</p>
<p><em>From the Author:</em> I decided to combine these all into a single thread, rather than creating five separate threads for these. For each lore, I was trying to focus on the ritual of conversion, which comes across to me as the most striking part of the converted roles. Each conversion ritual is based around a simple concept; destroy what the person holds most valuable to break down their sense of self, then rebuild them in the image of a loyal cultist. Beyond that, I tried simply to create a compelling narrative that fit a dark theme (it’s a blood cult, after all) and could also tie in to the existing lore. Feel free to reply with constructive criticism or requests for more details into my lore.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 21:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32621-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-cult-lore/32621.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Cult Lore</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
