<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Copypastes strategies?</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600</link>
    <description>When I was first starting the game a couple weeks ago, most games had at least one person with the same or similar copy/paste for the right half of their journal, It was long but basically the strategy of say if you are BD and find the assasain, block/jail him while you look for the MM etc..

within the last week not only haven&#39;t I seen that copypaste around, people look at me like I&#39;m crazy when I try and give those strategies. I got mocked by all 15 other players in one game, because after the drunk found the assasain, everyone thought not executing him on day 2 would be insanity. (which of course, basically made it so by day 3, we were exactly back to where we started, with  one less BD from the extra conversion the MM did).

I&#39;m aware there&#39;s a lot of newer players, and that coming from other social deduction games in which conversion isn&#39;t a core mechanic, ToL has a learning curve that people won&#39;t instantly grasp.

Does anyone have the copypaste of the strategy so that I can start putting it on my journals, to help educate the newer waves of people?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 17:55:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Copypastes strategies?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not wanting to force people into it, I’m wanting people to see the general concepts so that they are aware of them. Having basic knowledge of the game, executing an unseen every 3 days, is basically standing in place. I don’t think there’s any way to argue that slow and steady killing off of assasains or cult members, is actually going to end in a BD win.</p>
<p>It’s extremely simple math there, the unseen can’t kill if the assasain is roleblocked, they can’t convert if they already have all 3 groups filled. If you find the assasain day 2, and block him, the unseen can do nothing for the 3 days you can contain him. If you execute him, then a new assasain that you don’t know the identity of can kill freely, the mastermind can fill that slot back, and the unseen have exactly the same amount of members they had before the assasain was found.</p>
<p>My point is that I came to understand the strategy, because there was a long well written strategy that was either regularly pasted into people’s journals, or perhaps I just kept playing with the same guy, I would like to start copypasting that or a similar guide in my own journal, but I’m not as good at writing and I never thought to screencap it and I haven’t seen it in a long time. It isn’t forcing people to switch to that strategy, it is making them familiar enough with it that it isn’t a foreign language to them when someone suggests it in a game.</p>
<p>In the example I gave, the players eventually understood what I was talking about after I explained it to them in dead chat, but as it was their first time hearing that even suggested, it took 5 days in the game for the explanation to make sense to them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7600-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600.rss">Copypastes strategies?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Copypastes strategies?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aurelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I believe that you’re trying to force other playstyles that you don’t master upon yourself. which is bound to fail.<br>
why don’t you try?<br>
One thing is to have a very “convincing” Journal" Another is to have people actually comply<br>
For instance<br>
If you hear d2 someone got RBED, you might want to note that down in your log “occupied n1” so that they could ask.  in case he’s confirmed BD “is it true?” and he’d respond with yes.</p>
<p>To answer your question<br>
Experiment, And fine-tune your own playstyle. Don’t necessarily copy others, just try finding the BEST way you can play. and of course. enjoy playing <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smile.png?v=9" title=":smile:" class="emoji" alt=":smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 13:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7600-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600.rss">Copypastes strategies?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Copypastes strategies?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When I was first starting the game a couple weeks ago, most games had at least one person with the same or similar copy/paste for the right half of their journal, It was long but basically the strategy of say if you are BD and find the assasain, block/jail him while you look for the MM etc…</p>
<p>within the last week not only haven’t I seen that copypaste around, people look at me like I’m crazy when I try and give those strategies. I got mocked by all 15 other players in one game, because after the drunk found the assasain, everyone thought not executing him on day 2 would be insanity. (which of course, basically made it so by day 3, we were exactly back to where we started, with  one less BD from the extra conversion the MM did).</p>
<p>I’m aware there’s a lot of newer players, and that coming from other social deduction games in which conversion isn’t a core mechanic, ToL has a learning curve that people won’t instantly grasp.</p>
<p>Does anyone have the copypaste of the strategy so that I can start putting it on my journals, to help educate the newer waves of people?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7600-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/copypastes-strategies/7600.rss">Copypastes strategies?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
