<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class suggestion] The Insider</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102</link>
    <description>&gt;The Insider - Neutral Social?
Passive 1: Quality control - Immune to tampering at night. This includes, mind warp, frame, order, defile or similar ability&#39;s. 
Passive 2: Royal Blood - You may step up to be king
.
Day ability 1: External support - The targets next vote counts for 3 but it can&#39;t be changed. Can also work for voting execute or pardon on trial and can be used when anyone including you is on trial. Cannot be used on yourself (4 uses)
Day ability 2: External sabotage - The target votes for themselves and cannot undo their vote. Can be used on trial and makes their vote reversed. Exe to Pardon and Pardon to Exe, Abstains will turn into whatever you are voting for. (3 uses)
.
Note: Those ability&#39;s cannot be used on the king.
.
Night ability 1: Training record - Reveal your targets immunity&#39;s (Unlimited)
Night ability 2: Doge - Swap all visitors between yourself and your target. (Unlimited)
.
Goal: Be among the last 3 survivors (Like fool and Scorned the game can end anyway with more than 3 people leading to your loss)

Notes:
I wanted to create a Neutral survivor whose power was in the day rather than the night. The invest ability can be used to figure out what team people are on indirectly. Should probably mention that the immunity&#39;s are: Occupy immunity, Night immunity, Status immunity and Conversion immunity. That last one is given to the Prince and all Neutrals other than merc. At night you would use that information to figure out who to use Doge on. In the day you would use your abilitys to help the underdog and get more people killed.

I tried to make the social abilitys interesting by having it buff/nerf someone elses voting rather than letting your own votes be worth more. The day abilitys of this class might actually be better served on the Noble but I thought it would be cool to have neutrals with more day power.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 13:13:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Insider</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aurelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Decent idea :3 Happy Xmas!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 13:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23102-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102.rss">[Class suggestion] The Insider</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] The Insider</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>The Insider - Neutral Social?<br>
Passive 1: Quality control - Immune to tampering at night. This includes, mind warp, frame, order, defile or similar ability’s.<br>
Passive 2: Royal Blood - You may step up to be king<br>
.<br>
Day ability 1: External support - The targets next vote counts for 3 but it can’t be changed. Can also work for voting execute or pardon on trial and can be used when anyone including you is on trial. Cannot be used on yourself (4 uses)<br>
Day ability 2: External sabotage - The target votes for themselves and cannot undo their vote. Can be used on trial and makes their vote reversed. Exe to Pardon and Pardon to Exe, Abstains will turn into whatever you are voting for. (3 uses)<br>
.<br>
Note: Those ability’s cannot be used on the king.<br>
.<br>
Night ability 1: Training record - Reveal your targets immunity’s (Unlimited)<br>
Night ability 2: Doge - Swap all visitors between yourself and your target. (Unlimited)<br>
.<br>
Goal: Be among the last 3 survivors (Like fool and Scorned the game can end anyway with more than 3 people leading to your loss)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Notes:<br>
I wanted to create a Neutral survivor whose power was in the day rather than the night. The invest ability can be used to figure out what team people are on indirectly. Should probably mention that the immunity’s are: Occupy immunity, Night immunity, Status immunity and Conversion immunity. That last one is given to the Prince and all Neutrals other than merc. At night you would use that information to figure out who to use Doge on. In the day you would use your abilitys to help the underdog and get more people killed.</p>
<p>I tried to make the social abilitys interesting by having it buff/nerf someone elses voting rather than letting your own votes be worth more. The day abilitys of this class might actually be better served on the Noble but I thought it would be cool to have neutrals with more day power.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 23:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23102-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-insider/23102.rss">[Class suggestion] The Insider</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
