<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054</link>
    <description>**Note: Some of these classes might be outdated, so for people in the Golden Dragon SFoL please use the classcards provided in the SFoL&#39;s thread.**

I&#39;ve made some changes to the golden dragon class cards for whenever I host Golden Dragon 2, so I was hoping to get some feedback.

The main changes are:
* Most Golden Dragon classes have been nerfed.
* Accused, Prosecutor and Lawyer have been reworked.
* New NKs added: The Siren and The Collector
* New neutrals added: The rivals, the occultist and The Identity Thief
* Bounty Hunter has death immunity
* The Count can frame two people each night instead of 1 and starts with 1 use of Fate decided.
* EFoL notifications will be used. 
* Reptilians have been added, and will be the main scum faction.

Reptilians have been greatly changed from my original suggestion, so please give me your thoughts.

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;The Queen&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Unique Special, Unknown Alignment. Replaces the King.**
&gt; **Royal Audience (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection. The Queen can talk with all royals at night.
&gt; **Loyalty (Passive)** - If the starting Good Queen is executed on trial or killed by a Royal Guard, there won&#39;t be any trials the following day.
&gt; **The Royal Finger (Day)** - Put someone immediately on trial. This counts towards the trial limit. 2 uses.
&gt; **Heir (Day)** - Add or remove a player from the royal chat. If you are starting Queen you will also give or remove royal blood from them. - 3 uses if starting Queen, 1 otherwise. Can be used D1.
&gt; **Guards! (Night)** - Prevent all visits to a player. Can target yourself. 3 uses if starting Queen, 2 otherwise.
&gt; **Royal Decree (Night)** - Prevent a player from being accused tomorrow, and prevent any day abilities except your own from being used on them. 3 uses if starting Queen, 1 otherwise.
&gt; **Goal: Make sure your faction wins. If you are neutral, your goal is to survive.**

&gt; **Note:** Golden Dragon, Reptilian and Neutral Queen have the same abilities. Neutral Killers turn into the Psycho Queen. All neutrals will turn into Neutral Queen except for Neutral Killers and The Count.

&lt;big&gt;[color=orange]**The Golden Dragon**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
**Objective: Defeat the Cult/Unseen, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Bailiff[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Unique Golden Dragon, Investigative. Cannot be converted. Golden Dragon always start with a Bailiff**
&gt; **Interrogate (Day)** - Select a player. You will know who they visited last night. 2 uses.
&gt; **Investigate (Night)** - Check if a player is a member of the Reptilians. Players with eggs or hollow eggs will appear as Reptilians. Unlimited uses. 
&gt; [color=green]**Scale Removal (Night)**[/color] - Select a player, heal any eggs or venom they might have. 2 uses.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

&gt;**Convert immune**

----


&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Captain [/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Offensive. Converts into the Behemoth.**
&gt; **On Duty (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt;**Lead (Day)** - Select two players. Any targeted day abilities used on the first one will be redirected to the second one. Bypasses redirection immunity. Can target yourself. 2 uses.
&gt; **Command (Night)** - Select two players. Force the first player to target the second one. Can force a player to target you, but can&#39;t force them to target themselves. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Self Defense (Night)** - If you are attacked tonight prevent the attack and both you and your attackers will start bleeding and die in one day unless healed. 2 uses.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

---

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Elder[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Social. Converts into the Basilisk.**
&gt; **Moral Support (Day)** - Select a player. All their votes will count as two today. 2 uses.
&gt; **Elder&#39;s advice (Day)** - Today, your next vote for pardon will count as three (can be used during a trial). - 2 uses.
&gt; **Scold (Night)** - Prevent a player from voting tomorrow. Cannot target the Queen. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Words of Wisdom (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to the whole court. It will be delivered at the beginning of the day. 2 uses.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Executioner[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Unique, Golden Dragon, Killer. Converts into the Komodo.**
&gt; **Tenacity (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection
&gt; **Death Sentence (Day)** - Select a player. They cannot be healed and will lose all their immunities for the night (doesn&#39;t remove conversion immunity). 1 use.
&gt; **Execute (Night)** - Kill a player. Cannot be used until N3. 2 uses.
&gt; **Questionable Methods (Night)** - Select a player. If they are not GD they will start bleeding and die in one day unless healed. 1 use.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----


&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Gravekeeper[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Investigative. Converts into The Basilisk**
&gt; **Silent approach (Day)** - Stalk will give you extra information tonight. If a Killer, Offensive or Special Role visits your target you will get a message saying &quot;You saw a suspicious figure visit your target last night.&quot; 2 uses.
&gt; **Stalk (Night)** - Select a player. You will know who visits your target. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Exhume (Night)** - Select a dead player. You will know the classes that visited them on the night of their death. 2 uses. 
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----


&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Innkeeper[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Offensive. Converts into the Behemoth.**
&gt; **Busy man (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Special Mead (Day)** - Serve a special mead instead of beer tonight. Your night abilities will bypass occupy immunity tonight. 1 use.
&gt; **Special Ale (Day)** - Serve a special ale instead of beer tonight. Everyone occupied by your night abilities tonight will also be occupied the following night. 1 use.
&gt; **On the house! (Night)** - Give a free beer to a player, occupying them tonight. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Dinner Night (Night)** - Make a dinner at a player&#39;s room. Everyone that visits them tonight except yourself will be occupied. 2 uses. 
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Librarian[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Investigative. Converts into the Basilisk.**
&gt; **Hidden records (Day)** - Tonight, your record search ability can find murder records. If your target has ever visited someone on the night of their death, whether they killed them or not, you will get the following message: &quot;Your target has murder records.&quot; 1 use.
&gt; **Extensive research (Day)** - Tonight, your record search ability will also return the target&#39;s class type. 1 use.
&gt; **Record search (Night)** - Learn a player&#39;s records. Unlimited uses.
&gt; _Explanation:_
&gt; _There are three types of records: Medical records, Criminal records and Royal records. You will get one message for every type of record a player has. If a player has no records you will get the message. &quot;Your target has no records.&quot;_
&gt; _If your target has a healing ability, or if they have been affected by a healing ability before (whether it was required or not), you will get the following message: &quot;Your target has medical records.&quot;_
&gt; _If your target has an investigative ability, or if an investigative ability has been used on them you will get the following message: &quot;Your target has criminal records&quot;_
&gt; _If your target is a member of the Royal chat, or has ever been visited by a member of the Royal chat (including The Queen) you will get the following message: &quot;Your target has royal records.&quot;_
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Mage[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Support. Converts into the Komodo.**
&gt; **Ward (Day)** - Select a player. They will be immune to conversion. This effect ends if you die or are converted. - 1 use.
&gt; **Rewind (Night)** - Select a player and copy the effects of targeted abilities used on them the previous night. Doesn&#39;t copy self-targeted abilities, attacks, poison, bleeding, venom, conversion, investigative abilities and &quot;Rewind&quot;. Cannot be used on N1. - Unlimited uses. (Doesn&#39;t copy any abilities copied by &quot;Rewind&quot;. Also, if you copy an ability affected by a day ability such as On the House empowered by Special Mead, you will only copy the base ability and not the extra effects provided by the day ability). 
_Example: Medic uses Cure wounds on Ivo Bardolf on N1. Innkeeper also occupies Ivo Bardolf on N1. If mage uses rewind on Ivo Bardolf on N2, Ivo Bardolf would be healed and occupied again._
&gt; **Portal Trick (Night)** - Select a player. Everyone that tries to visit them tonight will be immune to occupation, redirection and visit prevention. 2 uses.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Medic[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Support. Converts into the Komodo.**
&gt; **Toxin Immunity (Passive)** - Immune to poison/bleeding/venom.
&gt; **Overtime (Day)** - The target of tonight&#39;s &quot;Cure wounds&quot; will also be healed the following night. (the extra heal doesn&#39;t count as a visit). 1 use.
&gt; **Double shift (Day)** - &quot;Cure wounds&quot; will target two players tonight. 1 use.
&gt; **Cure wounds (Night)** - Heal a player from attacks, poison, bleeding, eggs or venom. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Royal Guard[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Killer. Converts into the Komodo**
&gt; **Public Execution (Day)** - Sacrifice your life to kill a player in plain daylight. Cannot be used until Day 3. Cannot target the Queen. - 1 use.
&gt; **Duel (Night)** - Duel a player tonight. If they would attack someone, the attack will be prevented and they will start bleeding and die in 1 day unless healed. - Unlimited uses. 
&gt; **Coup (Night)** - Sacrifice your life to kill the Queen, bypassing her Guards! ability. Cannot be used until Night 3. - 1 use.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**
----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=orange]The Spy[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Golden Dragon, Social. Converts into the Basilisk.**
&gt; **Secret Code (Day)** - Select a non-royal player. You and said player will be able to speak to each other on a private day and night chat for as long as you both live. - 1 use. _(Cannot target Queen. This ability will fail if used on a player in the royal chat. If you or your target ever get into the royal chat, Secret Code&#39;s chat will end)._ 
&gt; **Spread Gossip (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to another player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Hearsay (Night)** - Select a player. They will be able to send you a message tonight. 4 uses.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Reptilians and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&lt;big&gt;[color=darkgreen]The Reptilians[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
Reptilians are a slow but powerful faction. Reptilian classes become stronger the longer they can stay alive. While there are only three reptilian classes that players can convert to, these classes can change their abilities to adapt to the current situation. This, combined with eggs that make people appear as Reptilians to investigators and Venom, a new status effect that works like a slower poison but disables day abilities, make Reptilians a very sneaky faction. 

Reptilian games start with a Matriarch and one random Reptilian. There can only be a maximum of 3 reptilians at a time

----

&gt;&lt;big&gt;[color=darkgreen]The Basilisk[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Reptilian Social, Converts from Social and Investigative classes.**
&gt; **Camouflage (Passive)** - The first time each player tries to investigate you they will be occupied.
&gt; **Evolve (Passive)** - You start with 2 evolution points. At the end of each night, you will gain 1 evolution point. At any point in the game you might DM the host to exchange your evolution points for abilities. (You cannot buy the same ability more than once. You can only have a maximum of 2 night and 2 day abilities, if you were going to buy a third day/night ability it would replace one of the older ones)
&gt; **These are the abilities the Basilisk can buy:**
&gt; **1 Evolution point:**
&gt; * **Lurk (Night)** - Select a player. You will know who visits them and who they visit. - 3 uses.
&gt; * **Mind Reading (Night)** - Select a player. They will be able to send you a message tonight. - 3 uses.
&gt; * **Hiss (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to another player. - 3 uses.
&gt; * **Influence (Day)** - Select a player. All their votes will count as two today. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Muting venom (Night)** - Prevent a player from voting tomorrow. Only your target player will be notified about this. Cannot target the Queen. - 3 uses.
&gt; 
&gt; **2 Evolution points:**
&gt; * **Crocodile Tears (Day)** - Today, your next vote for pardon will count as three. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Thorough Investigation (Night)** - Find out a player&#39;s records including murder records and the class type of a player. - 3 uses.
&gt; * **Reptilian Echoes (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to the whole court. It will be delivered at the beginning of the day. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Reptilian Link (Day)** - Select a non-royal player. You and said player will be able to speak to each other on a private day and night chat for as long as you both live. - 1 use. _(Cannot target Queen. This ability will fail if used on a player with royal blood. If you or your target ever get royal blood, the chat will end)._
&gt; 
&gt; **3 Evolution points:**
&gt; * **Petrifying Gaze (Night)** - Attack a player. If they die, they will turn into stone and their logs and class will be hidden. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Crippling Screech (Night)** - Attack all players affected by venom. - 1 use.
&gt; * **Venomous Skin (Night)** - Select a player. Anyone that accuses them of treason tomorrow will become envenomed and die in 3 days unless healed. - 2 uses.
&gt; **Goal: Defeat the Golden Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt;&lt;big&gt;[color=darkgreen]The Behemoth[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Reptilian Offensive, Converts from Offensive classes.**
&gt; **Hardened Shell (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Evolve (Passive)** - You start with 2 evolution points. At the end of each night, you will gain 1 evolution point. At any point in the game you might DM the host to exchange your evolution points for abilities. (You cannot buy the same ability more than once. You can only have a maximum of 2 night and 2 day abilities, if you were going to buy a third day/night ability it would replace one of the older ones)
&gt; **These are the abilities that Behemoth can buy:**
&gt; 
&gt; **1 Evolution point:**
&gt; * **Paralyzing Venom (Night)** - Occupy a player. -  3 uses.
&gt; * **Mind Control (Night)** - Force a player to target another. Can force them to target you, but cannot force them to target themselves. - 2 uses.
&gt;* **Lead (Day)** - Select two players. Any targeted day abilities used on the first one will be redirected to the second one. Bypasses redirection immunity. Can target yourself. - 2 uses.
&gt; 
&gt; **2 Evolution points:**
&gt; * **Constrict (Night)** - Select a player. Occupy everyone that visits them except Reptilians. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Permavenom (Day)** - Apply a permanent venom to a player. Said player will be unable to use day abilities until healed. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **New Skin (Night)** - Select a player. If they die tonight they will appear as a class of your choice. 2 uses.
&gt; 
&gt; **3 Evolution points:**
&gt; * **Iron Shell (Night)** - All reptilians will be immune to death, occupation, redirection and visit prevention tonight. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Tooth and nail (Night)** - Occupy a player through immunity tonight and envenom them. The venom will kill them in two nights unless healed. Envenomed players are unable to use day abilities. 2 uses.
&gt; * **Premature hatch (Day)** - If the matriarch lays an egg tonight, it will hatch immediately unless healed. 2 uses.
&gt; **Goal: Defeat the Golden Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt;&lt;big&gt;[color=darkgreen]The Komodo[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Reptilian Killer, Converts from Support and Killer classes.**
&gt; **Reptilian blood (Passive)** - Immune to poison, bleeding and venom.
&gt; **Evolve (Passive)** - You start with 2 evolution points. At the end of each night, you will gain 1 evolution point. At any point in the game you might DM the host to exchange your evolution points for abilities. (You cannot buy the same ability more than once. You can only have a maximum of 2 night and 2 day abilities, if you were going to buy a third day/night ability it would replace one of the older ones)
&gt; **These are the abilities that Komodo can buy:**
&gt; **1 Evolution point each:**
&gt; * **Delayed Pain (Night)** - Select a player and copy the effects of targeted abilities used on them the previous night. Doesn&#39;t copy attacks, conversion, poison/bleeding/venom, self-targeted abilities or investigative abilities. Has the same mechanics and restrictions as the Mage&#39;s &quot;Rewind&quot;. - 3 uses.
&gt; * **Death Sentence (Day)** - Select a player. They cannot be healed tonight and will lose all their immunities for the night (doesn&#39;t remove conversion immunity). 1 use.
&gt; * **Recovery (Night)** - Heal yourself or another reptilian from attacks, poison/bleeding/venom. 3 uses.
&gt; 
&gt; **2 Evolution points each:**
&gt; * **Egg Guardian (Night)** - Eggs and hollow eggs cannot be destroyed tonight. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Confusing Venom (Night)** - Select two players. All players targeting one of them will be forced to target the other. Bypasses redirection immunity. Can target yourself. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Venomous bite (Day)** - Envenom a player. They will die in three days unless healed. Envenomed players cannot use day abilities until its healed. 2 uses.
&gt; 
&gt; **3 Evolution points each:**
&gt; * **Fatal Fang (Day)** - The target will be afflicted with a fatal venom that will disable their day abilities and kill them in 1 day. Cannot be healed.-  1 use.
&gt; * **Noxious Fumes (Night)** - Select a player. Anyone that visits them tonight will become envenomed and die in two nights unless healed. Envenomed players cannot use day abilities. Can target yourself. - 2 uses.
&gt; * **Hollow egg (Night)** - Lay a hollow egg inside a player. When the matriarch uses hatch, your egg will hatch as well. Hollow eggs will always kill the player instead of converting them, and don&#39;t count towards the Matriarch&#39;s egg limit. This ability counts as an attack. There can only be 2 hollow eggs at the same time, shared between all Komodos. - 2 uses.
&gt;
&gt; **Goal: Defeat the Golden Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&gt;&lt;big&gt;[color=darkgreen]The Matriarch[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Unique Special, Reptilian**
&gt; **Maternal Love (Passive)** - The matriarch cannot be occupied while attempting to hatch her eggs. When the Matriarch dies, the oldest Reptilian will lose all their current abilities and turn into the new matriarch.
&gt; **Premature Hatch(Passive)**- If the matriarch dies before day 3 all her eggs will hatch automatically.
&gt; **Quick Growth (Day)** - Give a player 1 evolution point. 2 uses, shared.
&gt; **Lay Egg (Night)** - Lay an egg inside someone. They will not be notified about it. Can only have a maximum of 2 eggs at the same time. - Unlimited uses.
&gt; _(Players with eggs inside will appear as Reptilians when faction checked. The egg will be destroyed if the target is healed. Laying an egg counts as an attack for abilities like Duel and Self Defense)._
&gt; **Hatch (Night)** - Hatch all eggs and hollow eggs, turning the players into Reptilians. If a player is conversion immune they will die instead. There can only be a maximum of 2 more reptilians at a time (3 reptilians total with the matriarch), if a player would be converted while having the maximum number of reptilians, said player dies instead. - Unlimited uses. (This ability counts as a non-targeted ability, so it will bypass visit prevention and abilities that affect visiting players. If an egg is destroyed the same night you use hatch the target will not be killed/converted. Hatch will not kill death immune players)._
&gt; **Goal: Defeat the Golden Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

----

&lt;big&gt;[color=gray]Neutrals (Non NK)[/color]&lt;/big&gt;

&gt;&lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Accused[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt;**Unique Neutral, Offensive. Always spawns with Lawyer and Prosecutor**
&gt; **Human Resources (Passive)** - Immune to poison, bleeding, venom, occupation and redirection. 
&gt; **Missing record (Passive)** - Your visits are hidden from investigators other than the Prosecutor. You are allied to a random faction (GD or The Reptilians). If you are allied to the GD and executed on trial or killed by a Royal Guard&#39;s &quot;Public Execution&quot;, all the members of the Reptilians will gain one extra use of their limited use abilities. (You always appear as neutral to faction checks). If you are allied to the Reptilians and executed on trial the day will not end.
&gt; **Suspicious activities (Night)** - Occupy a player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Sketchy reunion (Night)** - Target a player, occupy all members of your rival faction attempting to visit your target. 3 uses.
&gt; **Goal: Survive to see you rival faction lose.**

----
&gt;&lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Bounty Hunter[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt;**Unique Neutral, Offensive**
&gt; **Your last job (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night. You will be given a random target at the beginning of the game.  If your target dies on trial or is killed by anyone else you will commit suicide the following night.
&gt; 
&gt; &gt;_**Notes**: Your target can be any class from any faction except for the Bailiff, the Queen or any class with permanent death immunity. A message will appear in chat telling everyone that there is a bounty hunter trying to kill said player, and there will be a small symbol next to their name that everyone can see. (Example: &quot;There is a bounty for John Smith&#39;s [12] head!&quot;)_
&gt; 
&gt; **A new life (Passive)** - One day after you successfully kill your target you will collect your bounty. After you collect your bounty you will win and leave the castle along with a player of your choice (except the Queen). (Leaving the castle is the same as dying).
&gt; 
&gt; **Intimidate (Day)** - Select a player. For the next two nights, if they try to visit your target they will be prevented. You can also use this ability on your target to occupy them through immunity tonight. 3 uses.
&gt; 
&gt; **The Perfect Chance (Night)** - Attempt to kill your target. If your target is still alive after using this ability, you will commit suicide. 1 use. 
&gt; 
&gt; **This is MY job (Night)** - Your target will be immune to death tonight and cannot be accused for treason tomorrow. You will also heal any poison or bleeding on them. 3 uses.
&gt;
&gt;**Goal**: Kill your target and collect the bounty.

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Cleric[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral, Support.**
&gt; **Sanctuary (Passive)** - People trying to visit you cannot be occupied or redirected, and their visit will be hidden from investigators. If they are an attacker, their attack will bypass healing.
&gt; **Brotherhood (Passive)** - You are immune to poison/bleeding/venom. If you would be attacked at night, redirect the attack to one of your visitors except the attacker, bypassing redirection immunity. If only the attacker visits you, you will die.
&gt; **Blessing (Day)** - Select a player. If they visit you tonight they will get a blessing that lasts for two days. The blessing makes the player immune to conversion, hides their visits and makes them appear not suspicious to investigators. 2 uses. 
&gt; **Mark of Light (Night)** - Heal a player from attacks and poison/bleeding/venom. If you are attacked tonight, the attack will be redirected to said player, bypassing redirection immunity. 2 uses. (Sanctuary will apply to attacks redirected this way, meaning they will bypass healing and be healed from investigators).
&gt; **Circle of Healing (Night)** - Heal everyone that visits you tonight from attacks and poison/bleeding/venom. Unlimited uses.
&gt;
&gt; **Goal:** Survive

----

&gt;&lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Diseased[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt;**Neutral, Offensive**
&gt; **Chronic disease (Passive)** - At the beginning of each day (starting from day 2) if you are not poisoned, bleeding or envenomed you will become poisoned. You will die in 2 days unless healed. 
&gt; **Sympathy (Passive)** Immune to death and occupation.
&gt;**Insurance (Day)** - Anyone that tries to heal you tonight will be immune to death and occupation. 3 uses.
&gt; **Pity (Night)** - Select a player. Anyone trying to visit said player will visit you instead. Unlimited uses. 
&gt; **Expunge (Night)** - Everyone who visits you tonight will die. If at least one person dies this way you will be healed of any poison/bleeding/venom. 2 uses.
&gt;
&gt;**Goal: Survive**.

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Good Twin[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral, Support. Always spawns with The Evil Twin.**
&gt; **Special Bond (Passive)** - You and your twin have a private chat. If your twin dies, you die as well.
&gt; **The Good Gene (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation. You will appear as GD to investigative results.
&gt; **Swap (Day)** - Swap class cards with your twin for the rest of the game. 1 use. (You will become the evil twin and the evil twin will become the good Twin. All limited use abilities will keep the same number of uses).
&gt; **Cleanup (Night)** - Make your twin occupy immune and hide their visits from investigators. 3 uses.
&gt; **Smart Protector (Night)** - Heal your twin from any poison/bleeding/venom, and occupy anyone trying to visit him. 3 uses
&gt; **Goal: You win as long as your twin achieves their goal, even if you are dead.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Identity Thief[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral Special**
&gt; **Sneaky (Passive)** - Immune to death for the first 3 nights or until you successfully steal someone&#39;s identity, whichever happens first.
&gt; **Steal Identity (Night)** - Attack a player except the Queen. If the attack is successful, their class and logs will be hidden and you will steal their class, abilities and goal. Any limited abilities you steal will keep the same number of uses they had before. - Unlimited uses 
&gt;&gt;_Additional notes:_
&gt;&gt;_(You lose this ability after successfully stealing someone&#39;s identity. You will not steal royal blood. If you kill a Reptilian you will start with the same amount of evolution points they had, you won&#39;t know who your teammates are and won&#39;t join them in night chat, but you do not count towards the convert limit. If you kill the Matriarch the oldest Reptilian will transform into the Matriarch and you will steal the abilities of the Reptilian that transformed instead. If you steal the identity of a Lawyer or Good Twin you will know who your teammate is but won&#39;t join them in night chat. If you steal the identity of a Rival or Prosecutor you will know who your target is. If you steal the identity of the Accused the Prosecutor will win and Lawyer will lose and commit suicide. If you steal the identity of a Siren&#39;s minion you will keep the goal they had before conversion instead)._
&gt;
&gt; **Goal: Steal someone&#39;s identity and complete their original goal.** 

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Lawyer[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt;**Unique Neutral, Support. Always spawns with Accused and Prosecutor**
&gt; **Restless (Passive)** - Immune to occupation. If the accused dies you will commit suicide the next night.
&gt; **Confidentiality agreement (Passive)** - You know who the Accused is. You and the accused share a private chat.
&gt; **Burn the evidence (Night)** - Prevent everyone except the Prosecutor from visiting the Accused tonight. - 4 uses. 
&gt; **Bribe (Night)** - Select a player and offer them a deal. If they accept, you will bribe them and prevent all visits on them tonight. Bribed players will be forced to pardon the Accused as long as you are alive (Doesn&#39;t work on The Queen or The Lawyer. Doesn&#39;t work on players that have already been blackmailed by the Prosecutor). - 3 uses.
&gt; **Goal: Make sure the accused achieves their goal.**

----
&gt; 
&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Occultist[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral Social**
&gt; **Demonic Shield (Passive)** - You are immune to death during the first two nights. 
&gt; **Public Sacrifice (Passive)** - If you are put up on trial, you will explode and die, bleeding the first two players that accused you and instantly ending the day. They will die the next night unless healed.
&gt; **The Mark (Day)** - You will appear suspicious to investigative results tonight. - 2 uses.
&gt; **Dark Thoughts (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to another player. - 2 uses.
&gt; **Mass Hysteria (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to the whole court. It will be delivered at the start of the next day. - 1 use.
&gt; **Goal: Get yourself on trial**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Prosecutor[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt;**Unique Neutral, Investigative. Always spawns with Lawyer and Accused.**
&gt; **Restless (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Trial Knowledge (Passive)** - You know who the Accused is. 
&gt; **The Trial Begins (Day)** - Instantly put the Accused on trial. Cannot be used until Day 4. - 1 use. This doesn&#39;t count towards the Trial limit.
&gt; **Gather Evidence (Night)** - You will know who the Accused visits and which ability they used. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Blackmail (Night)** - Select a player and offer them a deal. If they refuse, they will be unable to perform their night action. Blackmailed players are forced to vote execute on the Accused while you are alive. (Doesn&#39;t work on The Queen or The Lawyer. Doesn&#39;t work on players that have already been bribed by the lawyer) - 3 uses.
&gt; **Goal: Make sure the accused dies.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Rival[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral Social. Rivals always spawn in pairs.**
&gt; **Rivalry (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and redirection. 
&gt; **Nemesis (Passive)** - You know who the other Rival is. If you achieve your goal, you will gain unlimited uses of Fake Rumors. 
&gt; **Evade (Day)** - Become immune to death tonight. 2 uses. Can be used D1.
&gt; **Fake Rumors (Night)** - Send an anonymous message to another player. - 1 use.
&gt; **Frame (Night)** - Frame your rival, making them look suspicious to investigative abilities. - 2 uses.
&gt; **Goal: Live to see the other Rival die.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Shaman[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; Unique, Neutral, Offensive.
&gt; **Meditation (Passive)** - Immune to death and occupation.
&gt; **Pact (Passive)** - You will commit suicide on Night 6. This cannot be prevented in any way.
&gt; **Seance (Day)** - Discover a player&#39;s class type. - 2 uses.
&gt; **The Evil Eye (Day)** - Can only be used during a trial. If the person on trial is pardoned, they will commit suicide tonight. (suicide can be healed and won&#39;t kill death immune players). - 1 use.
&gt; **Soul Link (Night)** - Select two players. If one of them dies tonight, the other will commit suicide. (suicide can be healed and won&#39;t kill death immune players). - 3 uses.
&gt; **Voodoo Ritual (Night)** - Force a player to target another. Bypasses occupy immunity. - 3 uses.
&gt; **Goal: Survive.**

----

&lt;big&gt;[color=gray]Neutral Killers[/color]&lt;/big&gt;

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[Color=gray]The Beast Lord[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral, Killer.**
&gt; **Survival Instincts (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night.
&gt; **Lion Form (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Morph (Day)** - Change your second passive to a different one. You will keep that passive until you change it again. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-day cooldown. Can be used on day 1.
&gt; &gt; Available passives:
&gt; &gt; * **Lion Form (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection. 
&gt; &gt; * **Spider Form (Passive)** - You are immune to poison/bleeding/venom. Doesn&#39;t heal you if you change to this passive while you were already poisoned/bleeding/envenomed. You will be told if someone attempts to poison/bleeding/envenom you.
&gt; &gt; * **Chameleon Form (Passive)** - Your visits are hidden from investigators.
&gt; &gt; * **Owl Form (Passive)** - You are unaffected by day abilities, except for poison, venom or bleeding. You will be told when someone tries to use a day ability on you.
&gt; &gt; * **Eagle Form (Passive)** - You will know who visits you every night. 
&gt; 
&gt; **Rampage (Day)** - Your night ability will be instantly available tonight if its on cooldown. 1 use.
&gt; **Tiger companion (Night)** - Kill two players. Unlimited uses, but has a one-night cooldown.
&gt; **Tame (Night)** - Change your first night ability to a different one. You will keep that ability until you change it again. Unlimited uses.
&gt; &gt; Available night abilities:
&gt; &gt; * **Tiger companion (Night)** - Kill two players. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.
&gt; &gt; * **Rhinoceros companion (Night)** - Kill a player. Bypasses healing and death immunity. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown. 
&gt; &gt; * **Crocodile companion (Night)** - Kill a player and anyone that visits them. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown. 
&gt; &gt; * **Bear companion (Night)** - Kill everyone visiting you. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.
&gt; &gt; * **Snake Companion (Night)** - Envenom up to two players. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. Envenomed players cannot use day abilities.  Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.
&gt;
&gt;**Goal: Defeat the main factions and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Collector[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral Killer**
&gt; **Perseverance (Passive)** - Immune to death once.
&gt; **Analyze (Day)** - Select a player, you get a pairing of class types. Their class type will be one of the two. The pairings are Killer/Offensive, Support/Social and Special/Investigative. - Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Exploit Weakness (Day)** - Guess a player&#39;s exact class. If you guess it right, they will be killed immediately. (Can&#39;t be used on Queen). Players killed this way will also grant collect&#39;s bonus - 2 uses.
&gt; **Collect (Night)** - Kill a player. - Unlimited uses.
&gt; You will get a permanent buff the first time you kill a player of a specific class type:
&gt; * **Kill an offensive role:** You will become immune to occupation and redirection. 
&gt; * **Kill a support role:** You will become immune to poison/bleeding/venom. Perseverance now makes you immune to death permanently.
&gt; * **Kill a killer role**: &quot;Collect&quot; now bypasses healing.
&gt; * **Kill an investigative role:** Analyze now gives you the target&#39;s exact class.
&gt; * **Kill a social role**: Gain 2 extra uses of &quot;Exploit Weakness&quot;. When you use &quot;Exploit weakness&quot; you can guess two classes instead of one. If the target player is any of those classes they will die.
&gt; * **Kill a special role:** When you first get this buff, choose a class. You will appear as that class to investigators. Also hides your visits from investigators. 
&gt; * **Complete all other quests:** &quot;Collect&quot; can now target two players.
&gt;
&gt;**Goal: Defeat the main factions and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.**


----

&gt;&lt;big&gt;[Color=gray]The Count[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt;**Neutral, Social. (Has neutral killer goal and can&#39;t spawn with a neutral killer)**
&gt;**Tyranny (Passive)** - At any point in the game, you can DM the host to publicly reveal yourself as the Count. If you do this, all your votes and accusations will count as three.
&gt;**Resolve (Passive)** - Immune to death and occupation at night. You will appear as GD to faction checks.
&gt;**Mimic (Day)** - Select any ability from a non-killing Golden Dragon class and use it. If its a night ability, it will be used tonight instead (it will not count as visiting). 4 uses.
&gt;**Fate decided (Day)** - Kill a player in plain daylight.  1 use, you gain 1 extra use each time a member of the Golden Dragon is executed on trial. 
&gt;**Sow Discord (Night)** - Select up to two players and make them appear suspicious to investigative results. Unlimited uses.
&gt;**Political Backlash (Night)** - Select two players. If the first one would be executed on trial, the second one will die instead. Can target yourself. 2 uses.
&gt;**Goal: Defeat the main factions and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.**

**Note:** If the Count steps up he will turn into a Psycho Queen, since he is technically a Neutral Killer.

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Evil Twin[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral, Killer. Always spawns with The Good Twin**
&gt; **Special Bond (Passive)** - You and your twin can communicate at night. If your twin dies at night, his killer will be revealed to you.
&gt; **The Evil Gene (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night.
&gt; **Slash (Night)** - Kill a player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Psycho protector (Night)** - Protect your twin tonight, healing any poison/bleeding/venom effects on him and making him night immune. Everyone who visits your twin tonight will die. 3 uses.
&gt;**Goal: Defeat the main factions and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]The Psycho Queen[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Unique Special, Unknown Alignment. Replaces the King.**
&gt; **Royal Audience (Passive)** - You are immune to death, occupation and redirection. The Queen can talk with all royals at night.
&gt; **The Royal Finger (Day)** - Put someone immediately on trial. This counts towards the trial limit. 2 uses.
&gt; **Heir (Day)** - Select a player and give them Royal Blood, or remove it if they already have it. 1 use.
&gt; **Guards!** - Kill a player. Unlimited uses.
&gt;**Goal: Defeat the main factions and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.**


&gt;**Crowned from Neutral Killers or The Baron.**

----

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=Gray]The Siren[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral Killer**
&gt; **Charm (Passive)** - You are immune to death for the first 3 nights or until you convert your first minion, whatever happens first.
&gt; **Siren&#39;s song (Passive)** - You and your minion can speak at night. If you would die at night (including death by poison/bleeding/venom), your minion will die in your place.
&gt; **Siren&#39;s Gaze (Day)** - Select a player. If they can be converted you will know their class type. - 4 uses.
&gt; **Lure (Night)** - Select a player, if they are a convertible GD class you will convert them into a minion. They will keep their previous abilities, but their goal will change to &quot;Make sure the Siren wins.&quot;. If you already have a minion, your current minion will die (this cannot be healed or prevented in any way) - 3 uses. You will not lose a charge of this ability unless a player is converted.
&gt; **Attack Order (Night)** - Send your minion to attack a player, in addition to their chosen night action. If you don&#39;t have a minion you will attack them yourself - Unlimited uses.
&gt;**Goal:** Defeat the main factions and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:57:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ohey you’re alive</p>
<p>at least this means I have more time to prep</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/99</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-99</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah we want luxy to co-host because we do not want them in the game (<img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-98</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll co-host</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/97</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-97</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bumping since I made slight balance changes, specially to reptilians. And also to let people know that I’m looking for a cohost, mainly for vote counts since I will probably be less active than usual.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/96</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-96</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seems about right. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/ok_hand.png?v=9" title=":ok_hand:" class="emoji" alt=":ok_hand:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/95</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 20:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-95</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, in that case then I will just follow my heart and make 5 occultists guaranteed to spawn every game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/94</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 20:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-94</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Psycho, psycho but already established that feedback is meh…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/93</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 20:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-93</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>bumping this since GD2 is getting closer and I need feedback</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/92</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 20:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-92</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I made some changes to some classes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Captain has a new Day ability: Lead</li>
<li>Executioner’s Death Sentence removes all of a player’s immunities for one night (except conversion), including poison/bleeding immunity.</li>
<li>Gravekeeper Exhume was changed since it made no sense with the new FoL notification system.</li>
<li>Royal Guard’s duel no longer makes Royal Guard bleed. Instead it only bleeds the attacker (Royal Guard isn’t notified whether his duel works or not).</li>
<li>Accused, Lawyer and Prosecutor were reworked (again) since some of their abilities don’t work with the new notification system. Hopefully it works this time.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/91</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 05:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>also I would need to change lawyer and prosecutor since they cant really fake an occupation with new notification system</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/90</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 21:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>have to change gravekeeper’s exhume then probably</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/89</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 19:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i like games that aren’t overwhelmingly townsided<br>
so yeah, EFoL notifcations for the win</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/88</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Question, would you guys prefer old notification system on this or the new one?<br>
Some classes might need balance if we go the new one.</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-type="regular" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="4aebf28262df4c21d55f51f5529d1929">Old notification system (every class gets night resuls)</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="039eed28b6626e32fa7f37da122e1684">New notification system (EFoL)</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/87</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also, reptilians can completely disable a RG’s public execution with their venom which could help a bit when fake claiming it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/86</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While the dayvig is too confirmable it is also very risky since it kills the Royal Guard as well, so it might not always be a good idea to use it as soon as its available. Forcing a Royal Guard claim to use it just to confirm themselves could end up in GD losing 2 members at once, so I think royal guard is fine without more restrictions.</p>
<p>Ive also made most other classes except social ones more fake claimable, and even then there are scum roles that are able to fake claim otherwise confirmable roles like the Spy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/85</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 16:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been toying with this idea and I’d like your thoughts on it, <a class="mention" href="/u/psychoneirik">@psychoneirik</a>. Right now the Royal Guard is essentially the GD equivalent of a Knight, but it’s too risky to fake-claim as its dayvig is too easily confirm-able. So what is your opinion about adding an additional requirement to it such as requiring the Royal Guard to successfully duel a player, or even be given Royal Blood previously in order to use Public Execution?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/84</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 12:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/83</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also I added another NK “The Collector”, to kinda help counter mass-claiming.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/82</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess I should make him unique for balance reasons. 6 potential night kills with no guilt mechanic on BD is scary.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/81</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Blizer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, thats interesting. I just saw.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/80</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-80</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was thinking of making him not unique to make it a fake claimable role, but thinking about it it could probably be too chaotic having 2 BD classes with up to 3 kills each.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/79</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s no longer unique</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/78</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Blizer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since its unique, plus its less confirmable, he should be able to keep the immunity, because it fits thematically. He is based around trying to be judge jury and executioner on people he believes that are agansit the GD. hes supposed to be unrelenting in a way and aswell, he takes the prince slot for GD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/77</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also Im thinking whether to keep or remove his occupation immunity. Suggestions?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/76</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 19:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Golden Dragon 2 class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I changed the Executioner so it is now fake claimable. While it might be more boring than the old one, it is now less confirmable.  Also executioner is no longer unique and death sentence no longer notifies the target.<br>
Feedback or suggestions are appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054/75</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 19:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-69054-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/golden-dragon-2-class-cards/69054.rss">Golden Dragon 2 class cards</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
