<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Necromancer - (Neutral Killer)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-necromancer-neutral-killer/75663</link>
    <description>**The Necromancer (Neutral Killer)** This is a neutral killer centered around the idea of creating an army of undead. The zombies themselves are pretty bad and die easily but are still better than nothing. They can be used to keep the necromancer alive at night and also to create distractions to disrupt the main factions&#39; investigations or heals. And in the lategame, they can also be used to take control of the court if there are enough of them. The undead have very limited communication between each other so will often act stupidly or eratically. 

**Passive:**
Death immune on the first night.

**Day Ability 1:**
Necrosis: Cause a player to bleed (2 uses)

**Day Ability 2:**
Telepathic control: Telepathically send a message to all zombies (3 uses)

**Night Ability 1:**
Curse: Attack a player. If they die, they will be resurected as a zombie. (1 use)

**Night Ability 2:**
Resurect: Visit a player. If they die, they will be resurected as a zombie. If they do not die, regain 1 use of &quot;curse&quot;. (infinite uses) 

**Comments:**
Resurection is NOT a conversion, and thus convert-immune targets can become zombies. When resurected, a zombie is not told who the necromancer is or who the other zombies are. Also, if a knight becomes a zombie, they will keep their &quot;armoured&quot; passive if they still have it. Finally, the necromancer is given helpful icons to remind him of who he has zombified (like the sorc&#39;s bomb icons) Now on to the abilities of the zombie:

**Zombie (Neutral Killer)** This is only spawned when the necromancer resurects someone. Its goal is to make the necromancer win. If the necromancer dies, all zombies die the following morning. 

**Passives:**
Undead: Immune to bleeding. If killed during the night, they will appear as their original class pre-resurection. If killed during the day they will appear as a zombie.

**Day ability 1:**
Telepathic message: telepathically send a message to the necromancer; he will know who sent it. (1 use)

**Day Ability 2:**
Give life-force: Sacrifice yourself this night in order to heal the necromancer and give him one additional use of &quot;Curse&quot;. (1 use)

**Night Ability 1:**
Defend: Protect a player, giving your life to prevent the attack. (note: you do not kill the attacker, unlike the knight&#39;s similar skill; the &quot;armoured&quot; passive will prevent the first blocked attack if the zombie has it). Will not work on a target the necromancer is visiting (same as the sorc not attacking death immune people) (infinite uses)

**Night Ability 2:**
Moan: Become occupy/redirect immune for tonight and redirect target player to you. Will not work on the necromancer. (infinite uses)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 21:32:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-necromancer-neutral-killer/75663.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Necromancer - (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Random_Strategy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Necromancer (Neutral Killer)</strong> This is a neutral killer centered around the idea of creating an army of undead. The zombies themselves are pretty bad and die easily but are still better than nothing. They can be used to keep the necromancer alive at night and also to create distractions to disrupt the main factions’ investigations or heals. And in the lategame, they can also be used to take control of the court if there are enough of them. The undead have very limited communication between each other so will often act stupidly or eratically.</p>
<p><strong>Passive:</strong><br>
Death immune on the first night.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1:</strong><br>
Necrosis: Cause a player to bleed (2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong><br>
Telepathic control: Telepathically send a message to all zombies (3 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1:</strong><br>
Curse: Attack a player. If they die, they will be resurected as a zombie. (1 use)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2:</strong><br>
Resurect: Visit a player. If they die, they will be resurected as a zombie. If they do not die, regain 1 use of “curse”. (infinite uses)</p>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong><br>
Resurection is NOT a conversion, and thus convert-immune targets can become zombies. When resurected, a zombie is not told who the necromancer is or who the other zombies are. Also, if a knight becomes a zombie, they will keep their “armoured” passive if they still have it. Finally, the necromancer is given helpful icons to remind him of who he has zombified (like the sorc’s bomb icons) Now on to the abilities of the zombie:</p>
<p><strong>Zombie (Neutral Killer)</strong> This is only spawned when the necromancer resurects someone. Its goal is to make the necromancer win. If the necromancer dies, all zombies die the following morning.</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
Undead: Immune to bleeding. If killed during the night, they will appear as their original class pre-resurection. If killed during the day they will appear as a zombie.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability 1:</strong><br>
Telepathic message: telepathically send a message to the necromancer; he will know who sent it. (1 use)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 2:</strong><br>
Give life-force: Sacrifice yourself this night in order to heal the necromancer and give him one additional use of “Curse”. (1 use)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1:</strong><br>
Defend: Protect a player, giving your life to prevent the attack. (note: you do not kill the attacker, unlike the knight’s similar skill; the “armoured” passive will prevent the first blocked attack if the zombie has it). Will not work on a target the necromancer is visiting (same as the sorc not attacking death immune people) (infinite uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2:</strong><br>
Moan: Become occupy/redirect immune for tonight and redirect target player to you. Will not work on the necromancer. (infinite uses)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-necromancer-neutral-killer/75663/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-necromancer-neutral-killer/75663/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 03:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-75663-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-necromancer-neutral-killer/75663.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Necromancer - (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
