<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Giving NK&#39;s more information based tools</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/giving-nks-more-information-based-tools/41599</link>
    <description>Right now Possessor is my favorite NK. This is because the Possessor&#39;s primary and secondary night Ability&#39;s give the Possessor lots of Information being able to hear whispers, learn exact classes and reading others logs. While I don&#39;t think that the other NK&#39;S need anything quite as strong as the poss for information gathering I do think there are ways to make both other NK&#39;S more focused around using Information to trick people.

Reaper - no new abilitys. I simply want him to be able to read the journal of reaped players and possablely also be able to edit them. I&#39;d start with just reading them and add in editing them if Reaper starts to fall behind.

Sorcerer - Make one of her day Ability&#39;s Reveal the classes that visit target target player (possablely herself). Probably the one that hides visits.

These changes would not be that big on their own but it does let both classes open up their claimspace while not breaking them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 18:54:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/giving-nks-more-information-based-tools/41599.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Giving NK&#39;s more information based tools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right now Possessor is my favorite NK. This is because the Possessor’s primary and secondary night Ability’s give the Possessor lots of Information being able to hear whispers, learn exact classes and reading others logs. While I don’t think that the other NK’S need anything quite as strong as the poss for information gathering I do think there are ways to make both other NK’S more focused around using Information to trick people.</p>
<p>Reaper - no new abilitys. I simply want him to be able to read the journal of reaped players and possablely also be able to edit them. I’d start with just reading them and add in editing them if Reaper starts to fall behind.</p>
<p>Sorcerer - Make one of her day Ability’s Reveal the classes that visit target target player (possablely herself). Probably the one that hides visits.</p>
<p>These changes would not be that big on their own but it does let both classes open up their claimspace while not breaking them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/giving-nks-more-information-based-tools/41599/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/giving-nks-more-information-based-tools/41599/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 18:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41599-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/giving-nks-more-information-based-tools/41599.rss">Giving NK&#39;s more information based tools</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
