<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221</link>
    <description>&quot;Well, well. A glorious return? You expect to simply waltz up here and claim both fame and fortune for yourself? Not if I, the Swan have anything to do with it! Here you will face many a great foe and be challenged to prove yourself worthy.&quot;

# Welcome to Behind the Masks 3, hosted by yours truly, PKR.

[details=&quot;Rolecards&quot;]
[quote]
# [color=#FF8000]Augur[/color]

You are an [color=#FF8000][b]Augur[/b][/color]!

Death can never come too soon, for you there is new life in death. Those that die around you are merely wandering spirits, waiting for your guidance underneath your spiritual light. You offer repentance to all who dwindle on this plain of existence.

During the Action Phase, you may ask any dead players up to three questions divided (question length = 100 characters). The dead player may respond to each question(20 characters).

Once per game, during the Action Phase, you may message the moderator of the current game and ask 1 question about someone who is already dead. Questions against anyone who is currently alive will be ignored. The Moderator will not lie about what they tell you; the information is correct.

[i]Created by nighthawk101. Credit to Blackajack for flavor.[/i]
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#BF0000]Barbarian[/color]

You are a [b][color=#BF0000]Barbarian[/color][/b]!

Across the land, your name is whispered in fearful corners and shouted from the peaks of mountains. Mighty conquerors seek mighty trophies, and the Palace is certainly a worthy trophy.

Three times per game, during the Dinner Phase, you may intimidate one player, preventing them from acting (challenging), however they must accept all challenges made against them. PM the Moderator to use this power.

If you intimidate a player, the intimidated player will be announced at the beginning of the Challenge Phase.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#0A0A0A]Blackmailer[/color]

You are a [color=#0A0A0A][b]Blackmailer[/b][/color]!

Your hobby is certainly dirty- in that you dig up dirt. Research and preparation are the keys to success. Before you entered the Palace, you were already familiar with every tidbit and secret embedded in the past of the other players- secrets that will make them cringe in fear and do your bidding.

During the Dinner Phase, you may blackmail one player. PM the Moderator to use this power.

Blackmailed players must partake in a challenge during the Challenge Phase, or will die.

Only the blackmailed player will know that they are blackmailed.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#BF8040]Blacksmith[/color]

You are a [b][color=#BF8040]Blacksmith[/color][/b]!

Steel flows like water under your steady gaze and steady flame. The pounding of your hammer crafts works of art and workers of war. One of your weapons in a hand guarantees victory.

At the beginning of the Action Phase, you will be notified of the intended winner(s) of the accepted duel(s).

Three times per game, during the Action Phase, you may change the winner of a duel. PM the Moderator to use this power. You may use this ability once on yourself.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#FF40FF]Court Jester[/color]

You are a [color=#FF80FF][b]Court Jester![/b][/color]

Entertaining is your bread and butter, you live and breath laughter and lightheartedness. Capable of soothing even the loudest of mobs into a quiet peace and calmness. You will do anything to prevent death, including changing your act when it occurs.

When a player dies by non-execution your position on the duel/dance list is randomized (Credit to Blackajack for this one)

Once per game you may choose to entertain your fellow guests and force a skip of the current voting phase and preventing that the MAA Shot, Poisoner&#39;s Poison and the Current execution from taking place.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#808000]Man-at-arms[/color]

You are a [color=#808000]Man-at-arms[/color]!

All these poor people attempting to fool their way to riches, you have, and always has, been an excellent murderer. By detecting weakness in the group, you can spread fear with one simple line - Who done it?

Once per voting phase, you may shoot one person. They will not survive the shot unless they are the Soldier. If you shoot the Soldier, the Soldier will kill you instead.

You can only shoot losers of duels/dances.

Additionally, you also gain an additional shooting every time you defeat a player in a duel or dance.

The shooting is silent, meaning it does not reveal your role.

You cannot store more than 1 shot at a time.

You start off with one shot.

[i]Credit to Blackajack.[/i]
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#FF00BF]Musician[/color]

You are a [b][color=#FF00BF]Musician[/color][/b]!

Perfect pitch, perfect playing... perfect music. Hands dance across strings and keys as the notes rise and fall. No matter the tune, no matter the tempo, every song ascends to perfection in your grasp. Yet with a single twist, that song becomes an instrument of death.

At the beginning of the Action Phase, you will be notified of the intended winner(s) of the accepted dance(s).

Three times per game, during the Action Phase, you may change the winner of a dance. PM the Moderator to use this power. You may use this ability once on yourself.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#BF0080]Nymph[/color]

You are a [b][color=#BF0080]Nymph[/color][/b]!

*You are not human, but rather a spirit of the Earth. Over your millennia of existence, you have learned how to tap into your different energies in order to accomplish your tasks with ease.*

*You may tap into your power, your passion to release your inner fire, and allow the heat of your ethereal flames to destroy your opponents in a duel. Or, rather, you can embrace the serenity and tranquility and flow with the beauty and grace of water. Should you prefer to blend in, one can always find balance and safety in the forest…*

Each dinner phase you may choose between 3 positions: Fire, Nature and Water

When you&#39;re in the Water position you are moved to the top of the dance list and bottom of the duel

When you&#39;re in the Fire position, you are moved to the top of the duel list and bottom of the dance

When you&#39;re in the Nature you take a neutral stance in the middle

You are immune to the MAA and the Poisoner when in the Nature position only.

You start in the Nature position.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#004000]Peasant[/color]

You are a [b][color=#004000]Peasant[/color][/b]!

Every day, you go out onto your simple plot of land and farm. But those who look past your grubby face will find a mind as sharp as a tack. The world is an open book to you, as darting eyes pick out nuances in every scenario.

You will be notified whenever the Blacksmith or the Musician interferes in a challenge.

You will be notified of any secret plate switches.

You will be notified of the original target for the poisoner. (Not post-switch)
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#408040]Poisoner[/color]

You are a [b][color=#408040]Poisoner[/color][/b]!

There is no better color than the pale blue of asphyxiation. Or perhaps a simple white pallor. Hmm, but the rich re- No matter. Your art is that of death, slipped unnoticed into a vein, on the rim of a cup, among familiar foods...

You may poison a player&#39;s food during the Voting Phase. If they eat it, they will die during the dinner phase. PM the Moderator to use this power.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#804000]Professor[/color]

You are a [color=#804000]Professor[/color]!

A higher education you had, and a higher education you now teach. You are an expert in the field of social analysis. Whether it be his posture, or or his grin, or another tell that no one but you can pick up upon, all you need to determine the past, present, and true intentions of a man is to observe him carefully.

Whenever you guess a player&#39;s role, you may also submit a secondary guess to the moderator for the same player. If the secondary guess is correct, it will be displayed as your submitted guess, otherwise, your primary guess, whether correct or incorrect, will be displayed. Whenever you win a challenge, you may submit a third guess the following Dinner Phase.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#FF0000]Royal[/color]

You are a [b][color=#FF0000]Royal[/color][/b]!

The blood running through your veins is undeniably royal. An aura of command encircles and influences those who behold you. Combined with a forceful and assertive personality, you can direct others without their knowledge.

Your vote counts as two during the Voting Phase. PM the moderators to cast your second vote secretly.

Once per game, during the Voting Phase, you may force a vote. PM the Moderator to use this power.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#40BFFF]Soldier[/color]

You are a [b][color=#40BFFF]Soldier[/color][/b]!

You went off to war a simple peasant boy, unsure of the world. You returned not a man, but a soldier. With guns, war is hell. With magic, war is worse. Your mind was nearly shattered, and your body forever changed.

You are immune to poison.

You will kill the MAA when they shoot you.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#BF40FF]Sorcerer[/color]

You are a [b][color=#BF40FF]Sorcerer[/color][/b]!

Why must the magical elite linger among the unpowered civilians? No matter. Your victory is near certain, as you are obvious the the most cunning and clever person here. The other contestants must be grateful that your powers are too flashy.

Once per game, you may choose a player to magically kill. PM the Moderator to use this power.

When you use your power, you will be revealed as the Sorcerer. There are no restrictions on when you may use this power, only that you cannot use it if you are one of the losers in a voting phase.
[/quote]

[quote]

# [color=#4040FF]Student[/color]
You are a [b][color=#4040FF]Student[/color][/b]!

During your college years, you could never confine yourself to a single field of study. Thankfully, a natural knack for learning led to the collection of a wide variety of skills. In the Palace, this ability will serve you well, as duelling and dancing are simply other skills.

Each time you participate in a duel or dance and lose, you move up two slots on the corresponding list. Dead players count as being on the lists.
[/quote]

[quote]
# [color=#804000]Thief[/color]

You are a [b][color=#804000]Thief[/color][/b]!

The perfect crime remains unknown. It is a mark of your prowess as a thief that no one had heard your name or seen your exploits. You have stolen from the richest kings, scammed the brightest scholars... Switching plates is like taking candy from a baby.

You may switch player&#39;s plates up to 5 times **each Dinner Phase** without their knowledge. PM the Moderator to use this power. If the poisoner dies, you will become the new poisoner.
[/quote]
[/details]


## Signups
-Before the game begins, the moderator forms a rolelist of the available core and possibly experimental roles- typically 16 roles.
-The number of players is equal to the number of roles.
-Once signups open, players may “/join” the game and provide an animal mask to be referred to as.
-After all available slots have been filled, the roles will be randomly distributed among players via PM, with no repeated roles.
-Players may still join a backup queue once the game begins

## Basics
-The last player standing is the victor.
-A player’s role is not revealed when they die (of course, if their role was guessed you will know it).
-Players may PM other players during the game as long as the moderator is included.
-Dead players cannot post, but moderator discretion may permit a final post or a pre submitted last will.
-Actions, gifts, and guesses are sent to the moderator.
-No quoting/fake quoting mod messages

## Phases
-The game itself has four phases.
-Discussion is permitted and encouraged throughout all phases.

## Challenge Phase
-The Challenge Phase lasts 72 hours, or until all players have challenged or nochallenged and all pending challenges are resolved.
-The game begins on this phase.
-Players may “/challenge” other players to dances or duels.
-Once issued, the challenged player must choose whether to “/accept” the challenge or use a “/deny” (all players begin the game with a deny).
-If the challenged player does not respond by the end of the Challenge Phase, the challenge is automatically accepted.
-Each player may only challenge once per Challenge Phase (even if the challenge is denied), but can be challenged multiple times.
-If a player does not wish to challenge, they may instead “/nochallenge”. This allows the phase to end earlier. Players must still choose whether to accept or deny challenges.
-The results of the challenges will be posted at the end of the Action Phase (see Action Phase).
-The victors of duels and dances are determined by which player’s roles are higher on the respective list (see below), plus any interfering abilities.

**Duel**
Nymph (Fire Form)
Barbarian
Soldier
Man at arms
Blacksmith
Sorcerer
Peasant
Blackmailer
Nymph (Nature Form)
Poisoner
Professor
Student
Thief
Augur
Court Jester
Musician
Royal
Nymph (Water Form)

**Dance**
Nymph (Water Form)
Royal
Thief
Musician
Blackmailer
Peasant
Augur
Sorcerer
Nymph (Nature Form)
Poisoner
Court Jester
Professor
Soldier
Man at arms
Student
Blacksmith
Barbarian
Nymph (Fire Form)

## Action Phase
-The Action Phase lasts 24 hours, or until all actions have been received.
-Roles with abilities that are used during the Action Phase can PM the moderator to use them. Currently, this is the Blacksmith and Musician.
-At the moderator’s discretion, players may begin selected gifts (see Voting Phase).
-The results for duels and dances will be posted at the end of the Action Phase.

## Voting Phase
-The Voting Phase lasts 48 hours, or until a 90% majority has been reached or until all players have voted.
-The Voting Phase will still occur during the first round, but no players will be voted and no execution will occur.
-Any player who lost a duel or dance during the past Challenge Phase is a valid vote target.
-The player with the most votes at the end of the phase will be executed.
-If there is a tie, there is a revote. If the votes are still tied, no player is executed.
-The Court Jester, Man-at-arms, Royal, and Poisoner act during this phase. The Royal may also PM an extra vote.
-Players may also select gifts during this phase (see below).
-For each challenge participated in (no matter if won or lost) the player earns one gift. Gifts are revealed at the end of the Voting Phase.

## Gifts
Extra Deny- Grants an extra deny to deny a challenge (see Challenge Phase) (each player starts with one deny)
Extra Switch- Grants an extra plate switch to swap plates (see Dinner Phase) (each player starts with one switch)
Free Guess- During the upcoming Dinner Phase, you may make a guess as to a player’s role. If you are correct, they will be executed. You may only choose one of this gift per round.
Guess Immunity- You are not a valid guess target during the next Dinner Phase.
Premium Food- Your plate cannot be switched except from by the Thief and you are not a valid Poisoner target during the Voting Phase (you can still be poisoned if your plate is switched)
Gift Reserve - This gift can be redeemed at any point later in the game for a gift of your choosing. You can only hold up to 3 of this gift at a time.
Lottery Ticket - If you are the only one to take this gift, you get 2x the amount of gifts.

## Dinner Phase
-The Dinner Phase ends after 24 hours, or after all players have switched or noswitched.
-Each player is given a plate of food.
-You may “/switch” the food of any two players, consuming a plate switch (each player begins with one plate switch).
-If somebody has switch plates with you, you may not take it back directly and have to switch/noswitch again
-At the end of the phase, each player eats the food in front of them.
-Players who eat poison food will die (excluding the Soldier).
-The Barbarian, Blackmailer and Nymph act during this phase. The Thief may secretly switch plates during this phase.
-In addition, if you received a free guess as a gift, you must use it during the Dinner Phase. If you are correct, that player will be executed at the end of the Dinner Phase. All attempted guesses are revealed at the end of the Dinner Phase.
-If you do not have a free guess, you may still make a guess as to another player’s role as normal. However, if you are incorrect, you will be executed.

Signups:
1. Apprentice (The Otter) **Mischallenged the Nymph and got endgamed** - 2nd Place
2. Surge (The Mountain Walrus) **Poisoned by the Poisoner Dinner Phase 1** - 15th Place
3. Moleland (The Mole) **Executed Voting Phase 4** - 6th Place
4. Light (The Artic Fox) **Shot by the Man At Arms Voting Phase 4** - 6th Place
5. an_gorta_pratai (The Emu) **Executed by the Swan due to most votes Voting Phase 3** - 9th Place
6. Jane (The Kiwi) **Incorrect Death Stake Guess Dinner Phase 4** - 3rd Place
7. Zone_Q11 (The Gorilla) **Shot by the Man At Arms Voting Phase 2** - 13th Place
8. Hippoyeetus (The Robin) **Shot by the Man At Arms Voting Phase 3** - 9th Place
9. Wazza (The Dog) **RNG Guessed as the Poisoner Dinner Phase 3 by Ami** - 8th Place
10. Trochilidae (The Hummingbird) **Poisoned by the Poisoner Dinner Phase 2** - 11th Place
11. Ami (The Scorpion) *WINNER* [Victory Speech](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1270?u=pokemonkidryan) 
12. Insanity (The Crow) **Shot by the Man At Arms Voting Phase 1** - 16th Place
13. Mist1422 (The Eagle) **Guessed as the Blacksmith Dinner Phase 4 by Apprentice** - 3rd Place
14. Marshal (The Cat) **Incorrect Death Stake Guess Dinner Phase 4** - 3rd Place
15. astand (The Capybara) **Force Executed by the Royal Voting Phase 2** - 13th Place
16. PsychoKang (The Turkey) **Guessed as the Augur Dinner Phase 2 by Marshal** - 11th Place

Spectators: Katze, DatBird, gingerbeardgentleman</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 08:39:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Completed</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since you asked so nicely…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1626">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1626</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 08:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1626</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1625">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1625</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 05:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1625</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gingerbeardgentleman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yo, could somebody ping me when BtM 4 comes up? Please and thank you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1624">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1624</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 03:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1624</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sad my attempt to take control failed, but I regret nothing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1623">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1623</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 23:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1623</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trochilidae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yo i just wanna congratulate y’all i’d been following the thread even after i died and everyone did a really good job!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1622">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1622</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 23:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1622</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="PokemonKidRyan" data-post="1312" data-topic="83221">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/pokemonkidryan/40/17866_2.png" class="avatar"> PokemonKidRyan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Jane is MAA</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Jane, why ;-;;;;;;;;;</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1621">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1621</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 23:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1621</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Who is MAA ;-;</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1620">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1620</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 23:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1620</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mistyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you mean if i wasnt a GAMER</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1619">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1619</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1619</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…I was loyal to my alliance and my d1 alliance all made it pretty deep to the finals and if it weren’t for jane then we probably legitimately make it to the f4</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1618">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1618</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1618</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What Jane said</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1617">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1617</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1617</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everyone is Mafia Mafia</p>
<p>FFA basically.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1616">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1616</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1616</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>whats EiMM?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1615">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1615</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1615</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trochilidae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i’d never rolled student and i was so excited, but boom i get barely any challenges and boom poison lol<br>
definitely need to work on this for next game lmao</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1614">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1614</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1614</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s how EiMM ends up working tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1613">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1613</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1613</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Italy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>allying with marshal is a mistake though</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1612">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1612</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 17:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1612</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>These games are more fun when there are  multiple alliances and betrayals and shit as opposed to</p>
<p>“Lol we only ppl with alliance we gonna dominate”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1611">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1611</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 17:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1611</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trochilidae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>man i’m gonna have to start actually making alliances lmao</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1610">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1610</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1610</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zone_Q11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Uh… okay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1609">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1609</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 15:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1609</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He’s just dummy and switched names around.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1608">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1608</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 15:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1608</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zone_Q11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marshal" data-post="1576" data-topic="83221">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marshal/40/32698_2.png" class="avatar"> Marshal:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>zone is the future light</p>
<p>don’t go down this path light it’s not too late</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Uhm… wut?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1607">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1607</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 15:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1607</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was pretty confident it was Trochili</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1606">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1606</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 14:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1606</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d figured out Marshal was the most likely CJ but then I was like “Yeah, there’s no way he’s this lucky with rolls”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1605">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1605</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1605</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean I guess I could’ve lost to CJ</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1604">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1604</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 14:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1604</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh rip.  yeah it was fine.  I was guaranteed to at worst tie anything that wasn’t exactly fire form nymph</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1603">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1603</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 14:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1603</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was going to cancel it reeeeee.</p>
<p>Anyway, yeah bad move on my part.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1602">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221/1602</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 14:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83221-1602</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/behind-the-masks-3-royal-returns-game-end/83221.rss">Behind the Masks 3: Royal Returns (Game End)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
