<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>(Neutral Class Suggestion) The Exiled</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512</link>
    <description>The Exiled
Faction: Neutral
Type: Special
Cannot be converted


Background
An unwanted son of the king, he was discarded into the woods and proclaimed as dead by the King to the world. He now seeks to reclaim the throne which was rightfully his.

Win Condition
Become the King and Survive till the end of the game as King.

Passives
True Heir - Only usable upon the death of a king. As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King. When becoming King, become a Tyrant King instead.

Day Abilities
Enslave (One Charge Only) – Imprison a chosen target tonight and execute him at the end of the night. Will fail if used on the Prince, or a target that would be imprisoned by the Prince. Otherwise, bypasses occupy immunity. The target will be unable to tell the difference between the actual Prince and The Exiled. However, if the target is night immune, the actual execution would fail. Execution can’t be blocked by other abilities. (such as ice-ward)

Night Abilities
Dethrone (One Charge Only, only useable day 6 and after) - Kill the current King at the end of the night. Consumes a charge even if it fails.

Into the Shadows (Three Charges) – Become Night Immune. Investigative results will reveal you as a Blue Dragon Faction member for the night.


Tyrant King
(The court will see you as only a King)
Background
Formerly an exiled Prince, after finally seizing control of his rightful throne, he wishes to exact his revenge on those who chose to forget that he had ever existed in the past.

Passives
Tenacity - Immune to being occupied at night.
True Resolve – Immune to death only for one life.

Day Abilities
The Royal Finger - The King&#39;s next vote for treason will count twice.
Decide Fate - After the final vote, the King can veto the votes and decide if the fate of the person defending themselves. If the King decides to execute, the player on the stand is executed. If the King decides to pardon the player on the stand, they can&#39;t be accused of treason again that day.

Night Abilities
Dead of Night – Kill up to 2 targets of your choice.
Obliterate the Heretics! – Ignores Night Immunity and cannot be blocked by any ability, including occupation and heals and secures a single kill on a target of your choice.

Comments: 
Many people have been requesting for a character that has a unique winning condition, other than surviving or killing everyone. The Exile’s winning condition is unique as he needs to survive as a KING by the end of the game. Although it might seem unfair as compared to neutral characters that merely need to survive such as alchemist, the compromise is that the Exiled, once becoming Tyrant, has such a great impact on the direction of the game. Enslave is a very strong skill as it can cause the death of a character of his choice. However, the fact that there is another target getting imprisoned would warn the court of the fact that the Exiled is in court and might result in a warier court. Into the shadows can be a clutch skill to prevent your true identity as a neutral character from being detected by the Blue Dragon faction and the King, and could save your life if an attempt is made. Dethrone is an important skill to prevent games where the original king survives for very long, and hence causes the Exiled to not have a chance at becoming the King. However, if Dethrone fails, the Exiled would have to find alternate ways to slay the King. Through noble blood, it is an easy feat to becoming a King, especially as currently Blue Dragons with noble blood usually do not attempt to contest the throne (from my games at least). This mechanic force contest of the throne, as a Tyrant on the throne would be a disadvantage for both factions. Once the Tyrant is on the throne, he has the ability to significantly swing the tides of the game. He can choose to decimate one side and win with the other side, or destroy both factions at the same time.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 08:18:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>(Neutral Class Suggestion) The Exiled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>People were suggesting a king gain class. We have now got a great idea.</p>
<p>This is a great idea for a role. Much better than a become neutral king and survive.</p>
<p>I’d be happy to see this ingame</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 08:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-5512-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512.rss">(Neutral Class Suggestion) The Exiled</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>(Neutral Class Suggestion) The Exiled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Xenofly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Exiled<br>
Faction: Neutral<br>
Type: Special<br>
Cannot be converted</p>
<p>Background<br>
An unwanted son of the king, he was discarded into the woods and proclaimed as dead by the King to the world. He now seeks to reclaim the throne which was rightfully his.</p>
<p>Win Condition<br>
Become the King and Survive till the end of the game as King.</p>
<p>Passives<br>
True Heir - Only usable upon the death of a king. As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King. When becoming King, become a Tyrant King instead.</p>
<p>Day Abilities<br>
Enslave (One Charge Only) – Imprison a chosen target tonight and execute him at the end of the night. Will fail if used on the Prince, or a target that would be imprisoned by the Prince. Otherwise, bypasses occupy immunity. The target will be unable to tell the difference between the actual Prince and The Exiled. However, if the target is night immune, the actual execution would fail. Execution can’t be blocked by other abilities. (such as ice-ward)</p>
<p>Night Abilities<br>
Dethrone (One Charge Only, only useable day 6 and after) - Kill the current King at the end of the night. Consumes a charge even if it fails.</p>
<p>Into the Shadows (Three Charges) – Become Night Immune. Investigative results will reveal you as a Blue Dragon Faction member for the night.</p>
<p>Tyrant King<br>
(The court will see you as only a King)<br>
Background<br>
Formerly an exiled Prince, after finally seizing control of his rightful throne, he wishes to exact his revenge on those who chose to forget that he had ever existed in the past.</p>
<p>Passives<br>
Tenacity - Immune to being occupied at night.<br>
True Resolve – Immune to death only for one life.</p>
<p>Day Abilities<br>
The Royal Finger - The King’s next vote for treason will count twice.<br>
Decide Fate - After the final vote, the King can veto the votes and decide if the fate of the person defending themselves. If the King decides to execute, the player on the stand is executed. If the King decides to pardon the player on the stand, they can’t be accused of treason again that day.</p>
<p>Night Abilities<br>
Dead of Night – Kill up to 2 targets of your choice.<br>
Obliterate the Heretics! – Ignores Night Immunity and cannot be blocked by any ability, including occupation and heals and secures a single kill on a target of your choice.</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
Many people have been requesting for a character that has a unique winning condition, other than surviving or killing everyone. The Exile’s winning condition is unique as he needs to survive as a KING by the end of the game. Although it might seem unfair as compared to neutral characters that merely need to survive such as alchemist, the compromise is that the Exiled, once becoming Tyrant, has such a great impact on the direction of the game. Enslave is a very strong skill as it can cause the death of a character of his choice. However, the fact that there is another target getting imprisoned would warn the court of the fact that the Exiled is in court and might result in a warier court. Into the shadows can be a clutch skill to prevent your true identity as a neutral character from being detected by the Blue Dragon faction and the King, and could save your life if an attempt is made. Dethrone is an important skill to prevent games where the original king survives for very long, and hence causes the Exiled to not have a chance at becoming the King. However, if Dethrone fails, the Exiled would have to find alternate ways to slay the King. Through noble blood, it is an easy feat to becoming a King, especially as currently Blue Dragons with noble blood usually do not attempt to contest the throne (from my games at least). This mechanic force contest of the throne, as a Tyrant on the throne would be a disadvantage for both factions. Once the Tyrant is on the throne, he has the ability to significantly swing the tides of the game. He can choose to decimate one side and win with the other side, or destroy both factions at the same time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 07:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-5512-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-suggestion-the-exiled/5512.rss">(Neutral Class Suggestion) The Exiled</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
