<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Noble Changes: Day Role?</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583</link>
    <description>I feel like Noble&#39;s one of those classes that people don&#39;t particularly enjoy mostly for feeling a bit useless compared to other roles. I&#39;m sure CW feels the same to the point where it&#39;s being overhauled. That said, I feel like Noble could use some changes to make it more of a Day-oriented role instead of a Night one.

- Maid Spy: It&#39;s extremely powerful in niche circumstances but for the most part, it&#39;s very meh.
- Snoop: Similar to Maid Spy, but useful much more often. If people fake logs well though, Snoop is practically useless. Might get lucky and catch a bad log or just find someone without logs, but plenty of times it just does nothing with absolutely no confirmation (such as an Observer&#39;s Peek).

As for the Day abilities...

- Political Pressure: Does almost nothing other than being a good prove to the King. &quot;I&#39;m going to make 8 vote for himself&quot;. Feels kinda like old Butler &quot;Pardon and Poison&quot; proving. Very few times will the extra vote help.
- Noble Twin: Decent on its own (moreso than PP), but not enough of an impact to make a difference most of the time.

So to recap, you have an extremely weak, almost never useful night ability, a second one that is a bit more useful but plenty of times does nothing, and two day abilities that are also very lackluster, so let&#39;s  make the Day Phase the more powerful one for a Noble by changing how they work.

- Political Pressure: Block a player from voting for the day or force them to vote for someone else. You can change the person they accuse once (if the court changes their mind). 3 charges (up from 2), can be used on the same day as Blackmail.
- Blackmail: All that spying really paid off. While a player is being accused of treason, choose a player other than the one being tried. They will be forced to Execute, Abstain, or Pardon, based on your own vote. The court will know someone was Blackmailed using the same message as Noble Twin, but the blackmailed player will be privately told they were blackmailed. 3 charges (up from 2), can be used on the same day as Political Pressure.

Overall, this would give the Noble a very aggressive day phase when it comes to voting while still keeping the rather lackluster (but potentially useful if lucky) night phase they have now. Hopefully less people would hate playing the role then.

Aristocrat Edit: I think the Aristocrat is fine as it is TBH. Snoop is much stronger as Aristocrat than Noble at finding roles to report to your MM on who to convert or your Assassin on who to kill. Maid Spy can also be useful on players you notice keep whispering the King each day with info (while as a Noble it tends to not be as useful since you don&#39;t know if that player is BD or not while Unseen would know). Buffing their Day abilities might make Aristocrat _too_ good.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 11:46:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Noble Changes: Day Role?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey when your aristocrat and you make the prince vote the hunter feels good</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 11:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54583-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583.rss">Noble Changes: Day Role?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Noble Changes: Day Role?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Polarthief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A scenario that I’ve seen a grand total of 0 times in all my games, usually because Nobles die before the majority is ever a concern or they haven’t 100% figured out sides.</p>
<p>That niche scenario also comes at the cost of having a practically useless night phase.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54583-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583.rss">Noble Changes: Day Role?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Noble Changes: Day Role?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Political Pressure makes Noble effectively 2 people when tracking who has majority. That is stronger than king during the day because you can win when down a person while king can only use finger to break a tie. Noble Twins is useless in comparison.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54583-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583.rss">Noble Changes: Day Role?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Noble Changes: Day Role?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Polarthief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel like Noble’s one of those classes that people don’t particularly enjoy mostly for feeling a bit useless compared to other roles. I’m sure CW feels the same to the point where it’s being overhauled. That said, I feel like Noble could use some changes to make it more of a Day-oriented role instead of a Night one.</p>
<ul>
<li>Maid Spy: It’s extremely powerful in niche circumstances but for the most part, it’s very meh.</li>
<li>Snoop: Similar to Maid Spy, but useful much more often. If people fake logs well though, Snoop is practically useless. Might get lucky and catch a bad log or just find someone without logs, but plenty of times it just does nothing with absolutely no confirmation (such as an Observer’s Peek).</li>
</ul>
<p>As for the Day abilities…</p>
<ul>
<li>Political Pressure: Does almost nothing other than being a good prove to the King. “I’m going to make 8 vote for himself”. Feels kinda like old Butler “Pardon and Poison” proving. Very few times will the extra vote help.</li>
<li>Noble Twin: Decent on its own (moreso than PP), but not enough of an impact to make a difference most of the time.</li>
</ul>
<p>So to recap, you have an extremely weak, almost never useful night ability, a second one that is a bit more useful but plenty of times does nothing, and two day abilities that are also very lackluster, so let’s  make the Day Phase the more powerful one for a Noble by changing how they work.</p>
<ul>
<li>Political Pressure: Block a player from voting for the day or force them to vote for someone else. You can change the person they accuse once (if the court changes their mind). 3 charges (up from 2), can be used on the same day as Blackmail.</li>
<li>Blackmail: All that spying really paid off. While a player is being accused of treason, choose a player other than the one being tried. They will be forced to Execute, Abstain, or Pardon, based on your own vote. The court will know someone was Blackmailed using the same message as Noble Twin, but the blackmailed player will be privately told they were blackmailed. 3 charges (up from 2), can be used on the same day as Political Pressure.</li>
</ul>
<p>Overall, this would give the Noble a very aggressive day phase when it comes to voting while still keeping the rather lackluster (but potentially useful if lucky) night phase they have now. Hopefully less people would hate playing the role then.</p>
<p>Aristocrat Edit: I think the Aristocrat is fine as it is TBH. Snoop is much stronger as Aristocrat than Noble at finding roles to report to your MM on who to convert or your Assassin on who to kill. Maid Spy can also be useful on players you notice keep whispering the King each day with info (while as a Noble it tends to not be as useful since you don’t know if that player is BD or not while Unseen would know). Buffing their Day abilities might make Aristocrat <em>too</em> good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54583-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/noble-changes-day-role/54583.rss">Noble Changes: Day Role?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
