<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549</link>
    <description>So here is what&#39;s wrong with merc, it&#39;s boring, and useless except for 4 nights.  But that&#39;s not the MAIN reason why merc needs re-work.  The big problem is the entire structure/win condition.  When you&#39;re in an alliance of some sort, you spend all game trying to get that alliance to win since that&#39;s how you win.  With merc, your contract has to live but you can have a 2nd contract. Now, if i&#39;m somebody&#39;s merc, I should want to protect them with every fiber of my being.  But I don&#39;t feel that way with my first contract.  Mercs feel that with only 4 guards, there is no way to protect contract 1 till the end of the game, but and if you use all the guards early on, you have that many less to use on contract 2.  So naturally i wanna save my guards and let my contract survive as long as he can on his own and then use guards on contract 2.  that way i can contract and have 4 guards hopefully in the middle of the game.  It&#39;s not game throwing becuase thats a good way to meet my win condition, but it&#39;s not really the spirit of merc.  so it needs to be reworked.


I dont think a merc should be able to contract a 2nd time.  Not caring if first contract dies kinda ruins how merc should be.  I think only 1 contract but buff merc so he&#39;s fun, can help get 1 contract to the end of the game, and cares about that contract. also give him more than just he guard ability.  give him a day ability or another night abillity to make the class more dynamic.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 18:53:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Only time I feel good playing Merc is a Cult game where you can sort of predict the kill cycle and keep that first dude alive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 18:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Interesting idea. And perhaps it has to contract within the first three days?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 18:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe the Merc should start with no contract?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 17:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’d also kind be cool if you had one contract and you don’t have a win condition you just get more gold at the end based on the length of time your contact lives.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 16:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree that’s the way to win as merc. Just wish it wasn’t. Cuz I don’t feel like a merc if I don’t care about my contract.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 16:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If they get a refresh they prob need less charges, but I agree the best thing to do is use one n1 to prove role and then let them die and use charges on 2nd contract.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You could also refresh the uses of stand guard when you get a new contract. That removes the reason not to use them on the first.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 15:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-workwork</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So here is what’s wrong with merc, it’s boring, and useless except for 4 nights.  But that’s not the MAIN reason why merc needs re-work.  The big problem is the entire structure/win condition.  When you’re in an alliance of some sort, you spend all game trying to get that alliance to win since that’s how you win.  With merc, your contract has to live but you can have a 2nd contract. Now, if i’m somebody’s merc, I should want to protect them with every fiber of my being.  But I don’t feel that way with my first contract.  Mercs feel that with only 4 guards, there is no way to protect contract 1 till the end of the game, but and if you use all the guards early on, you have that many less to use on contract 2.  So naturally i wanna save my guards and let my contract survive as long as he can on his own and then use guards on contract 2.  that way i can contract and have 4 guards hopefully in the middle of the game.  It’s not game throwing becuase thats a good way to meet my win condition, but it’s not really the spirit of merc.  so it needs to be reworked.</p>
<p>I dont think a merc should be able to contract a 2nd time.  Not caring if first contract dies kinda ruins how merc should be.  I think only 1 contract but buff merc so he’s fun, can help get 1 contract to the end of the game, and cares about that contract. also give him more than just he guard ability.  give him a day ability or another night abillity to make the class more dynamic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 15:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34549-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-workwork/34549.rss">Mercenary Re-workwork</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
