<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629</link>
    <description>Hi guys, 

I&#39;m just writing this because I was temporarily banned for three days because of &quot;toxic behaviour.&quot; I realize I&#39;ve acted aggressively towards other players in this game, but as far as I remember, my behaviour was never unprovoked. 

I&#39;m fairly certain that if you check my logs you&#39;d notice that I&#39;m not &quot;toxic&quot; whenever I&#39;m not interacting with another toxic individual. In fact, if a player is new to the game, I&#39;m usually quite helpful and sympathetic to them, and it&#39;s usually pretty obvious when I&#39;m joking around with other players.

I am pretty sure I know which game sealed my fate for the ban, because I specifically remember arguing with three other people in the graveyard about what I should have done while playing the Prince, and ended up being flamed myself for being told that I acted like an idiot or &quot;new&quot; player. I can&#39;t recall the instance with complete accuracy, but I definitely remember not being the sole agitator.

I realize I have no power in this situation, and I hope that you guys might reconsider my three day ban. I honestly hate contributing to a toxic environment, but I don&#39;t think it&#39;s realistic for you guys to expect everyone to react to toxicity in the same way. I was brought up in an environment and time when quietism was seen as the worst response to aggression, and I realize this worldview has shifted rather drastically.

I understand that my ban is rather short, although it&#39;s taking place during my short week-long break from university. I hope that you&#39;ll reconsider, and I apologize for any problems that I&#39;ve caused in the interim. I&#39;ve enjoyed this game enough to buy three of my friends copies of it.

Best,
A devoted Throne of Lies player.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:31:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Methnor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intuition]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi Methnor,</p>
<p>Thanks for the quick response and thanks for looking into this.</p>
<p>I guess it’s pretty obvious that I find the results unfortunate, but there’s not much more for me to say.</p>
<p>Take care.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Methnor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Your case has been reviewed and it’s been decided that your ban will remain 3 days. The overwhelming amount of toxicity, as well as the gay slur and considering you have a history, disinclines the staff to lower your sentence.</p>
<p>I’m sorry the ban comes at an inconvenient time for you, but even if other players are toxic to you, it’s not a free pass to insult them back and certainly not multiple people for the length of an entire game. I understand that sometimes it’s hard to not lash back, but do it the correct way - report them at the end of the game for us to deal with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intuition]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi Methnor,</p>
<p>I did say those things, there’s really no use for me to deny that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Methnor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, of course not. You were banned because you called someone a “fgt” and spent the entire game telling people to lube up because you were going to violate them (ironically), among other things.</p>
<p>I can compile up a list of quotes for you from that game, if it’d help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intuition]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi Methnor,</p>
<p>Well, I was kind of lying, I don’t actually get banned everyday. Out of curiosity, was I banned because I claimed I could handle a ban?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Methnor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We can talk about more about this at length if you wish, but before we do, let me ask you something really quick.</p>
<p>What happened to this?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>(Dead) Reginald Selwyn [2] (Intuition687 - Hunter): i get banned every dya<br>
(Dead) Reginald Selwyn [2] (Intuition687 - Hunter): relax<br>
(Dead) Reginald Selwyn [2] (Intuition687 - Hunter): i can handle a ban</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intuition]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi guys,</p>
<p>I’m just writing this because I was temporarily banned for three days because of “toxic behaviour.” I realize I’ve acted aggressively towards other players in this game, but as far as I remember, my behaviour was never unprovoked.</p>
<p>I’m fairly certain that if you check my logs you’d notice that I’m not “toxic” whenever I’m not interacting with another toxic individual. In fact, if a player is new to the game, I’m usually quite helpful and sympathetic to them, and it’s usually pretty obvious when I’m joking around with other players.</p>
<p>I am pretty sure I know which game sealed my fate for the ban, because I specifically remember arguing with three other people in the graveyard about what I should have done while playing the Prince, and ended up being flamed myself for being told that I acted like an idiot or “new” player. I can’t recall the instance with complete accuracy, but I definitely remember not being the sole agitator.</p>
<p>I realize I have no power in this situation, and I hope that you guys might reconsider my three day ban. I honestly hate contributing to a toxic environment, but I don’t think it’s realistic for you guys to expect everyone to react to toxicity in the same way. I was brought up in an environment and time when quietism was seen as the worst response to aggression, and I realize this worldview has shifted rather drastically.</p>
<p>I understand that my ban is rather short, although it’s taking place during my short week-long break from university. I hope that you’ll reconsider, and I apologize for any problems that I’ve caused in the interim. I’ve enjoyed this game enough to buy three of my friends copies of it.</p>
<p>Best,<br>
A devoted Throne of Lies player.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10629-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/resolved-banned-for-toxicity/10629.rss">[RESOLVED] Banned for Toxicity</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
