<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I think Possessor&#39;s DN is bugged</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803</link>
    <description>#### What happened?
 So, if you&#39;re the one possessor jumps to, YOUR death note will appear on the body that possessor just jumped FROM.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen? 
I imagine that the death note shown should be the one the possessor has written.

#### Steps to reproduce: 
1. Write a death note
2. Have a possessor jump to you.
3. The previous body will have the death note you wrote on it.

#### Comments:
 This could be a 100% counter to possessor. Say you&#39;re a psy. Even though you can&#39;t kill, you write a death note saying &quot;If you&#39;re reading this, i am now possessed and this was poss jump -Kidal (3)&quot;. Possessor jumps to you. The old body shows that death note. In this situation, poss is forced to either prove himself as psychic, which he can&#39;t do, or claim something else entirely, but since king already likely knew his claim, he&#39;s pretty much screwed. 

It&#39;s happened to me before, i was playing phys and i was bored so i drew &quot;[my name] was here&quot; on my death note. Possessor jumped to me, and sure enough, my death note was on his corpse. He got executed right that day. Admittedly, it was stupid of BD to trust a random death note, but it still got the possessor hanged.

edit: formatting and some words</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 04:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I think Possessor&#39;s DN is bugged</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I am pretty sure it’s bugged too, some of my friends have been saying the same thing you said but it hasn’t happened to me</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 04:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-49803-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803.rss">I think Possessor&#39;s DN is bugged</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I think Possessor&#39;s DN is bugged</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kidal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>So, if you’re the one possessor jumps to, YOUR death note will appear on the body that possessor just jumped FROM.</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>I imagine that the death note shown should be the one the possessor has written.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<ol>
<li>Write a death note</li>
<li>Have a possessor jump to you.</li>
<li>The previous body will have the death note you wrote on it.</li>
</ol>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>This could be a 100% counter to possessor. Say you’re a psy. Even though you can’t kill, you write a death note saying “If you’re reading this, i am now possessed and this was poss jump -Kidal (3)”. Possessor jumps to you. The old body shows that death note. In this situation, poss is forced to either prove himself as psychic, which he can’t do, or claim something else entirely, but since king already likely knew his claim, he’s pretty much screwed.</p>
<p>It’s happened to me before, i was playing phys and i was bored so i drew “[my name] was here” on my death note. Possessor jumped to me, and sure enough, my death note was on his corpse. He got executed right that day. Admittedly, it was stupid of BD to trust a random death note, but it still got the possessor hanged.</p>
<p>edit: formatting and some words</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 23:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-49803-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/i-think-possessors-dn-is-bugged/49803.rss">I think Possessor&#39;s DN is bugged</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
