<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Masquerader (Blue Dragon) Converts to Harlequin (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345</link>
    <description>Based loosely on Batman/Bruce Wayne with conversion to the Joker/Harley Quinn. ;)

----

**Masquerader** (Blue Dragon) - During the day, you appear to be a foppish man of wealth. However, at night, your TRUE self emerges.

Portrait Icon: A festive person in colorful cloak and long-nosed party mask.

Passive:
**Rise** - If you are executed by vote, you will immediately become a Death Knight upon dying.

Day Ability:
**Party Foul** - Pretend to &quot;spill&quot; your wine on another player, creating a recognizable stain. You will be alerted if they visit you that night, at the end of the night. (4 uses.)

_^ Basically, if a stained player visits you, they are &quot;wisped&quot; to you only._

Night Ability 1:
**Noisemaker** - Give a player a noisemaker, telling their target that they visited them at the end of the night. (Unlimited uses.)

_^ The player you choose will be &quot;wisped&quot; to their target only. (Not you.) The player you choose will also be notified that they were given a party favor and their target was alerted._

Night Ability 2:
**Guest List** - Retreat to your quarters and study your guest list to see the number of evil players left in the game. Provides death immunity while in use. (2 uses.)

^ You are given a SINGLE number that includes ONLY evil players. IE: &quot;5 members of the evil faction remain alive.&quot; You do not receive names, just a general number of how many are left in unseen/cult that night. Does not include the Neutral Killer since there&#39;s always 1 guaranteed.

----

Converts to...

----

**Harlequin** (Unseen) - A formerly respected member of the kingdom whose reputation has been tarnished beyond repair. Others think you foolish, but you might be one step ahead of them...

Portrait Icon: A creepy, masked puppet-person. XD

Day Ability:
**Troll-O-Phone** - Select two players to speak in each other&#39;s names. Neither player will see the switch. (3 uses.)

_^ In other words, you select two players, and everyone but them see their names swapped. Player1 will talk with Player2&#39;s name, and vice-versa. Yes, people can figure it out - but that&#39;s why you should use this ability wisely and for maximum impact. Again, the players you selected will see both names correctly, so everything will seem right to them._

Night Ability 1:
**Vacant Stare** - Tell other members of the Unseen which players visited them at the end of the night. (3 uses.)

_^ Each member of the Unseen will see who visited them that night, as if their visitors have been &quot;wisped&quot; to them. You do not see the visitors of the other Unseen yourself._

Night Ability 2:
**Laughing Gas** - Select a living member of the Unseen to permanently change their class to _Evil Fool_. (Single use.)

 _^ &quot;Evil Fool&quot; isn&#39;t really a new class. It&#39;s just Fool with a goal difference. Please read below._

- Similar to how a Physician resurrects a dead player to become a Death Knight, the Harlequin would be able to turn a living Unseen member into a Fool.
- If possible, the Unseen member you select to change would have a Yes/No pop-up allowing them to agree to become Evil Fool or to decline it. This prevents a troll from converting Mastermind for no reason, etc.
- This specific converted Fool can only win by being executed AND having Unseen win. Hence &quot;Evil Fool&quot;. (This may be harsh, but it shouldn&#39;t be treated as a light choice.)
- Nothing changes except that this &quot;Evil Fool&quot; loses if Unseen lose, even if he&#39;s been executed. All other normal Fool class features still apply.
- The reason for the goal tweak is to prevent the new Fool from outing the Unseen &quot;because he&#39;s not Unseen anymore&quot;.
- The reason for this ability, in general, is to try to gain a bit of an upper hand if a member of the Unseen has been caught and is guaranteed to be executed. Even if there is no Harlequin and no Evil Fool, Unseen members will now be able to act Fool-like if caught and make people WONDER if the Harlequin made them an Evil Fool.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 23:34:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Masquerader (Blue Dragon) Converts to Harlequin (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[boukers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some good ideas here, but I think its doing a little too much, which makes it hard to balance. I feel like there are elements of 2 or more potential classes being mixed together here.</p>
<p>Also, Im not a fan of Troll-O-Phone, seems gimmicky and we can probably come up with something better.</p>
<p>Simplifying this a little would go a long way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 23:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47345-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Masquerader (Blue Dragon) Converts to Harlequin (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Masquerader (Blue Dragon) Converts to Harlequin (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like party foul and noisemaker as abilities, but I don’t like these classes in their entirety.  I especially don’t like Evil Fool, it makes it too dangerous to hang evils.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 23:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47345-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Masquerader (Blue Dragon) Converts to Harlequin (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Masquerader (Blue Dragon) Converts to Harlequin (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Based loosely on Batman/Bruce Wayne with conversion to the Joker/Harley Quinn. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Masquerader</strong> (Blue Dragon) - During the day, you appear to be a foppish man of wealth. However, at night, your TRUE self emerges.</p>
<p>Portrait Icon: A festive person in colorful cloak and long-nosed party mask.</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Rise</strong> - If you are executed by vote, you will immediately become a Death Knight upon dying.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Party Foul</strong> - Pretend to “spill” your wine on another player, creating a recognizable stain. You will be alerted if they visit you that night, at the end of the night. (4 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ Basically, if a stained player visits you, they are “wisped” to you only.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Noisemaker</strong> - Give a player a noisemaker, telling their target that they visited them at the end of the night. (Unlimited uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ The player you choose will be “wisped” to their target only. (Not you.) The player you choose will also be notified that they were given a party favor and their target was alerted.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Guest List</strong> - Retreat to your quarters and study your guest list to see the number of evil players left in the game. Provides death immunity while in use. (2 uses.)</p>
<p>^ You are given a SINGLE number that includes ONLY evil players. IE: “5 members of the evil faction remain alive.” You do not receive names, just a general number of how many are left in unseen/cult that night. Does not include the Neutral Killer since there’s always 1 guaranteed.</p>
<hr>
<p>Converts to…</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Harlequin</strong> (Unseen) - A formerly respected member of the kingdom whose reputation has been tarnished beyond repair. Others think you foolish, but you might be one step ahead of them…</p>
<p>Portrait Icon: A creepy, masked puppet-person. XD</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Troll-O-Phone</strong> - Select two players to speak in each other’s names. Neither player will see the switch. (3 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ In other words, you select two players, and everyone but them see their names swapped. Player1 will talk with Player2’s name, and vice-versa. Yes, people can figure it out - but that’s why you should use this ability wisely and for maximum impact. Again, the players you selected will see both names correctly, so everything will seem right to them.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Vacant Stare</strong> - Tell other members of the Unseen which players visited them at the end of the night. (3 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ Each member of the Unseen will see who visited them that night, as if their visitors have been “wisped” to them. You do not see the visitors of the other Unseen yourself.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Laughing Gas</strong> - Select a living member of the Unseen to permanently change their class to <em>Evil Fool</em>. (Single use.)</p>
<p><em>^ “Evil Fool” isn’t really a new class. It’s just Fool with a goal difference. Please read below.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Similar to how a Physician resurrects a dead player to become a Death Knight, the Harlequin would be able to turn a living Unseen member into a Fool.</li>
<li>If possible, the Unseen member you select to change would have a Yes/No pop-up allowing them to agree to become Evil Fool or to decline it. This prevents a troll from converting Mastermind for no reason, etc.</li>
<li>This specific converted Fool can only win by being executed AND having Unseen win. Hence “Evil Fool”. (This may be harsh, but it shouldn’t be treated as a light choice.)</li>
<li>Nothing changes except that this “Evil Fool” loses if Unseen lose, even if he’s been executed. All other normal Fool class features still apply.</li>
<li>The reason for the goal tweak is to prevent the new Fool from outing the Unseen “because he’s not Unseen anymore”.</li>
<li>The reason for this ability, in general, is to try to gain a bit of an upper hand if a member of the Unseen has been caught and is guaranteed to be executed. Even if there is no Harlequin and no Evil Fool, Unseen members will now be able to act Fool-like if caught and make people WONDER if the Harlequin made them an Evil Fool.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 23:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47345-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-masquerader-blue-dragon-converts-to-harlequin-unseen/47345.rss">[Class Suggestion] Masquerader (Blue Dragon) Converts to Harlequin (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
