<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712</link>
    <description>Now i only have around 30 hours on the game but the hunter seems to be designed more like a neutral class if anything.

So most of the games I&#39;m in the hunter is just randomly killing people which is a mixture of not knowing much about the game and having the ability to kill with no consequences but even if we do kill the hunter for it he will just get another bd with retribution.

The traps have a higher chance to target a bd than unseen as there is more bd with the ability to visit someone than an unseen so you either tell everyone your class or kill bd.

I think a class similar to hunter would work nicely as a neutral class but as a bd class it seems to work mostly against bd.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 07:33:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To clarify your argument<br>
<span class="hashtag">#hunters</span> are bad and should be removed because people are using them wrong !..#</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 07:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hunter can be used against fools and after fool is voted</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 01:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well lets just assume we know there is 3 unseen even though the only way to know that is to know who the unseen are.</p>
<p>You would have to wait until atleast there was 6/7 people before using any abilities as a hunter using your logic, assuming you survive that long.</p>
<p>I know the hunter can be used in certain situations which help but most of these situations stem from bd not looking at the facts and not voting for a proven unseen or 2 people being proven as unseen/neutral killers at the same time and there not being a prince or knight or butler or alch or drunk that can stop the other killer.</p>
<p>I never said the hunter cant be used correctly or carefully, just that this is not the way anyone uses it and the situations that it is useful in is rare to come by even if you survive the whole game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 01:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“No risk without reward”</p>
<p>played right, you will take risks that have a higher chance of success than failure. Randomly murdering has a higher chance of killing BD, as there are simply more BD, so it has a higher chance of failure.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 22:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well after i explained how people play the class the mod said that there’s no reward without risk so i conformed to this play style by simply killing people that i didn’t know were either bd or unseen/cult even though its a stupid way of playing.</p>
<p>The fact that you think its game throwing just shows you agree with me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You said you just wolfed people in protest of the class, seeming as though you wanted to prove hunter was not beneficial for BD; this makes it sound like you were purposefully game throwing</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 21:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yes if you know someone is bd and you purposely kill them as bd then yes obviously that’s game throwing, i dont know what your point is though.</p>
<p>According to some players being new to the game and not knowing what they are doing is game throwing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 18:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I only needed to read the first paragraph to realise you didn’t understand or read anything i previously wrote.</p>
<p>If ranked games became a thing i think that would fix all my issues i have with the game apart from the hunter trap is still bs and always will be bs.</p>
<p>‘Randomly killing is a last resort’<br>
I don’t even want to explain why that statement is stupid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 18:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hurting Bd’s chances as hunter in protest of the class is game throwing</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why do you say that as hunter you should risk killing bd for small chance of killing a unseen/cult ?<br>
I don’t think you have the patience for hunter , its true of others as well .<br>
But as BD collects info and suspects become apparent you may be privy to information that others aren’t , you don’t always know who to trust .<br>
Iamgine an evil king has just saved someone from an execution . You step in and make things right .</p>
<p>Randomly killing is a last resort not a main tactic .</p>
<p>Say you are down to 6 players , 2 guys are pretty sure bd , you are hunter , you have been patient and have some options left .<br>
So now you have 3 guys you are not sure about  , at  least 2 are probably unseen , send the wolf in on one of the guys you trust least .<br>
You have a decent chance  of doing some good at least 66%</p>
<p>Compare this to turn 3 wolf attack a random , just cos I don’t know how to play hunter and I think the class is stupid .<br>
over 50% of the guys at this stage are bd , so your likely to damage bd at this time .</p>
<p>Its about playing the odds and attacking those that are being a bit shady rather than just choosing a number in early turns and hoping for the best.</p>
<p>Also you can always get yourself confirmed and then you know the people coming after you are not got your best interest at heart .</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 10:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so you want to rely on a hunter to be very calculated when the rest of the bd isnt? So you think hunter is going to be the one thats calculated even though he has no investigative abilites and has no more info than any other bd.</p>
<p>I asked him twice why he attacked me and he wouldnt tell me plus this happens all the time with lots of people like i said.</p>
<p>prince knows how important they are to stay alive and use their ability wisely more often than hunters do. there are still prince that kill bd but you cant kill a prince as prince and they are a reliable and important role for investigation.</p>
<p>other roles that can kill have limitations which avoid the hunter issues.</p>
<p>the hunter trap is still no excuse in my opinion, it always kills bd.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
I just want to add i didn’t ruin the game on purpose but i did just kill people for no reason as apparently as a hunter you should risk killing bd for a small chance of it being a unseen/cult.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 19:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I completely agree but its just not what people are doing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think with the change of not allowing the Hunter to kill until Night 3, a lot more Hunters are going to be using their traps Night 1 and Night 2 since they feel the need to do SOMETHING even though it may not necessarily be a good play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="newarkinvaders" data-post="8" data-topic="3712">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/newarkinvaders/40/2154_2.png" class="avatar"> newarkinvaders:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As to you deliberately destroying a game because you don’t like hunters , you can also destroy a game if you are the prince or if you are any over class by deliberately playing badly .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thats called game throwing, you’ll mostly likely get a ban if you do it enough times.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 13:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As a hunter you have the ability to decide games , which can be real handy if you see that the rest of the BD are being lead down a windy road and couldn’t spot a Mastermind if he was sitting in a black swivel chair .</p>
<p>Maybe that hunter random targeted you , or maybe he had been watching and didn’t trust you .</p>
<p>As to you deliberately destroying a game because you don’t like hunters , you can also destroy a game if you are the prince or if you are any over class by deliberately playing badly .</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 12:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Best way to play hunter is to wait untill mid/end game when there are only 7-8 players left. By that point you have a very good chance to hit an evil if you to use your head.</p>
<p>Randomly attacking at the earliest opportunity is not how hunter is meant to be played.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 12:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Strangle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let me tell ya something this class is supposed to be a double edged sword you can either get a baddie or goodie with this .This class to be exact is meant to be used by people who know how to use vet and vig correct in Tos or can be used to force a silent player who could probs be evil to claim but at the same time he could be a powerful bd <em>class</em>.So yeah this is supposed to be used by logical people and those who know what is the correct choice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have never played ToS so i really don’t understand that analogy <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> sry.</p>
<p>In theory you are right but in my time playing the game i have only once seen a hunter kill only unseen/neutral and im not even sure if it was on purpose.</p>
<p>They can get healed but combined with poisoning and no guarantee of a physician, its not something I would want to rely on for a rogue hunter.</p>
<p>I’m sure its mainly that theres a lot of new people and they just waste the abilities but every game i have with hunter there is people raging from getting randomly hit by a wolf.</p>
<p>I also think retribution would kill bd or scorched more than unseen/cult as they are not stupid enough to vote for a hunter claim.</p>
<p>I consider it game throwing when hunters just kill bd all the time but really I blame the class more.</p>
<p>Either way if this is how the devs intended the class to be played then fair enough its their game and their vision.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
just want to add that i just got random shot by a hunter as a mm. need i say more? bd completely trusts me yet an idiot hunter completely ruins the game, game of deceit? or game of shooting everyone. I dont want to sound like im just salty after this happens to me because it happens to everyone all the time.<br>
EDIT 2:<br>
was just the hunter in a game and i honestly felt like i had the power to ruin peoples game and fun for completely no reason and even though i told them at the start a butler visited me and then died. I just killed who i wanted in protest of this class and i killed a bd and got lucky and got a cult leader but it was complete luck.<br>
the bd i killed even said he reported me that’s how annoyed he was and by your logic what i did was completely fine even if it was stupid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 03:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Both have the same meaning Simon <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 02:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or in this case, no reward without risk</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 02:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Consider the Veteran Role from Town of Salem.</p>
<p>If you look at the list in an average game, up to 3 mafia that can visit people, and around 7/8 town roles?</p>
<p>In this situation, the Hunter fairs similar, only different being that they have the option to set a trap or send a wolf to someone.</p>
<p>Also, just because the abilities are there, doesn’t necessarily mean you <strong>must</strong> use them. With that aside, Bleeding can be healed too. So it’s a lot more practical than ToS Veteran.</p>
<p>Hunter is powerful when used in the right situation.</p>
<p>Timing is everything. If it harms more BD than intended, it’s being used wrong. No risk without reward too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 02:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunter Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now i only have around 30 hours on the game but the hunter seems to be designed more like a neutral class if anything.</p>
<p>So most of the games I’m in the hunter is just randomly killing people which is a mixture of not knowing much about the game and having the ability to kill with no consequences but even if we do kill the hunter for it he will just get another bd with retribution.</p>
<p>The traps have a higher chance to target a bd than unseen as there is more bd with the ability to visit someone than an unseen so you either tell everyone your class or kill bd.</p>
<p>I think a class similar to hunter would work nicely as a neutral class but as a bd class it seems to work mostly against bd.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 02:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3712-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/hunter-feedback/3712.rss">Hunter Feedback</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
