<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alchemist Win Condition Suggestion</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277</link>
    <description>I read through the Alchemist lore a bit back, and the flavor of the character made me think of this.

Win condition: Effectively use your abilities 4 times.
(Four is just an assumed good number, but the main idea is for the flavor of testing potions.)

What this does:

_Yolo-bombs more enticing_; and therefore makes BD more suspicious of Alchemists.
_Night-time fool_; makes the Alchemist want to be a suspicious high-priority target, getting points towards victory if they are attacked.
_Removes generic &quot;stay alive&quot; win condition_; nowadays I see more and more Alchemists just claim D1 as they are trying to survive NK or evil faction attacks.

One thing I noticed... while it removes those endgame scenarios of a BD/Evil/Neutral trio, where the neutral player decides the game with no regard to the win condition. It makes one where the Alchemist doesn&#39;t want the game to end, as they are trying to finish testing their potions out. Much like what happens with late game fools.

At victory the Alchemist would leave the court, as the test subjects are no longer of use.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 01:26:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist Win Condition Suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Biperspectival]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, let me note first that I like the idea. That said, I don’t know that it could be implemented.</p>
<p>Firstly, if you heal poisons/bleeds, you’re going to achieve your win condition (as assassin/cl get 4 bleeds). In other words, if you survive, you’re basically guaranteed to win, with using yolos to top off your stacks.</p>
<p>If you make the required stacks more than 4, the alch is basically forced to yolo, and will get exed ASAP. If you make it less than 4, they’ll yolo twice, heal once, and have an easy win.</p>
<p>One thing I’ve considered is that you just say “screw it” and make alch a neut killer. Give them a limited use amount of heals to throw off the bd, and let stoneskin make them immune to EVERYTHING (attacks, king exes, prince exes, etc). This would be hard to do as well, but it would be sort of interesting…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 01:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53277-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277.rss">Alchemist Win Condition Suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist Win Condition Suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure I like this, I like alch’s betrayal thing going on and well scorned and inq’s betrayal abilities will be removed because now they kill themselves</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 01:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53277-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277.rss">Alchemist Win Condition Suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist Win Condition Suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[squidgyxombie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I read through the Alchemist lore a bit back, and the flavor of the character made me think of this.</p>
<p>Win condition: Effectively use your abilities 4 times.<br>
(Four is just an assumed good number, but the main idea is for the flavor of testing potions.)</p>
<p>What this does:</p>
<p><em>Yolo-bombs more enticing</em>; and therefore makes BD more suspicious of Alchemists.<br>
<em>Night-time fool</em>; makes the Alchemist want to be a suspicious high-priority target, getting points towards victory if they are attacked.<br>
<em>Removes generic “stay alive” win condition</em>; nowadays I see more and more Alchemists just claim D1 as they are trying to survive NK or evil faction attacks.</p>
<p>One thing I noticed… while it removes those endgame scenarios of a BD/Evil/Neutral trio, where the neutral player decides the game with no regard to the win condition. It makes one where the Alchemist doesn’t want the game to end, as they are trying to finish testing their potions out. Much like what happens with late game fools.</p>
<p>At victory the Alchemist would leave the court, as the test subjects are no longer of use.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-53277-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-win-condition-suggestion/53277.rss">Alchemist Win Condition Suggestion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
