<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Evangelical</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-evangelical/25612</link>
    <description>The Evangelical (Cult) - Converted from Paladin, Knight

Day Ability 1:
Glory to Mithras (Passive): If sacrified, the next eradicate is empowered.

Day Ability 2:
Cast Doubt (1 use): Disguises an executed Cult member as a Blue Dragon equivalent when it reveals the executed&#39;s class.

Night Ability 1:
Sermon (2 uses): Protects the Cult Leader when they attempt to convert from Smite. Paladin doesn&#39;t see the conversion take place.

Lore:
While the Paladin and Knight embody the virtues of the Blue Dragon and seek to protect them from evil, the Evangelical works with the Cult Leader to spread the will of Mithras. His tongue, sharper than an Assassin&#39;s knife, works to influence even the protected into their ranks. He will do what he must to make the Blue Dragon look weak and the Cult strong, even if it means making the Cult pass for Blue Dragon

Comments:
-Yes, cast doubt is basically a day time version of Herbalist defile. Given the chaos a BD execution can cause on its own, 1 use feels more balanced vs an Herbalist&#39;s 2 at night, but it should not exceed 2.
-Sermon might be ok with 3 over 2 as Smite vs Sermon is a giant guessing game, but I suspect 3 protected converts would be excessive
-I realize empowered eradicate was removed for a reason, but Paladin and Knight can be weak claims as is. Early game can leave the CL with low numbers, and hoping for a final blow late game requires actually making it that far.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 01:45:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-evangelical/25612.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Evangelical</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MishenNikara]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Evangelical (Cult) - Converted from Paladin, Knight</p>
<p>Day Ability 1:<br>
Glory to Mithras (Passive): If sacrified, the next eradicate is empowered.</p>
<p>Day Ability 2:<br>
Cast Doubt (1 use): Disguises an executed Cult member as a Blue Dragon equivalent when it reveals the executed’s class.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
Sermon (2 uses): Protects the Cult Leader when they attempt to convert from Smite. Paladin doesn’t see the conversion take place.</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
While the Paladin and Knight embody the virtues of the Blue Dragon and seek to protect them from evil, the Evangelical works with the Cult Leader to spread the will of Mithras. His tongue, sharper than an Assassin’s knife, works to influence even the protected into their ranks. He will do what he must to make the Blue Dragon look weak and the Cult strong, even if it means making the Cult pass for Blue Dragon</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
-Yes, cast doubt is basically a day time version of Herbalist defile. Given the chaos a BD execution can cause on its own, 1 use feels more balanced vs an Herbalist’s 2 at night, but it should not exceed 2.<br>
-Sermon might be ok with 3 over 2 as Smite vs Sermon is a giant guessing game, but I suspect 3 protected converts would be excessive<br>
-I realize empowered eradicate was removed for a reason, but Paladin and Knight can be weak claims as is. Early game can leave the CL with low numbers, and hoping for a final blow late game requires actually making it that far.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-evangelical/25612/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-evangelical/25612/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 01:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-25612-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-evangelical/25612.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Evangelical</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
