<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422</link>
    <description>In Mafia type games, there are two methods of deduction: Social and Logical.

Social deduction involves making reads in other player&#39;s behavior in the way they talk (or not talk) and vote.

Logical deduction involves taking in all claims and night actions and seeing what does not add up.



The problem lies in the logical deduction  part. There are so many night actions and ways to cross-reference claims. For example, you can claim Physician as Assassin, but then a Princess can see you are killer/off and you instantly get exed.

Now you may think, well shouldn&#39;t you claim something that makes it hard for people to cross-reference? Every class that is ideal for that has turned into a meme. KNIGHT CLAIM LUL CW CLAIM LUL  PRINCESS LUL. I&#39;ve found that the only consistent plays I can do as evil are extremely risky claims like Alchemist or even Mercenary (telling my evil partner to claim he was guarded). Otherwise, you&#39;re just sitting there hoping the spotlight doesn&#39;t shine on you.

Lying in this game is too difficult. In fact, the most ideal way to play evil is 100% social. You have to steer chat to such bedlam in order to pass into the mid and end game unscathed. This isn&#39;t always possible.

Not to mention Day 1 debs or investigations. Good luck. There is zero counter play. In typical Mafia games, you could counter-claim or your evil partner could counter claim that investigative. Doing that is suicide because BD has enough numbers, jails, king exe or CS (or DK) to make sure that even in the worst case scenario, you are trading a BD for an evil. 

Don&#39;t get me started on D1 scouts


Enough with me going on and on, let me shine light on the core problems that allow this to happen.

* No one knows what the role composition of the match is, so you can&#39;t plan your counter claims and craft appropriate lies.
* Too many players means that BD can afford bad exes. In fact, bad exes are typically good for BD, as it narrows down the evil players that have shaky enough claims as it is.
* Every class is semi-unique, meaning you can&#39;t claim a role that &quot;blends in&quot; with the majority. The ones that you can use to blend in (phys, knight, CW) are already super suspicious claims and you&#39;ll instantly get exed for it.
* There are some classes with night actions that absolutely dick you. Debauchery is unfun to use and unfun to play against. What can you possibly do when you get debbed? Even in the best case scenario where you claim Drunk and say you debbed the real Drunk and actually get him exed, you&#39;re just going to jail and dying. Trading a majority player for a minority is never good.
* The majority of classes are impossible to claim without someone pointing out your shit logs. GL claiming Observer or Psychic or Prince or anything that hasn&#39;t become a meme already.


Personally, the best solution to this problem involves reducing the player count per lobby and changing how class compositions are spawned each game. I suggest the following changes:
* Reduce lobby count to 14
* Show the class composition of each game (instead of the vague guidelines it has now)
* Adding vanilla BD roles and making power roles actual power roles (rather than villagers with low impact night actions)

There are other possible changes, but starting with this could be a good start.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 01:46:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, the 1-v-15 nature of an NK’s goal means that we can give them stuff that would be ridiculously overpowered for anyone else.  (It also limits how they can use it.)</p>
<p>I think Reapers being able to not just see but also edit reaped wills is very interesting, at least.  Maybe make the ability to edit the will of someone who was reaped last night into a night ability, so they have limited shots of it and have to skip a kill (or allow it to be used with a kill, but limit its usages.)</p>
<p>There’s other options they could have with their reaped victims, though.  Maybe the Reaper sees the victim’s will and role; then they have an option to “dust” that victim, hiding their will and role.  Then the Reaper could copy the will and role of someone they dusted and use that to claim (risky, since that person may have claimed to someone else already, but interesting.)  Of course, dusting someone would reveal the presence of a Reaper unless we gave the ability to clean people like that to another class as well.</p>
<p>I do like Reapers editing wills, though.  It opens up a lot of possibilities - I think it’d be worth risking it to see if it really makes them too OP (I suspect it would not.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/44</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 01:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-44</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well it’s NK so it’s ok if they have OP tools.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-43</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would be OK with reading the logs, but not changing them. Changing/deleting them would be far too op.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-42</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ami" data-post="35" data-topic="47422">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ami/40/31302_2.png" class="avatar"> Ami:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just do</p>
<p>N1-Window Peep</p>
<p>N2-The person who was Lynched D3</p>
<p>N3-person that was lynched D4,</p>
<p>Just use the dead’s logs to make more credible info and use dead people because they can’t contest it</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Smart courts lynch people whose logs only seem to target dead people.  Yes, this occasionally leads to a mislynch, but it gets increasingly implausible as the game goes on.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>An N1 peek is a dead giveaway (the one time I saw someone try to present a will for it, the response was a unanimous “lol, N1 peek” followed by a lynch.)  At the very least you’d wait to N2, after the first conversion and kill, since that drastically increases your chance of hitting an evil.  Even then, the reality is that most real Observers end up not peeking much, so a will that uses it aggressively is instantly super-suspicious - partially because a real Observer is going to want to witness lots of visits so they can prove themselves.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Most importantly, even if they spot neither of those things, you’ve forgotten that the Observer sees visits <span class="bbcode-i">to</span> their targets, not just <span class="bbcode-i">by</span> their targets.  All it takes is one person saying “wait, I visited X that night, why aren’t I on on there?”  Unlike Butler / Drunk logs, an Observer log can be contradicted by anyone who visited anybody you claimed to target, which you have no way of anticipating or knowing about.  No amount of paying attention or planning can let you avoid this - every lie in your Observer will is another roll of the dice on whether or not a living BD you’re unaware of visited that person that night.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Smart courts are going to know what’s already been said.  My response when someone presents an Observer will is “can anyone confirm this?”, and I check my <span class="bbcode-i">own</span> detailed logs to see if the confirmation is something that was already public information.  If nobody confirms a new, previously-undisclosed visit, you hang.  A real observer log will almost always have lots of confirms from people who haven’t spoken up before.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I have never seen anyone successfully fake Observer - not once, not in all my time playing the game.  Even in the outlandish situation where you manage to get past all of the problems I listed above, I would still say you succeeded primarily by (extreme) luck and not skill - again, it only takes <span class="bbcode-i">one</span> stray visit to blow your whole logs apart and get you insta-lynched.  (And, of course, any claim, no matter how far-fetched, can get past a sufficiently careless and inattentitive court - but we can’t balance the game around that.)</p>
<p>Like, can you theoretically claim Observer?  Sure, in the same way that you can claim Noble and hope nobody asks you to use your abilities.  (That’s why I called the category “basically impossible” rather than “literally impossible.”)  But it’s not really a realistic option against competent opponents.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 23:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-41</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ami" data-post="35" data-topic="47422">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ami/40/31302_2.png" class="avatar"> Ami:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>N1-Window Peep</p>
<p>N2-The person who was Lynched D3</p>
<p>N3-person that was lynched D4,</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Only an absolute newbie or an evil trying to pass it off would have window peeked N1. Why on earth would a legitimate observer use a peak on litterally the night where it is both the least likely to find an unseen (as there will only be 2 findables as the first conversion cannot have hit, and all 9 of the starting BD are alive and not converted yet). Not to mention scorned and fool are most likely to use their frames on n1, as that is the night when the most investigatives are alive. Oh and of course, obviously if it’s an unseen game the MM can’t be found yet… meaning there’s litterally only a total of 1 findable unseen.</p>
<p>Then when you go to “dead people that can’t contest”. The dead guy can’t contest, but there’s a 90%+ chance that one of the living guys can contest it. You know who the dead guy visited from his log… but for all you know he was visited by a sheriff, physician and knight that are still alive, and all 3 of those can absolutely call that out.</p>
<p>Now admitted, it can be gotten away with right now up until there is a veterans or ranked mode. as half of players don’t seem to even care to ask for, read logs or even have people do obvious tests. I mean it’s fake claimable in the same way that noble is fake claimable if nobody asks him to force anyone to vote. But realistically with 3 days worth of logs, there is a 90-99% chance that at least 1 living BD has information that can contradict your logs (even if currently there’s so many inexperienced players that you can slide it past them half the time).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 23:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-40</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh yes</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 22:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-39</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Orrr you put in insanely complex unreadable Observer logs which noone can be botherer to verify but look legit cuz they have so much detail</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-38</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I suggest spacing out window peaks, or using your unseen buddies</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-37</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UncannyLuck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Every time I’ve seen that tried the person was hung for only having dead people and/or peeking n1.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aquillion" data-post="26" data-topic="47422">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/psychic-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> Aquillion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Observer: Observer logs flatly require too much information to credibly fake.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just do<br>
N1-Window Peep<br>
N2-The person who was Lynched D3<br>
N3-person that was lynched D4,</p>
<p>Just use the dead’s logs to make more credible info and use dead people because they can’t contest it</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="33" data-topic="47422">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Priest - Anyone usually. Some classes might die and make it harder but for the most part it is much easier to fake a one off result. It also can give you a reason to be night Immune if Unseen calls you out N2 or something as Sorc or Poss.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Priest is kinda hard due to uniqueness. Other than that you are right.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Btw, on the Master rework thread I did an analysis of which additions can be faked:</p>
<p>Priest - Anyone usually. Some classes might die and make it harder but for the most part it is much easier to fake a one off result. It also can give you a reason to be night Immune if Unseen calls you out N2 or something as Sorc or Poss.</p>
<p>Psychic - Converted only. Too meny ways to prove otherwise</p>
<p>Noble - Converted only. If you used PP twice already then you can keep faking him if promoted however.</p>
<p>Scribe - Converted or Possessor. No one else can fake whisper reading.</p>
<p>Steward - Converted. Just like other offensive classes.</p>
<p>Maid - Anyone. If you know factions and can fake Princess you can fake this. Both of those are fairly straightforward to figure out as scum.</p>
<p>Squire - Anyone. However it won’t last forever.</p>
<p>CW - Anyone. His abilitys weren’t changed at all in terms of fakability.</p>
<p>In total this would add 4 classes that could be faked by classes other than their converted versions (counting scribe because of Possessor) And only 1 that can’t (the rest were already there)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/33</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 21:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-33</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Someone suggested a nice buff to Reaper earlier, letting him read the logs of the person he just reaped.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lol, possessor Prince.</p>
<p>If we did that, I’d feel like we’d at least have to buff the Reaper in turn. Seems like a good idea, it would make everyone a bit more paranoid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually suggested giving Possessors a way to copy any ability!  Basically, give the Possessor a day ability called “mimic”, which can only be used while possessing someone.  When activated, it gives you the Day and Night abilities of the class you’re possessing for the current day and the next night (you can use another Day ability that day, so you can actually use one of the abilities you’re faking.)</p>
<p>Some abilities would have to be off-limits (obviously no Prince), but I think it’d be very interesting and would make people far more paranoid about Possessors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You couldn’t have put it better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, unfortunately, looking at that list, the Mercenary and Hunter are the only roles I can see easily making more fakeable without drastic overhauls.  Plus I guess we could discuss whether the Princess really needs WoW and what she would get instead, but it doesn’t come up a huge amount.</p>
<p>Mostly it’s just something to consider when making new ideas or discussing potential changes - we want to make sure they move things towards more fakeable roles, or at least (most importantly) don’t reduce the number of fakeable roles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d say for some more claims we should first remove Mercenary notifications (which seems to be pushed by most people. It would be pretty hard to add any more claimable classes without completely redoing them.</p>
<p>I’d personally like to see some changes to Hunter (which I think you suggested) by making it non unique, removing Retribution and reducing wolves. Retribution is just kind of weird anyways.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ami" data-post="25" data-topic="47422" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ami/40/31302_2.png" class="avatar"> Ami:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m pretty good at logical deduction, so this will be biased</p>
<p>Evils actually have to put effort into their logs, while BD does not and if they rush their logs ofc they will be lynched, do your logs one night at a time. Not all in one night and pick a claim from N1 it’ll allow you to swap your claim to something else more believable, but once you claim publicly YOU ARE STUCK WITH IT. Logical Deduction is easier because the days go by fast social deduction is very hard.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve put together this list before, but <span class="bbcode-i">seriously</span>.  Most roles are not credible for a NK / MM to claim, outside of fairly-rare extenuating circumstances or relying on some extremely suspect tricks that most players will see through (ie. only ever targeting dead people.)  The roles you can claim:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Almost Always</span></p>
<p>Court Wizard, Knight, Paladin / Sheriff.  That’s it.<br>
Plus <span class="bbcode-i">maybe</span> Princess, for the Mastermind only, but you can’t WoW, and you’re not Noble, which can trip you up easily.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Rarely, or with significant risk</span><br>
Hunter:  Unique, and if a real hunter exists they’ll happily be the first to upvote you.  Can prove with bleed.<br>
Physician / Alchemist: Works at first, but you’ll get caught when asked to cure poison / bleed.<br>
Butler / Drunk:  Logs are not really fakeable.  People will ask someone to confirm your logs, and lynch you if nobody does.  Butler can also be asked to poison king, while Drunk’s deb makes his identity glaringly obvious.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Basically Impossible</span></p>
<p>Noble: Gets asked to prove by forcing someone to vote.<br>
Observer: Observer logs flatly require too much information to credibly fake.<br>
Prince:  Logs impossible to fake, real prince will kill you anyway.<br>
Psychic: Unique, logs impossible to fake, multiple ways to prove instantly.<br>
Mercenary: Produces messages for his target.<br>
Fool / Scorned: Not something you claim directly, but theoretically an option.  Gets you CSed, or executed by the King or Prince.</p>
<p>…you may occasionally be able to slip one of these impossible claims past an inattentive court, or happen to have an Aristocrat / Apostle who can help you prove at the exact moment you need to.  And you can technically give some of them to the Prince / Psychic, if you don’t mind dying the moment it comes up publicly.  But that’s basically luck, not skill, and it’s not at all reliable.  Realistically, in any given game, there are 3 or 4 Mastermind / NK claims that will hold up to any sort of scrutiny, and that’s being generous and giving you Princess.  That is not enough.</p>
<p>It’s not about effort.  No amount of “effort” will let the starting MM or an NK successfully duplicate Noble abilities, or pretend to be an Observer, or produce a Butler / Drunk will that BD will confirm.  The fact is that what people are calling logical deduction isn’t <span class="bbcode-i">deduction</span> at all - it’s just a matter of whether the BD follows a very simple, straightforward, mindless checklist of ways to verify roles or not.  If you claim something that they could confirm, as the MM or NK, you’re left crossing your fingers hoping they don’t check you, and the only way you can win is if they’re stupid like that.  For <span class="bbcode-i">them</span>, there is no logic and no deduction, just one binary choice with an obvious best option.  Deduction requires more complicated interactions, which means you can’t give BD easy ways to verify claims.</p>
<p>I feel that part of the problem is that some players are very proud of themselves for figuring out and reliably applying those same few linear tests; it <span class="bbcode-i">feels</span> like you’re some genius master of deduction for constantly spotting the dumb MMs who try to slip a Butler log past you.  But the fact is that that doesn’t really qualify as meaningful deduction - it’s too obvious, to the point where it could be seen as almost automatic among skilled players.</p>
<p>If you want interesting deductions, then evils need claims that can rely on more abstract and unique inferences in order to spot.  For instance, “why didn’t you protect XYZ?” is an interesting way to catch a Knight claim - they can give you a reason, then it’s up to the court to assess the validity of that reason and whether they trust it.  The best claims will allow for lies piled on lies like that, with BD having a lot of possible places to pull the thread, but no one obvious way to instantly and effortlessly figure out the truth.  Right now, the game rarely requires that level of deduction because the usable MM / NK claims are so limited that you can just lynch everyone claiming them in the late game if you haven’t found the MM / NK yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pretty good at logical deduction, so this will be biased<br>
Evils actually have to put effort into their logs, while BD does not and if they rush their logs ofc they will be lynched, do your logs one night at a time. Not all in one night and pick a claim from N1 it’ll allow you to swap your claim to something else more believable, but once you claim publicly YOU ARE STUCK WITH IT. Logical Deduction is easier because the days go by fast social deduction is very hard.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 17:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is commonly referred to as “Tactical” kills, and it is something I have been considering for a while.</p>
<p>Implementing it would, however, be tricky, as the Assassin does more than just kill.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DanielHatesGames" data-post="1" data-topic="47422">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/reaper-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> DanielHatesGames:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The problem lies in the logical deduction  part. There are so many night actions and ways to cross-reference claims. For example, you can claim Physician as Assassin, but then a Princess can see you are killer/off and you instantly get exed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>While I agree with many your general points… I think the problem is a bit different there. I have no problem with investigative abilities being mostly you’re screwed. It’s where the challange does come in. Can the investigative convince everyone it’s actually investigative… can evils counterclaim or undermine the investigative. Not to mention the general skill that comes from scum reading vs staying under the radar.</p>
<p>That being said the real problem to me at least, is the 80% of classes that leave blatently obvious footprints of occupied people, uncontestable observer logs, trail of debauched people, psychic links, self confirming accusation tweaks etc… poison/bleed healing, being unique etc… the window of claimable classes is pretty much just 4-5 classes, hence creating the lul-knight problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 16:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have an idea, though it relies on the possibility of two night abilities being used the same night.  What if we get rid of Assassin and replace one of the converted classes’ abilities with kill?  So the Nightwatch could for example kill someone and follow someone else the same night.  So instead of being promoted (more like demoted) to Assassin, you would simply have one of your abilities replaced with an attack.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Out of those you mention, only the NK needs to survive to the end of the game to win. MM has his passives and reappearance to carry him through the early game. Reaper and Possessor have chill and jump to get through the day phase and Sorcerer can ally itself with evil to get enough numbers.</p>
<p>I’m playing too much devil’s advocate here though. What ToL needs in my opinion is less general confirmability and more confirmability at high cost. Great examples are butler’s poison and hunters wolf. It confirms them beyond any doubt, but also severely jeopardizes whoever they target and in butler’s case itself. Something like having telepathy prevent linking that night, seems like a good tradeoff.</p>
<p>I don’t think psy should be nerfed too hard though, since he is one of the BD power roles along with prince. I’d prefer things like not having a message show up if you try to occ/deb an occupy immune. Drunks have HH to prove and butlers have their poison. Making hunter non-unique so it becomes a valid fake claim. Weakening Observer’s follow by only showing who their target visits and it needing to be empowered through some limited use day ability to show who visits their target as well. Noble’s force accuse only be visible to who is being forced to accuse and silent to everyone else.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 16:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lying as Evil is too difficult</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with the OP.  Throne of Lies is a great game but it still suffers in that it’s driven too much by logical deduction than social deduction.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Not to mention Day 1 debs or investigations. Good luck. There is zero counter play.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This is especially a problem for Reaper, as it makes him instantly lose the game.  Lategame debs can be countered though by baiting a drunk to deb you and then doing nothing that night (I won as Reaper by doing that).</p>
<p>Reaper should have some sort of counterplay to n1 debs.  No idea how though.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>No one knows what the role composition of the match is, so you can’t plan your counter claims and craft appropriate lies.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If the game gives information about role composition, it should only be given to evils and definitely not BD.  If it’s given to BD it defeats the entire purpose of what you are proposing.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Too many players means that BD can afford bad exes. In fact, bad exes are typically good for BD, as it narrows down the evil players that have shaky enough claims as it is.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Actually bad exes hurt BD and help the evil faction, since evil can replenish their numbers but BD can’t.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The majority of classes are impossible to claim without someone pointing out your shit logs.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This is true, and I think the solution to this is to give evils more abilities to confirm themselves.  Maybe increase the population limit of Unseen to 4 so we can keep confirmable Unseen in the game without having them immediately being turned into Assassin.  A Drunk that gets converted to Assassin is absolutely screwed if he gets put on stand, and this is because he didn’t deb or happy hour anyone that night.  This has nothing to do with social deduction.  If however an Alcoholic gets put on stand, the court can debate why is he happy houring the Sheriff who’s been carrying the game, and THIS is social deduction.  We need more of it.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Reduce lobby count to 14</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Please no, not sure how this helps at all.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Show the class composition of each game (instead of the vague guidelines it has now)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Only to the evil factions.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Allowing logical deduction alone to reliably solve things is bad for social deduction games; it can support very low-level play early on, but as soon as players master the mechanics, it makes the game boring, repetitive, and uninteresting, because experienced players will spot an “imperfect claim” instantly 100% of the time.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This 100%.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>While I agree a little bit with the fact that logical deduction might overrule the social deduction too much, I think you really neglected to mention a key part of ToL: conversion. That Physician that just healed the prince and you thought you could trust, might just be the new assassin that will stab him in the back. The psychic telepathy message that everyone always trusts, woops a frame from illusionist. Yes, the BD will always find you eventually given enough uses of their night abilities, however you should not allow the game to get there. It’s a race to the clock for both factions. Besides, I think too many unseen members forget that they are and should be expendable once they reach the 3 member limit, since MM has to convert again to kill most efficiently. Plus the very existence of the scorned always gives you some claimspace.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Unfortunately Unseen converted classes are rare because of the 3 member limit.  It should be increased to 4 and then other things changed  to compensate if this turns out to be overpowered for evil.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Possessors also flatly have to have the Psychic die to have any chance at all.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This is a problem with the Possessor that for some reason doesn’t look like it will be fixed anytime soon.  The psychic hardcounters possessor even though this isn’t intended and nothing is being done about it.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Honestly, this is part of the reason I’m so against splitting the community with a “Veterans” lobby, etc.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>When only experienced players play, any evil ploy will just fall apart. There will be “accepted” fake logs, game theory, etc. Which removes fun.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The problems should be fixed, not masked by mixing noobs with experienced players just so noobs can throw games in evil’s favor.  I want a vets lobby in spite of these problems, and it will actually highlight these problems so they can be dealt with more efficiently.  I don’t think it’s fun knowing I won as evil only because my opponents didn’t understand how the game works.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 15:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-47422-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lying-as-evil-is-too-difficult/47422.rss">Lying as Evil is too difficult</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
