<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sellsword not preventing Alchemist&#39;s Tar Potion</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922</link>
    <description>#### What happened? I was playing as Sellsword and guarded someone who an Alchemist occupied. Instead of the Alchemist being blocked and the person being able to do their action, the person that the Alchemist occupied was occupied but they also weren&#39;t according to the message they got, I can&#39;t remember exactly what it was.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen? The Alchemist would have been prevented and the person should have been able to execute the action just fine.

#### Steps to reproduce:
1. Have an Alchemist occupy someone
2. Have a Sellsword guard that same person
3. See what shows up for the person that was occupied and guarded

#### Comments: I don&#39;t know if it is with just the Alchemist&#39;s occupy or Butler and Invoker occupies too. I also don&#39;t know if it is the same with the Alchemist&#39;s other potions.

#### Update: I just had a game as Hunter where a Sellsword said they guarded me, but I got 2 messages saying someone tried to redirect me but I was immune. There was an Invoker in the game. The Sellsword was pretty open about being a Sellsword so I don&#39;t think he lied about guarding me. He was killed by prince, so that is his real class. I think it is the same situation, so the problem probably stems from occupying/redirection and not the Alchemist. It should have just stopped the Invoker and I shouldn&#39;t get a message, let alone 2. For this one I do have a screenshot: https://imgur.com/AKKynMJ</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 14:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sellsword not preventing Alchemist&#39;s Tar Potion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A) maybe the person lied and the alchemsit didn’t occupy them.<br>
B) maybe they were occupied through a different method like butler party</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 14:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72922-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922.rss">Sellsword not preventing Alchemist&#39;s Tar Potion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sellsword not preventing Alchemist&#39;s Tar Potion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NosduhYons]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened? I was playing as Sellsword and guarded someone who an Alchemist occupied. Instead of the Alchemist being blocked and the person being able to do their action, the person that the Alchemist occupied was occupied but they also weren’t according to the message they got, I can’t remember exactly what it was.</h4>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen? The Alchemist would have been prevented and the person should have been able to execute the action just fine.</h4>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<ol>
<li>Have an Alchemist occupy someone</li>
<li>Have a Sellsword guard that same person</li>
<li>See what shows up for the person that was occupied and guarded</li>
</ol>
<h4>Comments: I don’t know if it is with just the Alchemist’s occupy or Butler and Invoker occupies too. I also don’t know if it is the same with the Alchemist’s other potions.</h4>
<h4>Update: I just had a game as Hunter where a Sellsword said they guarded me, but I got 2 messages saying someone tried to redirect me but I was immune. There was an Invoker in the game. The Sellsword was pretty open about being a Sellsword so I don’t think he lied about guarding me. He was killed by prince, so that is his real class. I think it is the same situation, so the problem probably stems from occupying/redirection and not the Alchemist. It should have just stopped the Invoker and I shouldn’t get a message, let alone 2. For this one I do have a screenshot: <a href="https://imgur.com/AKKynMJ" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://imgur.com/AKKynMJ</a>
</h4>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-72922-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sellsword-not-preventing-alchemists-tar-potion/72922.rss">Sellsword not preventing Alchemist&#39;s Tar Potion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
