<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Simple Role Flag</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867</link>
    <description>To put it short and simple, the influx of new players due to the Steam summer sale is basically causing more toxicity to pile up as they play badly, which shouldn&#39;t come to be a surprise, but this problem is stupidly magnified whenever they end up getting a class that happens to be a cornerstone of their faction. So I propose a Simple Role system in order to mitigate this problem and prevent new players from getting too demanding roles before they even know how to even play the game, which in turn would stop them from being flamed over their poor plays strongly impacting the game thanks to the importance of their classes.

The Simple Role flag should be a toggle-able option in the account settings tab and when checked it will prevent the player from getting the King, the Prince, and the Mastermind as roles provided that at least one other player is not under this flag and they do not already have one of the SR classes as their own. In addition, players will be automatically flagged under this system if they have yet to play an _N_ number of games, have left many games recently, or have several reports against them.

Essentially, this flag would prevent new or toxic players, or allow those who want to play a game casually, to roll key classes in the game and severely hinder their faction by either ignorance, malice, or just because they wanted a relaxing game rather than being expected to carry as Prince. This in turn should both lower the toxicity and increase the quality of ToL matches.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 21:13:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Simple Role Flag</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Alice" data-post="4" data-topic="68867">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/alice/40/32176_2.png" class="avatar"> Alice:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wait, what? Was this silently added recently or did I miss a patch?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think they were privately added because when I checked an old patch it said</p>
<p>“Added King to classes that newer player’s can get”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 21:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68867-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867.rss">Simple Role Flag</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Simple Role Flag</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wait, what? Was this silently added recently or did I miss a patch? Back when I started long ago my first two classes were Prince and King. I didn’t complete screw up as I’ve had past experiences in social deduction games but I’m quite sure I haven’t seen any patch notes like this before.</p>
<p>Plus, expanding it to a player settings could be convenient for players who don’t want to play a  heavy-duty classes. Or preventing people with frequent leaving due to connectivity issues.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 20:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68867-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867.rss">Simple Role Flag</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Simple Role Flag</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As Mole said this is already quietly a thing</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 20:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68867-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867.rss">Simple Role Flag</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Simple Role Flag</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>New players already can’t be King, MM, CL or Prince</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 19:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68867-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867.rss">Simple Role Flag</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Simple Role Flag</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To put it short and simple, the influx of new players due to the Steam summer sale is basically causing more toxicity to pile up as they play badly, which shouldn’t come to be a surprise, but this problem is stupidly magnified whenever they end up getting a class that happens to be a cornerstone of their faction. So I propose a Simple Role system in order to mitigate this problem and prevent new players from getting too demanding roles before they even know how to even play the game, which in turn would stop them from being flamed over their poor plays strongly impacting the game thanks to the importance of their classes.</p>
<p>The Simple Role flag should be a toggle-able option in the account settings tab and when checked it will prevent the player from getting the King, the Prince, and the Mastermind as roles provided that at least one other player is not under this flag and they do not already have one of the SR classes as their own. In addition, players will be automatically flagged under this system if they have yet to play an <em>N</em> number of games, have left many games recently, or have several reports against them.</p>
<p>Essentially, this flag would prevent new or toxic players, or allow those who want to play a game casually, to roll key classes in the game and severely hinder their faction by either ignorance, malice, or just because they wanted a relaxing game rather than being expected to carry as Prince. This in turn should both lower the toxicity and increase the quality of ToL matches.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 19:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68867-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/simple-role-flag/68867.rss">Simple Role Flag</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
