<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Translation API Implemenation</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664</link>
    <description>If you could somehow implement one of the numerous translation APIs out there, it would surely be useful. If it were implemented, you wouldn&#39;t have to worry about region specific servers which separate the different player bases. I.e. With a translation API implemented into the game&#39;s linguistic processor, the doors open for more connection of peers- it would automatically translate the languages into the player&#39;s native language, and vice versa. I.e. A (for example) Russian could talk to someone from Portugal without even knowing, which could possibly also prevent prejudice.  

[If you google &quot;Translation API&quot;](http://lmgtfy.com/?q=Translation+API), you will see that many APIs designed for just this purpose have already been developed.

I believe it would be well appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 03:53:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Translation API Implemenation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Reviving thread/suggestion as language discrimination has begun. Idk if that’s what the proper word for it is but, rule 8. Ok, yes I’m only fully fluent In English personally, but I could see how this could affect those that can’t speak English very well. And it’s an awesome game, so I’d hate to see them unable to enjoy it fully due to lack of being able to communicate with teammates. Again, language “discrimination” isn’t probably the proper word, I just don’t really know what the proper term, if there is one, would be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 03:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-664-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664.rss">Translation API Implemenation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Translation API Implemenation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s a wonderful idea, but I don’t think many games were successful doing this. I’d definitely like to poke it in the future just for testing purposes. However, not until a release is stable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 01:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-664-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664.rss">Translation API Implemenation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Translation API Implemenation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[robflop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While this is a good idea, usually what’s lacking is the functionality of the APIs.</p>
<p>A possible problem would be that the API output is incorrect and you end up “saying” something you may never had intended to.</p>
<p>Also, I assume professional translation APIs aren’t free to use, so that would add costs in the long run.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 19:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-664-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664.rss">Translation API Implemenation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Translation API Implemenation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dooku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you could somehow implement one of the numerous translation APIs out there, it would surely be useful. If it were implemented, you wouldn’t have to worry about region specific servers which separate the different player bases. I.e. With a translation API implemented into the game’s linguistic processor, the doors open for more connection of peers- it would automatically translate the languages into the player’s native language, and vice versa. I.e. A (for example) Russian could talk to someone from Portugal without even knowing, which could possibly also prevent prejudice.</p>
<p><a href="http://lmgtfy.com/?q=Translation+API" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">If you google “Translation API”</a>, you will see that many APIs designed for just this purpose have already been developed.</p>
<p>I believe it would be well appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 18:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-664-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/translation-api-implemenation/664.rss">Translation API Implemenation</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
