<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Change Leaving/Rejoining Games</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609</link>
    <description>**Hello!**

I am making this thread because I have sort of a soft complaint to make.
For some months (I believe), players are able to re-enter games that they leave in case they lose connection or have a game crash, which is fair enough, because many games are mixed because of players dropping off.
However, many players leave the game on their own will on purpose as a meta on games.

I recently played a Classic game and the last players alive were 1 Good King (not starting), 1 Prince, 1 Hunter and 1 Mastermind turned Assassin. Basically, King and Prince were between Hunter and Assassin. They voted up the Hunter, since the Assassin left the game and, after pardoning him, they just let the game continue, because they were pretty sure that the Assassin wasn&#39;t the Hunter and had left. But no ... The assassin rejoined to avoid getting up on court and continued his duty. Yes, we did win, but imagine having this happen in a worse situation. I am not against letting people in when they drop off, but I would love if you would make a way so that players who leave on their own will cannot return on the following Night (if it&#39;s Day when they leave) or in the last 5 seconds of the Day. It&#39;s basically broken now. 

**Thanks for your time.**</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 16:11:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Change Leaving/Rejoining Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>I would love if you would make a way so that players who leave on their own will cannot return on the following Night (if it’s Day when they leave) or in the last 5 seconds of the Day.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Is there a way to even check whether the player left of their own free will?  I mean you can’t tell whether they unplugged their router on purpose or not <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/yum.png?v=9" title=":yum:" class="emoji" alt=":yum:"></p>
<p>My opinion on this issue is not allow any players to rejoin, period.  Because the number of players who genuinely lose connection on accident and then successfully rejoin is vastly dwarfed by the number of players who never reconnect but stay stuck in a connecting/disconnecting cycle that negatively impacts the game by having what is practically a second reaped person if the game happens to be a reaper game.</p>
<p>I mean yesterday I just won as Reaper because there were 2 reaped people, the guy I reaped and the disconnected one who never died until I reaped him for real <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/yum.png?v=9" title=":yum:" class="emoji" alt=":yum:">  Because of this disconnected person, the court could never vote me up even though I admitted to being Reaper</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66609-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609.rss">Change Leaving/Rejoining Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change Leaving/Rejoining Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But some people genuinely lose connection and when you lose connection most of the time you do not connect back. It’s happen to me a few times, but when some people have bad internet connection I would assume it would happen to those players more often.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 14:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66609-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609.rss">Change Leaving/Rejoining Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change Leaving/Rejoining Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[deltaes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Hello!</strong></p>
<p>I am making this thread because I have sort of a soft complaint to make.<br>
For some months (I believe), players are able to re-enter games that they leave in case they lose connection or have a game crash, which is fair enough, because many games are mixed because of players dropping off.<br>
However, many players leave the game on their own will on purpose as a meta on games.</p>
<p>I recently played a Classic game and the last players alive were 1 Good King (not starting), 1 Prince, 1 Hunter and 1 Mastermind turned Assassin. Basically, King and Prince were between Hunter and Assassin. They voted up the Hunter, since the Assassin left the game and, after pardoning him, they just let the game continue, because they were pretty sure that the Assassin wasn’t the Hunter and had left. But no … The assassin rejoined to avoid getting up on court and continued his duty. Yes, we did win, but imagine having this happen in a worse situation. I am not against letting people in when they drop off, but I would love if you would make a way so that players who leave on their own will cannot return on the following Night (if it’s Day when they leave) or in the last 5 seconds of the Day. It’s basically broken now.</p>
<p><strong>Thanks for your time.</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 11:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66609-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/change-leaving-rejoining-games/66609.rss">Change Leaving/Rejoining Games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
