<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Legendary Swordsman [Neutral Class] not serius fanmade</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686</link>
    <description>**The Legendary Swordsman** Neutral offensive/supp

**Swordsman of Legends (Passive)** Death immune as long as your not occcupied 
**Protective (Passive)**  You will protect your trainee when you are training with him making all abilites targeting him to be targeting you instead.

**Claiming a Favor (Day)** Claim a favor the king ows you force pardoning your trainee and making him unable to be voted up again today.
**Start Training (Day)** Take your trainee to your training ground tonight giving him new abilites for the night. -unlimited uses 1 day cooldown.

**Spar (Night)** Spar with a player occuping them and informing you if there a offensive or killer class
example; if there not it will say they have no potential
if  there killer it will say the look in there eyes there movements the are a killer class
if there a offensive class it will say there defensive tactics there rough hands the are a offensive class- Infinite uses
**Recruit (Night)** make a offensive or killer class your trainee in edition to there normal class does not work on magic users. -2 uses. will commit suicide if this ability has no charge left and your trainee is dead. you may only have 1 trainee at a time
Wincon: see your trainee finish all his training

**The Trainee** offensive/killer class facation based on what he is converted 
**In training (Passive)** During nights where **Start training** is used you need to use your night abilites (this passive replaces your currents passive expect retrubution)
**Will Training (Night)** Become occupy and redirection immune but you are occupied the following night bypasses occupy immunity -1 use. After using this ability it is replaced with **Endurens Training**
**Endurens Training (Night)** Become death immune but you will bleed and die in 1 day if you are not healed -1 use. after using this ability its replaced with **Combat Training**
**Combat Training (Night)** Your attacks now bypass death immunty but you cannot attack player during the next night-1 use. If you dont have a ability wich can attack a player your first ability is replaced with **Strike** instead and you gain another charge of this ability
**Strike (Night)** Kill a player- infinite uses</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 08:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Legendary Swordsman [Neutral Class] not serius fanmade</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[justaneut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah let me just fix that bud</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 08:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71686-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686.rss">The Legendary Swordsman [Neutral Class] not serius fanmade</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Legendary Swordsman [Neutral Class] not serius fanmade</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lily]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank god it’s not <strong>Serius</strong>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 07:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71686-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686.rss">The Legendary Swordsman [Neutral Class] not serius fanmade</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Legendary Swordsman [Neutral Class] not serius fanmade</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[justaneut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Legendary Swordsman</strong> Neutral offensive/supp</p>
<p><strong>Swordsman of Legends (Passive)</strong> Death immune as long as your not occcupied<br>
<strong>Protective (Passive)</strong>  You will protect your trainee when you are training with him making all abilites targeting him to be targeting you instead.</p>
<p><strong>Claiming a Favor (Day)</strong> Claim a favor the king ows you force pardoning your trainee and making him unable to be voted up again today.<br>
<strong>Start Training (Day)</strong> Take your trainee to your training ground tonight giving him new abilites for the night. -unlimited uses 1 day cooldown.</p>
<p><strong>Spar (Night)</strong> Spar with a player occuping them and informing you if there a offensive or killer class<br>
example; if there not it will say they have no potential<br>
if  there killer it will say the look in there eyes there movements the are a killer class<br>
if there a offensive class it will say there defensive tactics there rough hands the are a offensive class- Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Recruit (Night)</strong> make a offensive or killer class your trainee in edition to there normal class does not work on magic users. -2 uses. will commit suicide if this ability has no charge left and your trainee is dead. you may only have 1 trainee at a time<br>
Wincon: see your trainee finish all his training</p>
<p><strong>The Trainee</strong> offensive/killer class facation based on what he is converted<br>
<strong>In training (Passive)</strong> During nights where <strong>Start training</strong> is used you need to use your night abilites (this passive replaces your currents passive expect retrubution)<br>
<strong>Will Training (Night)</strong> Become occupy and redirection immune but you are occupied the following night bypasses occupy immunity -1 use. After using this ability it is replaced with <strong>Endurens Training</strong><br>
<strong>Endurens Training (Night)</strong> Become death immune but you will bleed and die in 1 day if you are not healed -1 use. after using this ability its replaced with <strong>Combat Training</strong><br>
<strong>Combat Training (Night)</strong> Your attacks now bypass death immunty but you cannot attack player during the next night-1 use. If you dont have a ability wich can attack a player your first ability is replaced with <strong>Strike</strong> instead and you gain another charge of this ability<br>
<strong>Strike (Night)</strong> Kill a player- infinite uses</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-71686-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-legendary-swordsman-neutral-class-not-serius-fanmade/71686.rss">The Legendary Swordsman [Neutral Class] not serius fanmade</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
