<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261</link>
    <description>**Name**: Princesses of Eso&#39;Ter

- **Faction**: Neutral
- **Class Type**: Killer / Offensive
- **Passive**: Deflects Death (temporary)
- If Aluna is dead, your visits can be seen and you will lose [Haunting of Eso&#39;Ter]
- If Olena is dead, you will lose [Make Love Not War] and [Plague of Eso&#39;Ter]

##Sister #1 - Aluna (Spectral)

####Night Ability:
&gt; **Haunting of Eso&#39;Ter (2 uses)**: Pick 2 targets, if either leaves their room they will be converted into a horseman. When Elona next attacks, the horsemen will attack the targets adjacent to hers. Additionally, you cannot use Olena&#39;s [Plague of Eso`Ter] until the Horseman have been used. If you are prevented from visiting your target that night, the horseman will be depleted.

####Passive:
&gt; **Spectral Guise**: You walk through the void with your sisters, hiding their visits.

##Sister #2 - Olena (Spectral)

#### Day Ability:
&gt; **Make Love Not War (1 use)**: The sisters appear peaceful to investigative targets. Choose a class-type to appear as to investigative abilities for the night. You will appear as Blue Dragon to Faction determining abilities for that night, as well.

#### Night Ability:
&gt; **Plague of Eso&#39;Ter (2 uses)**: You may choose 2 targets. The Horseman will infect those targets, causing them to pledge allegiance to (Cult/Unseen) that night and the next. You cannot use Aluna&#39;s [Haunting of Eso&#39;Ter] the next night.

##Sister #3 - Elona (Alive)

####Passive:
&gt; **Life Is Fleeting (2 charges)**: If Attacked, you will kill your attacker. Each time you deflect an attack, you lose a sister. If you are the only sister alive, you will not deflect any attacks and will die.
- [Rage of Eso&#39;Ter]: IF Elona is the only attacker left, her attacks will be guaranteed to kill her target.

#### Night Ability:
&gt; **Spectral Horseman**: Summon a Spectral Horseman from the ether to attack your target. Aluna and Olena can empower the Horseman.

##Lore: 
&gt; As Royalty of the Blue Dragon, they were always a target of the lessers. A converted Knight and a Mercenary captured their carriage and turned them over to the army of Mithras for gold. They were tortured for weeks and held for Ransom, but their Father never came. Eventually, Aluna and Olena died from ailments, leaving only Elona to see through the end of their days.

&gt; Aluna, alone and delirious, hears the calls of her sisters late one night. They provide a specific set of instructions -- chants even -- which allow her to   slip into the Ether, where Aluna and Olena are. They tell her of Spectral Horseman that they&#39;ve come into power over, and how they can be used to do their bidding in the ether. 

&gt; Elona soon learns that she&#39;s able to control the Spectral Horseman outside of the Ether and notifies her sisters at night. They devise a plan for Elona to escape the shackles of her confinement, kill their captors, and seek vengeance over the lands that turned on them.

This was my attempt at an NK that is a bit more complex in play style, risky, and also exposes themselves more than other NK&#39;s. They&#39;re not occupy immune, and they can be killed as well. Furthermore, they lose abilities and have to take advantages of exposures in the court in order to win.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 20:25:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elemfao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the tip! I’ll change the name and update the Lore.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 20:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73261-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261.rss">[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I recommend changing the name because of this gets added it’s just gonna confuse people and/or annoy them if they have to keep specifying what kind of princess</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 07:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73261-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261.rss">[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elemfao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apologies for the formatting, I guess Markdown doesn’t work as expected here. Hopefully it’s still readable. I’d love feedback on this as it’s my first attempt at class design.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 22:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73261-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261.rss">[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elemfao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Name</strong>: Princesses of Eso’Ter</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Faction</strong>: Neutral</li>
<li>
<strong>Class Type</strong>: Killer / Offensive</li>
<li>
<strong>Passive</strong>: Deflects Death (temporary)</li>
<li>If Aluna is dead, your visits can be seen and you will lose [Haunting of Eso’Ter]</li>
<li>If Olena is dead, you will lose [Make Love Not War] and [Plague of Eso’Ter]</li>
</ul>
<p>#<span class="hashtag">#Sister</span> <span class="hashtag">#1</span> - Aluna (Spectral)</p>
<p>###<span class="hashtag">#Night</span> Ability:</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Haunting of Eso’Ter (2 uses)</strong>: Pick 2 targets, if either leaves their room they will be converted into a horseman. When Elona next attacks, the horsemen will attack the targets adjacent to hers. Additionally, you cannot use Olena’s [Plague of Eso`Ter] until the Horseman have been used. If you are prevented from visiting your target that night, the horseman will be depleted.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>###<span class="hashtag">#Passive:</span></p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Spectral Guise</strong>: You walk through the void with your sisters, hiding their visits.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>#<span class="hashtag">#Sister</span> <span class="hashtag">#2</span> - Olena (Spectral)</p>
<h4>Day Ability:</h4>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Make Love Not War (1 use)</strong>: The sisters appear peaceful to investigative targets. Choose a class-type to appear as to investigative abilities for the night. You will appear as Blue Dragon to Faction determining abilities for that night, as well.</p>
</blockquote>
<h4>Night Ability:</h4>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Plague of Eso’Ter (2 uses)</strong>: You may choose 2 targets. The Horseman will infect those targets, causing them to pledge allegiance to (Cult/Unseen) that night and the next. You cannot use Aluna’s [Haunting of Eso’Ter] the next night.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>#<span class="hashtag">#Sister</span> <span class="hashtag">#3</span> - Elona (Alive)</p>
<p>###<span class="hashtag">#Passive:</span></p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Life Is Fleeting (2 charges)</strong>: If Attacked, you will kill your attacker. Each time you deflect an attack, you lose a sister. If you are the only sister alive, you will not deflect any attacks and will die.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>[Rage of Eso’Ter]: IF Elona is the only attacker left, her attacks will be guaranteed to kill her target.</li>
</ul>
<h4>Night Ability:</h4>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Spectral Horseman</strong>: Summon a Spectral Horseman from the ether to attack your target. Aluna and Olena can empower the Horseman.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>#<span class="hashtag">#Lore:</span></p>
<blockquote>
<p>As Royalty of the Blue Dragon, they were always a target of the lessers. A converted Knight and a Mercenary captured their carriage and turned them over to the army of Mithras for gold. They were tortured for weeks and held for Ransom, but their Father never came. Eventually, Aluna and Olena died from ailments, leaving only Elona to see through the end of their days.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Aluna, alone and delirious, hears the calls of her sisters late one night. They provide a specific set of instructions – chants even – which allow her to   slip into the Ether, where Aluna and Olena are. They tell her of Spectral Horseman that they’ve come into power over, and how they can be used to do their bidding in the ether.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Elona soon learns that she’s able to control the Spectral Horseman outside of the Ether and notifies her sisters at night. They devise a plan for Elona to escape the shackles of her confinement, kill their captors, and seek vengeance over the lands that turned on them.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This was my attempt at an NK that is a bit more complex in play style, risky, and also exposes themselves more than other NK’s. They’re not occupy immune, and they can be killed as well. Furthermore, they lose abilities and have to take advantages of exposures in the court in order to win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 22:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73261-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-princesses-of-esoter-nk/73261.rss">[Class Suggestion] Princesses (of Eso&#39;Ter) - NK</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
