<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Suggestion] Add a confirmation box prior to Item Shop Transaction</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560</link>
    <description>Greetings Imperium42 and Boslof:

To begin thanks for bring this game to the stream market.  For the time I&#39;ve committed to Throne of Lies so far, I&#39;ve overall enjoyed the experience. I had multiple pieces of feedback but wasn&#39;t sure if a single thread would be best or multiple threads with each item.  For now I&#39;ll create a separate thread for each item. Also I apologize if I miss any information as this is my first post on the forums. Below is an idea, though not sure if its a solid one, or how high on the priority list this would be.

Premise: As a ToL player, I would like to be presented with a confirmation box prior to committing to an Item Shop transaction.

Acceptance Criteria:
*Action occurs on the &quot;Customize Item Shop screen&quot; for the &quot;Weapons&quot; and &quot;Armor&quot; section (does not apply to the &quot;My Char&quot; section)
*After the user clicks any &quot;Buy Now (gp)&quot; button, the user is provided with a confirmation window
*Confirmation window has some text asking the ToL player if they are sure they want to complete the transaction
*Canceling the action on this confirmation window will cause the confirmation window to disappear and the gold associated to the item is not retracted from the user&#39;s account
*Confirming the action will establish the normal flow of operations to complete the transaction of acquiring the item.

Additional Notes:
*The main reason I&#39;m requesting this is that possible others may have done what I did and purchased an item by accidentally clicking on the &quot;Buy Now (gp)&quot; and I&#39;m not sure if there is a route in game to reverse the transaction (which I don&#39;t believe there is). I don&#39;t mind having the item I purchased (the Abaddon Axe)  but I was hoping to get a VoidStone of Corax or one of the Halloween outfits.

Thank you to anyone that takes the time to read this.  Happy deceiving :).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 13:57:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Add a confirmation box prior to Item Shop Transaction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aurelia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I must agree with you regarding the “Confirmation” Need.<br>
Thank you for pointing that out!! <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/blush.png?v=9" title=":blush:" class="emoji" alt=":blush:"> Sorry to hear that you purchased some wrong item <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
But! Play on! and, Lie to your fullest. and win lots of games. That = lots of gold :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 13:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7560-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560.rss">[Suggestion] Add a confirmation box prior to Item Shop Transaction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Add a confirmation box prior to Item Shop Transaction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pandatron76]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Greetings Imperium42 and Boslof:</p>
<p>To begin thanks for bring this game to the stream market.  For the time I’ve committed to Throne of Lies so far, I’ve overall enjoyed the experience. I had multiple pieces of feedback but wasn’t sure if a single thread would be best or multiple threads with each item.  For now I’ll create a separate thread for each item. Also I apologize if I miss any information as this is my first post on the forums. Below is an idea, though not sure if its a solid one, or how high on the priority list this would be.</p>
<p>Premise: As a ToL player, I would like to be presented with a confirmation box prior to committing to an Item Shop transaction.</p>
<p>Acceptance Criteria:<br>
*Action occurs on the “Customize Item Shop screen” for the “Weapons” and “Armor” section (does not apply to the “My Char” section)<br>
*After the user clicks any “Buy Now (gp)” button, the user is provided with a confirmation window<br>
*Confirmation window has some text asking the ToL player if they are sure they want to complete the transaction<br>
*Canceling the action on this confirmation window will cause the confirmation window to disappear and the gold associated to the item is not retracted from the user’s account<br>
*Confirming the action will establish the normal flow of operations to complete the transaction of acquiring the item.</p>
<p>Additional Notes:<br>
*The main reason I’m requesting this is that possible others may have done what I did and purchased an item by accidentally clicking on the “Buy Now (gp)” and I’m not sure if there is a route in game to reverse the transaction (which I don’t believe there is). I don’t mind having the item I purchased (the Abaddon Axe)  but I was hoping to get a VoidStone of Corax or one of the Halloween outfits.</p>
<p>Thank you to anyone that takes the time to read this.  Happy deceiving :).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 22:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7560-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/suggestion-add-a-confirmation-box-prior-to-item-shop-transaction/7560.rss">[Suggestion] Add a confirmation box prior to Item Shop Transaction</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
