<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600</link>
    <description>**Note: This is not a sign-up page. To sign up go to this link: https://forum.imperium42.com/t/fm-poker-mafia-2-signups-open/66245**

[details=&quot;Rules and gameplay&quot;]
:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] What is poker mafia?[/color] &lt;/big&gt;

Poker mafia works like a standard mafia game, with a town faction, an evil faction and a few neutrals. However, in Poker mafia most players start without any abilities and instead must get their abilities by placing a bid on the **Ability Pool**. 

(If you played the first Poker mafia game, you can skip to the &quot;What&#39;s new?&quot; section).

--------------

:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] Tokens[/color] &lt;/big&gt;

**Tokens** are the main currency of the game, and they are used to place bids on the **Ability pool** or to buy tickets for the **Roulette**.
All players get 5 tokens at the beginning of each day, and any unspent tokens will carry over to the next day. You can also get more tokens by winning at the **Roulette**, from **Events** or by **Selling back** your abilities.
Besides normal tokens, there are also 2 types of special tokens that you can only get from certain events or abilities:
* **Roulette tokens:** These can only be used to buy tickets for the **Roulette**.
* **Special tokens:** These can only be used to place a bid on the ability pool. A special token will always get the highest bid on an ability against any amount of normal tokens.

----

:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] Ability Pool[/color] &lt;/big&gt;

Every day there will be an **Ability Pool** with a certain number of abilities. The ability pool works similar to an auction: every player can place any number of tokens on one or more abilities in the pool, and at the end of the day the player that placed the highest bid on each ability will get said ability. Please note that unlike most auctions, **players who lose a bid will NOT get their tokens back.** Also, every bid you place will be private and won&#39;t be revealed to anyone.

The abilities on the pool will change every day, and the number of abilities in the pool will be equal to the number of living players minus 2, with a minimum of 2 abilities. In addition to those abilities, there will always be one extra [color=gold]**Golden**[/color] ability. Golden abilities are really powerful abilities that only have 1 use.

To place a bid on the pool, send a message to the host saying which ability and the number of tokens you want to place, for example: &quot;I want to place 5 tokens on ability #4&quot; or &quot;/bet 3 tokens on 4&quot;.

----
:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] Roulette[/color] &lt;/big&gt;

During the first 24 hours of each day, the **Roulette** will be available. During this time players will be able to buy roulette tickets for 1 token each (you can buy as many tickets as you want). 

**Available tickets:**
 &gt; **Gambling ticket:** This ticket allows you to place a bet on the roulette. You can bet for a color (red or black), a number (between 1 and 3) or a combination of both.
&gt; * Guessing the color correctly gives you 2 tokens for each ticket.
&gt; * Guessing the number correctly gives you 3 tokens for each ticket.
&gt; * Guessing both the color and the number correctly gives you 6 tokens for each ticket.
&gt; 
&gt; **You can buy as many gambling tickets as you want, but you may only place one bet.**
&gt;
&gt; **Rare tickets**: Out of everyone that buys these tickets, only 1 of them will get a price. Only 1 of these will be available each day.
&gt; 
&gt; * **Jackpot ticket**: Every token used to buy tickets from the roulette will be added to the jackpot (roulette tokens count as normal tokens for this purpose). The winner ticket will get all the money in the jackpot. Jackpot starts with 5 tokens.
&gt; * **Golden ticket**: The winner ticket will get a golden ability.
&gt; * **Special ticket**: The winner ticket will get a special token.

----
:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] Daily Events[/color] &lt;/big&gt;

Every day there will be a random event. Events give players new ways to get tokens or abilities. For extra info, see the &quot;List of events&quot; section.

----
:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] Selling back[/color] &lt;/big&gt;

If you don&#39;t like one of your abilities you can sell and it will go back into the ability pool. People will be able to bid for said ability like normal, but the tokens from the highest bid will go towards the seller. Sold abilities will have keep the same amount of remaining uses. You can only sell abilities during the day.

To sell an ability send a message to the host telling him which ability you want to sell. 

----
:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] Using multiple abilities [/color] &lt;/big&gt;

There is no cap to the number of abilities a player can have at the same time, but they can only use one day ability each day and one night ability each night, however every player can pay 3 tokens to use an extra ability. You can do this multiple times but it will cost you 3 tokens each time. You can&#39;t use the same ability multiple times per day/night.

----

:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] What is new?[/color] &lt;/big&gt; 

If you played the first poker mafia, you already know the main mechanics. However, some stuff has changed:
* All classes are able to get abilities from the pool.
* Godfather and all neutrals have been reworked.
* Two more neutrals have been added: The Entertainer and the Loan Shark
* A second NK has been added: The Elite (only 1 NK will spawn, however).
* Townies and mafiosos will be able to choose a gift at the start of the game (see class cards for the gifts they can choose from).
* Gambling events have been removed and replaced with the &quot;Roulette&quot;. 
* There are still daily events, but they no longer involve gambling (see the events section for more information).
* All classes can use more than one day or night abilities, but they must pay 3 tokens for every extra ability besides the first one. (You can&#39;t use the same ability multiple times).
* Godfather no longer needs to use tokens to kill.
* Godfather no longer buys abilities for his mafiosos, instead he can give them tokens.
* Selling an ability back no longer gives you a fixed amount of tokens, instead you get the tokens from the highest bid.

----

:game_die: &lt;big&gt;[color=gold] Special rules and interactions[/color] &lt;/big&gt; 
* Lynching a player will set the day timer to 12 hours. Players can keep discussing and placing bids on the ability pool, but won&#39;t be able to use day abilities during this time. Players cannot sell back abilities during this time either.
* Lynching a player ends the roulette immediately.
* Bids are private and will not be revealed to anyone, except for some specific abilities or events. 
* You can place or change your bets at any point during the daytime.
* Each night, a player will get **ALL** the abilities in which they had the most tokens.
* If there is a tie for the highest bid, the person with the less number of non-starting abilities will get the ability. If that is also a tie, it will be solved by rng.
* There are 8 different ability types: Support, Offensive, Social, Investigative, Killing, Gambling, Passive and Scum. There are also certain classes with starting abilities. These abilities will appear as &quot;Special&quot; to investigators.
* The abilities are given to the player at the beginning of the night, which means they can use them that same night.
* You can have more than 2 day and night abilities. There is no limit.
* If you use all uses on an ability, you will lose said ability. This means investigators won&#39;t be able to see that ability and you won&#39;t be able to sell it. This also applies to &quot;limited&quot; passive abilities such as one-time death immunity.
* You will know whether you got an ability or not at the beginning of the night. If you lose a bid, you will not know who got the ability.
*To prevent angle-shooting, every player is able to delay their actions or bids by asking the host.
*To help with fakeclaiming and prevent angle-shooting, players can ask the host for any flavor text such as &quot;You were occupied last night&quot; etc.
* Every player is able to ask the host any questions regarding mechanics or interactions, but asking for info about the game that can be considered cheating or angleshooting might result in a modkill.
[/details]

----
[details=&quot;Class cards&quot;]
&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=green]**Townie**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Town**
&gt; Choose one of the following gifts at the start of the game:
&gt; * **Abilty gift**: Start the game with a random, non-golden ability. (You can&#39;t get scum abilities from this gift).
&gt; * **Token gift:** Start the game with 3 extra tokens.
&gt; * **Golden gift:** Start the game with a Golden ticket. At the start of the game, one person with a golden ticket will be selected at random and get a free Golden ability. (Golden abilities are powerful one-shot abilities).
&gt;
&gt; **Goal: Defeat Town and the neutral killer** 

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=red]**Mafioso**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Mafia**
&gt; Choose one of the following gifts at the start of the game:
&gt; * **Abilty gift**: Start the game with a random, non-golden ability.
&gt; * **Token gift:** Start the game with 3 extra tokens.
&gt; * **Golden gift:** Start the game with a Golden ticket. At the start of the game, one person with a golden ticket will be selected at random and get a free Golden ability. (Golden abilities are powerful one-shot abilities).
&gt;
&gt; **Goal: Defeat Town and the neutral killer** 



&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=red]**The Godfather**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Mafia**
&gt; **Filthy Rich (Passive)** -  Immune to death at night. You get 3 extra tokens every day. You can give any amount of tokens to your mafiosos. Only the starting Godfather has this passive.
&gt; **Pass the torch (Passive)** - If you die, a mafioso of your choice will become the Godfather.
&gt; **Kill (Night)** - Attack a player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Goal: Defeat Town and the neutral killer**

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=gray]**The Gambler**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral**
&gt; **Lucky (Passive)** - You get 3 roulette tokens every day. (Roulette tokens can only be used to buy tickets for the roulette).
&gt; **Safe Bet (Night)** - Become immune to death tonight. Unlimited uses, but costs 5 tokens to use. Every time you use this ability its cost increases by 3 tokens permanently.
&gt; **Goal: Survive**

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=005050]**The Loan Shark**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral**
&gt; **Bribe (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night. If you are attacked you will give your attacker half of your tokens instead.
&gt; **Loan (Night)** - Give a player any amount of your tokens. Said player will be &quot;In debt&quot; until they pay you twice that amount of tokens. You cannot use this ability on a player that is already &quot;in-debt&quot; - Unlimited uses. 
&gt; **Collect (Night)** - Occupy all &quot;In debt&quot; players. 
&gt; **Goal: Get a total of 30 or more tokens. If you win, you will leave the casino and all players will lose 5 tokens.**

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=lightgreen]**The Leprechaun**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral**
&gt; **Broke (Passive)** - You start the game without tokens.
&gt;**Lucky 7 (Passive)** - Start the game with a random non-golden ability of each type except killer. (Support, Social, Offensive, Investigative, Passive, Gambling and Scum). These abilities cannot be sold and will only have 1 use.
&gt; **Goal: Survive to see town lose**

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=FF0080]**The Entertainer**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral**
&gt;**Last present (Passive)** - Whoever kills you will get a random Golden ability. If you are lynched, the first person to vote you will get it.
&gt; **Birthday present (Day)** - Give a present to a player. They can open it or give it to someone else. Whoever opens it will get a random ability. 3 uses.
&gt; **Exploding Present (Day)** - Give a present to a player. They can open it or give it to someone else. Whoever opens it will die. 1 use.
&gt; **Magic Trick (Night)** - Swap places with another player. Anyone visiting one of you will instead visit the other. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Goal: Survive**

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=brown] **The Cheater** [/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral Killer**
&gt; **Ace under the sleeve (Passive)** - Start the game with 2 Special tokens.
&gt; **Cheating death (Passive)** - Immune to death.
&gt; **All-in (Night)** - Kill a player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Goal: Defeat the Town and Mafia**

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=Gold] **The Elite** [/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Neutral Killer**
&gt; **VIP (Passive)** - Start the game with a Golden Killing ability of your choice. You cannot sell this ability. All of your Golden abilities have unlimited uses but a 1-day cooldown.
&gt; **Untouchable (Passive)** - Immune to death. 
&gt; **Goal: Defeat the Town and Mafia**
[/details]

----
[details=&quot;List of events&quot;]

- **Midas touch:** Today&#39;s ability pool will have 3 golden abilities instead of 1.
- **Mega pool**: Today&#39;s ability pool will have 5 extra common abilities.
- **Wildcard:** Everyone will be able to publicly vote for an event. The event with the most votes will start.
- **Silver medal:** The second highest bid on each ability from today&#39;s pool will also get a copy of said ability.
- **Consolation prize:** At the end of the day, players that didn&#39;t get any abilities from the pool will get a random ability.
- **2-for-1**: For every roulette ticket you buy today, you will get a second one of the same type for free.
- **Roulette madness:** All 3 rare tickets will be available today. Everyone will get 1 free rare ticket of each type.
- **You are special:** Everyone will be able to vote for a player other than themselves. When the majority is reached, said player will get a special token.
- **Gift Rain:** At random times during the day, a &quot;gift&quot; will appear. The first person to write **/claim** in public will get the gift! That person can choose to open the gift or give it to someone else. Each player can only claim 1 gift (whether they keep it or give it to someone else). Any abilities you get from gifts will be given to you immediately. 
- **Pawn shop**: Double any tokens you get from selling back an ability. 
- **Black Market**: Any ability you sell back today will give you 5 tokens and won&#39;t go into the pool.
- **Gift exchange:** Every player is able to select one of their abilities. The players that do will exchange said ability with a random player.
- **Pay to win:** You can pay 5 tokens to instantly gain a random ability. You can do this as many times as you want. 
- **Lynch Piñata:** Whoever is lynched today will have an amount equal to twice their tokens split between the players that voted to lynch them. The first person that voted to lynch them will get twice as many tokens. (Any tokens spent on tickets or on the ability pool will be split as well. This event only affects normal tokens).
- **Charity:** Donate any amount of tokens. An amount equal to twice the tokens donated by all players will be given to the player with least tokens.
[/details]

----
[details=&quot;List of abilities&quot;]

This is the list of abilities that can spawn in the pool. There are currently 140 different abilities.

:first_quarter_moon_with_face: = Night ability
:sun_with_face: = Day ability  
:shield: = Passive ability
:star: = Golden ability (Rare and powerful 1-shot abilities)  

Support
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select two players. Anyone that visits one of them will instead visit the other. Can target yourself. 3 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Heal a player from attacks, doesn&#39;t heal poison or bleeding. 4 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face:Heal a player from poison or bleeding. Doesn&#39;t heal attacks. 4 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Heal a player from attacks, poison or bleeding. 3 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Heal everyone visiting you tonight from attacks, bleeding or poison. 1 use. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Protect a player from all negative night abilities except poison, bleeding and death. 4 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Heal yourself from attacks, poison or bleeding. 2 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Prevent everyone from visiting a player. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Prevent everyone from visiting you. 1 use. 
- :sun_with_face: Protect a player from all negative day abilities except poison, bleeding and death. 3 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Copy one of your abilities and give it to another player. It will have the same remaining uses as the copied ability. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. They will be able to use multiple day ability tomorrow for free. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select a player. They will be able to use multiple night ability tonight for free. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select a player and give them 5 free tokens. Yay! 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Give a player a random common ability. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Give a player other than yourself 7 roulette tokens. These tokens can only be used to buy tickets from the roulette. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face:  Make a player immune to poison and bleeding. Can&#39;t target yourself. 1 use. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Heal up to 3 players from attacks, poison or bleeding. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select a player. Permanently redirect every attack or negative ability used on them to yourself. 1 use. 
- :sun_with_face: :star: Give a Special token to a player other than yourself. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select a player. Refresh all uses of their abilities. 1 use.



Passives
- :shield: You are immune to poison/bleeding. 
- :shield: You will be immune to the next negative ability used on you, except death, poison or bleeding.
- :shield: You are immune to death once. 
- :shield: You will get a random passive ability. At the beginning of each day, said passive will change into a new one.
- :shield: You will get a random common day ability and it will have a single use. At the beginning of each day, said ability will change into a different one.
- :shield: You will get a random common night ability and it will have a single use. At the beginning of each day, said ability will change into a different one.
- :shield: You are immune to occupation and redirection. 
- :shield: If you are lynched, you will immediately kill the first person to accuse you.
- :shield: For every ticket you buy you will get an extra ticket of the same type.
- :shield: Gain 3 more tokens at the beginning of each day.
- :shield: Gain 5 roulette tokens every day. These tokens can only be used to buy tickets for the roulette.
- :shield: Your tokens cannot be decreased or stolen by abilities.
- :shield: Reduces the cost of using extra abilities from 3 tokens to 1 token.
- :shield: Every common ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.
- :shield: If any ability from the pool doesn&#39;t get any bids, you will get that ability.
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on an ability, you will place an extra free token on said ability. 
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on a support ability on the pool, place 1 free token. Every support ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on a social ability on the pool, place 1 free token. Every social ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on an offensive ability on the pool, place 1 free token. Every offensive ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on a killer ability on the pool, place 1 free token. Every killer ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on an investigative ability on the pool, place 1 free token. Every investigative ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on a gambling ability on the pool, place 1 free token. Every gambling ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.
- :shield: Whenever you bid at least 1 token on a scum ability on the pool, place 1 free token. Every scum ability you get from the pool will have 1 extra use.


Scum
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Make yourself or another player appear not suspicious to investigators tonight. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Make a player appear suspicious to investigators tonight. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. They will get false results tonight. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Make a player believe they were attacked and healed. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Make a player believe they are poisoned. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: _with_face: :star: Select a player other than yourself. While you are alive, every investigative ability used on them will give fake results. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Select a player. If they die tonight or are lynched/dayviged, they will appear as a class of your choice and you will be able to write fake logs. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Every investigative ability will get false results tonight. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Rig tomorrow&#39;s roulette. No one will be able to win tokens and whoever wins the rare ticket prize will die. 1 use. 

Offensive
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Occupy a player. 4 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Force a player to target you. You will be immune to attacks redirected this way. 3 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Force a player to target you. You will NOT be immune to attacks redirected this way. 4 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Force a player to target another. Cannot force them to target you or themselves. 3 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Prevent a player from using day abilities for the rest of the day. 3 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select a player. They will be unable to buy tickets for the roulette. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select a player. They won&#39;t be able to bid any tokens in the ability pool today. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Force a player to target themselves. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Redirect the next targeted day ability to you. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select a player. If they use a day ability, they will target themselves. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Occupy everyone visiting you tonight. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player except yourself. Occupy everyone visiting them tonight. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. Redirect all players visiting them to yourself. You will NOT be immune to attacks redirected this way. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player and remove 1 use of all their abilities. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: Make a player instantly lose half of their tokens, rounded down (you won&#39;t know how many they lost). 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Occupy a player through immunity and make them lose all their non-starting passive abilities. 1 use. 
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select a player and an ability from the pool. Force them to bid all their tokens on said ability (doesn&#39;t work on special tokens). 1 use. 
- :sun_with_face: :star: Make a player lose all their tokens (doesn&#39;t include roulette tokens or special tokens). 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Occupy up to 3 players. 1 use.


Social
- :sun_with_face: Send an anonymous message to the court through the host. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Send an anonymous message to another player through the host. 3 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select a player. They cannot vote to lynch anyone today. They will not count towards majority. 3 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Decreases the number of votes required to lynch anyone by 1 today. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Increases the number of votes required to lynch anyone by 1 today. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: You will know which is the next day ability used (you won&#39;t know who used it). 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. You will both be able to send each other two 1000 character messages through the host over the course of the night. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select two players. They will be allowed to send each other two 1000 character messages through the host. The conversation will be later given to you. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Force a player to lynch another. They cannot change or rescind their votes. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. You will get all feedback that player gets tonight. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a dead player. You will get all feedback that player got on the night of their death. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select a player. While you both are alive, you will have a private day and night chat. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select a player. They cannot be lynched today. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select a player. The votes needed to lynch them today will be halved. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select up to 3 players. You and those 3 players will be able to send two 1000 character messages through the host over the course of the night. 1 use.

Killer
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Kill everyone visiting you tonight. You will be immune to attacks. 1 use.
-  :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player other than yourself. Make them death immune and kill everyone visiting them tonight. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Make yourself and a target player start bleeding. You will die in a day unless healed. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Bleed everyone visiting you tonight. You will be immune to attacks. 2 uses.  
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Kill a player. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: The next player to lynch anyone will become poisoned and die in 2 days unless healed. Everyone in court will be notified when this ability is used (they won&#39;t know who did it). 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Protect a player, making them immune to death and killing their attackers. 2 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Attempt to kill a player, if they are Town you will kill yourself instead. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Bleed a player. They will die in 1 day unless healed. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: Poison a player. They will die in 2 days unless healed. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Bleed a player. They will die in 2 days unless healed. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: The next player to use a day ability will become poisoned and die in 2 days unless healed. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select an ability from the pool. At the end of the day, whoever placed the highest bid will become poisoned and die in 2 days unless healed. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Kill a player. Bypasses everything, (healing, occupation, visit prevention, etc). Doesn&#39;t count as visiting and this ability is hidden from investigators. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Kill 2 players. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Kill a player in plain daylight, bypassing everything. Everyone will know you did it. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Imprison a player tonight. You will both be able to send each other two 1000 character messages through the host over the course of the night. You will be able to execute them (bypasses death immunity and prevents others from visiting). 1 use. 


Investigative
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Check if a player is a member of the town. 2 uses. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Check if a player is a member of the mafia. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Check if two players have the same faction. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Check if a player is neutral. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Follow a player to see who they visit. 4 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Follow a player to see who visits them. 4 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Follow a player to see who visits them and who they visit. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: You will be told who the mafia visits tonight. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Find out how many tokens a player has currently (doesn&#39;t detect roulette or special tokens). 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Select a player. You will be alerted if they use a day ability, and the type of the ability (starting abilities appear as special type). 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Reveal one of a player&#39;s random non-starting ability. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Reveal the type of the ability a player uses tonight (starting abilities appear as special type). 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Find out how many non-starting abilities a player has currently. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. You will be alerted if they have any Scum or Killer type abilities (doesn&#39;t detect starting abilities). 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Check the faction of a player. 1 use. 
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Check if a player attacks someone tonight. 3 uses.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Reveal a player&#39;s class to the whole court. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Select an ability from the pool. At the end of the day, you will know who placed a bid there and how many tokens. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Reveal the current highest bids on today&#39;s ability pool. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: :star: Select two players. You will know their faction. 1 use.


Gambling:
- :sun_with_face: Force the host to start a second event of your choice. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Swap all your tokens with another player. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: Select an ability from the pool. If said ability has the lowest bid at the end of the day you will get 5 tokens. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Steal a random ability from a chosen player. It will keep the same number of remaining uses. 1 use.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. You will get a copy of one of their abilities chosen at random (doesn&#39;t copy passives, special or golden abilities). The copied ability will always have 1 use. 3 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select any ability from the list and add it to tomorrow&#39;s ability pool. 2 uses.
- :first_quarter_moon_with_face: Select a player. You will steal any tickets they buy tomorrow. They won&#39;t be notified until the roulette ends. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Remove an ability from today&#39;s ability pool. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: At the end of the day, you will get a copy of the ability that got the lowest bid. 2 uses
- :sun_with_face: At the end of the day, you will get a copy of the ability that got the highest bid. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: Steal 5 tokens from a player and keep them for yourself. 2 uses.
- :sun_with_face: Steal all tokens from a dead player, including roulette or special tokens. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Remove all of your tokens and you will be unable to get tokens for the rest of the game. Gain 3 special tokens. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Remove all of your non-starting abilities. Gain 1 random common ability of each type, for a total of 8 abilities. (Passive, Support, Social, Offensive, Killer, Scum, Investigative and Gambling)
- :sun_with_face: :star: Curse an ability from the pool. No one will be able to get said ability and you will steal the tokens from everyone that placed a bid there (including special tokens). People will be notified when this ability is used, but they won&#39;t know which ability is cursed. 1 use.
- :sun_with_face: :star: Instantly steal any ability from the pool and keep it for yourself. 1 use.
[/details]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 18:52:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I might actually change the name, I just used it since the first game had more of a gambling and casino theme and all that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 18:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Its not really poker have said this from the beginning it might as well be called auction mafia. The poker is for clickbait</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus_Doodalee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Option 3: Make it bastard somehow</p>
<p>for <a class="mention" href="/u/margaret">@Margaret</a> 's benefit ofc</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 05:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Forgot the poll:</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="always" data-poll-type="regular" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="699f8f8fb963cab1986b6d4e1b6de5f3">Keep neutrals</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="5b881bac6517426b576160c86c828c0f">Remove neutrals</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 05:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Of course if I do end up keeping neutrals this probably wont be possible since 4 mafia + neutrals would make the game scumsided.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 05:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That should work</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Was planning to balance this out by giving scum an additional member. Also one of the changes I plan to make is to give mafia a shared token pool that can be used by any mafioso.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m spitballing here</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="psychoneirik" data-post="16" data-topic="65600">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/psychoneirik/40/12950_2.png" class="avatar"> psychoneirik:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In both previous games town has lost majority by day 3 or 4</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep, that’s definitely bad.</p>
<p>No additional kpn is too much harm for scum though.</p>
<hr>
<p>What if scum were able to choose one normal ability each at the start or something to compensate</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Blizer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly, i would keep Loan Shark atleast</p>
<p>Cause he literally doesnt give a shit who is who, and just needs to get his win condition.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My main concern is that this setup may be scumsided. In both previous games town has lost majority by day 3 or 4 and the game turns into a mafia vs nk game, which is one of the reasons I wanted to get rid of neuts, to lower the KPN and give town a better chance of winning.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Blizer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But like</p>
<p>Loan Shark fits so well into this FM</p>
<p>Because he doesnt ever need to be kingmaker, unless its the very end, which is him/her winning at that point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Blizer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For the sake of balance, i do think Lep should go, and maybe NK if you still think its too scumsided.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Blizer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm,</p>
<p>Honestly, The Neutrals in this game are interesting, due to the events and token mechanics.</p>
<p>Gambler is your regular survivor, with a twist</p>
<p>Loan shark is trying to keep the game going long enough to get tokens to get wincon</p>
<p>Lep is JOAT evil neut.</p>
<p>Entertainer is basically RNG itself</p>
<p>Honestly, aside from Lep, Neuts are quite unique to this game, and i do like them</p>
<p>Loan Shark feels like an actual neutral role tbh.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think it should work, but weren’t there nks before which increased kpn to 2?</p>
<p>The game should be fine, but I’m not certain the balance will be near 50-50</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Planning to host Poker Mafia 3 and I’m debating whether I should keep the neutrals or remove them to make the game more simple. The new role distribution would be 12 townies and 4 mafiosos (I also removed godfather). Thoughts?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Finals were over earlier than expected so Im gonna host this soon. I will add a signup page in a few minutes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 16:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is only one event related to lynching, or what other upsides do you mean?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 02:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t realize any downside to lynching other than killing he player I think their needs to be a downside because there is so much upside with events and stuff</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 22:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also I just counted the abilities and realized there are 140 of them lol, didnt expect them to be so many.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Im currently a bit busy IRL so I wont be able to host this yet, but I still wanted to post this early mainly for feedback and to let people know I will be hosting this soon. You can pre-sign up if you want.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 18:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/prejoin</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 18:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/pre-join?</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 18:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dont see signups <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/rage.png?v=9" title=":rage:" class="emoji" alt=":rage:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 18:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m adding this because I want the signup post to be a bit “cleaner” so Im adding all rules and class cards on a separate post. I’m also accepting feedback or suggestions.</p>
<p>I can accept pre-sign ups if people want, but please note that I won’t start the game until around 2 weeks or maybe more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 18:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-65600-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/poker-mafia-2-rules-and-class-cards/65600.rss">Poker Mafia 2: Rules and class cards</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
