<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Disconnect Solutions</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/disconnect-solutions/58041</link>
    <description>So, we know how early disconnects can really screw over the evils (and the merc). So, here&#39;s the changes I&#39;d suggest.

1) If you disconnect D1, you die Night 1.

The sad truth is that ToL has some bugs. One of the big ones is where the game crashes as you try to load into the game, causing you to d1 disconnect and not be able to reconnect until you die. As such, this (and d1 ragequits) will result in a Night 1 death so that new people can be promoted to their roles.

2) If an evil disconnects, Convert won&#39;t go on cooldown after the first successful use. Basically, you can get a new recruit faster after your teammate goes afk so you aren&#39;t quite so hobbled.

3) If the Merc&#39;s target goes AFK Day 1, then he gets a new target at random that night. Guard will guard this target instead if his normal target doesn&#39;t reconnect by the end of the night.

4) If the Neutral Killer goes AFK Day 1, then the assassin gets an extra use of poison and two-for-one, and the cult gets an extra use of Eradicate.

This is primarily because it&#39;s tough to cut through the swathes of BD without an NK to kill some people early. This is to help the evils kill a few more BD (it&#39;s not as good as an NK, but then again, your people won&#39;t be getting murdered either).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 22:14:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/disconnect-solutions/58041.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Disconnect Solutions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Biperspectival]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, we know how early disconnects can really screw over the evils (and the merc). So, here’s the changes I’d suggest.</p>
<ol>
<li>If you disconnect D1, you die Night 1.</li>
</ol>
<p>The sad truth is that ToL has some bugs. One of the big ones is where the game crashes as you try to load into the game, causing you to d1 disconnect and not be able to reconnect until you die. As such, this (and d1 ragequits) will result in a Night 1 death so that new people can be promoted to their roles.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>If an evil disconnects, Convert won’t go on cooldown after the first successful use. Basically, you can get a new recruit faster after your teammate goes afk so you aren’t quite so hobbled.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If the Merc’s target goes AFK Day 1, then he gets a new target at random that night. Guard will guard this target instead if his normal target doesn’t reconnect by the end of the night.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If the Neutral Killer goes AFK Day 1, then the assassin gets an extra use of poison and two-for-one, and the cult gets an extra use of Eradicate.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>This is primarily because it’s tough to cut through the swathes of BD without an NK to kill some people early. This is to help the evils kill a few more BD (it’s not as good as an NK, but then again, your people won’t be getting murdered either).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/disconnect-solutions/58041/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/disconnect-solutions/58041/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 22:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58041-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/disconnect-solutions/58041.rss">Disconnect Solutions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
