<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856</link>
    <description>One of our researchers has recently discovered a cult library. He has found many books in there and has returned them to us. The first one that we will be sharing in the cult&#39;s brainwashing. In the following chapters you will see,

First Cases of Brainwashing: Pg. 3 -11

Evolution of Brainwashing: Pg. 12-22

Types of Brainwashing: Pg. 23-33

_Crossed out_: Pg. 34-40
                                                                                           Pg:1

========================================================
Epilogue. 
We thank you for serving this cult willingly.... or not.
For It appears you have been accepted as a true believer in the lord Mithras!
Along with this, you have the responsibility of showing the weak Blue Dragon
the true way to enlightenment. Whether it be it willingly or not.
In this book we will discuss what to do when they don&#39;t want to join.......
                                                                                        Pg:2                                                                          

===================================================
First Cases of Brainwashing.
To first know the roots of our brainwashing we must first discuss the first brainwashing that occurred. 
The first brainwashing that occurred was on a simple little blue dragon member named Cecily Tolvain. This Blue Dragon member was a Priest, in which we thought would make a good believer in the art of Mithras and the Corax. We were right, and after brainwashing the priest into being a true believer, she began to give the current cult leader more and more power. We eventually sacrificed our loving cult member to kill the king, but to our surprise Mithras allowed us to destroy not 1 but 2 silly believers in the blue dragon. From that day forward, any priest we have converted was referred to as a ritualist! 

Pg: 3

===================================
Our second &quot;official&quot; brainwashing was on the king&#39;s daughter, the princess! Her name was a lovely one which was Isabel Lovall oh how do I love that name. She drove cult to a new road for she was the first queen to side with us, and our first seeker. It was rather simple to get us to join our side. After the death of her father by a Butler poisoning his drink, we were able to get her while she was at her low and make her happy. We asked her to remove her left eye to see into the true will of mithras and seek out our enemies and she did. For she was a child of mithras guided by his will. Due to the foolish blue dragon believing that she was still with them. They elected her as king, which guided more members to us. By allowing her guards to protect our current cult leader. She died the same way she lived, being poisoned by a butler. 
Pg:4

===================================
Our third &quot;Official&quot; brainwashing occurred shortly after the death of our queen of the cult.
A knight that she sent happened to be curious and looked inside of the room. To his surprise there was a wooden table with a small dagger and blood on it.We were standing in the room and he stood in shock. One of our fellow cultists knocked him out and tied him up for our amusement. We originally planned on killing him but Mithras himself convinced us otherwise. He told us that this body was powerful, powerful enough to only slightly go insane while he was possessing it. With this we untied the knight and dressed him in robes. He was completely in shock and in fear for his life for he realized that no matter what he did, he would be a cultist. Mithras possessed this body and told us of the new beginning of the cult for this man would be a invoker to his will. 

Pg:5

==================

_The Next page is filled with torn notes from a dead paladin_


My....My Brother
I love- --- -- ---- 
--- --- -- ---- -- ---- --- cult

---- ---- Insane -- -him 

my job is to destroy the cult

but how can I destroy my brother.

I cant give in to the cult,

I am a destroyer of mithras.

---- uh 

------ why is he

I don&#39;t deserve to wield this sword

For in heart I am truly a priest. 

--I----cant---live---with----this

I-give---into the cult
I praise to mithras.

Pg: 6

===============
HELP ME.
THIS PAGE WAS BLANK. SO I HAVE DECIDED TO WRITE ON IT
I HAVE DISCOVERED THIS JOURNAL AND I AM NOW TRAPPED IN THE CULT LIBRARY
I CAN HERE THE LAUGHS OF THE CULT LEADER.
I DO NOT KNOW WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
THIS IS MOST LIKELY BE THE LAST TIME AND THE FIRST TIME I WRITE IN THIS JOURNAL.
FAREWELL!
Pg.7

===============================================
Fourth Case of Brainwash
A unwanted intruder  

A while ago, a intruder discovered this library while I was writing this book. Heheheh, nobles from distant lands trying to discover our secrets, well i&#39;ll show them our secrets. Well anyway here is the story of hour first Apostle

A noble was sent to explore a new area of the castle one in which was thought to hold secrets of the cult. He loyally accepted this offer, for his dream was to be a lore master for the Blue Dragon. But once he arrived there he found this exact book! I was in the process of getting ready to convert a Psychic but it seems there is no need! That noble got cornered and here&#39;s the fun part. We tied him up! Yes, with this we had our invoker first destroy the noble&#39;s mind. For he was truly a messenger of mithras. If this noble learned that mithras really existed and how powerful he is he might have a fighting chance against the world! After our Invoker was done talking to the scared noble, I happened to ask him if he could be a messenger of the Corax. He responded, &quot;yes&quot;. We happened to now have a Noble on our side ooooh. This was special, so the cult happened to give him a book of the magic of the corax. We also gave him robes to show his true devotion to the cult. After a while we began to see fellow dead cult members, we knew this was because of the Noble who decided to join the cult, for not only was he a messenger of the living, but a messenger of the dead! At the beginning of Shadow Lessons of The Corax, it says that &quot;Only a Apostle can Master these&quot; so we happened to see that this noble mastered it, so we called him a Apostle. isn&#39;t that a great name?
pg: 8

===============================================

HAIL TO THE CORAX IT IS THE DARKNESS THAT CONTROLS THE WORLD! 

THE WEAK BLUE DRAGON WILL NEVER HOLD UP TO THE MIGHT OF THE CORAX
HAHAHAHAHAA
pg: 9

==============================================

_A blank page_

pg:10    

==============================================
Heheheeheehe we have so many members, all of which have been brainwashed, this is great.
Maybe finally we can take over the castle.
Pg:11 

=============================================
Evolution of Brain Washing
So brainwashing all started as a thing to get the blue dragon to believe in the cult. We needed a way to get the blue dragon to believe what we believe willingly or not. When that occurs we create the best believers out of them. But Let us discuss the Evolution of Brainwashing a simple blue dragon.  
Alright for the first type of brainwashing, mind. 
You would want to find a blue dragon member who is leaning toward betraying the blue dragon. 
This can make a blue dragon member eagerly joining the cult. 

Pg: 12

==============================================
After one of our cultists discussed a certain &quot;new&quot; type of brainwashing in order to make a true believer in the blue dragon realize their foolish ways.

First of all, we need to strap them to a chair, making sure they can&#39;t harm others.
Then, we need to show them the way of the path to the cult, in the next 4 pages it will discuss what to do for certain people. But in general you will want to show them the true way of our lord mithras and allow for them to show others the path to his glory. 

Pg: 13

==============================================
For Nobles and Physics 

If one of these people happen to come into your sight, you would want them for a-lot of reasons. So of the following are, Talking to the dead, easy communication, etc. 

In order to brainwash these types of people you will need first to have 
1. A book of the Corax.
2. Someone that they like that is dead.

In order to brainwash these types of people, you will first want to confront them about their one that they love that is dead. While this is going on you will need to mention that it is possible to talk to those that are dead if they follow the teachings of the corax. Present them with the book and do the typical push in the right direct.
After this is done, they will either come into the cult willingly or you will have to use a method discussed on page 18.

Pg: 14

==============================================
For Butlers, Drunks, Hunters, and Knights.

In order to make this person a true believer in the cult, you will need the following:

1. Communication with mithras
2. Information from the Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book Chapter 7

With both of these you will be able to make the person feel nothing, and that they don&#39;t have a purpose. And allow Mithras to possess their body, making the person do all that he asks. You will know when this happens when you are able to make them do anything you want. A typical thing to test them is to ask them to mark their back with the marks of the Corax. If they do, then a success. If they don&#39;t, then repeat the steps discussed in Chapter 7 of the Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book. Once done, you will have a willing flesh puppet to serve the cult!

Pg: 15

==============================================
For Court Wizards, Physicians, Mercenaries, and Priests.

What you will need for this conversion is the following

1. A ritual knife
2. Communication with the Lord of Darkness the Corax.
3. Teachings from The Advanced Book of Darkness, Teachings of the Corax, Chapter 8

What you will want to do is use the embrace of the corax to drive the person on the &quot;Right path&quot; once they are in confusion between the Darkness and the Light. You will want to use your spell of Σκιές on the person allowing them to follow into the darkness of the Corax. To test that this is done, you must provide a body of the blue dragon to them. If they are true to the Corax, give them the Ritual Knife to stab the body with. If they are not, repeat the process. If you don&#39;t think that they are still true after they stab the body. Proceed to tell them, &quot;The Person in which you stabbed in the heart was still alive&quot;. This is thrust the person into darkness allowing them to give in to the embrace of the Corax.

Pg: 16

 ==============================================
For Observers, Princesses and Paladins. 

The things you will need are the most for this one

1. Red Blindfold
2. Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book Chapter 9
3. Ritual Knife
4. Darkness of the Sight Book Chapter 3.

What you will first want to do is use your Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book, to make them think that their power can grow stronger and stronger. But in order to do that they must first let mithras guide them. You then will want to use the Darkness of Sight Book in order to give them the push in the right direct. This book discusses the useless factors of having eyes. For with eyes you will see death and destruct. Without eyes your sight is infinite. You will then want to hand them a ritual knife and encourage them to gauge out one of their eyes. If they don&#39;t, use the method on page 18. Once they do gauge out their own eye, you will want to cover it with a red blindfold in order to show to all their devotion to the cult. Tell them to follow the will of mithras and let his presence guide them. Then you will have a willing member of the cult and a seeker. 

Pg: 17

==============================================
This is the page in which anyone doesn&#39;t want to join the cult no matter what.
THIS SHOULD BE A LAST RESORT, DO NOT TELL ANY OTHER CULTISTS OF THIS.
IF YOU DO YOU WILL BE STUCK DOWN BY THE WILL OF MITHRAS.

Alright, CCS
or Cult Conversion Serum

Developed by Μπακούρα 

This Serum slowly devours the mind of the person you inject it into, until they are willing to do anything.
This Serum is located in the underside of your ritual table, password to it is 9 8 1 4.

Pg: 18

==============================================
Cult Leader Transition

If your current cult leader happens to die, a new one will become him. His mind will first fully be devoured by the will of mithras, and will receive all 5 of the Special History of the Cult Books. All advanced Cult Books. And have access to all cult books. He will be in charge of rituals and Brainwashings.

Pg: 19

============================

Complication:

If there happens to be a filthy paladin that bursts in and tries to stop the brainwashing, you can do the following.

1. Summon Mithras
2. Summon Fellow Cultists
3. Summon the Corax
4. Or For Threaten to kill the person that you are brainwashing.

Why is this in the brainwashing section you might ask? Well because it involves someone trying to stop your brainwashing!

Pg: 20

============================

_On the Next Page there is a ritual knife along with a poem_

_Mithras comes and all shall fall_
_Corax Destroys the light_
_Blue Dragon Join our Call_
_And the Castle is Destroyed all in the high of the night._

Pg: 21

==============================

_Notes are on the Next Page_

- Tonight we invade the Castle of Adiart
- Sending a Seeker and a Cult Leader 
- Seeker will find out the classes of the foolish Blue Dragon in there.
- Cult Leader Will recruit more to join our Cause.

Pg: 22

============================
Types of Brainwashing

In the Following pages we will discuss the types of Brainwashing.
Like the Following
- Recruitment
- Killing
- Advancement
- Silent 
- Darkness
- Mithras Advance 
- Light of Creation
- King (Pushing a Cultist to become king)
- Torture 
- Other

pg: 23

==========================
Recruitment was discussed on pg; 13

pg: 24

============================
Killing Brainwashing

This is only for if one of your cultists decide that they don&#39;t want to follow mithras&#39;s will. 

What you will do is first give them the knife and talk to them about it.

Tell them that if they don&#39;t kill them-self, then mithras will be displeased.

After this there is a 80% chance that they will.

The 20% just kill.

Pg: 25

============================
Advancement Brainwashing

There are many different types of Advancement

For Cult Leader Please go to pg: 19

As in advancements mostly you use for official ritual cult. You do not use advancements in scouting missions for cult. When we are doing advancements at our official ritual cult, we advance based on the amount of rituals each preform. In order to brainwash someone into advancing you will need for them to cut their hand. Once they do this the official cult advancement brainwashing is finished. 

Pg: 26

============================
Silent Influence

In this you attempt to brainwash a person, but don&#39;t. When you do this you want to make sure to hide your identity so then the word doesn&#39;t get out. With this the person will slowly go insane. Why would you do this? To cause chaos among the silly blue dragon to think that this person might be a silly little fool. 

Pg: 27

============================
Darkness Brainwashing

This is mostly different then silent brainwashing, instead of causing chaos this type of brainwashing is used to make a blue dragon or unseen or even Neutral commit suicide. This occurs after you cast the spell of σκοτάδι. The only way you are able to do this is by using spells talked about in the book of Shadows. 

Pg: 28

============================
Light of Creation

NO NO  OH NO
NO MY EYES
HELP HELP HELP NO 

Pg: 29

============================
King 

This is to give a cultists the push in the right direction to become king of the kingdom. The way you would want to do this is by first making them seem &quot;Royal&quot; make them boast. The need to feel like they are a king before becoming one. Then remind them of their job as king, to destroy all of the blue dragon. Once you do this, you just have to make sure no royals DARE to put their name forward and that the person who you want to become king is highly favored. 

Pg: 30

============================
Torture

The way you have to torture a person is a really hard process. What you want to do is either emotional torture or a basic version of torture. 

Emotional torture is were you get a person they love and make them kill them. Or else the will slowly die. Until they decide to join your cult. And if they ever betray you, you will kill the one that they love.

Basic is were you use your many torture machines. You use this torture to make them join your cult and if they try to defile you, you threaten to torture them again. 

Pg: 31

============================

_Roses are Black_
_Unseen Shall Die_
_Cult are Back_
_And the Blue Dragon Cry_

Pg: 32

============================

_Blood is on every corner of the page_

WE SHALL RISE!

Pg: 33

============================

_Corax spread darkness_
_Cult Follow_
_Blue Dragon find Carcasses_
_And we watch for we are hollow_ 

Pg: 34

============================

_We only hear_
_From Mithras&#39;s Ear_
_But a new cultist wonders_
_Right beyond yonder_ 

Pg: 35

============================

_We sense the presence_
_Of new Class here_
_For all we are peasants_
_Waiting for them to become our piers_ 

Pg: 36

============================

_Death Shall Come_
_To All Who Behave_
_With the Reapers from_
_Their all-mighty grave_

Pg: 37

============================

_Blue Dragon with their might_
_Cult will seek the fight_
_For the Unseen shall only act at night_
_In the Castle for these Days_

Pg: 38

============================

_This book comes to a close_
_For our cultists have rose_
_The Castle will fall_
_And soon shall all_

Pg: 39

============================

This is the end of this book, by the time you finish reading it you will either be cult leader, or soon be a cultists for this library that this book is kept is surrounded by cultists. So, either way, good luck and serve the cult well.

~ _Scratched Out_

Pg: 40

============================</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Later.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Where is your nobuz lore suggestion?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>:’( why you do this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think of it as ‘What the crap?’</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What do you think of the lore ;'0</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay then…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Because I need to one up myself</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why do you make such long lores?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cuz I can…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why though?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What the crap… I am going to make a lore of Bakura now…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>-bump because I want actual feedback rather then “Holy Fuck”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Holy Teemo</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 04:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Holy shit</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 02:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Uh oh, just read the book, so I’m soon to be a cultist?<br>
Nah, I just learned all the ways to counter you Cult now! BD can’t lose!</p>
<p>(Damn, amazing lore Bakura. 10/10. Such dedication)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>IS THE NOZBUGZ LORE NEXT? Also JFC christ Bakura</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One of our researchers has recently discovered a cult library. He has found many books in there and has returned them to us. The first one that we will be sharing in the cult’s brainwashing. In the following chapters you will see,</p>
<p>First Cases of Brainwashing: Pg. 3 -11</p>
<p>Evolution of Brainwashing: Pg. 12-22</p>
<p>Types of Brainwashing: Pg. 23-33</p>
<p><em>Crossed out</em>: Pg. 34-40<br>
Pg:1</p>
<p>========================================================<br>
Epilogue.<br>
We thank you for serving this cult willingly… or not.<br>
For It appears you have been accepted as a true believer in the lord Mithras!<br>
Along with this, you have the responsibility of showing the weak Blue Dragon<br>
the true way to enlightenment. Whether it be it willingly or not.<br>
In this book we will discuss what to do when they don’t want to join…<br>
Pg:2</p>
<p>===================================================<br>
First Cases of Brainwashing.<br>
To first know the roots of our brainwashing we must first discuss the first brainwashing that occurred.<br>
The first brainwashing that occurred was on a simple little blue dragon member named Cecily Tolvain. This Blue Dragon member was a Priest, in which we thought would make a good believer in the art of Mithras and the Corax. We were right, and after brainwashing the priest into being a true believer, she began to give the current cult leader more and more power. We eventually sacrificed our loving cult member to kill the king, but to our surprise Mithras allowed us to destroy not 1 but 2 silly believers in the blue dragon. From that day forward, any priest we have converted was referred to as a ritualist!</p>
<p>Pg: 3</p>
<p>===================================<br>
Our second “official” brainwashing was on the king’s daughter, the princess! Her name was a lovely one which was Isabel Lovall oh how do I love that name. She drove cult to a new road for she was the first queen to side with us, and our first seeker. It was rather simple to get us to join our side. After the death of her father by a Butler poisoning his drink, we were able to get her while she was at her low and make her happy. We asked her to remove her left eye to see into the true will of mithras and seek out our enemies and she did. For she was a child of mithras guided by his will. Due to the foolish blue dragon believing that she was still with them. They elected her as king, which guided more members to us. By allowing her guards to protect our current cult leader. She died the same way she lived, being poisoned by a butler.<br>
Pg:4</p>
<p>===================================<br>
Our third “Official” brainwashing occurred shortly after the death of our queen of the cult.<br>
A knight that she sent happened to be curious and looked inside of the room. To his surprise there was a wooden table with a small dagger and blood on it.We were standing in the room and he stood in shock. One of our fellow cultists knocked him out and tied him up for our amusement. We originally planned on killing him but Mithras himself convinced us otherwise. He told us that this body was powerful, powerful enough to only slightly go insane while he was possessing it. With this we untied the knight and dressed him in robes. He was completely in shock and in fear for his life for he realized that no matter what he did, he would be a cultist. Mithras possessed this body and told us of the new beginning of the cult for this man would be a invoker to his will.</p>
<p>Pg:5</p>
<p>==================</p>
<p><em>The Next page is filled with torn notes from a dead paladin</em></p>
<p>My…My Brother<br>
I love- — – ----<br>
— --- – ---- – ---- — cult</p>
<p>---- ---- Insane – -him</p>
<p>my job is to destroy the cult</p>
<p>but how can I destroy my brother.</p>
<p>I cant give in to the cult,</p>
<p>I am a destroyer of mithras.</p>
<p>---- uh</p>
<p>------ why is he</p>
<p>I don’t deserve to wield this sword</p>
<p>For in heart I am truly a priest.</p>
<p>–I----cant—live—with----this</p>
<p>I-give—into the cult<br>
I praise to mithras.</p>
<p>Pg: 6</p>
<p>===============<br>
HELP ME.<br>
THIS PAGE WAS BLANK. SO I HAVE DECIDED TO WRITE ON IT<br>
I HAVE DISCOVERED THIS JOURNAL AND I AM NOW TRAPPED IN THE CULT LIBRARY<br>
I CAN HERE THE LAUGHS OF THE CULT LEADER.<br>
I DO NOT KNOW WHAT WILL HAPPEN.<br>
THIS IS MOST LIKELY BE THE LAST TIME AND THE FIRST TIME I WRITE IN THIS JOURNAL.<br>
FAREWELL!<br>
Pg.7</p>
<p>===============================================<br>
Fourth Case of Brainwash<br>
A unwanted intruder</p>
<p>A while ago, a intruder discovered this library while I was writing this book. Heheheh, nobles from distant lands trying to discover our secrets, well i’ll show them our secrets. Well anyway here is the story of hour first Apostle</p>
<p>A noble was sent to explore a new area of the castle one in which was thought to hold secrets of the cult. He loyally accepted this offer, for his dream was to be a lore master for the Blue Dragon. But once he arrived there he found this exact book! I was in the process of getting ready to convert a Psychic but it seems there is no need! That noble got cornered and here’s the fun part. We tied him up! Yes, with this we had our invoker first destroy the noble’s mind. For he was truly a messenger of mithras. If this noble learned that mithras really existed and how powerful he is he might have a fighting chance against the world! After our Invoker was done talking to the scared noble, I happened to ask him if he could be a messenger of the Corax. He responded, “yes”. We happened to now have a Noble on our side ooooh. This was special, so the cult happened to give him a book of the magic of the corax. We also gave him robes to show his true devotion to the cult. After a while we began to see fellow dead cult members, we knew this was because of the Noble who decided to join the cult, for not only was he a messenger of the living, but a messenger of the dead! At the beginning of Shadow Lessons of The Corax, it says that “Only a Apostle can Master these” so we happened to see that this noble mastered it, so we called him a Apostle. isn’t that a great name?<br>
pg: 8</p>
<p>===============================================</p>
<p>HAIL TO THE CORAX IT IS THE DARKNESS THAT CONTROLS THE WORLD!</p>
<p>THE WEAK BLUE DRAGON WILL NEVER HOLD UP TO THE MIGHT OF THE CORAX<br>
HAHAHAHAHAA<br>
pg: 9</p>
<p>==============================================</p>
<p><em>A blank page</em></p>
<p>pg:10</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
Heheheeheehe we have so many members, all of which have been brainwashed, this is great.<br>
Maybe finally we can take over the castle.<br>
Pg:11</p>
<p>=============================================<br>
Evolution of Brain Washing<br>
So brainwashing all started as a thing to get the blue dragon to believe in the cult. We needed a way to get the blue dragon to believe what we believe willingly or not. When that occurs we create the best believers out of them. But Let us discuss the Evolution of Brainwashing a simple blue dragon.<br>
Alright for the first type of brainwashing, mind.<br>
You would want to find a blue dragon member who is leaning toward betraying the blue dragon.<br>
This can make a blue dragon member eagerly joining the cult.</p>
<p>Pg: 12</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
After one of our cultists discussed a certain “new” type of brainwashing in order to make a true believer in the blue dragon realize their foolish ways.</p>
<p>First of all, we need to strap them to a chair, making sure they can’t harm others.<br>
Then, we need to show them the way of the path to the cult, in the next 4 pages it will discuss what to do for certain people. But in general you will want to show them the true way of our lord mithras and allow for them to show others the path to his glory.</p>
<p>Pg: 13</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
For Nobles and Physics</p>
<p>If one of these people happen to come into your sight, you would want them for a-lot of reasons. So of the following are, Talking to the dead, easy communication, etc.</p>
<p>In order to brainwash these types of people you will need first to have</p>
<ol>
<li>A book of the Corax.</li>
<li>Someone that they like that is dead.</li>
</ol>
<p>In order to brainwash these types of people, you will first want to confront them about their one that they love that is dead. While this is going on you will need to mention that it is possible to talk to those that are dead if they follow the teachings of the corax. Present them with the book and do the typical push in the right direct.<br>
After this is done, they will either come into the cult willingly or you will have to use a method discussed on page 18.</p>
<p>Pg: 14</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
For Butlers, Drunks, Hunters, and Knights.</p>
<p>In order to make this person a true believer in the cult, you will need the following:</p>
<ol>
<li>Communication with mithras</li>
<li>Information from the Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book Chapter 7</li>
</ol>
<p>With both of these you will be able to make the person feel nothing, and that they don’t have a purpose. And allow Mithras to possess their body, making the person do all that he asks. You will know when this happens when you are able to make them do anything you want. A typical thing to test them is to ask them to mark their back with the marks of the Corax. If they do, then a success. If they don’t, then repeat the steps discussed in Chapter 7 of the Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book. Once done, you will have a willing flesh puppet to serve the cult!</p>
<p>Pg: 15</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
For Court Wizards, Physicians, Mercenaries, and Priests.</p>
<p>What you will need for this conversion is the following</p>
<ol>
<li>A ritual knife</li>
<li>Communication with the Lord of Darkness the Corax.</li>
<li>Teachings from The Advanced Book of Darkness, Teachings of the Corax, Chapter 8</li>
</ol>
<p>What you will want to do is use the embrace of the corax to drive the person on the “Right path” once they are in confusion between the Darkness and the Light. You will want to use your spell of Σκιές on the person allowing them to follow into the darkness of the Corax. To test that this is done, you must provide a body of the blue dragon to them. If they are true to the Corax, give them the Ritual Knife to stab the body with. If they are not, repeat the process. If you don’t think that they are still true after they stab the body. Proceed to tell them, “The Person in which you stabbed in the heart was still alive”. This is thrust the person into darkness allowing them to give in to the embrace of the Corax.</p>
<p>Pg: 16</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
For Observers, Princesses and Paladins.</p>
<p>The things you will need are the most for this one</p>
<ol>
<li>Red Blindfold</li>
<li>Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book Chapter 9</li>
<li>Ritual Knife</li>
<li>Darkness of the Sight Book Chapter 3.</li>
</ol>
<p>What you will first want to do is use your Teachings of Mithras Advanced Book, to make them think that their power can grow stronger and stronger. But in order to do that they must first let mithras guide them. You then will want to use the Darkness of Sight Book in order to give them the push in the right direct. This book discusses the useless factors of having eyes. For with eyes you will see death and destruct. Without eyes your sight is infinite. You will then want to hand them a ritual knife and encourage them to gauge out one of their eyes. If they don’t, use the method on page 18. Once they do gauge out their own eye, you will want to cover it with a red blindfold in order to show to all their devotion to the cult. Tell them to follow the will of mithras and let his presence guide them. Then you will have a willing member of the cult and a seeker.</p>
<p>Pg: 17</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
This is the page in which anyone doesn’t want to join the cult no matter what.<br>
THIS SHOULD BE A LAST RESORT, DO NOT TELL ANY OTHER CULTISTS OF THIS.<br>
IF YOU DO YOU WILL BE STUCK DOWN BY THE WILL OF MITHRAS.</p>
<p>Alright, CCS<br>
or Cult Conversion Serum</p>
<p>Developed by Μπακούρα</p>
<p>This Serum slowly devours the mind of the person you inject it into, until they are willing to do anything.<br>
This Serum is located in the underside of your ritual table, password to it is 9 8 1 4.</p>
<p>Pg: 18</p>
<p>==============================================<br>
Cult Leader Transition</p>
<p>If your current cult leader happens to die, a new one will become him. His mind will first fully be devoured by the will of mithras, and will receive all 5 of the Special History of the Cult Books. All advanced Cult Books. And have access to all cult books. He will be in charge of rituals and Brainwashings.</p>
<p>Pg: 19</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p>Complication:</p>
<p>If there happens to be a filthy paladin that bursts in and tries to stop the brainwashing, you can do the following.</p>
<ol>
<li>Summon Mithras</li>
<li>Summon Fellow Cultists</li>
<li>Summon the Corax</li>
<li>Or For Threaten to kill the person that you are brainwashing.</li>
</ol>
<p>Why is this in the brainwashing section you might ask? Well because it involves someone trying to stop your brainwashing!</p>
<p>Pg: 20</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>On the Next Page there is a ritual knife along with a poem</em></p>
<p><em>Mithras comes and all shall fall</em><br>
<em>Corax Destroys the light</em><br>
<em>Blue Dragon Join our Call</em><br>
<em>And the Castle is Destroyed all in the high of the night.</em></p>
<p>Pg: 21</p>
<p>==============================</p>
<p><em>Notes are on the Next Page</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Tonight we invade the Castle of Adiart</li>
<li>Sending a Seeker and a Cult Leader</li>
<li>Seeker will find out the classes of the foolish Blue Dragon in there.</li>
<li>Cult Leader Will recruit more to join our Cause.</li>
</ul>
<p>Pg: 22</p>
<p>============================<br>
Types of Brainwashing</p>
<p>In the Following pages we will discuss the types of Brainwashing.<br>
Like the Following</p>
<ul>
<li>Recruitment</li>
<li>Killing</li>
<li>Advancement</li>
<li>Silent</li>
<li>Darkness</li>
<li>Mithras Advance</li>
<li>Light of Creation</li>
<li>King (Pushing a Cultist to become king)</li>
<li>Torture</li>
<li>Other</li>
</ul>
<p>pg: 23</p>
<p>==========================<br>
Recruitment was discussed on pg; 13</p>
<p>pg: 24</p>
<p>============================<br>
Killing Brainwashing</p>
<p>This is only for if one of your cultists decide that they don’t want to follow mithras’s will.</p>
<p>What you will do is first give them the knife and talk to them about it.</p>
<p>Tell them that if they don’t kill them-self, then mithras will be displeased.</p>
<p>After this there is a 80% chance that they will.</p>
<p>The 20% just kill.</p>
<p>Pg: 25</p>
<p>============================<br>
Advancement Brainwashing</p>
<p>There are many different types of Advancement</p>
<p>For Cult Leader Please go to pg: 19</p>
<p>As in advancements mostly you use for official ritual cult. You do not use advancements in scouting missions for cult. When we are doing advancements at our official ritual cult, we advance based on the amount of rituals each preform. In order to brainwash someone into advancing you will need for them to cut their hand. Once they do this the official cult advancement brainwashing is finished.</p>
<p>Pg: 26</p>
<p>============================<br>
Silent Influence</p>
<p>In this you attempt to brainwash a person, but don’t. When you do this you want to make sure to hide your identity so then the word doesn’t get out. With this the person will slowly go insane. Why would you do this? To cause chaos among the silly blue dragon to think that this person might be a silly little fool.</p>
<p>Pg: 27</p>
<p>============================<br>
Darkness Brainwashing</p>
<p>This is mostly different then silent brainwashing, instead of causing chaos this type of brainwashing is used to make a blue dragon or unseen or even Neutral commit suicide. This occurs after you cast the spell of σκοτάδι. The only way you are able to do this is by using spells talked about in the book of Shadows.</p>
<p>Pg: 28</p>
<p>============================<br>
Light of Creation</p>
<p>NO NO  OH NO<br>
NO MY EYES<br>
HELP HELP HELP NO</p>
<p>Pg: 29</p>
<p>============================<br>
King</p>
<p>This is to give a cultists the push in the right direction to become king of the kingdom. The way you would want to do this is by first making them seem “Royal” make them boast. The need to feel like they are a king before becoming one. Then remind them of their job as king, to destroy all of the blue dragon. Once you do this, you just have to make sure no royals DARE to put their name forward and that the person who you want to become king is highly favored.</p>
<p>Pg: 30</p>
<p>============================<br>
Torture</p>
<p>The way you have to torture a person is a really hard process. What you want to do is either emotional torture or a basic version of torture.</p>
<p>Emotional torture is were you get a person they love and make them kill them. Or else the will slowly die. Until they decide to join your cult. And if they ever betray you, you will kill the one that they love.</p>
<p>Basic is were you use your many torture machines. You use this torture to make them join your cult and if they try to defile you, you threaten to torture them again.</p>
<p>Pg: 31</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>Roses are Black</em><br>
<em>Unseen Shall Die</em><br>
<em>Cult are Back</em><br>
<em>And the Blue Dragon Cry</em></p>
<p>Pg: 32</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>Blood is on every corner of the page</em></p>
<p>WE SHALL RISE!</p>
<p>Pg: 33</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>Corax spread darkness</em><br>
<em>Cult Follow</em><br>
<em>Blue Dragon find Carcasses</em><br>
<em>And we watch for we are hollow</em></p>
<p>Pg: 34</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>We only hear</em><br>
<em>From Mithras’s Ear</em><br>
<em>But a new cultist wonders</em><br>
<em>Right beyond yonder</em></p>
<p>Pg: 35</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>We sense the presence</em><br>
<em>Of new Class here</em><br>
<em>For all we are peasants</em><br>
<em>Waiting for them to become our piers</em></p>
<p>Pg: 36</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>Death Shall Come</em><br>
<em>To All Who Behave</em><br>
<em>With the Reapers from</em><br>
<em>Their all-mighty grave</em></p>
<p>Pg: 37</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>Blue Dragon with their might</em><br>
<em>Cult will seek the fight</em><br>
<em>For the Unseen shall only act at night</em><br>
<em>In the Castle for these Days</em></p>
<p>Pg: 38</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p><em>This book comes to a close</em><br>
<em>For our cultists have rose</em><br>
<em>The Castle will fall</em><br>
<em>And soon shall all</em></p>
<p>Pg: 39</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p>This is the end of this book, by the time you finish reading it you will either be cult leader, or soon be a cultists for this library that this book is kept is surrounded by cultists. So, either way, good luck and serve the cult well.</p>
<p>~ <em>Scratched Out</em></p>
<p>Pg: 40</p>
<p>============================</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2856-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-history-of-the-cult-brainwashing/2856.rss">[Lore Suggestion] History of the Cult, Brainwashing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
