<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679</link>
    <description>**How to MM for Dummies**

**Step 1: Open this Guide** 
If you&#39;re reading this, great! You&#39;ve done it.

**Step 2: Get Mastermind**
Mastermind is the most important and most pivotal class for the &quot;main&quot; antagonist faction, the Unseen. Unlike the Cult Leader, the Mastermind will not be replaced once past Night 3. So while you&#39;re able to make some mistakes in the first 3 nights, be warned, once it&#39;s the fourth day within the courts of Castle Adiart, there&#39;s no going back, and no room for mistakes.

**Step 3: Coordination**
As the Unseen, the key you need to win games, or at least have an advantage, is to make sure that EVERY MEMBER is coordinated. This means Assassins, Mastermind, and other classes must work together and share information. This means from here, there are two paths that the Unseen can go down.

**Path A: Classic**

**Step 4A: Deceiving**
The classic way to play as the Unseen is to silently kill off the Blue Dragon and divert suspicion that comes towards any of your members when your faction is full (3 Members). While this is safer in the short term, this does not go so well in the long-term, as the Mastermind is bound to be found sooner or later by luck if the assassin does not kill off the Blue Dragon investigators and offensives quick enough. 

Classic claims for the Mastermind is Princess and Sheriff, as he shows up a Special and Investigator class to Princesses, and has the Foresight ability that helps him see which classes are convertible. 
However, you may also claim Knight (This is REALLY not recommended), or Physician, as well as Hunter or Butler, due to your occupy immunity. 
However, be warned; without substantial evidence and finding Unseens, your claims will often come under suspicion.

**Step 5A: Getting Majority**
One way to go beyond your 3-member limit is to convert a Royal and to put them on the throne by killing a King. Royals who are converted still keep their Royal Blood passive when becoming an assassin, so they can be crowned in any situation, as long as Blue Dragon royals aren&#39;t there to counter them.
Another way is to befriend Neutrals who will trust you. Alchemists, Scorned, and Fool will be usually willing to join you when it&#39;s late-game, due to the Neuts Out Meta. And voting up the Fool or the Scorned target is also beneficial to the Unseen more than to the Blue Dragon.
But unless the Neutral Killing isn&#39;t a Sorcerer, try to throw them under the bus before securing the throne, as leaving them alive will cause a lot of problems.
Remember to have the Prince dead before you out yourselves or to vote up the Prince on the day you out yourself, as he&#39;ll give you a lot of problems if he&#39;s alive in this late-game phase.
Remember to count and make sure who are Blue Dragon and who are Neutrals, as if you miscounted, you&#39;ll be in for a wild ride when you get voted up. 

**Path B: Pseudo Cult**

**Step 4B: Bussing**
This is a method I like to play as the Mastermind, or try to convince the Mastermind to play as when I&#39;m in the Unseen. The Cult, with a maximum of 4 members, can afford to kill off their players and convert again. Well, they&#39;re forced to do that. However, there are advantages to being a Mastermind and acting like a Cult.

Claims: If you claimed Sheriff or Observer as a class, this path will be the best way for you to play. As the Mastermind, try to out your assassin (WITH THEIR PERMISSION) on days right before you can convert again, as bussing your teammates with their permission will allow you to
1. Gain the trust of BD as a solid Investigative Class
2. Allow you to stay off the radar, and
3. Convert again

Doing so has the benefits of opening up space in your faction! This bypasses steps 4A and 5A, as you don&#39;t need to hide and deceive the Blue Dragon, all you need to do is to keep unwanted attention completely away from yourself. Assassins are easily replaceable, but once the Mastermind is dead, the game is essentially over. 

**Step 5B: Smart Conversion**
If possible, try to kill or convert Court Wizards early on so that you can enter late game and safely convert key classes to your side. The goal is to not hide and protect your members, but to put up a façade and to gain numbers far faster. In this phase, you should be Prince hunting as well, as he is your main threat, and you cannot convert him. 

Key classes that you should try to convert are:

- Sheriff
- Drunk
- Princess
- Psychic

as they are useful classes to both BD and Unseen, and with a Drunk or Princess on your side, you can safely make plans to kill off the starting King and insert them on the throne instead.

**Step 6: Securing the Throne**
Two ways this can go: if there is currently an Evil King on the throne, getting the turning vote will be far easier, as you can potentially have 5 votes as the Unseen, due to the King&#39;s Royal Finger. Neutral Kings will also be willing to turn and join the Unseen cause when the scales tip for the Unseen&#39;s favor. 
If you know by now that there is a Good King on the throne, (i.e. constantly whispering with confirmed BD, lynching Unseen, etc.) vote him up first or have him dead before you try to secure the throne. 
Once you gain majority and eliminate the Good King and the Prince, there is not much else the Blue Dragon can do to stop your path of conquest.

If there&#39;s information to be added, please leave your feedback.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 05:51:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Interestingly, I was the MM once and I death tunnelled with my own assassin. BD believed the Assassin and I died. Unseen won as everyone trusted my assassin</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 05:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-36679-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679.rss">[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree with this method. Bussing should usually be done when you have found your next conversion target, conversion is not on cooldown and you have 3 members. If someone of the unseen faction accuses a BD and manages to get them executed, you cannot convert that evening and your fellow unseen will probably be now jailed and executed. If that is assassin he cannot kill that night and you cannot convert that night either, since there are still 3 members alive. If you’re bussing, you should do it in such a way that the unseen will definitely die. If the unseen dies, any claims he has made turn void and might actually aid whoever he was accusing, because “no unseen would rally to get their own executed”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 19:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-36679-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679.rss">[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Rather than bussing your own members you should have the members you are sacrificing accuse someone else in a way that would fit if you were accusing a MM. (ex-claiming they are OCC Immune when they claimed not to be or saying they are Special/Invest when they claimed phys.) This gets all of the benefits of bussing except he takes a BD down with him. Yes that includes the whole making it harder to find you because you are muddying the waters constantly at every chance you get.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 19:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-36679-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679.rss">[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>How to MM for Dummies</strong></p>
<p><strong>Step 1: Open this Guide</strong><br>
If you’re reading this, great! You’ve done it.</p>
<p><strong>Step 2: Get Mastermind</strong><br>
Mastermind is the most important and most pivotal class for the “main” antagonist faction, the Unseen. Unlike the Cult Leader, the Mastermind will not be replaced once past Night 3. So while you’re able to make some mistakes in the first 3 nights, be warned, once it’s the fourth day within the courts of Castle Adiart, there’s no going back, and no room for mistakes.</p>
<p><strong>Step 3: Coordination</strong><br>
As the Unseen, the key you need to win games, or at least have an advantage, is to make sure that EVERY MEMBER is coordinated. This means Assassins, Mastermind, and other classes must work together and share information. This means from here, there are two paths that the Unseen can go down.</p>
<p><strong>Path A: Classic</strong></p>
<p><strong>Step 4A: Deceiving</strong><br>
The classic way to play as the Unseen is to silently kill off the Blue Dragon and divert suspicion that comes towards any of your members when your faction is full (3 Members). While this is safer in the short term, this does not go so well in the long-term, as the Mastermind is bound to be found sooner or later by luck if the assassin does not kill off the Blue Dragon investigators and offensives quick enough.</p>
<p>Classic claims for the Mastermind is Princess and Sheriff, as he shows up a Special and Investigator class to Princesses, and has the Foresight ability that helps him see which classes are convertible.<br>
However, you may also claim Knight (This is REALLY not recommended), or Physician, as well as Hunter or Butler, due to your occupy immunity.<br>
However, be warned; without substantial evidence and finding Unseens, your claims will often come under suspicion.</p>
<p><strong>Step 5A: Getting Majority</strong><br>
One way to go beyond your 3-member limit is to convert a Royal and to put them on the throne by killing a King. Royals who are converted still keep their Royal Blood passive when becoming an assassin, so they can be crowned in any situation, as long as Blue Dragon royals aren’t there to counter them.<br>
Another way is to befriend Neutrals who will trust you. Alchemists, Scorned, and Fool will be usually willing to join you when it’s late-game, due to the Neuts Out Meta. And voting up the Fool or the Scorned target is also beneficial to the Unseen more than to the Blue Dragon.<br>
But unless the Neutral Killing isn’t a Sorcerer, try to throw them under the bus before securing the throne, as leaving them alive will cause a lot of problems.<br>
Remember to have the Prince dead before you out yourselves or to vote up the Prince on the day you out yourself, as he’ll give you a lot of problems if he’s alive in this late-game phase.<br>
Remember to count and make sure who are Blue Dragon and who are Neutrals, as if you miscounted, you’ll be in for a wild ride when you get voted up.</p>
<p><strong>Path B: Pseudo Cult</strong></p>
<p><strong>Step 4B: Bussing</strong><br>
This is a method I like to play as the Mastermind, or try to convince the Mastermind to play as when I’m in the Unseen. The Cult, with a maximum of 4 members, can afford to kill off their players and convert again. Well, they’re forced to do that. However, there are advantages to being a Mastermind and acting like a Cult.</p>
<p>Claims: If you claimed Sheriff or Observer as a class, this path will be the best way for you to play. As the Mastermind, try to out your assassin (WITH THEIR PERMISSION) on days right before you can convert again, as bussing your teammates with their permission will allow you to</p>
<ol>
<li>Gain the trust of BD as a solid Investigative Class</li>
<li>Allow you to stay off the radar, and</li>
<li>Convert again</li>
</ol>
<p>Doing so has the benefits of opening up space in your faction! This bypasses steps 4A and 5A, as you don’t need to hide and deceive the Blue Dragon, all you need to do is to keep unwanted attention completely away from yourself. Assassins are easily replaceable, but once the Mastermind is dead, the game is essentially over.</p>
<p><strong>Step 5B: Smart Conversion</strong><br>
If possible, try to kill or convert Court Wizards early on so that you can enter late game and safely convert key classes to your side. The goal is to not hide and protect your members, but to put up a façade and to gain numbers far faster. In this phase, you should be Prince hunting as well, as he is your main threat, and you cannot convert him.</p>
<p>Key classes that you should try to convert are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sheriff</li>
<li>Drunk</li>
<li>Princess</li>
<li>Psychic</li>
</ul>
<p>as they are useful classes to both BD and Unseen, and with a Drunk or Princess on your side, you can safely make plans to kill off the starting King and insert them on the throne instead.</p>
<p><strong>Step 6: Securing the Throne</strong><br>
Two ways this can go: if there is currently an Evil King on the throne, getting the turning vote will be far easier, as you can potentially have 5 votes as the Unseen, due to the King’s Royal Finger. Neutral Kings will also be willing to turn and join the Unseen cause when the scales tip for the Unseen’s favor.<br>
If you know by now that there is a Good King on the throne, (i.e. constantly whispering with confirmed BD, lynching Unseen, etc.) vote him up first or have him dead before you try to secure the throne.<br>
Once you gain majority and eliminate the Good King and the Prince, there is not much else the Blue Dragon can do to stop your path of conquest.</p>
<p>If there’s information to be added, please leave your feedback.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 18:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-36679-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/guide-how-to-mm-for-dummies-v-1-0-15/36679.rss">[Guide] How to MM for Dummies (v 1.0.15)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
