<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Faction suggestion] The Demons</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780</link>
    <description>Spawns with the fallen and the exorcist.

&gt;The Fallen
Infernal special
**Passives ability: Infernal rapture** Upon dying by any means, all corrupted players will become a demon, the type determined by how long they have been corrupted.
**Passive ability two: Infernal resilience** Immune to death at night
**Night ability: Corrupt** (infinite uses) Corrupt the target player. They will not know they were corrupted. They will be immune to death until the infernal rapture. If they are a class that can&#39;t be corrupted, you will kill them instead.
**Day ability: Marty** (1 use) You will die at the end of the next night, even if you are imprisoned.

If a player was corrupted the same night the fallen died, they will become a Lemure. If they were corrupted 1-2 nights before, they will become an imp. If they were corrupted 3 nights before, they will become a lesser demon. 4 nights before become greater demon, and 5 nights or more before become an arch demon.

&gt;The Lemure
Infernal special
**Passive ability: Apprenticeship** You will become an imp upon the a demon dying. Until then, when a demon is occupied, you will carry out whatever they attempted to do.

&gt;The Imp
Infernal offensive
**Night ability: Mischief** (infinite uses) Occupy the target. 
**Day ability: Sabotage** (two uses) The next time the target attempts to use a day ability, it will fail. They will still expend a use, but the effect will not take place. 

&gt;The lesser demon
Infernal killing
**Day ability: Sap life** (infinite uses) Mark the target. When they die, you will gain a use of _slay._ You can only have one marked target at a time.
**Night ability: slay** (1 use) kill the target

&gt;Greater demon
Infernal support
**Night ability: Hellish rebuke** (3 uses) Make the target demon immune to death tonight, and kill anyone who attacks them. 
**Night ability: Fissure** (1 uses) Open a pit below the target to swallow and kill them and everyone who visits them except the prince.

&gt;Arch Demon
Infernal killing
**Passive ability:** Immune to death at night
**Day ability: Soul Split** (day, 2 uses) If you are executed today, you will take the two selected targets with you.
**Night ability: Hell-raise** (infinite uses) Make the target appear to be a demon to investigators



--------------------
&gt;The Exorcist
Blue dragon investigative; unique
**Passive ability: Higher calling** When the fallen dies, you shall become the saint.
**Night ability one: Test morals** (infinite uses) determine if your target is corrupted.
**Night ability two: Purify** (1 uses) if your target is corrupted, remove their corruption. They cannot be corrupted again.

&gt;The saint
Blue dragon investigative
**Night ability: Find morality** (infinite uses) You will be told the name of one player who is not a demon. You will not be told the same player&#39;s name twice.
**Night ability: Ward evil**  (2 uses) you will occupy and demons who attempt to visit the target.

-------------------------
The goal of the demons is the standard antagonist faction goal. The demons meet at night, and can speak with the dead fallen.

If you didn&#39;t understand, here is an explanation:

The fallen corrupts players, giving them death immunity. Upon the fallen&#39;s death, all corrupted players become demons. The type of demon is determined based on how long they were corrupted.  There is no limit on how many players can be corrupted, and so there is no limit on the demon count.

Infernal means demon in this, didn&#39;t think &quot;demon&quot; was a good faction name.

The prince, exorcist, saint, and all neutrals besides the mercenary are immune to being corrupted/tainted.


---------------------------------------
fallen spawns ------- corrupts players, giving them death immunity. Exorcist can find them and reverse it --------- fallen dies. corrupted players become demons, exorcist becomes saint</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 13:46:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Faction suggestion] The Demons</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Marty please tell me</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 13:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2780-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780.rss">[Faction suggestion] The Demons</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction suggestion] The Demons</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="3" data-topic="2780">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and what spelling mistakes?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Marty can tell you one of them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 13:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2780-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780.rss">[Faction suggestion] The Demons</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction suggestion] The Demons</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I removed “taint morals”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2780-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780.rss">[Faction suggestion] The Demons</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction suggestion] The Demons</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>would it be balanced if i gave exorcist unlimited uses of purify?</p>
<p>and what spelling mistakes?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 12:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2780-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780.rss">[Faction suggestion] The Demons</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction suggestion] The Demons</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="1" data-topic="2780">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>so there is no limit on the demon count.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Without a limit, you’ve instantly made this overpowered and unbalanced.</p>
<p>Also, this is all a mess.</p>
<p>1st off, go through and correct all your spelling, the same way you did with a hundred other people’s post before.</p>
<p>2nd, your whole demon corrupt on nights thing is a mess and should have been done via a chart rather than a sentenced list.</p>
<p>3rd, a lot of your class types + abilities don’t go together and most of the abilities are unbalanced as hell.</p>
<p>4th, your hard counters are unbalanced as hell.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 05:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2780-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780.rss">[Faction suggestion] The Demons</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction suggestion] The Demons</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Spawns with the fallen and the exorcist.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The Fallen<br>
Infernal special<br>
<strong>Passives ability: Infernal rapture</strong> Upon dying by any means, all corrupted players will become a demon, the type determined by how long they have been corrupted.<br>
<strong>Passive ability two: Infernal resilience</strong> Immune to death at night<br>
<strong>Night ability: Corrupt</strong> (infinite uses) Corrupt the target player. They will not know they were corrupted. They will be immune to death until the infernal rapture. If they are a class that can’t be corrupted, you will kill them instead.<br>
<strong>Day ability: Marty</strong> (1 use) You will die at the end of the next night, even if you are imprisoned.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If a player was corrupted the same night the fallen died, they will become a Lemure. If they were corrupted 1-2 nights before, they will become an imp. If they were corrupted 3 nights before, they will become a lesser demon. 4 nights before become greater demon, and 5 nights or more before become an arch demon.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The Lemure<br>
Infernal special<br>
<strong>Passive ability: Apprenticeship</strong> You will become an imp upon the a demon dying. Until then, when a demon is occupied, you will carry out whatever they attempted to do.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Imp<br>
Infernal offensive<br>
<strong>Night ability: Mischief</strong> (infinite uses) Occupy the target.<br>
<strong>Day ability: Sabotage</strong> (two uses) The next time the target attempts to use a day ability, it will fail. They will still expend a use, but the effect will not take place.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The lesser demon<br>
Infernal killing<br>
<strong>Day ability: Sap life</strong> (infinite uses) Mark the target. When they die, you will gain a use of <em>slay.</em> You can only have one marked target at a time.<br>
<strong>Night ability: slay</strong> (1 use) kill the target</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Greater demon<br>
Infernal support<br>
<strong>Night ability: Hellish rebuke</strong> (3 uses) Make the target demon immune to death tonight, and kill anyone who attacks them.<br>
<strong>Night ability: Fissure</strong> (1 uses) Open a pit below the target to swallow and kill them and everyone who visits them except the prince.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Arch Demon<br>
Infernal killing<br>
<strong>Passive ability:</strong> Immune to death at night<br>
<strong>Day ability: Soul Split</strong> (day, 2 uses) If you are executed today, you will take the two selected targets with you.<br>
<strong>Night ability: Hell-raise</strong> (infinite uses) Make the target appear to be a demon to investigators</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>The Exorcist<br>
Blue dragon investigative; unique<br>
<strong>Passive ability: Higher calling</strong> When the fallen dies, you shall become the saint.<br>
<strong>Night ability one: Test morals</strong> (infinite uses) determine if your target is corrupted.<br>
<strong>Night ability two: Purify</strong> (1 uses) if your target is corrupted, remove their corruption. They cannot be corrupted again.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The saint<br>
Blue dragon investigative<br>
<strong>Night ability: Find morality</strong> (infinite uses) You will be told the name of one player who is not a demon. You will not be told the same player’s name twice.<br>
<strong>Night ability: Ward evil</strong>  (2 uses) you will occupy and demons who attempt to visit the target.</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<p>The goal of the demons is the standard antagonist faction goal. The demons meet at night, and can speak with the dead fallen.</p>
<p>If you didn’t understand, here is an explanation:</p>
<p>The fallen corrupts players, giving them death immunity. Upon the fallen’s death, all corrupted players become demons. The type of demon is determined based on how long they were corrupted.  There is no limit on how many players can be corrupted, and so there is no limit on the demon count.</p>
<p>Infernal means demon in this, didn’t think “demon” was a good faction name.</p>
<p>The prince, exorcist, saint, and all neutrals besides the mercenary are immune to being corrupted/tainted.</p>
<hr>
<p>fallen spawns ------- corrupts players, giving them death immunity. Exorcist can find them and reverse it --------- fallen dies. corrupted players become demons, exorcist becomes saint</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2780-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-the-demons/2780.rss">[Faction suggestion] The Demons</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
