<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017</link>
    <description>[details=&quot;Alchemist&quot;]
&gt; Alchemists&#39; heal is strange to me. It is a staple of her kit, but it doesn&#39;t really make sense with her wincondition. *Optimally*, the Alchemist wants games to end faster - which would imply they aren&#39;t healing too many people. I may be projecting my own playstyle here, as I typically get 1 heal max and then use both of my bombs over the course of the game and no-action every other night.
&gt; 
&gt; I also believe that 3 stoneskins is one too many, but evidently in the past 2 was too few. Since games usually end on Day 6 or Day 7, 3 nights of night immmunity would be 60% (3/5 nights) or 50% (3/6 nights) of the game. As opposed to 40% or 33.3%, which actually presents a dilemma on how to use them. However, in longer games, 2 nights of death immunity can equate a measly 25% or even less, and as a Survivor class that is pretty poor. 
&gt; 
&gt; Finally, if Alchemist is going to keep her heal, I do not think it should be unlimited use. Limited use heals would encourage better decisionmaking with how to use those heals. It doesn&#39;t entirely make sense for a neutral to have unlimited heals if their wincondition doesn&#39;t involve healing (like old FoL Alch) and as a side effect of making heal a limited use ability, Alchemist shouldn&#39;t count towards the &quot;guaranteed healer&quot; like it currently does. Although I believe that even if their heal remains as an infinite use ability, Alchemist should not be a &quot;guaranteed&quot; healer.
[/details]
 

&gt; TLDR: 
&gt; 	- **Remove Alchemist from the &#39;Guaranteed Healer&#39; spawn pool (currently Alchemist/Chrono/Phys)**
&gt; 	- *Make Heal a limited use ability (3 uses?)*
&gt; 	- *Reduce Stoneskin from 3 to 2 uses*

	
	


[details=&quot;Fool&quot;]
&gt; While I personally think Fool is too easy to win as, I think a lot of that has to do with the games meta and the players. 
&gt; 
&gt; Trollbox is a genius ability and fits Fool perfectly. Frame is an ability that really can&#39;t be changed and is very powerful for what it&#39;s supposed to do - but it&#39;s limited use and requires *you* to be targetted by an investigative ability, so that&#39;s not too bad. However, I think Fool being always incompatible (without framing) is simply too easy for Fool. No other investigative class gets inaccurate results from a non-framing Fool. *Although a change here could be an indirect Maid buff.*
[/details]


&gt; TLDR: 
&gt; 	- **Make Fool not always incompatible when not Framed** (I think always Compatible would be most balanced)
	


[details=&quot;Inquisitor&quot;]
&gt; I think the biggest problem with Inquisitor is that heathens are aware that they are heathens. Pretty simple, really. There&#39;s no need to have Inquisitors&#39; existence outted just by existing, and it can encourage &quot;BD Inquisitors&quot; 
&gt; 
&gt; There&#39;s also no reason this class should stay alive upon winning, as unlike Scorned and Mercenary there is no more &quot;objective&quot; they can do. Although this does weaken the possibility of fakeclaiming Inquisitor. 
[/details]
 

&gt; TLDR:
&gt; 	- **Heathens should not be aware that they are heathens**
&gt; 	- *Suicide upon victory* 


[details=&quot;Scorned&quot;]
&gt; Scorned is the only Neutral I actually think is on the weaker side, but it has a well designed kit for its wincondition. I&#39;ve already suggested this in the #feedback-balance channel to fairly negative feedback, but the only buff I can really think of to Scorned that isn&#39;t massively gamechanging would be the follows.
&gt; 
&gt; Change their wincondition from &quot;*See* two marked targets executed.&quot; to &quot;*Get* two marked targets executed.&quot;. The only difference this would make is that if you are killed the night you mark somebody who gets executed the next day (as your 2nd mark), or die to a Hunter you marked (as your 2nd mark), you&#39;d still win. Not a gamebreaking buff, but a small one. Perhaps an exception to the Hunter arrow. 
&gt; 
&gt; Additionally, after victory, currently Scorned is just *there*. They can&#39;t use their abilities, so they just become a person with a vote. While I personally am not a fan of victorious neutrals surviving, the current solution of just making Scorned a vanillized class is awful. Taking a page from Mercenary, Scorned should be able to continue using their abilities and get bonus GP for successful frames. An exact number could be debated, but I think 20 or 25 is a good start.
[/details]


&gt; TLDR: 
&gt; 	- *Let a dead Scorned get credit for a marked targets execution* 
&gt; 	- Either
&gt; 		- *Suicide upon victory* 
&gt; 		- **Give Scorned an incentive to go for additional frames upon victory** 
	

[details=&quot;Mercenary&quot;]
&gt; Mercenary simply has to occupy 4 people to win, which is very easy given the current meta of open claiming and is generally very easy in any meta. While I think the class is too easy I only think the the number of brilders to win should be increased by 1 (from 6 to 7) 
&gt; 
&gt; Additionally, I do think there&#39;s a problematic interaction with how Mercenaries interact with eachother. 
&gt; 
&gt; I don&#39;t actually know what the best solution is to &quot;who gets what if multiple Mercenaries are on the same target&quot;, but being the higher numbered Mercenary is extremely unsatisfying and quite frustrating at times. Making Merc unique is an option, and with how powerful Shield is, wouldn&#39;t be completely unjustified. I do like this solution a lot more, as Shield is such a powerful protective ability and having so many occupies going around can be unfun for all occupiable classes.
&gt; 
&gt; The alternative options are to somehow give both Mercenaries brilders. I don&#39;t believe giving both Mercs the full amount would be at all fair, as it&#39;d be extremely easy. Giving both Mercs half brilders is an option, although then you have to deal with rounding up or down in the inevitable &quot;.5&quot; situations.
[/details]


&gt;TLDR:
&gt; 	- **Make Mercenary need 7 brilders to win** 
&gt; 	- Either:
&gt; 		- **Make Merc unique** 
&gt; 		- *Divide brilders to both Mercenaries if two are on the same target in half (rounding up or down)*


[details=&quot;Sellsword&quot;]
&gt; I think Sellsword needs an entire rework. The class concept of being an &quot;evil merc&quot; isn&#39;t exactly unique, and the wincondition is way too generous for how much mechanical power this class has.
&gt; 
&gt; I think one direction to consider (if the &quot;evil neut&quot; theme stays) is weakening the class, giving it one time death immunity from non-BD killers, and perhaps making the wincondition a tad harder. The goal I have in mind is making Sellsword a class that assists the evils socially more than mechanically. 
&gt; 
&gt; While I understand the place a naturally evil-leaning neutral has in the game, I&#39;d still personally like to see this class reworked to be more like old Contract Merc. But I&#39;m totally a bit biased here ^^
[/details]
 


&gt; TLDR:
&gt; 	- **Rework this class** (preferably along the lines of old Contract Merc)
  
	

[details=&quot;Pretender&quot;]

&gt; I don&#39;t really want to talk about this class, because I don&#39;t think I can give it a fair assessment. I&#39;m very biased here. I think this iteration of Pretender is just fundamentally an awful class.
&gt;
&gt; A neutral who has the wincon of getting kinged is certainly something that *can* work, but this ain&#39;t it.

[/details]
 

&gt; 
&gt; TLDR:
&gt; 	- **Rework/Remove**

Thoughts? I think there&#39;s some more specific class changes I&#39;d like to look into in the future, but in my eyes a topic on *every* neutral was better to get some discussion started, and I think at face value every single neutral has room for improvement. ~~Although &quot;rework pret&quot; &quot;rework SS&quot; isn&#39;t exactly revolutionary feedback~~ :sweat_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 22:21:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t disagree, hence why I’m proposing nerfs/reworks to literally every neutral that isn’t Scorned.</p>
<p>And willing to concede that my small buff to Scorned might also be unnecessary. (it was italicized for a reason)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 22:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="katze" data-post="41" data-topic="80017" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/katze/40/30997_2.png" class="avatar"> katze:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Compared to other neuts, there’s a lot more that can go wrong.</p>
<p>Target dies? Can’t get credit towards wincon<br>
Occupied/jailed target?  Can’t get credit towards wincon<br>
Two leads? Better hope you get listened to, or you can’t get credit towards wincon</p>
<p>Meanwhile with other neuts:</p>
<p>Inq Occed? who cares, other people are dying, meaning your heathens are closer to being more obvious</p>
<p>Alch/Fool? lol, what can go wrong here</p>
<p>Merc? shield prince and you’re 3/4 to winning</p>
<p>Sellsword? you can literally die n1 and win half of the time</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Difficult neuts are not bad for the game</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 22:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One day I was so out of patience to play Poss I just claimed Paladin D2 with a redcheck<br>
It was cult.game.<br>
I lynched the CL<br>
Never jumped but they thought I was possed so they executed me</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this is great when I’m Unseen and terrible when I’m Fool</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have an inexplicable ability to talk myself out of getting executed even when executing me is absolutely the rational choice</p>
<p>The other day I was found Unseen N1 and nearly got pardoned (on the theory that I was framed BD, not the theory that I  should be chainjailed) with an Obs claim</p>
<p>today I was found S/I as MM claiming Drunk, got the Princess executed, didn’t get executed in jail (to be fair that kind of made sense in context), and the next day proceeded to get the last mislynch we needed by claiming to have debbed someone to a dead person</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>be katze<br>
be fool<br>
claim fool d1 like an alpha<br>
hide n1 like an alpha<br>
get sorcbombed<br>
fuck up text formatting</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>&gt;be marshal the fool<br>
&gt;claim reaper with only reaper left in game<br>
&gt;king’s vote needed to kill me<br>
&gt;king chilled<br>
&gt;same thing happens the next day<br>
&gt;i keep tauting the king like i chilled him<br>
&gt;they finally up me<br>
&gt;fooled<br>
&gt;reaper win</p>
<p>my best fool story</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Arete" data-post="44" data-topic="80017">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/arete/40/30476_2.png" class="avatar"> Arete:</div>
<blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>be Arete</p>
</blockquote>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>this is where you went wrong</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>&gt; be Arete the Fool<br>
&gt; claim CW<br>
&gt; know that 14 was jailed N2<br>
&gt; ‘N2 - Empower 14 - no aid’<br>
&gt; no one notices (except Kape the Merc, who thinks I’m evil and claims SS to me to try to get me to pop his shield)<br>
&gt; spend like three days TBing people to say ‘how did 9 visit 14 when 14 was jailed?’<br>
&gt; finally get executed several days later</p>
<hr>
<p>&gt; be Arete the Fool<br>
&gt; claim Knight<br>
&gt; never get investigated or do anything else that might indicate BDness<br>
&gt; spend several days refusing to vote up the obvious Mastermind, who basically everyone thinks is evil<br>
&gt; also refuse to CS the outed Sellsword<br>
&gt; get accused of  being gamethrowing BD<br>
&gt; die to bleed because Unseen bled me for some reason</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just claim knight lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 03:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="katze" data-post="41" data-topic="80017">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/katze/40/30997_2.png" class="avatar"> katze:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fool? lol, what can go wrong here</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You clearly have not seen me playing Fool <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/upside_down_face.png?v=9" title=":upside_down_face:" class="emoji" alt=":upside_down_face:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Compared to other neuts, there’s a lot more that can go wrong.</p>
<p>Target dies? Can’t get credit towards wincon<br>
Occupied/jailed target?  Can’t get credit towards wincon<br>
Two leads? Better hope you get listened to, or you can’t get credit towards wincon</p>
<p>Meanwhile with other neuts:</p>
<p>Inq Occed? who cares, other people are dying, meaning your heathens are closer to being more obvious</p>
<p>Alch/Fool? lol, what can go wrong here</p>
<p>Merc? shield prince and you’re 3/4 to winning</p>
<p>Sellsword? you can literally die n1 and win half of the time</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had a game the other day where the Scorned got their second mark by disguising the NK as the class they were fakeclaiming as</p>
<p>it was a pretty good meme</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>frame is the far more +ev move n2</p>
<p>but disguse is funnererer</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>literally the strat is</p>
<p>disg d1 neuts as NK</p>
<p>“flirt” them K/O</p>
<p>get them exed with little to no resistance minus mechanics.</p>
<hr>
<p>n2 just frame or disg someone and say they “attacked” with WoW.</p>
<p>alternatively, “flirt” a S/S or S/I claim as K/O and disgusie them as prince and make everyone think they gamethrew as you laugh from the grave</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m willing to concede that Scorned needs a buff (there is a reason it’s italicized in the OP); but I still don’t see a world where it’s not the hardest neutral <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><s>Mostly cause every neutral is easy</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah the frame isn’t how you win scorned.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scorned is easy for people who are willing to actually push on anyone and hard for people who just mark people all game and hope someone hits their frames</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>scorned is easy for vets.</p>
<p>harder to get screwed over n1.</p>
<p>probably easier for vets and harder for newbies.</p>
<p>Depends on who you want to balance for</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In this current meta? Merc practically wins for free if they don’t die N1/N2 and Inq as well.</p>
<p>Alch can claim D1 and go AFK and probably still win half of the time.</p>
<p>While I think some players overestimate how hard Scorned is, I think it’s the only neutral that even requires effort to win at the moment. Which is why I don’t see harm in a tiny buff for it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>merc.</p>
<p>alch.</p>
<p>inq.</p>
<p>fool is the same amount of easy</p>
<p>and SS is the easiest</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Which neutral do you think is harder than Scorned?</p>
<p>Given half of them can win just by existing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>scorned is one of the easiest neuts</p>
<p>i think i had like a 70% scorned winrate when i played TOL</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I look at it in a similar vein to Fool, who can win while reaped.</p>
<p>It’s a small buff to the hardest non-NK neutral.</p>
<p>If you play well, you can win more.</p>
<p>Otherwise, you have one extra chance to secure a win you wouldn’t have previously had.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ToL Neutral Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JakeTheWolfie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, it doesn’t feel like clutch winning and winning more mesh together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80017-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tol-neutral-suggestions/80017.rss">ToL Neutral Suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
