<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pretender Rework</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212</link>
    <description>&gt; [color=&quot;gray&quot;]**The Pretender** :shield: [/color]
&gt; -
&gt; [color=&quot;gray&quot;]**Neutral Special**[/color]
&gt; **Passive:**
&gt; **Dirty Blood:** You are death immune once and appear as royal to investigative checks.
&gt; **Usurper:** During the King election, votes for you will be multiplied by the number of Kings you have successfully killed. (starting at 1x, so if you kill one king you get 2x which is royal blood, 2 kings 3x, etc.)
&gt; 
&gt; **Day:**
&gt; **Ballot Mixing (3 use):** Mark a player. The next time they step for King, all votes for them will be invalid. You can have multiple players marked. Marks disappear if you die.
&gt; **Distract (2 use):** Silence target player for 20 seconds. They will not be able to speak, vote or use abilities for the duration. 
&gt; 
&gt; **Night:**
&gt; **Blood Test (inf use):** Check if a player has Royal Blood or is the King. If they are you will attack them tonight. They can not be healed. Cannot be used on the same target twice in a row.
&gt; **Mimicry (inf use):** Use the first ability of the last Non-Unique class with Royal Blood that you killed.
&gt; 
&gt; *Win condition: Become King and survive until the end of the game.*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 16:02:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this was exactly the idea.<br>
Usurper will allow the Unseen to FORCE the election of an evil King. Early game its just terrible since everyone will see it.  but late.  this could be a decisive factor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/58</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-58</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>These are the best class proposals I’ve ever seen, imagine how dramatic that would be for Usurper to just instantly become king?  Nothing would match it except Decide Fate.  Terrible early game of course but would win late games.</p>
<p>Success’s investigative ability (royal blood check) is fantastic, it’s very useful yet easy to fake.  Before Maid this sort of things was a problem for MM’s fake claim but not anymore.</p>
<p>And being able to give royal blood to someone is very cool too, even though lore wise would make more sense on King.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/57</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 11:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-57</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Audreyaloy" data-post="53" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/audreyaloy/40/3180_2.png" class="avatar"> Audreyaloy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>** (Passive)** - Crowned. During elections for a new king, votes for you will count for 2, this passive will be considered as royal blood by other pretenders.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why is this not just actually royal blood</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 07:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-56</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Already changed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/55</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 23:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-55</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so bascally</p>
<p>a worse princess but slightly better duchess in some way?</p>
<p>eh, could be a bit more original</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/54</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 22:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-54</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I got a fix for you people …</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="Blue">Successor</font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="Blue">Blue Dragon Social </font></strong><br>
** (Passive)** - Crowned. During elections for a new king, votes for you will count for 2, this passive will be considered as royal blood by other pretenders.<br>
** (Night)** - Blood Test. Check if a player has royal blood, if they are, you will learn their classes. (infiinite uses)<br>
** (Night)** - Promotion. Give Royal blood passive to a player, they will appear as a royal to investigators (1 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Defeat the Unseen, the Cult, along with any neutrals who seek to harm you.</p>
<p>Become</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="Purple"> Pretender</font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="Purple">Unseen Special</font></strong><br>
** (Passive)** - Usurper Upon election for a new king. you will directly become the Evil King, ignoring all votes.<br>
** (Night)** - Expert Framing  (infinite uses), Check and frame a player, you will learn their possible class types, and anyone else who investigate this target shall receive shall received framed results<br>
(Night)** -  Disguise (3 uses), disguise a player, if said player dies tonight or tomorrow, they shall appear as the class you have selected. ( can target yourself or other members of the unseen)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Defeat the Blue Dragon along with any neutrals who seek to harm you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/53</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 22:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-53</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well see noble  being fake-claimable when they can remove noble Twin.   then you have to be lucky and hope no Phys, Chrono, Knight or invest classes just noticed you claimed their logs are not real, to no get executed. like Observer…   (while the class could be easily fake-claimed, you realise like me. it carry Way more risks.</p>
<p>Invoker, cannot  hh right now… I’ve tried and and the 2nd target become impossible moment I click on the first…   So no… invoker cannot Happy hour right now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/52</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 01:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-52</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Audreyaloy" data-post="50" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/audreyaloy/40/3180_2.png" class="avatar"> Audreyaloy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And they cannot happy hour</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>they can actually. Just select the same target twice.</p>
<p>And I said noble is fake claimable with 2 abilities. You need at least 2 abilities designed with fake claiming noble in mind in order to fake claim noble. But with those 2 it’s doable.</p>
<p>Specifically you need whisper reading and force vote. Gossip can be faked although not reliably.</p>
<p>Drunk just needs omni-redirect</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/51</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-51</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>multiple points here</p>
<p>1 Invoker cannot claim Drunk for more then 2 nights. And they cannot happy hour, thanks to a recent fix. Making it. a bit hard to kill Drunk. Also. since Drunk is a powerfull BD class. It is not a good idea to king a drunk claim.</p>
<p>2 Noble is the worst fake-claim ever, is not only easily confirmable. but gossip on random, it can be pretty hard to fake alone, especially. if you claim there was a phys on your target and no one claim to be a phys</p>
<p>2 Scorned can be redirected to the king. but they should only execute a GOOD king when they have 1 mark, since the Good King  passive will prevent the court from having a 2nd execution. its the same as Scorned framing a fool night 1. one might think its super for both neutral. but once the fool passive  trigger, the Scorned cannot get any mark at all for the next two nights. And During those two days, the court might question them for (leads)… but nothing she offer is good for herself. Also, redirectiong scorned to the King require a DRUNK. An outed Scorned is not very dangerous. Beside, very often, you can find original evils, without any investigative works…<br>
Imagine a bit. scorned framing a prince… the situation is not dangerous by itself. good king will pardon, while evil king will execute, but they would act the same without a scorned.</p>
<p>Seeker might step for king.   but for Mastermind, especially when the original, assassin is dead… its crazy.</p>
<p>right now. Sellsword is the only scum sided neutral. you say Inq is scum sided.  But I find that more often, when I am heretic, no one cares about me. that I must fake claim as BD, since the Knight as more important things to do, then protecting a fellow bd member from a neutral. We even have (BD inqs), who out day 1, and directly give then heathens classes. If there is a neutral I would execute without any though, its the INQ. but people I play with do not share this idea.</p>
<p>Also.    the Unhealable part is what I hate the most. its not needed at all.</p>
<p>on that note. I am so late…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/50</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 20:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-50</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Audreyaloy" data-post="48" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/audreyaloy/40/3180_2.png" class="avatar"> Audreyaloy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A scorned can make a BD king win, because of the simple that executing the king, is a contraduction to her own goal. as she cannot frame the king, and executing good king will stop trials during the next day, the same way, a Scorned has no reason to execute an evil king</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>None of this is relevant and it also has exceptions. If a Scorned is redirected she can mark a King. The frame won’t matter but she can still win due to executing a King.</p>
<p>Sellsword stepping for King doesn’t matter for the purposes of this discussion. The point is that a Sellsword is scum and BD will want to Kill a known Sellsword when given the option.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Audreyaloy" data-post="48" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/audreyaloy/40/3180_2.png" class="avatar"> Audreyaloy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The only way for an evil pret to exist. Would to give him drunk/noble/princess abilities all at the same time. by Changeing Blood Test into something like (create potion) from old Alchemist who had 4 potions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>She doesn’t need Princess Abilities.</p>
<p>Mastermind and seeker already are sufficient deterrents to mindlessly kinging Princess claims.</p>
<p>That just leaves Noble and Drunk. And if we remove twin (which has an entire list of reasons to do) then both classes can be faked at once with the 2 night abilities and 2 day abilities.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Audreyaloy" data-post="48" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/audreyaloy/40/3180_2.png" class="avatar"> Audreyaloy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but there is a problem with that , what we do with starting evil king. Killing the evil king is detrimental to evil.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hence the difference between scum and a scum sided neutral. This is not a game design problem, but rather something the Pretender will need to consider as a player.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/49</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 20:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-49</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A scorned can make a BD king win, because of the simple that executing the king, is a contraduction to her own goal. as she cannot frame the king, and executing good king will stop trials during the next day, the same way, a Scorned has no reason to execute an evil king</p>
<p>Sellsword can step for king, just saying. as else, an easy way to prove a sellsword. would be to ask everyone to step for king. and who ever does not step is evil.</p>
<p>The only way for an evil pret to exist. Would to give him drunk/noble/princess abilities all at the same time.  by Changeing Blood Test   into something like (create potion) from old Alchemist who had 4 potions.</p>
<p>but there is a problem with that ,   what we do with starting evil king.     Killing the evil king is detrimental to evil.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/48</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 19:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-48</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Regardless though. In order for Pretenders wincon to be engaging the BD must not want Pretender to be King.</p>
<p>Right now you open claim Pretender, use Ballet Swap to prove yourself, and get Kinged when the King dies.</p>
<p>This isn’t interesting or involved and it doesn’t improve King election dynamics.</p>
<p>If BD actively wanted to avoid making the Pretender a King then she would have to fake claim and thus inherently puts suspicion on claims that generally get Kinged.</p>
<p>That’s why my ideal solution would be to make Pretender very good at fake claiming several Classes. But then also make Pretender King have the Sellsword wincon rather than the Alchemist wincon.</p>
<p>That way Pretender is a scum that wants to prioritize looking BD before turning on the BD when elected. And she’s still possible to scumread since she needs to not do so well at being BD that scum will lose after she is elected.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/47</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 16:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-47</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not counting pretender (because that’s the class being changed here) there are only 2 neutral classes that can freely side with BD. Merc and Alchemist to be specific.</p>
<p>Sellsword cannot ever side with BD.</p>
<p>NK is NK</p>
<p>All other neuts can technically win with BD but are inherently harmful to BD when trying to win.</p>
<p>Inquisitor wants 2-3 specific BD players dead. Scorned wants to get players executed regardless of faction, and just by existing makes it harder to trust investigators. And fool prevents 2 to 3 days of executions, including the day you executed the fool.</p>
<p>So Neutrals that are incentivized to side with scum are more common than Neutrals that are not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/46</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 16:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-46</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would not  go that way. When you Suggest a neutral class. Normally. we want a class that can side toward any side as they want, as they long as they can accomplish their objective.   this current pretender is extremely dangerous to any Royals.   and Extremely dangerous to the BD if every they king prince, as they attack the prince the same night as they find him.</p>
<p>Also. sadly. even with Mimicry, the Pret cannot   really fake claim Drunk, noble. and will be unable to fake claim princess.   So. you want to take the thrones, but are unable to fake any kind of royal class. I mean you must kill a drunk to fake drunk… so  the first nights, you’ll have nothing to say, except I debauch the deads</p>
<p>the current pret aint perfect. but he got something to claim. his worst problem actually are not royals. but butlers. who will never hesitate to poison the pret king</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/45</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 07:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-45</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pretender is a mistake this is still a mistake but a better mistake.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 04:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-44</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pretty sure making Pretenders an auto exe is the entire point</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 03:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-43</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Audreyaloy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Current pret has investigatives abilities. and very good abilities to offer to the BD. In exchange for their support. And the results of the pretender cannot be fake. …</p>
<p>This pret has nothing to offer to the BD.  so this would kill the pret out Meta. Which is a good point. in fact, the only thing it can offer, is to find mm, when they claim princess. as it more chance to kill prince, and others royals. No one will leave an outed pretender alive.</p>
<p>And a problem, is that it has an unhealable attack, I think this would put too messure on the knight, who cannot be everywhere at the same time.</p>
<p>while its true I dislike the current pretender, and hate bd pretenders as evil. the Pret cannot investigate during all games, he normally has 3 nights, before he has to kill king. and the longer the game goes, with fewer person, the pret might actually side with evil.</p>
<p>I prefer the current pretender to this rework… Sorry, but I think this is a mistake.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 23:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-42</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="40" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This would probably be in Maid’s Matchmake class card info; it just sounds weird to read it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>On Maid it would be even weirder. Also we could introduce more Royalty checkers later too.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="40" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In essence, the passive is <em>almost</em> useless.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or you can claim CW, Maid, literally anything if you get unlucky with Blood Tests and use your bonus votes to sneak a King win from the others.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="40" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Would you be told what you killed when you kill them?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because the attack is unhealable, if you manage to attack them, they would die. So barring Defile, you would know. Even if they were to be Defiled, you would know thanks to Mimicry, which would basically become the Royals ability. Mimicry is like a placeholder, it becomes whatever the Royal had.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="40" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The infinite use effectively makes you a pseudo-NK similar to Alch or Inq except you have unlimited attacks on Kings and Royals.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah that’s what I was afraid of, but you can’t really limit it. I could do can’t target each player once but then you could get screwed over by King guards. If you got some idea for this, hit me up, always happy to improve my designs.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="40" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That said, what about in games where there <em>are</em> no royals</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what Usurper was designed for. Can’t get a confirmed deb or gossip? Kill the King for easier elections.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="40" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d almost rather it pierce non-King Night-Immunity if it has to pierce something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think I made this back in allies King, you might be right about it piercing guards instead. We’ll see.</p>
<hr>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Polarthief" data-post="40" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/polarthief/40/3752_2.png" class="avatar"> Polarthief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Overall, better than live Pret</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good enough, into the game with it <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 12:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-41</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Polarthief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Dirty Blood:</strong> You are death immune once and <strong>appear as royal to investigative checks.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This would probably be in Maid’s Matchmake class card info; it just sounds weird to read it.</p>
<aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Usurper:</strong> During the King election, votes for you will be multiplied by the number of Kings you have successfully killed. (starting at 1x, so if you kill one king you get 2x which is royal blood, 2 kings 3x, etc.)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t see you being voted up without getting an early confirmation, and if you did, you’re basically like live Pretender anyway, but now you have 3 claims: Princess (like live), Drunk, and Noble. In essence, the passive is <em>almost</em> useless.</p>
<aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Mimicry (inf use):</strong> Use the first ability of the last Non-Unique class with Royal Blood that you killed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Would you be told what you killed when you kill them? I don’t see this ability working otherwise (esp when bodies can be defiled). Drunk would be especially weird since it requires 2 targets (well, the first targeting the second).</p>
<aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Blood Test <strong>(inf use)</strong></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is the biggest bit that scares me. The infinite use effectively makes you a pseudo-NK similar to Alch or Inq except you have unlimited attacks on Kings and Royals. I’m not sure how much I’d really care for that, especially if it’s a 3-neut game of Alch/Inq/Pret.</p>
<p>That said, what about in games where there <em>are</em> no royals (besides Prince, obviously)? That would make your night abilities effectively worthless, except for killing the King and Prince (though killing Prince would likely screw you more than anyone else). Idk, I like the concept, but I feel that the execution would be heavily dependent on the RNG of what classes are in the game.</p>
<p>Also with how much heal-piercing we have in the game already, I don’t think we really need another. I’d almost rather it pierce non-King Night-Immunity if it has to pierce something.</p>
<p>Overall, better than live Pret, but I don’t know if I would like the actual implementation. I feel like the meta would keep having the open Pret claims. This is especially the case if there’s a Princess as having them check you would confirm. S/I is non-framed and clearly not NK. On top of that, you can use Distract to pseudo-confirm yourself too (bonus points if found as S/I prior). People are already fine with putting Pret in, they’d be more fine with it to get you out of the potential killing role you start in.</p>
<p>Just my two cents.</p>
<p>PS: This is only a ‘necro’ because Kape posted this in Feedback Discussion on the Discord last night <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Didn’t even notice the date on the most recent post!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 10:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-40</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soulshade55r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Win condition: Become King and survive until the end of the game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=umDr0mPuyQc" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=umDr0mPuyQc</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 06:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-39</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yattien]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Usurper:</strong> During the King election, votes for you will be multiplied by the number of Kings you have successfully killed. (starting at 1x, so if you kill one king you get 2x which is royal blood, 2 kings 3x, etc.)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Start at normal Royal Blood (2x), increasing from there.</p>
<aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Ballot Mixing (3 use):</strong> Mark a player. The next time they step for King, all votes for them will be invalid. You can have multiple players marked. Marks disappear if you die.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Much more useful than reversing a king, which never does much anyway, short of reversing the slam pardon to an exe on the prince, people won’t usually exe the king and just believe he was revered. All it did was proof the pretender.</p>
<aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Blood Test (inf use):</strong> Check if a player has Royal Blood or is the King. If they are you will attack them tonight. They can not be healed. Cannot be used on the same target twice in a row.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Much more useful. I never liked the whole “check if they are royal before you can attack them” thing. Old Inq never had to test for magic before attacking, he just stopped the attack if they weren’t magical. Even worse, you know a person is royal (out prince for example) but mechanically you can’t do anything until you test them.<br>
This solves that.</p>
<aside class="quote group-guides" data-username="Kape" data-post="1" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kape/40/16017_2.png" class="avatar"> Kape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Mimicry (inf use):</strong> Use the first ability of the last Non-Unique class with Royal Blood that you killed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d be concerned about getting a game with only 1-2 royals, making this useless if you’re not the one to kill them. A pity mechanic to help might be useful, such as you gaining a random dead royals abilities after x days or something might be useful. Otherwise I like it, gives the Pretender more flexibility in claims other than princess.</p>
<p>Overall, if it stops the stupidly annoying Immortal BD Princess pretender play then go for it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-38</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="firekitten" data-post="5" data-topic="76212">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/firekitten/40/24106_2.png" class="avatar"> firekitten:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Your first priority is BALANCE when making or reworking a class</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually balance is the FINAL priority when making or reworking a class.</p>
<p>The first priority is establishing the purpose behind the class/rework. You want something that fundamentally works at what it’s supposed to be and THEN you worry about it’s effectiveness.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 16:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-37</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lastday3312]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is this suppose to discourage BD pret?</p>
<p>since it doesn’t look like it,it just encourage NK pret.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 16:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah right. Forgot about that</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pretender Rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maid matchmake.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76212-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/pretender-rework/76212.rss">Pretender Rework</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
