<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061</link>
    <description># Forum of Lies is in need of a new Blue Dragon Killer!
# And you can help! 

Starting immediately and going on until April 7th - We&#39;re accepting ideas for a new Blue Dragon killer to be added into Forum of Lies. 

# Prize -

The winner of this competition will have their class added into the official version of Forum of Lies. (barring balance modifications)

In addition to this, the winner will recieve a game on steam up to 20 dollars of their choice from me. 

# Competition Rules.
* The Win condition for the class must be:
 &quot;*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*&quot;

* The Class must have the ability to directly or indirectly kill other players. It must be convertible and have both the Unseen version and Cult Alts available.

* The class&#39; type must be &#39;Killer.&#39;, and it&#39;s faction must be &#39;Blue Dragon&quot;.... Yeah, go figure. 

* The format for the class card must be the same as all the other Forum of Lies cards. If you aren&#39;t comfortable formatting it manually, you may use [this class card creator.](http://puu.sh/Ax2nE/391a6a63ea.html)

* You must have previously participated in at least one Forum of Lies, Special Forum of Lies, Newbie Forum of Lies, or Experimental Forum of Lies. 

* Winners will be chosen by the Forum of Lies Team ( Myself, @Icibalus, @Solic ) on April 7th, and the winner will be announced shortly after. 

* No cheating! Don&#39;t copy other player&#39;s ideas. Don&#39;t steal other people&#39;s custom classes from elsewhere on the forum. All the obvious stuff. 

* You may submit any number of classes - however, you can only win once. Quality &gt; Quantity.

## Bonus Points. 

* Try to keep the theme fitting with Forum of Lies. Make it something unique and special, but don&#39;t break the theme too hard!  

* Make it powerful, but try to keep it at a fair level. If necessary, we can nerf it after the fact - but start strong to leave a good impression. 

# The competition begins... now! You may post your submissions in a class card format in response to this post.

# Submissions:

https://forum.imperium42.com/t/class-suggestion-the-ranger-and-the-bandit/73903?u=orangeandblack5

https://forum.imperium42.com/t/archer-bd-killer-sharpshooter-unseen-support/75718

[details=The Crusader]
&gt;# [color = steblue]  The Crusader [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = steblue] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Providence (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the Blue Dragon faction visits you this coming night, they will be prevented and bled. - 2 uses
**Hand of God (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Blue Dragon faction visits them they will be bled by you. This does not stop their actions. - Infinite uses
**Deus Vult (Night)** - Attacks and kills two targets. You will also die of exhaustion the night they use this ability regardless of the ability&amp;rsquo;s outcome. - 1 use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Zealot [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
&gt;**(Providence) Blood Providence (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the Cult visits you this coming night, they will be prevented and bled the next day. - 2 uses
&gt;**(Hand of God) Hand of Mithras (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Cult visits them they will be bled. This does not stop their actions. - Infinite uses
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Deus Vult): Incarnation of Mithras (Night)** - Allows the Cult Leader to kill an additional target if you are sacrificed. - 1 uses

&gt;# [color = purple] The Zealot [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Killer [/color]**
**Piety (Day)** - The Zealot will be shown as a member of the Blue Dragon to faction checks if investigated the coming night. - 3 uses
**Martyrdom (Day)** - If a player is executed this day, the Zealot can choose to sacrifice themselves in order to stop the execution and save the accused played while also bleeding their first accuser. - 1 use
**Malleus Maleficarum (Night)** - Bleeds any player that attempts to visit your target tonight. - 3 uses
**Regicide (Night)** - Attacks and kills the King while bypassing all forms of healing and immunities. Regicide will also kill the Zealot the same night. - 1 use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/details]


[details=The Duelist]
&gt;# [color = steblue]  The Duelist [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = steblue] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count twice.
**Schuld (Passive)** - If you have killed any Blue Dragon-aligned players in the match, then you will not be allowed to receive votes to become the King.
**Versetzen (Day)** - Grants night immunity for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then you will gain a use of Zornhau. - 2 uses
**Mittelhau (Night)** - Redirects the selected player&amp;rsquo;s action to you while also granting yourself immunity to all redirected attacks and conversions, then attack the player. If you successfully kill a player then you will gain a use of Zornhau. Disables the your night abilities if the target is aligned with the Blue Dragon. - Infinite uses
**Zornhau (Night)** - Prevents you from being occupied or redirected, then attacks the your target and kills them, bypassing healing and night immunity. Disables your night abilities if the target is aligned with the Blue Dragon. - 0 uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Baronet [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult 1 Point Alt:**[/color]
**Royal Blood (Passive)**
**(Schuld): Grausamkeit (Passive)** - If you become a Devout King, then Dark Gods&#39; Crown can be used twice per corpse.
**(Versetzen): Opfern (Day)** - Grants night immunity to you for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then the Cult Leader&#39;s next Blood of Mithras will be free of charge. - 2 uses
**(Mittelhau): **Vergeltung** (Night)** - Redirects the player onto you. If they attack you then you will counterattack and kill them. - Infinite uses
[color = darkred] **Cult 2 Point Alt:**[/color]
**(Zornhau): Königsmord (Night)** - Kills the King, bypassing everything. If the you kill a Devout King, then you will commit suicide. - 1 uses

&gt;# [color = purple]The Baronet [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple]Unseen Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Royal Blood (Passive)** - Your votes for King will count twice.
**Gerissen (Passive)** - If you become the King, then you will gain one use of Scheme despite not being the starting King.
**Vom Tach (Night)** - Deflects any incoming attack against all members of the Unseen and kills the attacker. - Three uses
**Missgunst (Night)** - Removes Royal Blood from a target for the remainder of the game. - 1 use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/details]


[details=The Thaumaturge]
&gt; # [color = steblue] The Thaumaturge [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = steblue] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Thaumaturgic Focus (Passive)** - You are immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Thunder (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Thunder on your target, causing them to explode and kill the player before they are converted while also putting the conversion on cooldown. You are notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the conversion happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses
**Sigil of Fire (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Fire on your target, causing them to explode and kill any player that attacks the target, but does not prevent any actions against them. You are notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the attack happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Arcanist [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Sigil of Thunder): Thunderbolt of Corax (Night)** - If the Cult&#39;s conversion is off cooldown then you can put it on cooldown to enact an additional kill that is guaranteed to succeed. - Infinite uses
**(Sigil of Fire): Inferno of Mithras (Night)** - You will kill yourself and anyone visiting you. - One use


&gt;# [color = purple] The Arcanist [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Social [/color]**
**Arcane Focus (Passive)** - You are immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Illusion (Night)** - Choose a class and sets a Sigil on another Unseen player and they will show up as the chosen class to any Investigative roles that visits them. The Sigil is destroyed once the target is visited by an Investigative, requiring them to be recast. - Infinite uses
**Sigil of Madness (Night)** - Puts a Sigil of Madness on a player, permanently giving them a Mind Warp effect until you die. - 1 use
&gt;*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

[/details]


[details=The Warrior]
&gt;# [color = steblue] The Warrior [/color]
&gt;
&gt;**[color = steblue] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]**
&gt;**Combat Ready (Passive)** - If you are attacked during the first two nights, you will be immune and will counterattack instead of dying.
**Bloodlust (Passive)** - For every successful kill, you will gain an additional night of Combat Ready.
**Raging Axes (Night)** - Attacks and kills a player. If the target was Blue Dragon-aligned, then you will lose your night abilities and you will be shown as Unseen or Cult to faction checks. - Infinite uses
**Taunt (Night)** - Redirects the target&amp;rsquo;s night action to the yourself. Redirects past the second night will trigger Combat Ready. - One use
&gt;*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;**Converts into **[color = purple] The Marauder [/color]** or **[color = darkred] The Invoker [/color]****
[color = darkred]**Cult points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
[color = darkred]**Cult Alt:**[/color]
**(Bloodlust): Blood for Blood (Passive)** - If you are sacrificed for Blood of Mithras, then the kill will bypass all forms of protection.
**(Raging Axes): Anstreim&#39;s Paranoia (Night)** - All Killer-type classes will be show as members of this Cult for this night. - One use


&gt;# [color = purple] The Marauder [/color]
&gt;**[color = purple] Unseen Offensive [/color]**
**Massacre (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation, death at night, and will counterattack against attackers. This passive is lost once you are promoted to an Assassin.
**Aura of Dread (Day)** - All non-Killer roles will be prevented from visiting the Marauder this coming night. - One use
**Boast (Night)** - Redirects the target player to yourself - Infinite uses
**Glare (Night)** - Occupies a player for the night. If your target is successfully occupied and is also attacked the same night then they cannot be healed and their night immunity will be bypassed. - One use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/details]

The Warrior Blue Dragon Killer
Trained (Passive) - Will not kill if there is more than one visitor using Tarnish
Silent Impact (Day) - make someone bleed and die the next night not knowing, cannot use until D3 - 1 Use. 
Rusted Armour (Day) - Be Immune to attacks tonight - 1 Use. 
Backstab (Night) - force a player to target you if they are attacking killing them, you won&#39;t be immune to attacks unless you used RA - 3 Uses. 
Tarnish (Night) - Protect someone killing a visitor - 2 Uses. 

The Crusader Unseen Killer
Light Armour (Day) - Make yourself Immune to death at night also appearing as Blue Dragon - 1 Use. 
Second plot (Night) - if the Assassins Kill fails or is jailed/Occupied you&#39;ll carry out the kill on a new target of your choice - Infinite
Dark Rage (Night) - If assassins target fails to be killed you&#39;ll bleed them unknowingly they will die the next night - 1 Use. 

Cult alts. 
Rusted armour - 1 Use. 1 pt. 
Cult Rage, if CLs convert fails you&#39;ll bleed the target Unknowingly making them die next night - 1 Use. 1 pt. 
Second plot - if CL is jailed, occupied or fails night action you may carry out a kill on someone - 2 Uses 2pt.

&gt;# [color = &quot;steblue&quot;] The Duelist [/color] 
&gt;**[color = &quot;steblue&quot;] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]** 
**Competitive (Passive)** - Occupy and Redirect immune
**Last stand (Passive)** - If you are the last Blue Dragon alive then Strike bypasses death immunity
**Parry (Night)** - If Target player visits you then remove their immunity’s and redirect them to themselves - Infinite uses 
**Strike (Night)** - Occupy and kill target player - 3 uses 
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **[color = &quot;darkred&quot;] 2 cult points. Each ability costs 1 [/color]**
&gt;
&gt; Last Stand -&gt; Retaliation - Each time after a cultist dies to something besides Blood of Mithras, the next Blood of Mithras will not kill the cultist selected. Does not stack. 
&gt;
&gt; Strike -&gt; Expose - Chose a player and a class. If the target is that class then kill them bypassing healing and death immunity. (2 uses) 

&gt;# [color = &quot;purple&quot;] The Gladiator [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;purple&quot;] Unseen Offensive [/color]** 
**Competitive (Passive)** - Occupy and Redirect immune
**Berserk (Passive)** - If the Mastermind is dead then Stagger has unlimited uses and Occupies the target.
**En guard (Day)** - You will redirect anyone visiting the Unseen to your target bypassing Occupy immunity tonight. - 2 uses 
**Counter (Night)** - If Target player visits you then remove their immunity’s for 2 nights (including this one) and redirect them to themselves. - Infinite uses 
**Stagger (Night)** - Disable target players passives for 2 nights (including this night). They won’t be informed - 2 uses 
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

[quote]
&lt;big&gt;[color=steblue]**Archer**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;

[color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Killer**[/color]

**Bag Of Arrows (Passive)** - You start with 2 arrows, and cost them to use abilities.

**Make Arrow (Day)** - Receive an arrow at the end of tonight. You will not receive any arrow from this ability if **Loyal Guard** is used tonight, regardless if you killed anyone or not. [Infinite Use]

**Sleepiness Night (Day)** - Become occupy and redirect immune tonight. [2 Use]

**Steady Aim (Night)** - Target a player, if they attack someone then you will attack them. Receive 1 arrow on succeed kill. [1-Arrow Cost]

**Loyal Guard (Night)** - If you are attacked tonight, occupy the attacker and attack them. Receive 2 arrows if no attacker are detected. [2-Arrows Cost]

*Your objective is to defeat the [color=purple]**Unseen**[/color] or [color=darkred]**Cult**[/color] and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]



[quote]
**Converts into [color=purple]**TrapShooter**[/color] or [color=darkred]**The Acolyte**[/color]**

[color=darkred]**Cult Point : 2 | Each ability cost 1 point.**[/color]

[color=darkred]**Cult Alts**[/color]
**Bag of Arrows (Passive)** =&gt; **Blood Arrow (Passive)** - If your [color=darkred]**Cult Leader**[/color] being attacked tonight, you will occupy and attack the attacker. Only take effect once.

**Make Arrow (Day)** =&gt; **Blood Pressure (Day)** - Test a player to see if they are healer or not. Receive result at the end of the night. [2 Use]

**Steady Aim (Night)** =&gt; **Cult Eyes (Night)** - Follow a player, if they target your [color=darkred]**Cult**[/color]&#39;s member, occupy and attack them. [3 Use]

**Loyal Guard (Night)** =&gt; **Mithras Will&#39;s (Night)** - Attack unhealablely a player without [color=darkred]**Cult Leader**[/color] command, will suidice if the attack did not kill them. Receive back the use and not attack if you are occupied or redirected. [1 Use]

*Your objective is to defeat the [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]

[quote]
&lt;big&gt;[color=purple]**TrapShooter**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;

[color=purple]**Unseen Offensive**[/color]

**Cup Of Coffee (Day)** - Giving the [color=purple]**Unseen**[/color] hidden occupy and redirect immunity  while giving you normal immunity for tonight. [2 Use]

**Arrow Trap (Night)** - Occupy a player, if they are occupy immune, you receive another use of **Armor Piercing**. [4 Use]

**Armor Piercing (Night)** - Make [color=Purple]**Assassin**[/color]&#39;s attack tonight being unhealable. Anyone who visited the [color=Purple]**Assassin**[/color]&#39;s target will be occupied. [1 Use]

[/quote]

[quote]
&lt;big&gt;[color=darkred]**Acolyte**[/color]&lt;/big&gt;

[color=darkred]**Cult Killer**[/color]

**Spirit of Mithras (Passive)** - Starting with the second use of the Cult Leader’s Blood of Mithras, if you would be sacrificed, the first time you will not die.

**Curse of Mithras (Night)** - If the target is bled tomorrow, they will die in 1 night instead of 2 nights. [1 Use]

*Your objective is to defeat the [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon**[/color] and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
[/quote]

&gt; # [color = &quot;steblue&quot;] The Watch [/color]
&gt; **[color = &quot;steblue&quot;] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]**
**Careful Planning (Day)** - If you get redirected tonight, you will not attack. - 2 uses
**Reckless Preparations (Day)** - Your attacks at night cannot be stopped or healed. They can be redirected. - 1 use
**No Access (Night)** - If your second target targets your first target, attack your second target. - Infinite uses
**Counter-attack (Night)** - If your target attacks you you will prevent their attack and counter-attack them. Counter-attacks ignore guards(but neither innate immunity nor healing) - 2 uses
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;# [color = &quot;purple&quot;] The Accomplice [/color]
 &gt;**[color = &quot;purple&quot;] Unseen Killer [/color]**
**Murder Plans (Day)** - The Assassin will be unaffected by guards tonight, and cannot be seen. - 1 use
**Keep Off (Night)** - If your second target targets your first target, who must be a member of the Unseen, attack your second target. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **[color=darkred]2 Cult Points, each ability costs 1.
Cult Alts:[/color]** **Counter-Attack (Night)** -&gt; **Shielding Conversion(Night)** - If the Cult Leader attempts to convert a person tonight they and their target will be protected from attacks and Occupy. - 1 use
**No Access (Night)** -&gt; **No Access (Night)**- If your second target targets your first target, attack your second target. - 1 use

&gt; # **[color=steblue]The Lancer[/color]**
&gt;**[color=steblue]Blue Dragon Killer[/color]**
**Outmatched (Passive) -** You are immune to attacks from marked targets and will attack them if you&#39;re attacked by them.
**Knock Off (Day) -** Prevent a player from using day abilities for the rest of the day. They will only be able to use their first night ability the following night. - 2 Uses
**Pointed Lance (Night) -** Target a player and mark all of their visitors. Players will know when they&#39;re marked. If a marked player does nothing at night, their mark will be removed. If a currently marked player gets marked again, they&#39;ll be attacked. - Infinite Uses
**Armor Break (Night) -** Remove a player&#39;s first passive for tonight and the next night. 3 Uses

&gt;**Converts into [color=purple]The Horseman[/color] or [color=darkred]The Acolyte[/color]**
**[color=darkred]Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1 [/color]**
**[color=darkred]Cult Alt:[/color]**
**(Outmatched): Overwhelm (Passive) -** Any player you visit will lose their occupy and redirection immunity until you die.
**(Pointed Lance): Madness (Night) -** If the Cult Leader failed to convert their target tonight, you will kill them no matter what. 2 Uses.

&gt; # **[color=purple]The Horseman[/color]**
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
**Trample (Day) -** Trample a player, changing all of their infinite use abilities to 3 uses left.
**Selfless Oath (Night) -** You will die in the place of any Unseen who dies tonight and tomorrow. 2 Uses
**Phantom Steed (Night) -** The Assassin will not appear to visit anyone tonight and cannot be killed by a Knight or Hunter bear tonight.

&gt;# &lt;font color=&quot;steblue&quot;&gt;The Firebrand&lt;/font&gt;
&gt; &lt;font color=&quot;steblue&quot;&gt;**Blue Dragon Killer**&lt;/font&gt;
&gt; **Cuts and Scars (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
&gt; **Fire Thrower (Day)** - Set a player on fire, they will die at the end of tonight. - 1 use.
&gt; **Deathmark (Night)** - Deathmark a player. - 3 uses.
&gt; **Final Burn Out (Night)** - Kill all deathmarked players. - 1 use.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; **Converts into &lt;font color=purple&gt;The Firebreather&lt;/font&gt; or &lt;font color=darkred&gt;The Acolyte&lt;/font&gt;**
&gt; &lt;font color=darkred&gt;**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs 1&lt;/font&gt;**
&gt; **(Fire Thrower) Mithras Burn (Day)** - Set a player on fire, they will die at the end of the night.- 1 use.
&gt; **Two Cult Point Alt Ability:**
&gt; **(Deathmark + Final Burn Out) Mithras&#39; Targets** - Deathmark a player and kill all current death marked players. - 1 use.

&gt;# &lt;font color=&quot;purple&quot;&gt;The Firebreather&lt;/font&gt;
&gt; &lt;font color=&quot;purple&quot;&gt;**Unseen Killer**&lt;/font&gt;
&gt; **Cuts and Scars (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
&gt; **Feet of Fire (Day)** - If target player attempts to use an action today, they will be prevented from doing so. - 2 uses.
&gt; **Fire Thrower (Day)** - Set a player on fire, they will die at the end of tonight. - 1 use.
&gt; **Marksman (Night)** - Deathmark a player. - 3 uses.
&gt; **Final Burn Out (Night)** - Kill all deathmarked players. - 1 use.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; Should note some things about the class:
&gt; * The Unseen version shares their use abilities with their BD counterpart apart from **Fire Thrower**.
&gt; * **Final Burn Out** and it&#39;s counterparts bypass night immunity and can only be stopped by healing.

&gt; # &lt;font color=&quot;purple&quot;&gt;The Firebreather&lt;/font&gt;
&gt; &lt;font color=&quot;purple&quot;&gt;**Unseen Support**&lt;/font&gt;
&gt; **Cuts and Scars (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding.
&gt; **Arsonist Flames (Passive)** - Once you become the Assassin, you will gain one extra use of Rupture.
&gt; **Feet of Fire (Day)** - If target player attempts to use an action today, they will be prevented from doing so. - 2 uses.
&gt; **Marksman (Night)** - Deathmark a player, if the Assassin attacks them it will bypass night immunity. - 3 uses.
&gt; **Flame Gas (Night)** - Prevent all investigative abilities to all Unseen players tonight. - 1 use.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt; # **[color=steblue]The Court Jester[/color]**
&gt; **[color=steblue]Blue Dragon Killer[/color]**
**Musical Entertainment (Day) -** Disable a random passive/ability that your target has for 2 nights. You will gain a use whenever a Blue Dragon dies. 0 Uses.
**Rhapsody (Day) -** Pick a player. All occupies, redirects, and attacks to you tonight will be redirected to that player. Bypasses occupation and redirection immunity. 1 Use. Gains another use at the end of every 3rd night.
**Rope Trap (Night) -** Set up a rope trap at a player&#39;s room. If they get attacked or get converted, all visitors will be occupied through immunity the next night. 4 Uses.
**Circus Accident (Night) -** Select a player. They&#39;ll be occupied tonight. They&#39;ll die two nights later or when they visit you, whichever happens first. If they&#39;re immune, they&#39;ll be bled instead. You cannot use this ability while another player is currently affected by it. 2 Uses.

&gt;**Converts into [color=purple]The Clown[/color] or [color=darkred]The Acolyte[/color]**
**[color=darkred]Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies [/color]**
**[color=darkred]Cult 1 Point Alt:[/color]**
**(Rhapsody): Blood Ode (Day) -** Bleed yourself and another player. 1 Use.
**(Rope Trap): Blood Aura (Night) -** Frame a target for tonight and the next. 2 Uses.
**[color=darkred]Cult 2 Point Alt:[/color]**
**(Circus Accident): Rage of Mithras (Night) -** Heals whoever the Cult Leader attacks tonight but the Cult Leader will be able to kill two players for free the next night. Only works if the Cult Leader uses Blood of Mithras. 1 Use.

&gt; # **[color=purple]The Clown[/color]**
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
**Nightmarish Laugh (Day) -** Prevent a player from voting for the rest of the day. If they already did, prevents them from changing it. 2 Uses.
**Spotlight (Night) -** Redirect all visitors of your first target to your second target but not vice versa. 3 Uses.
**Tightrope Walk (Night) -** Occupy your target. The next night they will be redirected to whoever they targeted last night.

&gt; # [color=steblue]Witness[/color]
&gt; [color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Killer**[/color]
&gt; 
&gt; **Bullshit Fluke (Passive)** -If you are attacked twice in one night, you will live by an extremely freakish coincidence.
&gt;
&gt; **Talks Too Much (Day)** - Publicly announce &quot;I am the witness, and I believe [statement]&quot;. If the statement is true, you will kill any Blue Dragon players you visit tonight. The statement MUST  be about the game. - Infinite uses 
&gt; 
&gt; **Bystander (Night)** - Have a nice, friendly, visit at somebody&#39;s house. If you are targeting a player who is either not Blue Dragon or has visit prevention, you will stay home and visit yourself.  - Infinite uses
&gt; 
&gt; **OOOOOOOOOOOPS (Night)** - Have a nice, friendly visit at somebody&#39;s house, but through your own stupidity cause your own demise instead.- 1 use

&gt; [color=brown]**Cult Points - 1 Ability Cost - 1**[/color]
&gt; **Talks Too Much --&gt; Chats During Sermons (Day)** - Publically announce &quot;I am the witness, and I believe [statement]&quot;. If the statement is true, the entire Cult will be night immune tonight. The statement MUST  be about the game. - 1 use.

&gt; # [color=purple]Gossipier[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Support**[/color]
&gt; 
&gt;  **Evily Laughs Too Much (Day)** - Publicly announce &quot;I am the witness, and I believe [statement]&quot;. If the statement is true, the Assasin will bypass immunity tonight. The statement MUST  be about the game. - Infinite uses 
&gt; 
&gt;  **Bystander (Night)** - Have a nice, friendly, visit at somebody&#39;s house. If you are targeting a player who is either not Blue Dragon or has visit prevention, you will stay home and visit yourself.  - Infinite uses
&gt; 
&gt; **wait shi- (Night)** - While attempting to set up your master plan, accidentally cause your own death, but make the Unseen appear Not Suspciious for tonight and tommorow night because the castle can&#39;t believe they&#39;d recruit somebody that stupid  - 1 use

&gt; &lt;big&gt; [color=steblue]The Royal Guard[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon, Killer.**
&gt; **Public Execution (Day)** - Sacrifice your life to kill a player in plain daylight. Cannot be used until Day 3. Cannot target the King. - 1 use.
&gt; **Escort (Night)** - Select a player. Anyone attempting to visit them will be immune to occupation and redirection. - Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Coup (Night)** - Kill whoever the King targets tonight, bypassing death immunity. Cannot be used until Night 3 - 1 use.

&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult points 2:**
&gt; **Cult alts** : [/color]
&gt; **1 point (Escort): Portal of Blood (Night)** : Make the other cult members immune to occupation and redirection tonight. 1 use.
&gt; **1 point (Coup): Mithras’ Crown (Night)**: Secretly prevent the King from performing their night action. 1 use.
&gt; **2 points (Public execution): Public Sacrifice (Day)** - Sacrifice your life to kill a player in plain daylight. The cult leader won’t be able to use Blood of Mithras today. 1 use.

&gt; [color=purple]&lt;big&gt;The Warden&lt;/big&gt;[/color]
&gt; **Unseen, Killer. Converts from the Royal Guard.**
&gt; **Veteran Killer (Passive)** - If you turn into the assassin, you will keep the &quot;Public Execution&quot; ability.
&gt; **Public Execution (Day)** - Sacrifice your life to kill a player in plain daylight. Cannot be used until Day 3. Cannot target the King. The assassin won&#39;t be able to attack the night after you use this ability. 1 use.
&gt; **Second Chance (Night)** - Select a player. If the assassin is unable to kill their target tonight for any reason, you will attack said player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Goal: defeat the Golden Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.**

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=steblue]The Martyr&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Blue Dragon Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Divine Power (Day)** - You can perform an extra action tonight. (You can use both abilities or use the same ability two times). - 1 use.
&gt; **Penitence (Night)** - Select a player. The effects of this ability are different depending on how many times you have used it on the same player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; 
&gt; * First time: Contrition - Prevent all visits on your target.
&gt; * Second time: Confession - Check your target’s class type.
&gt; * Three or more times: Penance - Attack the player.
&gt; 
&gt; **Absolution (Night)** - The effects of this ability depend on how many times you have used it.
&gt; * First time: Revelation - You will know who visits you tonight.
&gt; * Second time: Purification - Prevent all visits on yourself tonight.
&gt; * Third time: Salvation - Kill yourself in order to heal everyone else in the court. Your death cannot be prevented in any way.

&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult points 2:**
&gt; **Cult alts** :[/color]
&gt; **1 point: Divine Power (Day)**
&gt; **1 point (Penitence): Mithras’ Crown (Night)** : Select a player. The effects of this ability are different depending on how many times you have used it on the same player. 3 uses.
&gt; 
&gt;  *  First time: Confession - Check the target&#39;s class type
&gt;  * Second time: Contrition - Prevent all non-cult visits on the player.
&gt;  * Three or more times: Penance - Bleed a player. They will die in 1 day unless healed.
&gt; 
&gt; **1 point (Absolution): Blood Communion (Passive)** - If you are sacrificed with Blood of Mithras, all other cult members will be healed.

&gt; &lt;big&gt;[color=purple]The Sacrifice&lt;/big&gt;
&gt; **Unseen Killer** [/color]
&gt; **Divine Power (Day)** - You can perform an extra action tonight. (You can use both abilities or use the same ability two times). - 1 use.
&gt; **Penitence (Night)** - Select a player. The effects of this ability are different depending on how many times you have used it on the same player. Unlimited uses.
&gt; 
&gt; * First time: Contrition - Prevent all visits on your target.
&gt; * Second time: Confession - Check your target’s class type.
&gt; * Three or more times: Penance - Attack the player.
&gt; 
&gt; **Absolution (Night)** - The effects of this ability depend on how many times you have used it. - 3 uses.
&gt; * First time: Revelation - You will know who visits the unseen tonight.
&gt; * Second time: Purification - All members of the unseen will appear not suspicious to investigators tonight.
&gt; * Third time: Salvation - Kill yourself in order to prevent all visits on the unseen tonight and give the assassin an extra use of all their abilities.

[details=&quot;The Enchanter&quot;]
&gt; # [color=steblue] The Enchanter[/color]
&gt;[color=steblue]**Blue Dragon Killer**[/color]
**Enchant (Day)** - Enchant a player,making them silently occupy inmune and unable to be healed.Targeting a enchanted player will unenchant them. - Infinite uses
**Earth Spell (Night)** - Target an enchanted player and another player,if the first visits the second or another enchanted player they will be bleed sometime tomorrow - Infinite uses
**Fire Spell (Night)** - If any player you enchanted visits anyone enchanted they will die bypassing night inmunity - 2 uses
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*


&gt;**Converts into [color=purple]The Hex Master[/color] or [color=darkred]The Acolyte[/color]**
[Color=darkred]**Cult points: 2**[/color]
[Color=darkred]**1 point Cult Alts**[/color]
**(Enchant)Blood Mark** -Put a blood mark on a player.-infinite uses
**(Earth Spell)Circle of Blood** -Target a marked player.If they attemp to target any member of the cult they will be prevented and bleed sometime the next day.-3 uses
[Color=darkred]**2 point Cult Alt**[/color]
**(Fire Spell)Magical Sacrifice** -Sacrifice yourself and kill 2 players bypassing everything if they were Blood Marked or were enchanted by yourself.If they weren’t,silently bleed them,killing them on 1 night.You can’t be targeted by the Cult Leader’s Blood of Mithras when you use this.-1 use


&gt;# [color=purple] The Hex master [/color]
&gt;[color=purple]**Unseen Offensive**[/color]
**Hex (Day)** - Permanently hex a player,and make them receive incorrect results the next night.All players you enchanted previously will be unenchanted and hexed(will not receive incorrect results)- Infinite uses
**Hypnotize (Night)** - Target a hexed player and another player.If the first attemps to target the unseen they will be redirected to the second and will be bleed sometime tomorrow. - Hypnotize uses
**Magic Box (Night)** - Target a unseen player and a hexed player.The unseen player will be guaranteed to visit your second target - 1 use
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm*
[/details]

&gt;## [color=#00b0e0]The Spiritual Warrior[/color]
&gt;**Blue Dragon Killer**
**Harmonic Combo (Day)** - You select target that disables their immunity at next day vulnerable for further attacks and other negative effects until following night ended - 1 use
**Critical Strike (Night)** - You select target to attack and disrupts your target that is attempting to attack or use other negative effect otherwise it’s normal attack, you regain 1 use of Harmonic Combo when you or other attacker killed the target from your day ability only twice per game - infinite uses
_Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt;**Converts into [color=#800080]The Essence Warrior[/color] or [color=#800000]The Acolyte[/color]**
&gt;**[color=#800000]Cult points: 2[/color]**
**[color=#800000]1 point Cult Alts[/color]**
**(Harmonic Combo)** Combo of Corax (Day) - In addition of what your Cult Leader use whether it’s Disguise or Rupture, you can select the second target for one specific ability - 1 use / 2 uses
**(Finishing Strike)** Climax of Mithras (Night) - Select Rupture target that is about to die will also kill visitors to the target who doesn’t have death immunity - 1 use / 2 uses

&gt;## [color=#800080]The Essence Warrior[/color]
&gt;**Unseen Killer**
**Purpose of Discord (Passive)** - Emboldened by The Mastermind, you have occupation and redirection immunity as long The Mastermind lives, you also won’t turned into The Assassin
**Pendulum (Day)** - You select either The Mastermind or The Assassin, should they get attacked or by negative effects in following night then you take their place and attack back - 1 use
**Power Attack (Night)** - Kill a player, if you got Chronomancer, Drunk, Knight, Hunter, Prince, Spiritual Warrior or Neutral Killer dead by your kill or Assassin&#39;s kill then you regain 1 use of Pendulum or your next Power Attack gains death immunity and heal bypass shared by only twice per game - Infinite uses
_Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm._

&gt; # **[color=steblue]The Warlord[/color]**
&gt; **[color=steblue]Blue Dragon Killer[/color]**
**The Adiart Empire (Passive) -** You are immune to death on the first three nights.
**Protectorate (Day) -** If your target dies tonight, you will gain a use of Casus Belli. You will gain another use whenever a Blue Dragon dies at night. You can not gain more than 1 use per night. 1 Use.
**Peace Treaty (Day) -** Select two players. If one of them attempts to attack or convert you or the other tonight or the next night, you will occupy them and attack them. If the attack fails, you will gain a use of Warmongerer. You will gain another use whenever Casus Belli is used. 2 Uses.
**Warmongerer (Night) -** Attack a player. You will gain another use whenever a non-Blue Dragon dies. You will lose 2 uses if you kill a Blue Dragon. If the attack fails and you attack them again the following night, you will be guaranteed to kill them. You can have -1 Uses. 0 Uses.
**Casus Belli (Night) -** Attack up to 2 players. If all players you attacked are Blue Dragon, you will lose all uses of all abilities. 0 Uses.

&gt;**Converts into [color=purple]The Revolutionary[/color] or [color=darkred]The Acolyte[/color]**
**[color=darkred]Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: Varies [/color]**
**[color=darkred]Cult 1 Point Alt:[/color]**
**(The Adiart Empire): Last Battle (Passive) -** Any Cult member who is attacked at night will be healed and then bled sometime the next day. Only triggers once.
**(Protectorate): Branding Ritual (Day) -** If your target dies tonight, they will be sacrificed to Mithras instead of the Cult member the Cult Leader chose. Cannot be used on Cult members. 2 Uses.
**(Warmongerer): Open Wound (Night) -** If whoever the Cult Leader attacks tonight survives, they will be bled. 1 Use.
**[color=darkred]Cult 2 Point Alt:[/color]**
**(Peace Treaty): Banishment (Day) -** Prevent two players from visiting each other for the rest of the game. 2 Uses.
**(Casus Belli): Corax&#39;s Vengeance (Night) -** Select a Cult member. If they die tonight or the following day and it wasn&#39;t caused by Blood of Mithras, they will automatically be sacrificed to Mithras the next night.

&gt; # **[color=purple]The Revolutionary[/color]**
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
**Secret Spies (Passive) -** Whenever there is a King election, you know who everybody votes.
**Greater Adiart (Passive) -** Upon conversion, the Assassin will be able to kill two players the next night.
**Replacement (Day) -** Swap roles with the Assassin or Mastermind. 1 Use.
**Traitors (Night) -** All Killer classes that visit a member of the Unseen tonight will instead be occupied and attacked. 3 Uses
**Break In (Night) -** Guarantees all visitors to your target visits your target. (Bypasses occupy, redirect, prevention) 3 Uses

&gt; # [color=steblue]The Executioner[/color]
&gt; **Blue Dragon Killer**
&gt; **Death Sentence (Day)** - You may choose a player and mark them with &quot;Death sentence&quot; until the end of the following night. You can only mark each player once per game. You can also mark yourself once per game (you won&#39;t be able to use &quot;Execute&quot; if you mark yourself). You cannot mark the King.
&gt; **Execute (Night)** - Attack the player marked by &quot;Death Sentence&quot;. If you kill a member of the Blue Dragon your &quot;Death Sentence&quot; passive will be disabled for two days. - Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Witness Protection (Night)** - Prevent everyone from visiting the player marked by &quot;Death Sentence&quot;. - Unlimited uses.

&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Alts**[/color]
&gt; [color=darkred]**2 points (Death Sentence and Witness protection):**[/color] **Death Sentence (Day) + Veil of Blood (Night)** - Select a class type. Prevent classes of that type from visiting the player marked with &quot;Death Sentence&quot; - 3 uses.
&gt; [color=darkred]**2 points (Execute)**:[/color]**Forbidden Seal (Night)** - Mark a player. The next time they try to use an ability with a limited number of uses (including tonight), if you are still alive, they will be occupied. (Works on both day and night abilities). Cannot target the King. - 2 uses.

&gt; # [color=purple]The Hangman[/color]
&gt; **Unseen Offensive**
&gt; **Death Sentence (Day)** - You may choose a player and mark them with &quot;Death sentence&quot; until the end of the following night. You can only mark each player once per game. You cannot mark the King.
&gt; **Tight Noose (Night)** - Occupy the player marked by &quot;Death Sentence&quot;. If they attempt to perform the same action on the following night, they will be occupied one more time. - Unlimited uses.
&gt; **Forged Records (Night)** - Make the target appear suspicious to investigators both tonight and the following night - Unlimited uses.

&gt; # [color = &quot;steblue&quot;] The Headhunter [/color]
&gt; **[color = &quot;steblue&quot;] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]**
**Focused on Target (Passive)** - You cannot be redirected.
**Evaluating Failure (Passive)** - If you kill a Blue Dragon, you cannot use your abilities the next night
**Punishment (Day)** - If the one you use Hunt Accomplices on tonight was one of those responsible for an execution of a Blue Dragon today, attack them. - Infinite uses
**Determine Habits (Day)** - Pick a starting class except Prince, Mastermind and Cult Leader. If you use Hunt Accomplices tonight on someone with this starting class, attack them. - 3 uses
**Hunt Accomplices (Night)** - Target someone. If they were converted last night, attack them. - Infinite uses
**Decapitation (Night)** - Target someone. If they are the Cult Leader, Prince or Mastermind, you kill them. This cannot be prevented. Your target cannot convert you tonight. - 1 use
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

&gt;Converts into **[color=purple] The Bribed[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Acolyte[/color]** 
**[color=darkred]Cult Points:[/color]** 2, each ability costs 1.
**[color=darkred]Cult Alts:[/color]** Punishment -&gt;**Bloody Punishment (Day)** - If the one you use Hunt Associates on tonight was one of those responsible for an execution of a member of the Cult today, attack them. - 1 use
Determine Habits -&gt;**Determine Habits (Day)** - Pick a starting class except Prince, Mastermind and Cult Leader. If you use Hunt Associates tonight on someone with this starting class, attack them. - 1 use
Hunt Accomplices -&gt;**Hunt Associates (Night)** - Target someone. If they were visited by a Blue Dragon Investigative last night, attack them. - 2 uses

&gt; # [color = &quot;purple&quot;] The Bribed [/color]
&gt; **[color = &quot;purple&quot;] Unseen Killer [/color]**
**Distracted by Wealth (Passive)** - You are occupied the night after you got converted.
**I am no Assassin (Passive)** - You do not turn into the Assassin
**Escort (Day)** - Target The Mastermind. If they would be imprisoned, kill the Prince instead. You cannot use abilities tonight. - 1 use
**Urgency (Day)** - You cannot be occupied tonight if no Assassin is alive. - 1 use
**Decapitation (Night)** - Target someone. If they are the Cult Leader, Prince or Mastermind, you kill them. This cannot be prevented. - 1 use
**Death to the Blue Dragon! (Night)** - If no Assassin is alive, attack your target. Else, determine what caused the Assassin&#39;s attack to fail. - Infinite uses
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 04:05:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><s>Or maybe it was me angleshooting everything that caused you to make moderrors in the first place</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/469">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/469</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 04:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-469</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s a valid conclusion tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/468">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/468</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-468</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>conclusion: Firekitten leads to me not making mod errors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/467">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/467</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-467</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>back then I still made moderrors frequently</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/466">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/466</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-466</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it was obviously a dark age filled with a lot of struggle</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/465">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/465</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-465</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about the time where it was the PRE firekitten age</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/464">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/464</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-464</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh right, there was a time when I didn’t exist in FoL.<br>
<em>god the pre-ici FoL era was ages ago</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/463">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/463</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-463</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/462">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/462</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 18:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-462</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Emilia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Life in general is kinda stupid</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/461">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/461</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 18:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-461</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Coven in general is kinda stupid</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/460">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/460</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-460</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Medusa killing neutral killers is stupid tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/459">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/459</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-459</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No Deputy was after one game</p>
<p>I wish Crusader was gone but there hasn’t been a significant balance update on ToS in over two years, and I don’t think anything in Coven has changed at all since release</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/458">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/458</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 18:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-458</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wait, Crusader was removed?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/457">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/457</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-457</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We don’t need Crusader</p>
<p>It was immediately removed after its first game with good reason</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/456">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/456</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 16:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-456</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>that can explain why it seems weak tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/455">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/455</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 16:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-455</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was an awful class and it’s better gone</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/454">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/454</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 16:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-454</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s weird because it seems strong</p>
<p>but if you think about it. It seems weak in practice</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/453">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/453</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 16:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-453</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>seems weirdly weak</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/452">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/452</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 16:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-452</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s true <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/man_shrugging.png?v=9" title=":man_shrugging:" class="emoji" alt=":man_shrugging:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/451">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/451</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 16:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-451</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t make it, also I did say it would need balancing man</p>
<p>It’s from september 2017</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/450">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/450</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-450</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GamerPoke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And Duty first doesnt give target immunity. Well, guard might</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/449">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/449</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-449</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GamerPoke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wazza" data-post="447" data-topic="76061">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/wazza/40/41244_2.png" class="avatar"> Wazza:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Ambush (Night)</strong> - You will stand guard next to your door tonight, killing any visitors. Does not bypass death immunity - 2 uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You still die if attacked by attacker, mostly will kill BD, cant kill MM, and would still be converted by the Cl killing him. Really bad</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/448">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/448</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 15:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-448</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1><font color="steblue">The Deputy (Unofficial Class)</font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="steblue">Blue Dragon Killer</font></strong><br>
<strong>Ambush (Night)</strong> - You will stand guard next to your door tonight, killing any visitors. Does not bypass death immunity - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Duty First (Night)</strong> - You will guard your target and attack one random visitor. If they’re attacked, you will attack the Killer first. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to Eliminate the Unseen, The Cult, and any Neutrals who stand against you</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>I get the contest is over but this class should be brought back in my opinion just balanced a bit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/447">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/447</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 15:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-447</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah thank you, at least I am glad</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/446">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/446</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 10:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-446</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Emilia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Geyde" data-post="331" data-topic="76061" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/geyde/40/32764_2.png" class="avatar"> Geyde:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/orangeandblack5">@orangeandblack5</a>’s Ranger wins!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/445">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061/445</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 10:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-76061-445</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-blue-dragon-killer-competition/76061.rss">Forum of Lies Blue Dragon Killer Competition</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
