<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Soul Collector - Neutral Offensive</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221</link>
    <description>**The Soul Collector** is a Neutral Offensive Class that specializes in keeping the dead alive a little longer and collecting their souls. 

**Win Condition**
The Soul Collector&#39;s win-condition is simple - Collect 4 Souls while alive. This can be done through the use of your abilities.

**Passive** 
Soul Mastery - When you die, you&#39;ll be able to jump to another Body of your choosing on the next night, taking over it and collecting their soul. This can only happen once during the game.

**Day Ability** 
Soul Link - Links two players&#39; souls for the next night. If the first player is to die, he&#39;ll instead consume the second player&#39;s soul and survive. The second target&#39;s body will remain alive for a day after his soul is consumed, but unable to act. If the first target dies later in the game, you&#39;ll collect his soul. (3 Uses)

**Night Abilities** 
Soul Flare - Marks a target with a Soul Flare. If that target was to die, his soul will remain alive as a Wisp for an extra day and night. After that, you&#39;ll collect their Soul, making them unable to be resurrected. (∞ uses)
_

Soul Bind - Link one of your Collected Souls to a living Body. The original soul of that body will be collected by you instead. (1 Use)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 23:18:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Soul Collector - Neutral Offensive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 15:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-14221-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Soul Collector - Neutral Offensive</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Soul Collector - Neutral Offensive</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BearWithMe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Soul Collector</strong> is a Neutral Offensive Class that specializes in keeping the dead alive a little longer and collecting their souls.</p>
<p><strong>Win Condition</strong><br>
The Soul Collector’s win-condition is simple - Collect 4 Souls while alive. This can be done through the use of your abilities.</p>
<p><strong>Passive</strong><br>
Soul Mastery - When you die, you’ll be able to jump to another Body of your choosing on the next night, taking over it and collecting their soul. This can only happen once during the game.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability</strong><br>
Soul Link - Links two players’ souls for the next night. If the first player is to die, he’ll instead consume the second player’s soul and survive. The second target’s body will remain alive for a day after his soul is consumed, but unable to act. If the first target dies later in the game, you’ll collect his soul. (3 Uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities</strong><br>
Soul Flare - Marks a target with a Soul Flare. If that target was to die, his soul will remain alive as a Wisp for an extra day and night. After that, you’ll collect their Soul, making them unable to be resurrected. (∞ uses)<br>
_</p>
<p>Soul Bind - Link one of your Collected Souls to a living Body. The original soul of that body will be collected by you instead. (1 Use)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-14221-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-soul-collector-neutral-offensive/14221.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Soul Collector - Neutral Offensive</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
