<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Lich (NK)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524</link>
    <description>&gt; # [color = &quot;slateblue&quot;] The Lich [/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Killer [/color]** 
**Phylactery (Passive)** - At the beginning of the game, two random players are designated as the Lich’s Phylactery Holders with only the Lich knowing who their holders are. If both of them die, the Lich will die the following night. The Lich will know the classes of his Phylactery Holders.
**Undeath (Passive)** - As long as the Phylactery Holders are alive, at every night the Lich will automatically revive themselves whenever they are dead, regardless of how they died. If one of the Phylactery Holders has already died, then the Lich will gain immunity to occupation and redirection.
**Spectral Mist (Day)** - For the coming night, the Lich will heal one of his Phylactery Holders. - 3 uses 
**Black Fog (Day)** - For the coming night, the Lich prevents all investigative type classes from visiting one of his Phylactery Holders. - 3 uses 
**Finger of Decay (Night)** - Instantly kills a player during the night. If the user was just revived the previous day then this attack bypasses night immunity and healing. - Infinite uses 
**Death&#39;s Curtains (Night)** - Grants night immunity to both the Lich’s Phylactery Holders and makes them appears as members of the Blue Dragon to faction checks. - 3 uses 
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way. The Phylactery Holders do not need to die for you to win.*

Theme: A neutral killer whose main mechanism of survival is to essentially keep two players alive, somewhat similar to Merc-like NK, or like FoL&#39;s Revenant.
Survivability: The Lich is essentially immortal, even to lynches, while both Phylactery Holders are still alive.
Late-game: Providing his Holders aren&#39;t executed or nightkilled the Lich essentially has an insanely strong late-game.

Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:16:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Lich (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this a lot also <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  Is there a compelling reason to not let him choose his Phylactery Holders D1 though?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70524-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Lich (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Lich (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="slateblue"> The Lich </font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Phylactery (Passive)</strong> - At the beginning of the game, two random players are designated as the Lich’s Phylactery Holders with only the Lich knowing who their holders are. If both of them die, the Lich will die the following night. The Lich will know the classes of his Phylactery Holders.<br>
<strong>Undeath (Passive)</strong> - As long as the Phylactery Holders are alive, at every night the Lich will automatically revive themselves whenever they are dead, regardless of how they died. If one of the Phylactery Holders has already died, then the Lich will gain immunity to occupation and redirection.<br>
<strong>Spectral Mist (Day)</strong> - For the coming night, the Lich will heal one of his Phylactery Holders. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Black Fog (Day)</strong> - For the coming night, the Lich prevents all investigative type classes from visiting one of his Phylactery Holders. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Finger of Decay (Night)</strong> - Instantly kills a player during the night. If the user was just revived the previous day then this attack bypasses night immunity and healing. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Death’s Curtains (Night)</strong> - Grants night immunity to both the Lich’s Phylactery Holders and makes them appears as members of the Blue Dragon to faction checks. - 3 uses<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way. The Phylactery Holders do not need to die for you to win.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Theme: A neutral killer whose main mechanism of survival is to essentially keep two players alive, somewhat similar to Merc-like NK, or like FoL’s Revenant.<br>
Survivability: The Lich is essentially immortal, even to lynches, while both Phylactery Holders are still alive.<br>
Late-game: Providing his Holders aren’t executed or nightkilled the Lich essentially has an insanely strong late-game.</p>
<p>Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70524-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-lich-nk/70524.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Lich (NK)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
