<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702</link>
    <description>So I was looking at all the current roles in FoL’s and I was thinking of some roles that I feel this game needs.

I believe this game needs a neutral role that can convert, that way people have a better chance of being converted so no one feels left out.
I also added a Neutral role that can increase the win rate of the Neutral Killer.
I also think there needs to be a new Investigative, Social, and Support Roles so stronger roles like Offence and Killing have a less chance of rolling.
I also added a new Special role that can be very beneficial towards the impact of the game.
Make sure to give me your feedback of what you think!

[color=yellow]The Parasite[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color=yellow]Neutral Killer[/color]

**Host Instinct** (Passive) When you convert someone to be your Host their alignment will change to yours, they will share a Chat with you. If you use Infectious Bite They will perform it Instead of you and you will perform all their other night actions instead. (If you die then the host will also die with you). Additionally if no Host has died yet you are Night Immune.
**Egg Plant** (Day) You will lay an egg on Target Player, causing them to be framed as your alignment and lose all immunities they have. - 2 Uses
**Side Effect** (Day)  While not having any Host, you may choose 2 Target players and for as long as your alive, if one of them dies the other will also die. -2 Uses
**Infectious Bite** (Night) - Kill the Target Player. If you use this action while not having a Host you will instead convert them into your Host. You can only have 1 Host at a time. - Infinite Uses :crown:
**Poisonous Venom** (Night) - Target a Player and During the next following day within 24 Hours that player and all their visitors will become bleed and die within 2 Days. - 1 Use :crown:
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, and the Unseen or Cult.

[color = steblue]The Mortician[/color]
[color = steblue]Blue Dragon Social[/color]

**Dead Silent** (Passive) If you choose to target someone that was on the top wagon they will lose all access to current and future chat communication other then ones you made.
**Extraction** (Day) Choose a player to extract at night, They will believe and will be told they are jailed. You both will be able to send each other a single 1000 character message through the host. - 2 Uses
**Deceased Communication** (Day) Choose a target. They will receive a chat with the executed target today and may talk with them as much as they like, as such the executed target will not be added into dead chat until your target is dead -Infinite Uses - :crown:
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.

Converts into [color = purple]The Grave Digger[/color] or [color = gold]The Apostle[/color]

[color = purple]The Grave Digger[/color]
[color = purple]Unseen Social[/color]

**King’s Wishes** (Passive) Upon becoming The Grave Digger if the king is an evil king they will join the Unseen Chat.
**Silenced Grave Stone** (Passive) Whenever you target someone, they will lose access to current and future chat communication other then ones you made.
**Graveyard Discussion** (Day) Choose a player to bring to the graveyard at night, they will think they were jailed and be occupied and be prevented from being visited. You both will be able to send each other a single 1000 character message. You will repeat this process for 2 nights. - 1 Use
**Grave Communication** (Day) Choose a target. They will receive a chat with the executed target today and may talk with them as much as they like, as such the executed target will not be added into dead chat until your target is dead. The Dead Chat will be able to view the conversation - Infinite Uses
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.

[color = gold]The Apostle[/color]
Upon being converted to Apostle you will retain all your Mortician abilities.

[color = steblue]The Mimic[/color]
[color = steblue]Blue Dragon Support[/color]

**Evil Side** (Passive)
You retain any abilities you currently have if you convert into The Ritualist 
**Morning Mimic** (Day) Choose a target and copy their Day ability (If they don’t have a Day ability you will regain your Use.)
(If they have multiple day abilities you will receive a random one) - 1 Use
**Midnight Mimic** (Night) Choose a target and copy their night ability. (If they have multiple night abilities you will receive a random one) - 1 Use
**Swapping Brilliance** (Night) Choose a target and trade your night ability with theirs - 1 Use
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.

Converts into [color = purple]The Copycat[/color] or [color = gold]The Ritualist[/color]

[color = purple]The Copycat[/color] 
[color = purple]Unseen Support[/color]

**Good Side** (Passive) You will automaticity receive any abilities you had when you were The Mimic.
**You Too** (Passive) All Abilities Used on you will also be used on the target who used them on you
**I’ll Be You** (Day) Choose a target and you will appear as their role upon your death - 1 Use
**Still Brilliant** (Night) Make Yourself appear as a The Mimic role to all Investigations for the night - 1 Use
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.

[color = steblue]The Mathematician[/color]
[color = steblue]Blue Dragon Investigative[/color] 

**Differences** (Passive) If anyone that you have targeted this game becomes converted you will be informed about it
**Calculus** (Night) Choose 2 Target, you will know if neither, one or both targets ever visited each other. (Your targets don’t have to be alive.) - 2 Uses
**Focused Determination** (Night) Choose a target and you will know what type of action they took the previous night - Unlimited Uses
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.

Converts into [color = purple]The Gambler[/color] or [color = gold]The Seeker[/color]

[color = purple]The Gambler[/color] 
[color=purple]Unseen Investigative[/color]

**Dice Roll** (Passive)  Upon being killed or executed you will appear to be a different role decided by random.
**Chosen Cards** (Day) - Choose 2 targets and redirect them to each other tonight. You will also be informed of who they were originally trying to target - 2 Uses.
**Winging It** (Night) - Choose a target and call a role, if your right you will appear as that role to Dice Roll instead of it being decided by random. - Infinite Uses
**Cheat Play** (Night) - Choose a target and you will know all types of actions they took for each night. - 3 Uses
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.

[color = steblue]Time Keeper[/color] :shield: :fire:
[color = steblue]Blue Dragon Special [/color]

**Lock in Time** (Passive) You have conversion immunity while Refocus Time Hasn’t been used. Once Refocus Time has been used you will lose conversion immunity.
**Focus Time** (Passive) You will Focus the last Voter of the day 
**Slow Time** (Day) Delay target’s next vote making whoever they vote next they immediately vote at the start of the next day. - 2 Uses
**Forward Time** (Night)  Delay target’s action making them preform their action the next night instead of tonight. - Unlimited Uses
**Refocus Time** (Night) You will cause all Focus Targets to become Repetitive in time. Causing them to repeat their previous action and then they will die at the end of the following day.- 1 Use
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.

You convert into [color = purple]Time Disrupter[/color] or [color = gold]Paradox[/color]

[color = purple]Time Disrupter[/color]
[color = purple]Unseen Special[/color]

**Relocation** (Day) Choose 2 target and anonymously make votes against them today count for the opposite one instead. - 2 Uses
**Disrupting Force** (Night) Choose a target and delay their action until the next following night. - Infinite Uses
**Ripple in Time** (Night) Force all players to visit themselves tonight - 1 Use 
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.

[color = gold]Paradox[/color]
[color = gold]Cult Special[/color]

**Prophecy of Time** (Passive) You will not spawn in the game as random cult
**Butterfly Effect** (Passive) Each time someone would be executed that execution is delayed until the next day. 
**Constant Continuation** (Night) Choose a target and force them to repeat the same action they made the previous night - Infinite Uses
**Time Explosion** (Night) Kill all players who uses an action that they have previously used on the same target. - 1 Use
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.

[color=olive]The Predator[/color]
[color=olive]Neutral Offensive[/color]

**Killer Instinct** (Passive) Choose a Neutral Killer role as soon as you receive this Rolecard. You will become that Neutral Killer role if the original Neutral Killer dies.
**Observing Eye** (Day) Check someone to see if they are Good or Evil. (NK will always show up as Evil) - Infinite Uses
**The Hunt** (Night) Hunt a target. If they are a Member of the Blue Dragon or Unseen/Cult you will occupy them. If it’s the Neutral Killer you will kill them bypassing night immunity. If the Neutral Killer is the same role you picked you will kill yourself instead and you will win the game if they win, ignoring your win con. - Infinite Uses
Your objective is to achieve your win con as the chosen neutral killer role. If you aren’t the chosen neutral killer you lose. If you win so does the original neutral killer.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 01:33:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fuck<br>
I’ve been had</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 01:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Geyde" data-post="14" data-topic="83702">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/geyde/40/32764_2.png" class="avatar"> Geyde:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>host of problems</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I see what you did there</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’ll be hard for TimeKeeper to be converted.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Parasite</p>
<p>First things first<br>
Converting NK creates a whole host of problems regarding implementation</p>
<p>Now onto balance matters<br>
This NK has insane kp. It has conversion (evaluated at higher end of 2kp), an uninformed loverizer effect which the condition of is not hard at all to meet, and extremely easy endgaming potential<br>
It takes all the aspects that make Sorc extremely annoying to play against and turns it up substantially</p>
<p>You can try not going for a n1 convert and just try to use side effect twice alongside poisonous venom on a “stronger town player”<br>
The conversion is fine theoretically but it’s absurdly strong</p>
<p>So as for the balance side it’s stronger than the strongest nk currently (sorc) by a long shot since instead of bypassing endgame and having a relatively unstable early / midgame, you have a precarious early game and extremely strong everything else</p>
<p>additionally it’s neutral<br>
cop doesn’t peek for neutrals<br>
it peeks for scum</p>
<p>literally only a faction check would work on this<br>
conversion nk seems fine in concept<br>
but it’s extremely annoying to play against because lolmultiball taken to the extremes</p>
<hr>
<p>Mortician</p>
<p>No<br>
I get that you find fakeclaim prince to be interesting<br>
And yes, it’s theoretically cool<br>
but no</p>
<p>it’s also obscenely confirmable so ehhhhh</p>
<p>also dead silent interaction with scumchat is extremely stupid.</p>
<hr>
<p>Mimic</p>
<p>Works only if you have feedback<br>
If it does have feedback, it’s suddenly ridiculously strong as an investigative because it’s both almost entirely confirmable and other such ridiculous things</p>
<p>also can swap with abilities it shouldn’t be able to use, ie the scum kill, convert, nk kill, prince, etc<br>
tons of bullshit</p>
<hr>
<p>Mathematician</p>
<p>This isn’t ToS<br>
Being able to determine the converted player extremely easily is extremely frustrating to play against<br>
This also works on n1 for some ungodly reason</p>
<p>FD operates as a rolecop in a semi-open setup<br>
And rolecops are really fucking good when there are no false positives / negatives</p>
<hr>
<p>Time Keeper</p>
<p>Semi open setup<br>
Refocus time is also kind of wack but not super wack<br>
bad</p>
<p>Time Disrupter</p>
<p>Scum role<br>
That can effectively decide<br>
the lynch<br>
twice</p>
<p> &gt;be prince<br>
 &gt;time keeper got converted<br>
 &gt;die immediately<br>
 &gt;be nk<br>
 &gt;time keeper still converted<br>
 &gt;die immediately</p>
<p>unseen win</p>
<hr>
<p>Predator</p>
<p>Neutral<br>
Day<br>
Cop</p>
<p>There are obvious other problems<br>
If BD kills NK<br>
That’s a mislynch<br>
Because now you’re NK and they wasted a day</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 18:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="astand" data-post="8" data-topic="83702" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/astand/40/32914_2.png" class="avatar"> astand:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>NK that can convert.</p>
<p>Nice.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s balanced though if you read it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 16:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>petition to pin this thread and delete all other ones like this post to sign</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 09:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Emilia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ChopChop" data-post="1" data-topic="83702">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/chopchop/40/35926_2.png" class="avatar"> ChopChop:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I believe this game needs a neutral role that can convert</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ChopChop" data-post="1" data-topic="83702">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/chopchop/40/35926_2.png" class="avatar"> ChopChop:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Extraction</strong> (Day) Choose a player to extract at night, They will believe and will be told they are jailed. You both will be able to send each other a single 1000 character message through the host. - 2 Uses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>why would this be a thing + confirmable</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ChopChop" data-post="1" data-topic="83702">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/chopchop/40/35926_2.png" class="avatar"> ChopChop:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Mimic<br>
Blue Dragon Support</p>
<p><strong>Evil Side</strong> (Passive)<br>
You retain any abilities you currently have if you convert into The Ritualist<br>
<strong>Morning Mimic</strong> (Day) Choose a target and copy their Day ability (If they don’t have a Day ability you will regain your Use.)<br>
(If they have multiple day abilities you will receive a random one) - 1 Use<br>
<strong>Midnight Mimic</strong> (Night) Choose a target and copy their night ability. (If they have multiple night abilities you will receive a random one) - 1 Use<br>
<strong>Swapping Brilliance</strong> (Night) Choose a target and trade your night ability with theirs - 1 Use<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>this is too op due to being able to invest, confirm themselves and use normal abils</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 08:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SirDerpsAlot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Petition to delete this thread like to sign</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 06:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[astand]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry, not reading after that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 06:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[astand]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>NK that can convert.</p>
<p>Nice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 06:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[astand]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure, I have feedback.</p>
<p>Delete FoL.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 06:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/arete">@Arete</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/appelsiini">@Appelsiini</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/alice">@Alice</a><br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/astand">@astand</a></p>
<p>You all are “A” smart’s.<br>
Can I have some feedback?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 05:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can I have actual feedback please?<br>
Thanks.<br>
I mean at least Katze helped me with an error.<br>
Thank you Katze! <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/clap.png?v=9" title=":clap:" class="emoji" alt=":clap:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 05:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>okay i read every class</p>
<p>my feedback:</p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-username="ChopChop" data-post="1" data-topic="83702">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/chopchop/40/35926_2.png" class="avatar"> ChopChop:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Predator<br>
Neutral Offence</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><strong>Neutral Offensive</strong>*</p>
<p>that is all</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 05:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes<br>
Yes<br>
Yes<br>
Yes<br>
and<br>
Yes</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 05:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No<br>
No<br>
No<br>
No<br>
and<br>
No</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 05:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I was looking at all the current roles in FoL’s and I was thinking of some roles that I feel this game needs.</p>
<p>I believe this game needs a neutral role that can convert, that way people have a better chance of being converted so no one feels left out.<br>
I also added a Neutral role that can increase the win rate of the Neutral Killer.<br>
I also think there needs to be a new Investigative, Social, and Support Roles so stronger roles like Offence and Killing have a less chance of rolling.<br>
I also added a new Special role that can be very beneficial towards the impact of the game.<br>
Make sure to give me your feedback of what you think!</p>
<p><font color="yellow">The Parasite</font> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"><br>
<font color="yellow">Neutral Killer</font></p>
<p><strong>Host Instinct</strong> (Passive) When you convert someone to be your Host their alignment will change to yours, they will share a Chat with you. If you use Infectious Bite They will perform it Instead of you and you will perform all their other night actions instead. (If you die then the host will also die with you). Additionally if no Host has died yet you are Night Immune.<br>
<strong>Egg Plant</strong> (Day) You will lay an egg on Target Player, causing them to be framed as your alignment and lose all immunities they have. - 2 Uses<br>
<strong>Side Effect</strong> (Day)  While not having any Host, you may choose 2 Target players and for as long as your alive, if one of them dies the other will also die. -2 Uses<br>
<strong>Infectious Bite</strong> (Night) - Kill the Target Player. If you use this action while not having a Host you will instead convert them into your Host. You can only have 1 Host at a time. - Infinite Uses <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"><br>
<strong>Poisonous Venom</strong> (Night) - Target a Player and During the next following day within 24 Hours that player and all their visitors will become bleed and die within 2 Days. - 1 Use <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"><br>
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, and the Unseen or Cult.</p>
<p><font color="steblue">The Mortician</font><br>
<font color="steblue">Blue Dragon Social</font></p>
<p><strong>Dead Silent</strong> (Passive) If you choose to target someone that was on the top wagon they will lose all access to current and future chat communication other then ones you made.<br>
<strong>Extraction</strong> (Day) Choose a player to extract at night, They will believe and will be told they are jailed. You both will be able to send each other a single 1000 character message through the host. - 2 Uses<br>
<strong>Deceased Communication</strong> (Day) Choose a target. They will receive a chat with the executed target today and may talk with them as much as they like, as such the executed target will not be added into dead chat until your target is dead -Infinite Uses - <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"><br>
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p>Converts into <font color="purple">The Grave Digger</font> or <font color="gold">The Apostle</font></p>
<p><font color="purple">The Grave Digger</font><br>
<font color="purple">Unseen Social</font></p>
<p><strong>King’s Wishes</strong> (Passive) Upon becoming The Grave Digger if the king is an evil king they will join the Unseen Chat.<br>
<strong>Silenced Grave Stone</strong> (Passive) Whenever you target someone, they will lose access to current and future chat communication other then ones you made.<br>
<strong>Graveyard Discussion</strong> (Day) Choose a player to bring to the graveyard at night, they will think they were jailed and be occupied and be prevented from being visited. You both will be able to send each other a single 1000 character message. You will repeat this process for 2 nights. - 1 Use<br>
<strong>Grave Communication</strong> (Day) Choose a target. They will receive a chat with the executed target today and may talk with them as much as they like, as such the executed target will not be added into dead chat until your target is dead. The Dead Chat will be able to view the conversation - Infinite Uses<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p><font color="gold">The Apostle</font><br>
Upon being converted to Apostle you will retain all your Mortician abilities.</p>
<p><font color="steblue">The Mimic</font><br>
<font color="steblue">Blue Dragon Support</font></p>
<p><strong>Evil Side</strong> (Passive)<br>
You retain any abilities you currently have if you convert into The Ritualist<br>
<strong>Morning Mimic</strong> (Day) Choose a target and copy their Day ability (If they don’t have a Day ability you will regain your Use.)<br>
(If they have multiple day abilities you will receive a random one) - 1 Use<br>
<strong>Midnight Mimic</strong> (Night) Choose a target and copy their night ability. (If they have multiple night abilities you will receive a random one) - 1 Use<br>
<strong>Swapping Brilliance</strong> (Night) Choose a target and trade your night ability with theirs - 1 Use<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p>Converts into <font color="purple">The Copycat</font> or <font color="gold">The Ritualist</font></p>
<p><font color="purple">The Copycat</font><br>
<font color="purple">Unseen Support</font></p>
<p><strong>Good Side</strong> (Passive) You will automaticity receive any abilities you had when you were The Mimic.<br>
<strong>You Too</strong> (Passive) All Abilities Used on you will also be used on the target who used them on you<br>
<strong>I’ll Be You</strong> (Day) Choose a target and you will appear as their role upon your death - 1 Use<br>
<strong>Still Brilliant</strong> (Night) Make Yourself appear as a The Mimic role to all Investigations for the night - 1 Use<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p><font color="steblue">The Mathematician</font><br>
<font color="steblue">Blue Dragon Investigative</font></p>
<p><strong>Differences</strong> (Passive) If anyone that you have targeted this game becomes converted you will be informed about it<br>
<strong>Calculus</strong> (Night) Choose 2 Target, you will know if neither, one or both targets ever visited each other. (Your targets don’t have to be alive.) - 2 Uses<br>
<strong>Focused Determination</strong> (Night) Choose a target and you will know what type of action they took the previous night - Unlimited Uses<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p>Converts into <font color="purple">The Gambler</font> or <font color="gold">The Seeker</font></p>
<p><font color="purple">The Gambler</font><br>
<font color="purple">Unseen Investigative</font></p>
<p><strong>Dice Roll</strong> (Passive)  Upon being killed or executed you will appear to be a different role decided by random.<br>
<strong>Chosen Cards</strong> (Day) - Choose 2 targets and redirect them to each other tonight. You will also be informed of who they were originally trying to target - 2 Uses.<br>
<strong>Winging It</strong> (Night) - Choose a target and call a role, if your right you will appear as that role to Dice Roll instead of it being decided by random. - Infinite Uses<br>
<strong>Cheat Play</strong> (Night) - Choose a target and you will know all types of actions they took for each night. - 3 Uses<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p><font color="steblue">Time Keeper</font> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fire.png?v=9" title=":fire:" class="emoji" alt=":fire:"><br>
<font color="steblue">Blue Dragon Special </font></p>
<p><strong>Lock in Time</strong> (Passive) You have conversion immunity while Refocus Time Hasn’t been used. Once Refocus Time has been used you will lose conversion immunity.<br>
<strong>Focus Time</strong> (Passive) You will Focus the last Voter of the day<br>
<strong>Slow Time</strong> (Day) Delay target’s next vote making whoever they vote next they immediately vote at the start of the next day. - 2 Uses<br>
<strong>Forward Time</strong> (Night)  Delay target’s action making them preform their action the next night instead of tonight. - Unlimited Uses<br>
<strong>Refocus Time</strong> (Night) You will cause all Focus Targets to become Repetitive in time. Causing them to repeat their previous action and then they will die at the end of the following day.- 1 Use<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult, and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p>You convert into <font color="purple">Time Disrupter</font> or <font color="gold">Paradox</font></p>
<p><font color="purple">Time Disrupter</font><br>
<font color="purple">Unseen Special</font></p>
<p><strong>Relocation</strong> (Day) Choose 2 target and anonymously make votes against them today count for the opposite one instead. - 2 Uses<br>
<strong>Disrupting Force</strong> (Night) Choose a target and delay their action until the next following night. - Infinite Uses<br>
<strong>Ripple in Time</strong> (Night) Force all players to visit themselves tonight - 1 Use<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p><font color="gold">Paradox</font><br>
<font color="gold">Cult Special</font></p>
<p><strong>Prophecy of Time</strong> (Passive) You will not spawn in the game as random cult<br>
<strong>Butterfly Effect</strong> (Passive) Each time someone would be executed that execution is delayed until the next day.<br>
<strong>Constant Continuation</strong> (Night) Choose a target and force them to repeat the same action they made the previous night - Infinite Uses<br>
<strong>Time Explosion</strong> (Night) Kill all players who uses an action that they have previously used on the same target. - 1 Use<br>
Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon and any Neutrals that seek to do you harm.</p>
<p><font color="olive">The Predator</font><br>
<font color="olive">Neutral Offensive</font></p>
<p><strong>Killer Instinct</strong> (Passive) Choose a Neutral Killer role as soon as you receive this Rolecard. You will become that Neutral Killer role if the original Neutral Killer dies.<br>
<strong>Observing Eye</strong> (Day) Check someone to see if they are Good or Evil. (NK will always show up as Evil) - Infinite Uses<br>
<strong>The Hunt</strong> (Night) Hunt a target. If they are a Member of the Blue Dragon or Unseen/Cult you will occupy them. If it’s the Neutral Killer you will kill them bypassing night immunity. If the Neutral Killer is the same role you picked you will kill yourself instead and you will win the game if they win, ignoring your win con. - Infinite Uses<br>
Your objective is to achieve your win con as the chosen neutral killer role. If you aren’t the chosen neutral killer you lose. If you win so does the original neutral killer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 03:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-83702-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-fol-roles-that-should-be-added-to-the-game/83702.rss">New FoL Roles that should be added to the game</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
