<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867</link>
    <description>Name: Samurai (Unique)
Faction: Blue Dragon
Type: Killer

Abilities:

Passive: Honor Bond: If you take the life of a innocent man you will put away your blade and pray for then each night being able to talk to them. 

Passive: Sharpened Blade: Your blade is sharpened, your attacks bypass night immunity. (Regular Night immunity, not including healing). 

Day: Heavy Armor: Equip yourself with heavy armor, anyone who attacks you will break their own blade and It will take a night for them to repair it. You will be immune to the first attack. (2 uses)

Night: Duel: Send a letter to a player challenging them to a duel, the night you send it they will receive the message &quot;You have been challenged to a duel!&quot;. The next night the duel begins. (Infinite Uses)

Night: Passing of Blade: Pass your blade onto another person, making them a samurai, if you do this you shall kill yourself to complete the ritual. (1 use)

Class Name: Ninja
Faction: Unseen
Type: Offensive

Abilities:

Passive: High Priority: When you are converted to the unseen you will receive a list of 3 people, the three people that talk the most. These are the only people you can use your abilities on (Doesn&#39;t count king or Unseen members) (If all targets die you will get a new list).

Day: Shadow Knife: Stab a Person in the back, not killing them, but making them bleed, they will bleed out in 2 days. (1 use).

Night: Lurk Around: Lurk around a player&#39;s room, if they were to find any information, you will steal it and they will receive the message &quot;Your information was stolen!&quot;. (Infinite Uses). 

Night: Kidnap!: Kidnap a Player, torturing them. Once you have tortured them to the will of the mastermind, you will take your own life to complete the ritual. (1 use, doesn&#39;t transfer) (Can only be Used at Night 8). 


Reasoning: 

Passive: Honor Bond: If you take the life of a innocent man you will put away your blade and pray for then each night being able to talk to them. 

I feel as though the samurai should not be pushed with death for killing a person but with loosing their most important ability. But with this the get another ability that can only give information to them. Like leads Scum ideas and Etc. 

Passive: Sharpened Blade: Your blade is sharpened, your attacks bypass night immunity. (Regular Night immunity, not healing).

With this ability i feel as though there needs to be balance for if the Samurai was to get a delay into killing their target, it can mean that a person who is innocent can call for a healer to save them. 


Night: Duel: Send a letter to a player challenging them to a duel, the night you send it they will receive the message &quot;You have been challenged to a duel!&quot;. The next night the duel begins. (Infinite Uses)

A very powerful ability at that, but it is not as powerful for your opponent receives a warning, meaning the duel can be prevented by you being imprisoned or they are imprisoned. Maybe you are occupied, but with this you also have another powerful ability, and if nothing of these happen and you take a innocent life, you can still communicate information with them. 

Night: Passing of Blade: Pass your blade onto another person, making them a samurai, if you do this you shall kill yourself to complete the ritual. (1 use) (Only works on people who are regularly convertible). 

This is a powerful ability and well, for it can turn the tide of a game. With this the Samurai kills themself, meaning that there cant be multiple samurais at the same time. Although I can see how this ability may be hard to balance. In reality this ability is a gamble, for it can be hated or liked. 

Ninja

Passive: High Priority: When you are converted to the unseen you will receive a list of 3 people, the three people that talk the most. These are the only people you can use your abilities on (Doesn&#39;t count king or Unseen members).

With powerful abilities I feel as though there always needs to be a limitation to it. i feel as though this fits the name of the class, for Ninjas are like assassins, but they are hired to take out targets. 

Day: Shadow Knife: Stab a Person in the back, not killing them, but making them bleed, they will bleed out in 2 days. (1 use).

I feel as though this ability can be powerful, in so you have to use it wisely. For if it was already established that it was a unseen game, you can easily be confirmed as evil. But if not, you can mislead people into thinking that it is a cult game. or if you are not going for the way of a deception, you can team this with a poisoning from a assassin, creating a powerful combination. Or you can just go solo and act like a assassin poisoning someone.  

Night: Lurk Around: Lurk around a player&#39;s room, if they were to find any information, you will steal it and they will receive the message &quot;Your information was stolen!&quot;. (Infinite Uses). 

Another Really Powerful ability, for it can basically shut down investigative classes, and most likely get them executed for no information. But meanwhile it can easily confirm you. BUT you have to realize your passive for sometimes you don&#39;t get alot of investigative targets from the passive. 

Night: Kidnap!: Kidnap a Player, torturing them. Once you have tortured them to the will of the mastermind, you will take your own life to complete the ritual. (1 use, doesn&#39;t transfer) (Can only be Used at Night 8). 

A extremely powerful ability, for it will be the only class that can convert another into unseen other then the mastermind. With this it has to have MAJOR draw backs. Like for example your passive still applies meaning you only have 3 targets to choose from (assuming they are all still alive). And once you die it is extremely easy to narrow down who the Ninja might be for who ever talked the most are the targets. With this I decided to make it so it can only be used on Night 8, for it can be a tide turner if the mastermind is already dead.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 21:15:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Intuition]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the idea of honor bond, but I wonder if maybe instead of adding an extra class, that passive could be reworked into the knight?</p>
<p>I feel as if playing the Knight is right now somewhat uneventful, and I think that if you accidentally coldsteeled a BD, instead of  forcing the Knight to commit suicide, it would be great if the Knight could be able to talk to the person he coldsteeled as well as continue guarding someone else. That way, the knight becomes more interactive and useful, still maintaining the ability to keep coldsteeling if he does not fail.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 04:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11867-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867.rss">[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Braixen" data-post="1" data-topic="11867">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/braixen/40/26209_2.png" class="avatar"> Braixen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(Regular Night immunity, not including healing).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Its gives you a warning if a samurai is going to duel you the night before he duels you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 02:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11867-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867.rss">[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Night immunity should be a rare thing to bypass. We don’t need more death immunity bypassers</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 02:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11867-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867.rss">[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Name: Samurai (Unique)<br>
Faction: Blue Dragon<br>
Type: Killer</p>
<p>Abilities:</p>
<p>Passive: Honor Bond: If you take the life of a innocent man you will put away your blade and pray for then each night being able to talk to them.</p>
<p>Passive: Sharpened Blade: Your blade is sharpened, your attacks bypass night immunity. (Regular Night immunity, not including healing).</p>
<p>Day: Heavy Armor: Equip yourself with heavy armor, anyone who attacks you will break their own blade and It will take a night for them to repair it. You will be immune to the first attack. (2 uses)</p>
<p>Night: Duel: Send a letter to a player challenging them to a duel, the night you send it they will receive the message “You have been challenged to a duel!”. The next night the duel begins. (Infinite Uses)</p>
<p>Night: Passing of Blade: Pass your blade onto another person, making them a samurai, if you do this you shall kill yourself to complete the ritual. (1 use)</p>
<p>Class Name: Ninja<br>
Faction: Unseen<br>
Type: Offensive</p>
<p>Abilities:</p>
<p>Passive: High Priority: When you are converted to the unseen you will receive a list of 3 people, the three people that talk the most. These are the only people you can use your abilities on (Doesn’t count king or Unseen members) (If all targets die you will get a new list).</p>
<p>Day: Shadow Knife: Stab a Person in the back, not killing them, but making them bleed, they will bleed out in 2 days. (1 use).</p>
<p>Night: Lurk Around: Lurk around a player’s room, if they were to find any information, you will steal it and they will receive the message “Your information was stolen!”. (Infinite Uses).</p>
<p>Night: Kidnap!: Kidnap a Player, torturing them. Once you have tortured them to the will of the mastermind, you will take your own life to complete the ritual. (1 use, doesn’t transfer) (Can only be Used at Night 8).</p>
<p>Reasoning:</p>
<p>Passive: Honor Bond: If you take the life of a innocent man you will put away your blade and pray for then each night being able to talk to them.</p>
<p>I feel as though the samurai should not be pushed with death for killing a person but with loosing their most important ability. But with this the get another ability that can only give information to them. Like leads Scum ideas and Etc.</p>
<p>Passive: Sharpened Blade: Your blade is sharpened, your attacks bypass night immunity. (Regular Night immunity, not healing).</p>
<p>With this ability i feel as though there needs to be balance for if the Samurai was to get a delay into killing their target, it can mean that a person who is innocent can call for a healer to save them.</p>
<p>Night: Duel: Send a letter to a player challenging them to a duel, the night you send it they will receive the message “You have been challenged to a duel!”. The next night the duel begins. (Infinite Uses)</p>
<p>A very powerful ability at that, but it is not as powerful for your opponent receives a warning, meaning the duel can be prevented by you being imprisoned or they are imprisoned. Maybe you are occupied, but with this you also have another powerful ability, and if nothing of these happen and you take a innocent life, you can still communicate information with them.</p>
<p>Night: Passing of Blade: Pass your blade onto another person, making them a samurai, if you do this you shall kill yourself to complete the ritual. (1 use) (Only works on people who are regularly convertible).</p>
<p>This is a powerful ability and well, for it can turn the tide of a game. With this the Samurai kills themself, meaning that there cant be multiple samurais at the same time. Although I can see how this ability may be hard to balance. In reality this ability is a gamble, for it can be hated or liked.</p>
<p>Ninja</p>
<p>Passive: High Priority: When you are converted to the unseen you will receive a list of 3 people, the three people that talk the most. These are the only people you can use your abilities on (Doesn’t count king or Unseen members).</p>
<p>With powerful abilities I feel as though there always needs to be a limitation to it. i feel as though this fits the name of the class, for Ninjas are like assassins, but they are hired to take out targets.</p>
<p>Day: Shadow Knife: Stab a Person in the back, not killing them, but making them bleed, they will bleed out in 2 days. (1 use).</p>
<p>I feel as though this ability can be powerful, in so you have to use it wisely. For if it was already established that it was a unseen game, you can easily be confirmed as evil. But if not, you can mislead people into thinking that it is a cult game. or if you are not going for the way of a deception, you can team this with a poisoning from a assassin, creating a powerful combination. Or you can just go solo and act like a assassin poisoning someone.</p>
<p>Night: Lurk Around: Lurk around a player’s room, if they were to find any information, you will steal it and they will receive the message “Your information was stolen!”. (Infinite Uses).</p>
<p>Another Really Powerful ability, for it can basically shut down investigative classes, and most likely get them executed for no information. But meanwhile it can easily confirm you. BUT you have to realize your passive for sometimes you don’t get alot of investigative targets from the passive.</p>
<p>Night: Kidnap!: Kidnap a Player, torturing them. Once you have tortured them to the will of the mastermind, you will take your own life to complete the ritual. (1 use, doesn’t transfer) (Can only be Used at Night 8).</p>
<p>A extremely powerful ability, for it will be the only class that can convert another into unseen other then the mastermind. With this it has to have MAJOR draw backs. Like for example your passive still applies meaning you only have 3 targets to choose from (assuming they are all still alive). And once you die it is extremely easy to narrow down who the Ninja might be for who ever talked the most are the targets. With this I decided to make it so it can only be used on Night 8, for it can be a tide turner if the mastermind is already dead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 01:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11867-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-samurai-ninja/11867.rss">[Class Suggestion] Samurai/Ninja</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
