<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089</link>
    <description>The Prophet wants to predict who will win, and in being sore loser, does what it can to manipulate the future towards its prediction.

The Prophet is a neutral with a varying win-con, Its job is to predict who will win but doing so before he/she gets killed. The prophet can still get play out of dying early by interacting with psychics or just waiting to see if he/she will win.


Win condition: Predict which faction will win. You win if that faction wins. The day after you make your prediction a message reading [i]&quot;The Prophet has seen the future and decided on his prediction&quot;[/i] will be posted in chat.

[b]Day Abilities[/b]

[i]Predict future[1 Use]:[/i] Predict the faction that will win in the end. Choose between Blue Dragon/Evil/Neutral killer. You win if that faction wins.

[b]Night Abilities[/b]

[i]Manipulate outcome[3 use][/i] Prevent anyone from visiting your target

[i]Check in[1 use][/i] Check to see how many members there are of each faction.


The Prophet is meant to be a class that can have a slightly &#39;gambling&#39; feel to it, you can of course predict night 1 to make sure you don&#39;t die before you make your prediction but the longer you wait the higher is your chance of being right. But making your choice leads to it being announced making players of &quot;enemy&quot; factions wanting to get rid of you.


I&#39;d love to hear feedback on the concept and balance and generally just what people think about the idea :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 11:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nobody" data-post="7" data-topic="27089">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nobody/40/2617_2.png" class="avatar"> Nobody:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The only thing I am still unsure of is the 3-night time limit, with not having chosen a side you can’t win so i feel like that mechanic would in itself construct a time limit, even more so since both sides can see you as a threat until you claim your side.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe that having a time limit carries the same idea as the Mercenary having to form another contract. As long as the Mercenary is contract-less he is no threat to anyone, so you can just leave him alone. He survives for as long as he can stand that period with zero preoccupation. I believe that that would happen with the Prophet as well, but with an even longer time period and that would hurt the overall gameplay. It’s not unacceptable since it follows the idea of the Alchemist. He isn’t a threat until he is. So yeah, you can follow that road with no problem!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nobody" data-post="7" data-topic="27089">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nobody/40/2617_2.png" class="avatar"> Nobody:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I hope you’ll enjoy version 2 as much at version 1</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m sure I will!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nobody]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now this is some really great feedback <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I am currently working on a v2.0 and your feedback has really hit the spot with some of the feelings i had myself and it brought forward some things i hadn’t even considered.</p>
<p>The only thing I am still unsure of is the 3 night timelimit, with not having chosen a side you can’t win so i feel like that mechanic would in itself construct a timelimit, even more so since both sides can see you as a threat until you claim your side.</p>
<p>I hope you’ll enjoy version 2 as much at version 1 <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 11:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cool Idea Nobody! Glad to see you around! Here are my thoughts about it, if I may. I will try to be as thorough as possible to help strengthen your plans for this class.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>The win condition is awesome. Especially the announcement of it, I agree with you that it’s needed. The thing is, instead of a global message that said: “The Prophet has chosen the Blue Dragon as winners of this match.”, just make it say something like “The Prophet has chosen his champions.”. This is a social deduction game, a game of lie. Allow the Prophet to hide his true intentions if need be and leave space for people to wonder if he’s an ally or not after all that’s what neutrals are in the end, a mystery. If you read all of my suggestion, I believe you might agree with me that the path I’m trying to make you follow will not make this an instant killed neutral, as he could turn into a very powerful ally.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I would just like to add a simple suggestion to your day ability. A passive. <strong>Gambling Addiction: If you do not use your day ability until n3, you will commit suicide.</strong> That gives you a time limit, very necessary since you could just wait until unseen had the majority to side with them. It also gives you a little time to analyze the field and make your choice, without taking the gamble out of it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Both night abilities are extremely investigative/offensive. So he wouldn’t be a Support class, but that’s not a problem. My opinion would be to take the investigative out of it. Check-out the Check in ability (See what I did there? <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smile.png?v=9" title=":smile:" class="emoji" alt=":smile:">). Either make it an offensive class with occupy or a support with visits prevention.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Manipulate outcome, as it is, is too much. You cannot have a skill that works one way with your allies and another with your enemy. Spread it. Night Ability 1 occupies the target. Night Ability 2 occupies whoever visits your target. That would be as an offensive class, of course. The support version could be: Night Ability 1 prevents visits to your target. And in that case, I would not encourage a second ability that prevents people from leaving their room or something like that.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Either path you choose to follow is great, it’s a very nice idea and I hope to have helped you make it even better. I’ll be here to discuss further if you wish. Have a nice day!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 01:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thiar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this idea.</p>
<p>I think prediction shouldnt be public. Instead when you make prediction you can send any message you want and it will be announched in the morning (like old noble crier) so ppl know that prophet is in the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 12:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nobody]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks a lot for the feedback. I’ll go through it point by point with what i’ve thought about the topics <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>I’ve felt that the prediction needed to be public since it puts a sort of urgency in doing it since it out you are there and which side you have choosen, this kinda prevents the problem that we had with first edition inquisitor where he simply outs himself and then wins with BD. as for other neutrals claiming prophet, there are so many roles as neut that you can claim and not be able to prove so I really don’t see a problem with prophet being where it is, you could simply lie and say you haven’t chosen yet, and though it is a gamble it is still as good as saying “i’m alch, ill heal tonight to prove”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I really think there is enough here, but only if he choose BD. he can occupy and see players factions(kinda) which is really strong, perhaps as strong, as the alchemist and if he has publicly stated his side he can’t backstab you like the alch can.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>the first night action can be used prior to making your choice from their specific wording, it simply occupies a player.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I am unsure about the night actions right now since manipulate outcome technically does the same as check in, just better so i’ll have to look them over again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 08:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[methomps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Interesting.  What I think it most needs is (1) that the prediction not be made public, to allow for other neutrals to claim Prophet; (2) more in terms of tilting the scale on whether or not to execute the prophet (i.e., why not simply neuts out); and (3) something to do at night and/or day prior to making the prediction.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nobody]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Comments from discord and elsewhere:</p>
<p>“I think it’s interesting with a neut that isn’t instant exe, worth trying out at least”</p>
<p>“I think it might be a bit too easy to win with, but there could be a spot for it if executed correctly”</p>
<p>More to come over time, I think it’s good to post it here so the feedback is collected in one spot</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 20:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nobody]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Prophet wants to predict who will win, and in being sore loser, does what it can to manipulate the future towards its prediction.</p>
<p>The Prophet is a neutral with a varying win-con, Its job is to predict who will win but doing so before he/she gets killed. The prophet can still get play out of dying early by interacting with psychics or just waiting to see if he/she will win.</p>
<p>Win condition: Predict which faction will win. You win if that faction wins. The day after you make your prediction a message reading <span class="bbcode-i">“The Prophet has seen the future and decided on his prediction”</span> will be posted in chat.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Day Abilities</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Predict future[1 Use]:</span> Predict the faction that will win in the end. Choose between Blue Dragon/Evil/Neutral killer. You win if that faction wins.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Night Abilities</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Manipulate outcome[3 use]</span> Prevent anyone from visiting your target</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Check in[1 use]</span> Check to see how many members there are of each faction.</p>
<p>The Prophet is meant to be a class that can have a slightly ‘gambling’ feel to it, you can of course predict night 1 to make sure you don’t die before you make your prediction but the longer you wait the higher is your chance of being right. But making your choice leads to it being announced making players of “enemy” factions wanting to get rid of you.</p>
<p>I’d love to hear feedback on the concept and balance and generally just what people think about the idea <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 12:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27089-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-prophet-neutral-support-v2-0/27089.rss">[Class Suggestion] Prophet (Neutral/Support) V2.0</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
