<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499</link>
    <description>Passive: The Sound of Silence - As long as the Bard is alive and healthy (poisoned, reaped or any other bad status will interrupt the passive), no player can be silenced or chilled. Any attempts to do so will lead to the message: &quot;The Bard has prevented the silence&quot;.

Day ability 1: Capriccio of Confidants (2 uses) - Reveal Bard&#39;s presence to a target. He and the Bard will be immune to votes of treason during that day. This may be used during a trial.

Night ability 1: Hero&#39;s Ballad (infinite uses) - Assure that your target will succeed in his actions tonight.
Night ability 2: Minuet of Solitude (3 uses) - Prevents the player from receiving any visitors.

Notes: 
We are missing supports that do anything other than healing or guarding. The cult has them and so does unseen. The Wikia states that: &quot;Support classes aid and defends other players by healing them from poisoning/injury **_or other supportive abilities, such as assisting another bypass immunities._**&quot;, however, there is no current Blue Dragon member that enforces the last part. The Bard may be converted, but I chose not to make his unseen counterpart. Mostly because I didn&#39;t feel the need to. I think it&#39;s easy to see how this whole kit could be tweaked to help the unseen.
This class is incredibly strong if used correctly, but much like the CW can aid the enemy without knowing. His day ability has two uses for a simple reason. He has one use to prove himself and another to make a really game-changing action.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 16:53:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Coatsman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly I’d like this class more if it was a neutral. As lore wise, bards can be known to be travel (how else are they going to sing of their tales) and they would have plenty to see. Being a neutral would allow bards to have both negative and positive impacts on the game without handicapping a faction if they were allocated to one.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 16:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30499-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss">The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with <a class="mention" href="/u/vandalay">@Vandalay</a> that the current day ability for the Bard is Overpowered and would confirm every single time. So I think that the ability Breaking the Silence would help more, and doing that would allow for more classes to utilize certain offensive day abilities. And that passive is Really OP, which is why I would suggest to change it to Breaking the Silence</p>
<p>As for the Night Abilities, I think Hero’s Ballad is a really good ability here, but for the Minuet of Solitude, which is basically a Ice Ward like the CW, I think that a better ability would be something that would assist people.</p>
<p>And I think I know what would really help for a Bard. Something that goes alongside my idea of deprivation of limited-use abilities.</p>
<p>(Btw thanks for your help with my Thief and Rogue idea)</p>
<p>My idea for a second ability for the Bard would be…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Revitalizing Rhyme: (3) (Day)<br>
Choose one person and restore all uses of their limited-use abilities. Even if the class has no limited, the usage of Revitalizing Rhyme will decrease by one.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 22:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30499-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss">The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the concept, but I think it’s too far on the self confirming axis. IMO one of the bigger issues with the game right now, is the lack of fakable claims. Should a competitive/ranked mode come out down the road in which inexperienced players aren’t the majority… we are already at a point where it is dangerously likely to get a mass “claim or die”, “OK now we can focus on the 6 claims that can’t be tested”.</p>
<p>I like both of the night abilities</p>
<p>Maybe some changes</p>
<p>Day ability “break the silence”. All instances of chill, distract etc… are automatically removed. (I don’t think reaped really should count, reaped people are already dead). Perhaps a buff to distract to make it say 30 seconds will add utility</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 17:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30499-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss">The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>However I would prefer to change Minuet of Solitude to something else though, more supportive</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 08:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30499-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss">The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Unique class for sure, man!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 05:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30499-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss">The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This would be OP and really useful but it would have to be a unique role because it hinders bad passives</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 05:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30499-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss">The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Passive: The Sound of Silence - As long as the Bard is alive and healthy (poisoned, reaped or any other bad status will interrupt the passive), no player can be silenced or chilled. Any attempts to do so will lead to the message: “The Bard has prevented the silence”.</p>
<p>Day ability 1: Capriccio of Confidants (2 uses) - Reveal Bard’s presence to a target. He and the Bard will be immune to votes of treason during that day. This may be used during a trial.</p>
<p>Night ability 1: Hero’s Ballad (infinite uses) - Assure that your target will succeed in his actions tonight.<br>
Night ability 2: Minuet of Solitude (3 uses) - Prevents the player from receiving any visitors.</p>
<p>Notes:<br>
We are missing supports that do anything other than healing or guarding. The cult has them and so does unseen. The Wikia states that: “Support classes aid and defends other players by healing them from poisoning/injury <strong><em>or other supportive abilities, such as assisting another bypass immunities.</em></strong>”, however, there is no current Blue Dragon member that enforces the last part. The Bard may be converted, but I chose not to make his unseen counterpart. Mostly because I didn’t feel the need to. I think it’s easy to see how this whole kit could be tweaked to help the unseen.<br>
This class is incredibly strong if used correctly, but much like the CW can aid the enemy without knowing. His day ability has two uses for a simple reason. He has one use to prove himself and another to make a really game-changing action.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 05:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-30499-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-bard-blue-dragon-support/30499.rss">The Bard (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
