<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047</link>
    <description>I went to DM Hoard of the Dragon Queen
 And we&#39;re in the middle of chapter 1
 By the way, a very good part was that they stole a religious figure with a Tiamat symbol
 And they asked Eadryan (priest) who was the god of this statuette
 Eadryan had +7 in Religion
 But none of that matters
 Because Eadryan rolled 1 on d20
And now they are so believering that it was a cult of Bahamut, the 5-headed metallic dragon, that was attacking the city
 And that Tiamat is a big yellow chromatic dragon, the only yellow one in the world</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 16:05:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off-Topic (Thronepass)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TheBlueElixir" data-post="55" data-topic="80047">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/theblueelixir/40/29077_2.png" class="avatar"> TheBlueElixir:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>plus my parents yelling at me to get off my computer are <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/upside_down_face.png?v=9" title=":upside_down_face:" class="emoji" alt=":upside_down_face:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>feel you</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 16:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-56</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheBlueElixir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry</p>
<p>I don’t think I could</p>
<p>im about to multitab and trying to DM a DND session with the boys and trying to balance a game to host here</p>
<p>granted none of those are pressing all of those plus my parents yelling at me to get off my computer are <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/upside_down_face.png?v=9" title=":upside_down_face:" class="emoji" alt=":upside_down_face:"></p>
<p>When I have time between that ill probably read some of whats going on but I don’t think I could put a lot of time into it</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 16:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-55</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hmmm</p>
<p>tbh i think i could make time for it</p>
<p>but only if it started after community fm finishes or after i die in it</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 04:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-54</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes now we have three ppl<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/geyde">@Geyde</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/maximusprime">@maximusprime</a> <a class="mention" href="/u/theblueelixir">@theblueelixir</a> would you play if I did it</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 04:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-53</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i mean, if u could show all, that’d be pretty cool</p>
<p>they all seem really neat and i love fantasy politics cause it’s so much more fun than… real life ones… lol</p>
<p>but pick ur favs first if u want</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 04:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-52</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>          <a href="https://gamepedia.cursecdn.com/l5r_gamepedia_en/thumb/d/df/Dragon_Clan_mon.png/250px-Dragon_Clan_mon.png?version=4828cc7478d4b3ab6c3a2c8d8abf11db" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://gamepedia.cursecdn.com/l5r_gamepedia_en/thumb/d/df/Dragon_Clan_mon.png/250px-Dragon_Clan_mon.png?version=4828cc7478d4b3ab6c3a2c8d8abf11db" width="250" height="251">
          </a>
<br>
“Know yourself and you will never be defeated.”<br>
✤ DRAGON CLAN ✤</p>
<p>Enigmatic and mysterious, the Samurai of the Dragon Clan have trod their own path since the Empire was created. More individualistic and less concerned with material wealth than other clans, the Dragon has much in common with the monks of Brotherhood of Shinsei, despite the considerable variety among their families.</p>
<p>Intra-clan relations: The Togashi follow their personal interests that are so secret that no one could detail them, which leaves the effective role of military leader with the Mirumoto daimyo, the largest family in the clan. The link between the Agasha and the Mirumoto is very strong, and students from both families are encouraged to observe students from the other and learn from them. This means that the Mirumoto are highly attuned to the Five Elements, and the Agasha understood the basics of strategy. There is a rivalry friendly between Agasha and Kitsuki. Shugenjas see investigators as their little brothers, sometimes calling them oto-oto / otouto (little brother) and imo-oto / imouto (little sister).</p>
<p>Togashi order ✣<br>
“I don’t see more than you. You look to the wrong place.” - T o g a s h i.<br>
A monastic order instead of a real family, the Togashi accept everyone who joins them, as long as they are able to embrace the order’s teachings and endure their tests, which many do not. Over the centuries, monks of this order have used the divine blood of the Dragon Kami to create mystical tattoos that grant them incredible supernatural powers.<br>
+1 Reflexes Bonus</p>
<p>Kitsuki family ✣<br>
“Every detail carries its implications of truth.” - Kitsuki Method.<br>
The ever-perceptive Kitsuki serve the Dragon Clan as magistrates and representatives at court, though better suited to the latter. However, even at court, a Kitsuki’s ability to perceive the truth<br>
when presented with lies it has always proved tremendous value for the Dragon in his quest for a Empire free of tricks and betrayal.<br>
+1 Awareness Bonus</p>
<p>Mirumoto family ✣<br>
“Defy Definition.”<br>
The Mirumoto are the broad shoulders that carry the burden of the Dragon Clan. While the Togashi seek their unique path of enlightenment, the Mirumoto rule the clan in everything but name, overseeing their day-to-day operations and making up the army. Composing more than half of the Clan numbers, the Mirumoto are the samurai of the Dragon most easily found in the Empire.<br>
+1 Agility Bonus</p>
<p>✣ Agasha family ✣<br>
“Humanity is the only creature that discusses and can choose not to.” - A g a s h a.<br>
The Agasha family was founded by a shugenja named Agasha, a follower of Togashi, the founder of the Clan Dragon. Your role is to be responsible for maintaining the knowledge of the dragon. They are the recorders of history  and the observers of fate. Followers of the Path of Purification, their rules have been changed to allow retreat into the mountains while seeking enlightenment.<br>
+1 Perception Bonus</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 03:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-51</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since I have a total of 02 people half-interested<br>
pick which clan to post resume of next</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-charttype="pie" data-poll-type="regular" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="9b9c2d64f45b099a26d47db2b0faaa80">crane</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="13310b90b26a03314352f1cd9178796e">dragon</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="f93649ea3e969039d0847a61d03db668">lion</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="9962ebee503d32a1f06bdf3724ddecee">phoenix</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="e681e2307aba385dab93f09a563fb84f">scorpion</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="a2e0286bff5c99f96d090a92f535fc8d">unicorn</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 02:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-50</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh shit! i love that type of stuff</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 01:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-49</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yes</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 01:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-48</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>          <a href="https://i.imgur.com/RbB8AHS.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://i.imgur.com/RbB8AHS.png" width="152" height="229">
          </a>
</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 01:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-47</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>damn this sort of reminds me of the poppy war (book)</p>
<p>probably bc i just finished the first book like a few days ago tho</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 01:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-46</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>basically there is an entire section on the GM’s book on how it differs from traditional fantasy but summing it up: They are samurai. Nobles. They are cared for and given money by a lord, but are expected to die for them at any moment.</p>
<p>And what follows up is less combat. When they happen it is usually against other humans.<br>
Unless you are on the Shadowlands. Being on the Shadowlands is asking to be attacked by demons.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Summary</summary>
<p>sian Versus Narration<br>
Western Narration<br>
One of the most exclusive features of Legend of the Five RPG rings is that it is set in a world based on Asian culture, history and religion. As we have already discussed throughout this chapter, many fantasy RPGs are based in a western setting, usually pseudo-medieval in structure and concept, with a flexible social structure and few cultural rules or restrictions. In contrast, L5A depends on intensely from Asian culture - mainly from Asian culture feudal Japan, which forms the most direct inspiration for the game - to create the tone and atmosphere of your game, and imbue drama and emotional intensity in their narratives.<br>
Why emphasize culture so much? It would certainly be possible to play L5R in a more western style as a game where Asian elements were little more than a backdrop background. But this would be little different than playing an RPG conventional fantasy with a change in the scenario of bottom. It would lose the unique atmosphere that makes L5A a game in itself.<br>
What makes L5A “Asian” and not “Western” in style? The most basic element is the vital importance of society and culture. Characters are not lonely “adventurers” roaming the landscape - they are members of the samurai caste, with specific social role and duty. They have a master, a clan and an Emperor who are sworn as loyal vassals and unquestionable, willing to die at any moment. Furthermore, as samurai, they are part of an elaborate system<br>
social relations, etiquette and traditions - a system that they must follow, no matter how cruel this may seem to them, because the alternative is disgrace or death.<br>
The concept of a character trapped in the social order and moral rokugani, facing impossible choices between loyalties and conflicting expectations, is sometimes called “Samurai drama”, a concept very strange to many RPGs Western style. Samurai drama stems from the samurai (even samurai with supernatural powers) are human beings, with emotional needs, preferences and flaws that humanity suffers. The Bushido code and the social and cultural rokugani make demands that lead human beings normal to your emotional limits and beyond. Bushido hopes for perfection, but no human being is perfect. Even samurai, created in a tradition of absolute respect for Bushido and customs, can find situations where their emotions and innate humanity will clash with the demands of Rokugan, or where he finds himself unable to decide between conflicting loyalties.<br>
A good L5R game makes samurai drama an element main part of his narrative. Emotional and psychological conflicts of the rokugani social order offer a much more challenging attractive to the character than any fight, duel or argument.<br>
The essence of samurai drama and the most powerful element of story that the Master can create from it is an agonizing choice - for example, a choice between love and duty, or between loyalty to your clan or your friend. If the lord of a samurai order you to do something, but the voice of your ancestors tells you otherwise, who should he obey? For the virtues of Bushido he owes reverence and alliance to both. Such choices must be key points of any history and development of any character. Players will remember those moments more intensely than any mere combat.</p>
<p>The Hero in Asian Stories<br>
The modern image of the hero expressed in many RPGs is distinctly western, perhaps even more “Hollywood”. He (usually a he, but the role seldomly changes when the gender does) is a lonely and powerful individual who denies authority and follows its own path, winning and triumphing in its own terms. However, Asian cultures tend to see heroes as people who preach moral principles - the principles of their society - in the face of bitter adversity or even in defeat. To them, the “Hollywood” hero doesn’t look much with a hero after all - he looks much more like a bandit or a criminal.<br>
As an example, consider the Chinese folk hero Wong Fei-Hung, protagonist of countless kung fu films. Fei-Hung is a doctor, a respected member of society who values ​​Chinese virtues and moral precepts. It is described as a wise and peaceful man, and uses his formidable skills kung-fu only when forced by the villains - who are invariably corrupt, violent and immoral individuals, do not rarely “tainted” by Western influence. Well away from the rebel Hollywood cop!</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 01:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-45</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>in that it focuses more on rp and less on combat? that sounds nice</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-44</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaximusPrime" data-post="41" data-topic="80047">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/maximusprime/40/9732_2.png" class="avatar"> MaximusPrime:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but is this basically like dnd</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no it is very different.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-43</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s ok merc it happens we still love you</p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/a/3/a391e1e621a62117bb2d6f59f86c950836934e80.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="nl0nw70wp2ssrWoxokKom5kWNqw" width="495" height="475"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-42</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sounds interesting but is this basically like dnd and will be done on the forums</p>
<p>eh idk if i have time or motivation for that with the community fm rn and also i’ve never done this type of stuff so i’ll likely just watch</p>
<p>sorry merc</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-41</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>CRAB</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/0/1/019c1b1fc092b91890c69571aaf80881ac5d941d.jpeg" data-download-href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/019c1b1fc092b91890c69571aaf80881ac5d941d" title="image"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/original/3X/0/1/019c1b1fc092b91890c69571aaf80881ac5d941d.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="eeVQc0t4SsjOXT4CkxclMlIk6F" width="690" height="387" data-small-upload="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/uploads/default/optimized/3X/0/1/019c1b1fc092b91890c69571aaf80881ac5d941d_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">845×475 150 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-40</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>gave up on the quick resumes would take way too much translation<br>
but lemme vent a little bit<br>
if there is a system that you do not want to minmax on, it’s Rokugan, because everything there encourages you to make a well-rounded functional human being, from fluff to how much experience is given to you and how fast you level up. The fluff and the crunch both encourage you to be a well-versed samurai.<br>
And there is always someone who minmaxes for combat on all games I have played and GMed on this system who ends up doing almost nothing other than causing the party trouble socially because combats on this game are rare. We have had 50 game sessions and 6 combats. 3 of them in 3 consecutive sessions because they were inside Hell.<br>
Ended up the character got itself killed and after blaming everyone else a little bit I told him to fuck off until he stopped arguing. For a new character I encouraged him to play Crane, high-honor Crane. Cranes have to be polite and the example of courtesy itself to other clanes.<br>
If that does not work I’m kicking him from the table on all honesty.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 15:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-39</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll throw here the quick Clan resumes I hand out to my players.</p>
<details>
<summary>
Crab Clan</summary>
<p><img src="https://gamepedia.cursecdn.com/l5r_gamepedia_en/thumb/0/08/Crab_Clan_mon.png/250px-Crab_Clan_mon.png?version=6ff33d0705001c5ef9efc4aa72e7ec6b" alt="" width="250" height="235"></p>
<p>"We are the Wall! "<br>
✤ CRAB CLAN ✤</p>
<p>The rigid Crabs are the defenders of Rokugan, responsible for ensuring that the Empire’s southern border is safe from the demons of the Shadowlands. Centuries of constant war against inhuman opponents have turned Crabs into immensely powerful and brutally practical warriors, but they have little use in civility or manners. As a result, they are normally considered brutes and barbarians by other clans.</p>
<p>Intra-clan relations: The Hiruma are close to all the families of the clan due to the versatility of the family, and basically the only one within the clan near of the introverted Kuni. The co-dependency relationship within the clan is firmly established and it is very rare that there is any internal dispute or conflict between families. The Kaiu are also especially close to the Yasuki - they make the means of transporting their goods, and the Yasuki bring materials for their engineering projects.</p>
<hr>
<pre><code>   ✣ Hida Family ✣
   " I   w i l l   n o t   f a l l . "
</code></pre>
<p>The descendants of the Kami Hida are the largest and most powerful samurai in the entire Empire. The burden of defending the Empire falls on them, and they are incredible warriors and talented defensive strategists.<br>
Hida Samurai sometimes resent other Clans for enjoying their protection while still mocking the Crab for its mannerisms.</p>
<p>Bonus:   +1 Strength</p>
<hr>
<pre><code>   ✣ Hiruma Family ✣
   " W e   a r e   l i k e  s m o k e   o n   t h e   w i n d. "
</code></pre>
<p>Silent and deadly, the Hiruma are the Crab’s scouts and yojimbo. They are agile and graceful while the Hida are powerful, and warriors from both families tend to complement each other very well. Hiruma samurai sometimes have the unhealthy duty of exploring the Shadowlands in search of enemies, a task that leads many to death or ruin.</p>
<p>Bonus:   +1 Agility</p>
<hr>
<pre><code>   ✣ Yasuki Family ✣
   " M a y   y o u r   c u p   b e   a l w a y s   f u l l   a n d   y o u r   h a n d s   n e v e r   e m p t y. "
</code></pre>
<p>Strangely different from the other Crab families, the Yasuki are slim in physique and quick to think. They were once part of the Crane Clan, but they joined the Crab in the third century, sparking Rokugan’s first major internal war. They are merchants and courtiers, always looking for ways to gain advantages for their Clan, and tend to be more concerned with monetary gain than what is considered respectable for someone of the samurai caste.</p>
<p>Bonus:   +1 Awareness</p>
<hr>
<pre><code>   ✣ Kuni Family ✣
   " I   k n o w   o u r   e n e m y. "   –   K u n i   Y o r i.
</code></pre>
<p>Sinister in appearance and deed, the Kuni are among the most feared shugenja families in the Empire. The family leadership long ago determined that the only hope of defeating the Shadowlands was to understand them, and so the Kuni have knowledge of things that would drive many other men mad.</p>
<p>Bonus:  +1 Intelligence</p>
<hr>
<pre><code>   ✣ Kaiu Family ✣
   " T h e   s t r e n g t h   o f   a   m o u n t a i n   l i e s   o n   i t s   b a s e. "
</code></pre>
<p>The industrious Kaiu are responsible for the most impressive and ancient engineering feats in the entire Empire. They are the siege engineers and architects of the Crab Clan, and are responsible for keeping the Carpenter’s Great Wall at the height of their defenses.</p>
<p>Bonus:   +1 Intelligence</p>
</details>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 13:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-38</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe I can GM it to you guys if you are interested</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 12:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-37</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercenary]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Samurai setting that is less edgy and more magical game of thrones. There are seven clans who mostly bitch against one another but are all allies against everything that is not Rokugan.<br>
Heavy emphasis on Bushidō, social customs, political affairs and samurai drama.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 06:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what’s a rokugan :^)</p>
<p>teach me the wisdom</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/35</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 04:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N.1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s an rpg based in the rokugan universe IIRC</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 04:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>welcome back but what is this</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 04:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-33</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Merc GMin thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am expressing interest in this</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 03:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80047-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/merc-gmin-thread/80047.rss">Merc GMin thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
