<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722</link>
    <description>

The Court Wizard

Blue Dragon Support

    Ice Wall: (D) (2)
    Create a wall of ice outside your door tonight. 
    All visits to you will be prevented tonight.

Note:  Gives CW staying power with protection from attacks / potential Fool. Strengthens evil CW/Fool claims, as them showing up sus could be a night that a fool used frame instead of hide.  Fire wall may also need to be changed to allow the Sages to target themselves.

    Magical Barrier: (N) (oo)
    Protect a player from all negative effects and conversion. Does not prevent kills.  

Note: The **TARGET** will be notified that a barrier was cast on them **if** any negative effect or conversion was prevented.  The Court Wizard will receive a binary &#39;Your barrier prevented something&#39; or &#39;Your barrier did not prevent anything&#39; notification.  This change allows CW to prove themselves, while not entirely closing fake claims.  Emphasis on a Barrier that doesn&#39;t prevent anything, doesn&#39;t give feedback that the target was barriered, a Sage losing barrier isn&#39;t going to die right away if they claim barriers on people not getting occupied.

    Gust (Tornado Rework for CW): (N) (2)
    Cause all players targeting the target player to instead target the second.

Note:  Personally I believe Tornado/Teleport is, unfortunately, much more useful to coordinated evil class attacks but very beneficial to the game.  Removing it from CW completely will cause it to need to be removed from at least Sage, as it being used will immediately out the Sage.  Sage&#39;s Tornado and Ritualists Teleport will remain unchanged could remain in game with this one-way Tornado change.

**Potential Tornado replacements** - If Tornado isn&#39;t going to be on CW, Sage is going to need something else as well.  Maybe Ritualist as well.
     Detection: (N) (2) (CW)
     Place an alarm on the target players room.  
     They will be told the class, but not the number, of all visitors to them tonight.  
     Does not count as visiting.
Note:  Kind of a more investigative replacement, but as it doesn&#39;t directly give feedback to the Court Wizard, or the numbers of any visitors, it should fall into the Empowers ally category.  Empowers them with information!

    Illusion: (N) (oo) (Sage)
    Cast an illusion on the target player&#39;s room tonight.  
    They will be told the class, but not the number, of all visitors to them tonight. 
    You can select one converted class to show as visiting them as well.  Does not count as visiting.
Note:  Kind of risky to use a lot, but it can really help with throwing BD off your trail.  Empowers your target with false information!

    Vision of Mithras: (N) (3) (Ritualist)
    Curse the target with visions from Mithras tonight.  
    They will be told the class, but not the number, of all visitors to them tonight.
    If they are visited by members of the Blue Dragon it will tell them that the converted version of one of them
    visited them instead.  Does not count as visiting.
Note:  Maintains the theme of Detection and Illusion, but instead lies about one of the visitors.  Empowers your target with bad information!

Sage retains Wall of Fire and Ritualist retains Brotherhood and Will of Mithras.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 23:45:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, the devs definitely don’t want Tornado as the primary ability. Perhaps as a situational secondary, but CW definitely needs a fun/intriguing new primary night ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 23:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54722-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722.rss">CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rana31]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hit tab as I was changing it and it submitted before I was finished, oopsy.  A good Sage can claim that they magic barriered someone they believe was not affected by a disable that night, which is also what a fool would do.  Or that they used Detection (Illusion / Vision of Mithras) or Gust (Tornado / Teleportation) depending on if Tornado gets replaced.  The fact that it got submitted early really hurt how it appears, but give it another look over now that all I wanted is there.</p>
<p>Restating this if it wasn’t clear enough in main post, Detection / Illusion / Vision of Mithras is only there if Devs want Tornado completely gone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 22:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54722-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722.rss">CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Agreed. Must we say this everywhere</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 22:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54722-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722.rss">CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is not simple nor effective. All you did was add detection, which is likely to do nothingand only has 2 uses. You also made CW really confirmable, which is what we DO NOT want. Sage doesn’t have Magic Barrier anyway, so if he comes up sus to check just ask who he MBed. If they don’t confirm, he’s fool unless he was confirmed before, which means he’s sage. If someone does confirm, they’re likely both evil.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 21:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54722-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722.rss">CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rana31]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Court Wizard</p>
<p>Blue Dragon Support</p>
<pre><code>Ice Wall: (D) (2)
Create a wall of ice outside your door tonight. 
All visits to you will be prevented tonight.
</code></pre>
<p>Note:  Gives CW staying power with protection from attacks / potential Fool. Strengthens evil CW/Fool claims, as them showing up sus could be a night that a fool used frame instead of hide.  Fire wall may also need to be changed to allow the Sages to target themselves.</p>
<pre><code>Magical Barrier: (N) (oo)
Protect a player from all negative effects and conversion. Does not prevent kills.  
</code></pre>
<p>Note: The <strong>TARGET</strong> will be notified that a barrier was cast on them <strong>if</strong> any negative effect or conversion was prevented.  The Court Wizard will receive a binary ‘Your barrier prevented something’ or ‘Your barrier did not prevent anything’ notification.  This change allows CW to prove themselves, while not entirely closing fake claims.  Emphasis on a Barrier that doesn’t prevent anything, doesn’t give feedback that the target was barriered, a Sage losing barrier isn’t going to die right away if they claim barriers on people not getting occupied.</p>
<pre><code>Gust (Tornado Rework for CW): (N) (2)
Cause all players targeting the target player to instead target the second.
</code></pre>
<p>Note:  Personally I believe Tornado/Teleport is, unfortunately, much more useful to coordinated evil class attacks but very beneficial to the game.  Removing it from CW completely will cause it to need to be removed from at least Sage, as it being used will immediately out the Sage.  Sage’s Tornado and Ritualists Teleport will remain unchanged could remain in game with this one-way Tornado change.</p>
<p><strong>Potential Tornado replacements</strong> - If Tornado isn’t going to be on CW, Sage is going to need something else as well.  Maybe Ritualist as well.<br>
Detection: (N) (2) (CW)<br>
Place an alarm on the target players room.<br>
They will be told the class, but not the number, of all visitors to them tonight.<br>
Does not count as visiting.<br>
Note:  Kind of a more investigative replacement, but as it doesn’t directly give feedback to the Court Wizard, or the numbers of any visitors, it should fall into the Empowers ally category.  Empowers them with information!</p>
<pre><code>Illusion: (N) (oo) (Sage)
Cast an illusion on the target player's room tonight.  
They will be told the class, but not the number, of all visitors to them tonight. 
You can select one converted class to show as visiting them as well.  Does not count as visiting.
</code></pre>
<p>Note:  Kind of risky to use a lot, but it can really help with throwing BD off your trail.  Empowers your target with false information!</p>
<pre><code>Vision of Mithras: (N) (3) (Ritualist)
Curse the target with visions from Mithras tonight.  
They will be told the class, but not the number, of all visitors to them tonight.
If they are visited by members of the Blue Dragon it will tell them that the converted version of one of them
visited them instead.  Does not count as visiting.
</code></pre>
<p>Note:  Maintains the theme of Detection and Illusion, but instead lies about one of the visitors.  Empowers your target with bad information!</p>
<p>Sage retains Wall of Fire and Ritualist retains Brotherhood and Will of Mithras.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 21:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54722-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/cw-rework-potentially-simple-and-effective/54722.rss">CW rework - Potentially Simple and effective</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
