<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Wine of the Servant [Servant]</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-wine-of-the-servant-servant/2600</link>
    <description>I was just wandering down the hall one day when this man came up to me and showed me the truth about what that &#39;King&#39; has caused, he is merely a fool trying to mess with what he doesn&#39;t understand. I then still didn&#39;t believe this man and he showed me even more proof about what ALL of the Blue Dragon has done, including me. I begged him to have mercy on me and luckily he listened. 

He bribed me not to go back to my past ways of the Blue Dragon faction or else he would give the proof of what I had done out and then they would surely accuse me of treason. I merely had thought that the king all those years ago was against me so I poisoned him with nightshade. At the time I did not know what this hypocritical cult had done. Yet somehow they bribed me into taking an oath I would regret immediately.

As soon as I took that oath, they doused me straight into the darkest secrets of their secretive faction. They had done exactly what I had done but on a much... much larger scale. Even they don&#39;t know the exact number of castles that they have slain. Once we finished with Castle Demwir, we moved straight onto the next castle, **this** castle. The one we like to call Adiart. I have seen too many of this tribe slain. I have fears that I may be next however I have been fairly anonymous in this castle. Even the **leader** of the Unseen himself doesn&#39;t know my true name. He just thinks, like most, that my name is Ivo Savage and I am the Servant.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 07:26:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-wine-of-the-servant-servant/2600.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Wine of the Servant [Servant]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was just wandering down the hall one day when this man came up to me and showed me the truth about what that ‘King’ has caused, he is merely a fool trying to mess with what he doesn’t understand. I then still didn’t believe this man and he showed me even more proof about what ALL of the Blue Dragon has done, including me. I begged him to have mercy on me and luckily he listened.</p>
<p>He bribed me not to go back to my past ways of the Blue Dragon faction or else he would give the proof of what I had done out and then they would surely accuse me of treason. I merely had thought that the king all those years ago was against me so I poisoned him with nightshade. At the time I did not know what this hypocritical cult had done. Yet somehow they bribed me into taking an oath I would regret immediately.</p>
<p>As soon as I took that oath, they doused me straight into the darkest secrets of their secretive faction. They had done exactly what I had done but on a much… much larger scale. Even they don’t know the exact number of castles that they have slain. Once we finished with Castle Demwir, we moved straight onto the next castle, <strong>this</strong> castle. The one we like to call Adiart. I have seen too many of this tribe slain. I have fears that I may be next however I have been fairly anonymous in this castle. Even the <strong>leader</strong> of the Unseen himself doesn’t know my true name. He just thinks, like most, that my name is Ivo Savage and I am the Servant.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-wine-of-the-servant-servant/2600/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-wine-of-the-servant-servant/2600/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 07:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2600-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-wine-of-the-servant-servant/2600.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Wine of the Servant [Servant]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
