<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestions] Diseased/Plague Doctor</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256</link>
    <description>**Class:** Diseased (Neutral Killer) :gun:

**Basic info:** The Diseased is a neutral killing class that spreads their disease with every person they visit, Let&#39;s say player 1, got the disease (They don&#39;t know) And play 1 visited player 2, and player 3 visited player 1, they would all get the disease.

The diseased can kill **only** the people they infect, they can only kill 1 person at a time for the first 4 nights, then kill 2 people at a time the rest of the game.

**Day ability:** Threaten (x3) - The victim of this will get the notification **&quot;You have been threatened by the diseased, you cannot talk for the rest of the day&quot;** and like the notification says, they will not be able to talk for the rest of the day.

**Day Ability:** Infect - Infect a person with the disease (You can start doing this Day 2)

**Night Ability:** Relieve Misery - Kill 1 to 2 of the people who are infected (Like it says in the details, you may only kill 2 of the infected after night 4)

**Night Ability:** No Mercy (x2) - Can kill a player that is not diseased

**Class:** Plague Doctor (Neutral Investigative) :mag:

**Basic info:** Like the inquisitor, the Plague Doctor only appears when the diseased is in game, the Plague Doctors goal is to live to see the diseased dead.

**Passive:** Bacterial Studies - Cannot be infected

**Day ability:** Disinfect - Disinfect an infected player

**Night ability:** Check - Check to see if the player is Infected/The diseased, There are two notifications for this **&quot;Your target is infected!&quot;** or **&quot;Your target is the diseased!&quot;** (If a fool uses &quot;Frame&quot; the target will show up as the diseased)

**Night ability:** Kill Diseased - Kill the diseased player

Hope you liked my ideas, thanks :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 13:36:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestions] Diseased/Plague Doctor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam17z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It should not be your Target is the diseased because that seems like a hard counter, I think for everyone it should say either your target is infected or your target is not infected.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-50256-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256.rss">[Class Suggestions] Diseased/Plague Doctor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestions] Diseased/Plague Doctor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHCube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only thing I disliked about this is the plague doctor.  Hardcounters shouldn’t even exist</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-50256-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256.rss">[Class Suggestions] Diseased/Plague Doctor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestions] Diseased/Plague Doctor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Class:</strong> Diseased (Neutral Killer) <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/gun.png?v=9" title=":gun:" class="emoji" alt=":gun:"></p>
<p><strong>Basic info:</strong> The Diseased is a neutral killing class that spreads their disease with every person they visit, Let’s say player 1, got the disease (They don’t know) And play 1 visited player 2, and player 3 visited player 1, they would all get the disease.</p>
<p>The diseased can kill <strong>only</strong> the people they infect, they can only kill 1 person at a time for the first 4 nights, then kill 2 people at a time the rest of the game.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability:</strong> Threaten (x3) - The victim of this will get the notification <strong>“You have been threatened by the diseased, you cannot talk for the rest of the day”</strong> and like the notification says, they will not be able to talk for the rest of the day.</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability:</strong> Infect - Infect a person with the disease (You can start doing this Day 2)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability:</strong> Relieve Misery - Kill 1 to 2 of the people who are infected (Like it says in the details, you may only kill 2 of the infected after night 4)</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability:</strong> No Mercy (x2) - Can kill a player that is not diseased</p>
<p><strong>Class:</strong> Plague Doctor (Neutral Investigative) <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/mag.png?v=9" title=":mag:" class="emoji" alt=":mag:"></p>
<p><strong>Basic info:</strong> Like the inquisitor, the Plague Doctor only appears when the diseased is in game, the Plague Doctors goal is to live to see the diseased dead.</p>
<p><strong>Passive:</strong> Bacterial Studies - Cannot be infected</p>
<p><strong>Day ability:</strong> Disinfect - Disinfect an infected player</p>
<p><strong>Night ability:</strong> Check - Check to see if the player is Infected/The diseased, There are two notifications for this <strong>“Your target is infected!”</strong> or <strong>“Your target is the diseased!”</strong> (If a fool uses “Frame” the target will show up as the diseased)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability:</strong> Kill Diseased - Kill the diseased player</p>
<p>Hope you liked my ideas, thanks <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 22:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-50256-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-diseased-plague-doctor/50256.rss">[Class Suggestions] Diseased/Plague Doctor</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
