<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Pixie (Neutral)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-pixie-neutral/39369</link>
    <description>**Pixie** (Neutral) - A chaotic loon who only exists to have fun and cause trouble.

----

**Please note:** This is based on a defunct previous suggestion but is substantially changed. I&#39;ve created it _specifically to be fun to play and mess with people_. So naturally, it&#39;s trolly and annoying.

----

Passive:
**Fairy Glamour** - Players who investigate you will be given their own investigative results. (King sees you as his faction, Princess sees info as if she checked another Princess, etc.)

Day Ability 1:
**Wabba-Whack** - Cast a spell on a target player, causing a random daytime effect that would otherwise belong to a different class. (4 uses.)
Low chance of: Poison/Bleeding (Depending on faction in round.)
Medium chance of: Distract
High chance of: Troll Box

Day Ability 2:
**Puzzle Box** - The player you select will see others’ messages as gibberish for the next 10 seconds. (4 uses.)

Example: _PlayerName: 8 is cult._
Becomes: _PlayerName: 8 bs flod._

Night Ability 1:
**Warped Mirror** - Redirect the selected player to target themselves. (Unlimited use. Of course this DOES NOT include obviously broken things like Prince’s execution.)

Night Ability 2:
**Transmute** - You may choose to permanently take the class of a dead Neutral player if you so choose. Usable after 5 days. (Single use. Effect is permanent.)

----

**Goal:** Survive (like Alchemist) while having as much fun at others&#39; expense as possible. ;) If you choose to change classes, your goal changes to that of the class you chose -- of course.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 05:06:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-pixie-neutral/39369.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Pixie (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Pixie</strong> (Neutral) - A chaotic loon who only exists to have fun and cause trouble.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Please note:</strong> This is based on a defunct previous suggestion but is substantially changed. I’ve created it <em>specifically to be fun to play and mess with people</em>. So naturally, it’s trolly and annoying.</p>
<hr>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Fairy Glamour</strong> - Players who investigate you will be given their own investigative results. (King sees you as his faction, Princess sees info as if she checked another Princess, etc.)</p>
<p>Day Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Wabba-Whack</strong> - Cast a spell on a target player, causing a random daytime effect that would otherwise belong to a different class. (4 uses.)<br>
Low chance of: Poison/Bleeding (Depending on faction in round.)<br>
Medium chance of: Distract<br>
High chance of: Troll Box</p>
<p>Day Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Puzzle Box</strong> - The player you select will see others’ messages as gibberish for the next 10 seconds. (4 uses.)</p>
<p>Example: <em>PlayerName: 8 is cult.</em><br>
Becomes: <em>PlayerName: 8 bs flod.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Warped Mirror</strong> - Redirect the selected player to target themselves. (Unlimited use. Of course this DOES NOT include obviously broken things like Prince’s execution.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Transmute</strong> - You may choose to permanently take the class of a dead Neutral player if you so choose. Usable after 5 days. (Single use. Effect is permanent.)</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Goal:</strong> Survive (like Alchemist) while having as much fun at others’ expense as possible. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> If you choose to change classes, your goal changes to that of the class you chose – of course.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-pixie-neutral/39369/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-pixie-neutral/39369/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 04:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39369-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-pixie-neutral/39369.rss">[Class Suggestion] Pixie (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
