<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Enforcer</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-enforcer/3039</link>
    <description>To turn your back on the Blue Dragon is one thing, but to be trusted as its protector and ignore their pleas to be saved is another. The Knight was trusted to protect Castle Adiart and its royals from harm. This was especially true once the Unseen began to take a hold on the power structure. 

The Knight wished for only one thing, to protect the Blue Dragon from harm. This all changed on one fateful night, when he received a visit from the Mastermind. He knew what was happening immediately, and adamantly refused on the spot to join the Unseen. However, the Mastermind was not here to convince the Knight, as he knew of his unwavering loyalty. Instead, he offered him an ultimatum: either he join the Unseen and refuse to protect those he was sworn to, or his entire family who lived on Adiart soil would be killed. The Knight initially was in disbelief, refusing to acknowledge that the Unseen would already have that kind of power. In response, as if expecting this reaction, the Mastermind revealed a small painted picture, elegantly done, but clearly of his wife, and their two children. The Knight could feel his heart shattering, realizing that either way, he would be causing the deaths of people he had spent his entire life trying to protect. The Mastermind said without hesitation, &quot;Choose now, as the safety of your family very much depends on it.&quot;

The Knight had been broken. The loyalty he vowed to keep was torn away, and he knew it would cause many deaths. However, he could not let his family be harmed because of him, regardless of anything else. As the Mastermind left the room, his new follower trailed behind. No longer the Knight, but now the Enforcer, a violent and angry force to be reckoned with.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 16:07:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-enforcer/3039.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Enforcer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To turn your back on the Blue Dragon is one thing, but to be trusted as its protector and ignore their pleas to be saved is another. The Knight was trusted to protect Castle Adiart and its royals from harm. This was especially true once the Unseen began to take a hold on the power structure.</p>
<p>The Knight wished for only one thing, to protect the Blue Dragon from harm. This all changed on one fateful night, when he received a visit from the Mastermind. He knew what was happening immediately, and adamantly refused on the spot to join the Unseen. However, the Mastermind was not here to convince the Knight, as he knew of his unwavering loyalty. Instead, he offered him an ultimatum: either he join the Unseen and refuse to protect those he was sworn to, or his entire family who lived on Adiart soil would be killed. The Knight initially was in disbelief, refusing to acknowledge that the Unseen would already have that kind of power. In response, as if expecting this reaction, the Mastermind revealed a small painted picture, elegantly done, but clearly of his wife, and their two children. The Knight could feel his heart shattering, realizing that either way, he would be causing the deaths of people he had spent his entire life trying to protect. The Mastermind said without hesitation, “Choose now, as the safety of your family very much depends on it.”</p>
<p>The Knight had been broken. The loyalty he vowed to keep was torn away, and he knew it would cause many deaths. However, he could not let his family be harmed because of him, regardless of anything else. As the Mastermind left the room, his new follower trailed behind. No longer the Knight, but now the Enforcer, a violent and angry force to be reckoned with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-enforcer/3039/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-enforcer/3039/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 16:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-3039-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-enforcer/3039.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Enforcer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
