<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Redeemed (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90</link>
    <description>Day Ability 1: The Ever Lasting Mark
[PASSIVE] The Ancient runes of Corax still mark your body Despite Being weakened they still hold power. You are Immune to Night Ability&#39;s 

Night Ability 1: Avatar of The Fallen Angel 
You Send an avatar of the Fallen angel to keep protecting an ally from death. they gain Immune to death if they don&#39;t already have it as long as the angel protects them. you are able to target yourself with this ability 

Night Ability 2 direct the avatar 
[1-Night Cooldown] You Change the target of avatar of the fallen angel protecting someone else. if the target of avatar of the fallen angel was killed in a way the avatar can&#39;t protect, you ignore this cooldown 

Lore:
She was the most powerful cult leader of the cult that worships Mithras that even existed, but one night a fallen angel was was able her to free herself something that was thought near impossible. the fallen angel was banished from grace for siding with that demon in life and it used all its strength to save her. she still retains some of the power that she was able to get from him but refuse&#39;s to use them for evil purposes.

she and the angel from that day shared goal&#39;s beliefs everything.
everything in the world that is evil always has a glimmer of good so matter how small I will find their&#39;s for I am the king&#39;s Angel 

Night Room: The Church

Converted Class[The Ritualist Blackrose Offense 

Day Ability 1: The Strengthed Mark
[PASSIVE] The Ancient runes of Corax still mark your body but they have no fully grown in power but have granted you more power than what you thought. You are Immune Night Ability&#39;s and death at night 

Night Ability 1: Leech
The Target of this ability has its blood stolen by you, you can target each member only once and you are unable to to target other black rose members 

Night Ability 2: Blood Sacrifice 
every target that you targeted with the steal some blood ability die&#39;s this night. if you stole your own blood or the blood of a black rose member somehow they are not killed 

Lore:
She was the most powerful cult leader of the cult that worships Mithras that even existed, but one a fallen angel was was able her to free herself something that was thought near impossible. the fallen angel was banished from grace for siding with that demon in life and it used all its strength to save her. she still retains some of the power that she was able to get from him but refuse&#39;s to use them for evil purposes.

however one day the black rose recruited her and even since that 1 fateful night she threw everything she stood for and started using her dark gifts again and the more she abandoned the angels teaching&#39;s the stronger her powers. and because she sided with the evil forces the fallen angel had abandoned her never again to aid her. for she was not able to save her from this path of misery

Night Room: The Church

Comments:
hey there just wanted to explain some things before I end up my idea

for 1 if you are killed or converted the avatar of the angel no longer affects it&#39;s the latest target.
unlike a class like a physician, the advantage of the being a redeemed is that night ability can&#39;t affect you meaning if someone blocks you. you are still able to protect making it in a way stronger but only when conditions are met.
any class that attacked a target protected by the avatar simply gets a message saying your target was immune to your attack instead. your target was immune because a fallen angel was guarding it because the only people who would know who this is the black rose or some other killer.

normaly fallen angels are ment to be evil angels and that stuff, but my fallen angel is only fallen because of what I did in life and it formed a close bond with the Redeemed so really its really nice people just misunderstand it 

and yes the Redeemed is a female seeing how you did request that we all think of more female characters. also the fallen angel is a...is a.... well honestly I don&#39;t even know stop asking me these things.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 18:29:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Redeemed (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>for 1 I am Loving those ability names more(wish I was a bit better at naming have always been terrible)</p>
<p>and yea it is a cult leader turned good then bad again but is not helping the demon just the black rose with some different powers</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 18:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-90-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Redeemed (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Redeemed (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[B_Psycho2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Night ability 2 should be called Leech.</p>
<p>Night ability 1 called Blood Sacrifice.</p>
<p>Short and sweet.</p>
<p>But anyways, this is a cult leader turned good, then bad again? Tough life</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 17:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-90-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Redeemed (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Redeemed (Blue Dragon Support)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Day Ability 1: The Ever Lasting Mark<br>
[PASSIVE] The Ancient runes of Corax still mark your body Despite Being weakened they still hold power. You are Immune to Night Ability’s</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: Avatar of The Fallen Angel<br>
You Send an avatar of the Fallen angel to keep protecting an ally from death. they gain Immune to death if they don’t already have it as long as the angel protects them. you are able to target yourself with this ability</p>
<p>Night Ability 2 direct the avatar<br>
[1-Night Cooldown] You Change the target of avatar of the fallen angel protecting someone else. if the target of avatar of the fallen angel was killed in a way the avatar can’t protect, you ignore this cooldown</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
She was the most powerful cult leader of the cult that worships Mithras that even existed, but one night a fallen angel was was able her to free herself something that was thought near impossible. the fallen angel was banished from grace for siding with that demon in life and it used all its strength to save her. she still retains some of the power that she was able to get from him but refuse’s to use them for evil purposes.</p>
<p>she and the angel from that day shared goal’s beliefs everything.<br>
everything in the world that is evil always has a glimmer of good so matter how small I will find their’s for I am the king’s Angel</p>
<p>Night Room: The Church</p>
<p>Converted Class[The Ritualist Blackrose Offense</p>
<p>Day Ability 1: The Strengthed Mark<br>
[PASSIVE] The Ancient runes of Corax still mark your body but they have no fully grown in power but have granted you more power than what you thought. You are Immune Night Ability’s and death at night</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: Leech<br>
The Target of this ability has its blood stolen by you, you can target each member only once and you are unable to to target other black rose members</p>
<p>Night Ability 2: Blood Sacrifice<br>
every target that you targeted with the steal some blood ability die’s this night. if you stole your own blood or the blood of a black rose member somehow they are not killed</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
She was the most powerful cult leader of the cult that worships Mithras that even existed, but one a fallen angel was was able her to free herself something that was thought near impossible. the fallen angel was banished from grace for siding with that demon in life and it used all its strength to save her. she still retains some of the power that she was able to get from him but refuse’s to use them for evil purposes.</p>
<p>however one day the black rose recruited her and even since that 1 fateful night she threw everything she stood for and started using her dark gifts again and the more she abandoned the angels teaching’s the stronger her powers. and because she sided with the evil forces the fallen angel had abandoned her never again to aid her. for she was not able to save her from this path of misery</p>
<p>Night Room: The Church</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
hey there just wanted to explain some things before I end up my idea</p>
<p>for 1 if you are killed or converted the avatar of the angel no longer affects it’s the latest target.<br>
unlike a class like a physician, the advantage of the being a redeemed is that night ability can’t affect you meaning if someone blocks you. you are still able to protect making it in a way stronger but only when conditions are met.<br>
any class that attacked a target protected by the avatar simply gets a message saying your target was immune to your attack instead. your target was immune because a fallen angel was guarding it because the only people who would know who this is the black rose or some other killer.</p>
<p>normaly fallen angels are ment to be evil angels and that stuff, but my fallen angel is only fallen because of what I did in life and it formed a close bond with the Redeemed so really its really nice people just misunderstand it</p>
<p>and yes the Redeemed is a female seeing how you did request that we all think of more female characters. also the fallen angel is a…is a… well honestly I don’t even know stop asking me these things.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-90-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-redeemed-blue-dragon-support/90.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Redeemed (Blue Dragon Support)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
