<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What classes are worth hiding?</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve seen lots of people refuse to claim early when accused. Sometimes they are just evil but when they aren&#39;t the reason usually is that they are too important. Thing is that I often see people doing this flip butler/sheriff/Knight or some other unimportant class in the grand scheme of things. So the question is: What classes are so important that you need to hide from the court? Note: I am not talking about claiming in whispers to someone that isn&#39;t confirmed, there is good reason not to do that regardless of class.

Personally I avoid claiming as:
Prince, Psychic and sometimes I avoid claiming as a hunter strat.

Not claiming as hunter is important because if he always claimed then attacking someone who avoids claiming when you are evil is always a good idea.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 10:38:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What classes are worth hiding?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bart_Auringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Which assumes people give you time to even type.<br>
Half the time there is one accusation and you’re on trial in under a second.</p>
<p>As far as not claiming to say, a psychic.  That’s another thing.  Psychics die and leave logs often outting you even if you ask them not to.  They also get converted, which instantly spells your doom.</p>
<p>I often don’t claim to them even as some crap class so that when they die I take the hit as say, a Butler, over something important.</p>
<p>On the stand the only class that can maybe not claim is hunter, if you strongly suspect the person accusing you is evil, but even that is a crap shoot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 10:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32640-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640.rss">What classes are worth hiding?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What classes are worth hiding?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Loudo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You should never refuse to claim when you are accused.<br>
I’ve never seen that accomplishing anything. Best case scenario, you just end up wasting everyone’s time. Worst case scenario, you’ll have to claim anyway, but on trial where an Evil King could just execute you.</p>
<p>Claiming publicly to be an important class is usually pretty safe. If you claim early, you’ll attract everyone’s protections, which usually means you’ll live longer. The only times I see the Prince die early is when no one knows who he is.<br>
And if you die, you just make everyone’s Knight or Physician claims invalid, which takes away like half of the usual fake evil claims.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 10:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32640-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640.rss">What classes are worth hiding?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What classes are worth hiding?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if only important classes didn’t claim, then unseen/cult knows the people refusing to claim are important. Even given hunter, that still informs them they are a target, and they can stop you from bearing by alcoholic happy hour or just waiting a bit. If you aren’t hunter, they can kill you by having ritualist/sage switch them with player X and having CL/assassin attack player X and switch onto important player</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32640-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640.rss">What classes are worth hiding?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What classes are worth hiding?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But if someone accuses you then what claims would you still withhold? (assume you are not on the stand yet)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 01:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32640-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640.rss">What classes are worth hiding?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What classes are worth hiding?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jimpjorps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In the early game, when cult/unseen are trying to blindly convert/recruit members so that they don’t get crippled early on by a random NK kill or a lucky investigation, every reveal is potentially important – you’ve confirmed to their CL/MM that you’re BD and whether or not you’re convertible (and if nobody looks into you again after you’ve claimed and been converted, you have a strong alibi now).  Even as something minor like butler or knight, I’d only reveal that early if I had a piece of information that I felt strongly would be a net positive for BD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 01:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32640-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640.rss">What classes are worth hiding?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What classes are worth hiding?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve seen lots of people refuse to claim early when accused. Sometimes they are just evil but when they aren’t the reason usually is that they are too important. Thing is that I often see people doing this flip butler/sheriff/Knight or some other unimportant class in the grand scheme of things. So the question is: What classes are so important that you need to hide from the court? Note: I am not talking about claiming in whispers to someone that isn’t confirmed, there is good reason not to do that regardless of class.</p>
<p>Personally I avoid claiming as:<br>
Prince, Psychic and sometimes I avoid claiming as a hunter strat.</p>
<p>Not claiming as hunter is important because if he always claimed then attacking someone who avoids claiming when you are evil is always a good idea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32640-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/what-classes-are-worth-hiding/32640.rss">What classes are worth hiding?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
