<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Occassional Total System Freeze</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/occassional-total-system-freeze/61392</link>
    <description>It only happens every now and then, but it&#39;s very serious. Sometimes, I&#39;ll be in the middle of a game and it freezes up completely. I can&#39;t Ctrl+Alt+Delete out, and Windows has completely frozen up. The only thing I can do at that point is force a shutdown. Usually, it happens around voting time. It&#39;s especially a problem because this isn&#39;t one of those games where you can just drop out in the middle of it.

I am a new user, so I can&#39;t upload any files, but here are some mediafire links to my output log.

[Mediafire link](http://www.mediafire.com/file/77mufdqc4w48rpd/output_log.txt)

Plus, here&#39;s a crash log from a while back. It&#39;s the only one I have, because the freeze-up doesn&#39;t produce crash logs. I&#39;m not sure if the crash was related to the freeze, but it&#39;s worth an upload.

[Mediafire link](http://www.mediafire.com/folder/duxxv64klbcp6/2018-04-23_203326)

Here are my specs:
AMD Athlon II X4 640
AMD Radeon HD 6700 Series
8 GB Ram
Windows 7 Home Premium, 64-Bit

I enjoy this game, but until this gets fixed, I&#39;ll have to stop playing for the good of my aging computer.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 12:42:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/occassional-total-system-freeze/61392.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Occassional Total System Freeze</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[steggieav]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It only happens every now and then, but it’s very serious. Sometimes, I’ll be in the middle of a game and it freezes up completely. I can’t Ctrl+Alt+Delete out, and Windows has completely frozen up. The only thing I can do at that point is force a shutdown. Usually, it happens around voting time. It’s especially a problem because this isn’t one of those games where you can just drop out in the middle of it.</p>
<p>I am a new user, so I can’t upload any files, but here are some mediafire links to my output log.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.mediafire.com/file/77mufdqc4w48rpd/output_log.txt" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Mediafire link</a></p>
<p>Plus, here’s a crash log from a while back. It’s the only one I have, because the freeze-up doesn’t produce crash logs. I’m not sure if the crash was related to the freeze, but it’s worth an upload.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.mediafire.com/folder/duxxv64klbcp6/2018-04-23_203326" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Mediafire link</a></p>
<p>Here are my specs:<br>
AMD Athlon II X4 640<br>
AMD Radeon HD 6700 Series<br>
8 GB Ram<br>
Windows 7 Home Premium, 64-Bit</p>
<p>I enjoy this game, but until this gets fixed, I’ll have to stop playing for the good of my aging computer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/occassional-total-system-freeze/61392/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/occassional-total-system-freeze/61392/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 12:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-61392-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/occassional-total-system-freeze/61392.rss">Occassional Total System Freeze</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
