<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171</link>
    <description>

Objective: Kiss 2 people (or maybe 3 I&#39;m not the developer)

Ability 1 (Day): Entrance somebody to follow you to the lake (your base) where he/she will be occupied during the night. Since it is only the first night there, they will not kiss you yet! Only the second night will be person be ready to kiss. The player can also decide if they want to visit the mermaid again. If yes: you get a kiss. If no: the mermaid will place a curse on you. The mermaid also won&#39;t be able to entrance some else that night, so she&#39;ll be all alone.

Night Ability 1 (Kiss): once your target is ready to be kissed, they will get a blessing from the mermaid. The blessing gives the player night invincibility for 1 night (or more or less up to you guys) and now their votes count for 2 instead of 1, but still 3 for the king (lasts for 3 days). Also they will not be able to talk for 1 day because they are so stunned about the kiss. 

Night ability 2 (Mermaids curse): If the player does not return for a second &quot;date&quot; with the mermaid, the mermaid will place a curse upon you, which will not allow you to talk for 2 days, and not allow you to write in your will for 2 days. Also since you broke the mermaid&#39;s heart, you can never kiss her again this game. You jerk!  (Curse is placed at the end of the night you didn&#39;t want to go on the date)


&quot;Ultimate ability&quot;: Once 2 players have been kissed, you are night immune. You won the game. Still, you can impact the game. You have 2 spells to choose from now! (All chosen the day before).
1: make all players not be able to use a will for the following 2 nights, except the ones you have kissed
2: identify the roles of your lovers

(Each have a charge of 1)
So don&#39;t get on her bad side if you know what&#39;s good for ya :wink: 


Lore: (Coming soon)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 06:21:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sebastianbit1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, it’s anonymous. Although the mermaid probably has a good body, and nice soothing voice. The mermaid can offer her name though, be it the real one or not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 06:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-171-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss">Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>alright then<br>
does the person know who the mermaid is? for one I know I would not kiss someone wearing a mask</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 05:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-171-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss">Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sebastianbit1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, well when the mermaid makes you follow her, you can still talk to her. Although that’s all you can do, no other abilities. That’s why there’s an option for you to not return to her, because that one night that you were occupied was wasted, and if you are a valuable class, you can’t afford another night occupied.</p>
<p>Also the kiss can give you night invinciblity for a night.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 04:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-171-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss">Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the rewarding that the kiss power gives but don’t give more votes still op even for a support</p>
<p>for the 1st day ability don’t make it that they are occupied makes sense for prince since they are jailed but instead make it that if they can talk to someone else at night they can’t do it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 23:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-171-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss">Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sebastianbit1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It takes 2 full nights for a mermaid to get a kiss. The mermaid can choose a player to bring to her place (Only conversation would happen during that night).<br>
When the night ends, a normal day would happen for the mermaid and player. When that day ends, there will be a notification for the player if he wants to visit the mermaid again. If he doesn’t want to, the mermaid will be left alone for the entire night, while the other player does what he usually does on a normal night. BUT. The mermaid will realize that the player is not going to her place, and will get mad. At the end of that night the player who didn’t attend to her place will get a notification like “the mermaid has realized you left her, she placed a curse upon you.”</p>
<p>If all goes well for the mermaid, she would get her two kisses in 4 days (since it takes two dates with her to get a kiss). There are classes however who would not benefit as much from the blessings the kiss gives. Also, maybe the player really need to visit this one person, and don’t have time for the mermaid to take up their night for a blessing they don’t necessarily need.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 23:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-171-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss">Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoulShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s a good idea but I don’t think you should give the player who is kissed 1 more vote since the king needs to use a day ability to gain other just giving 2 is kinda op and makes it easy for everyone to known a mermaid is around<br>
Giving Night immune is enough for a support</p>
<p>also, how would mermaids curse work and why would you use it over kiss only makes it take longer to win.<br>
and most of her hurting ability block the use of will and prevent them from talking more annoying than anything else if I say myself</p>
<p>also, only 2 people to kiss? so you win on night 2?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-171-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss">Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sebastianbit1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Objective: Kiss 2 people (or maybe 3 I’m not the developer)</p>
<p>Ability 1 (Day): Entrance somebody to follow you to the lake (your base) where he/she will be occupied during the night. Since it is only the first night there, they will not kiss you yet! Only the second night will be person be ready to kiss. The player can also decide if they want to visit the mermaid again. If yes: you get a kiss. If no: the mermaid will place a curse on you. The mermaid also won’t be able to entrance some else that night, so she’ll be all alone.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1 (Kiss): once your target is ready to be kissed, they will get a blessing from the mermaid. The blessing gives the player night invincibility for 1 night (or more or less up to you guys) and now their votes count for 2 instead of 1, but still 3 for the king (lasts for 3 days). Also they will not be able to talk for 1 day because they are so stunned about the kiss.</p>
<p>Night ability 2 (Mermaids curse): If the player does not return for a second “date” with the mermaid, the mermaid will place a curse upon you, which will not allow you to talk for 2 days, and not allow you to write in your will for 2 days. Also since you broke the mermaid’s heart, you can never kiss her again this game. You jerk!  (Curse is placed at the end of the night you didn’t want to go on the date)</p>
<p>“Ultimate ability”: Once 2 players have been kissed, you are night immune. You won the game. Still, you can impact the game. You have 2 spells to choose from now! (All chosen the day before).<br>
1: make all players not be able to use a will for the following 2 nights, except the ones you have kissed<br>
2: identify the roles of your lovers</p>
<p>(Each have a charge of 1)<br>
So don’t get on her bad side if you know what’s good for ya <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Lore: (Coming soon)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 05:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-171-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mermaid-neutral-support-if-on-good-side/171.rss">Mermaid (Neutral-Support if on good side)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
