<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848</link>
    <description>Let me be straight to the point.... I LOVE THIS GAME, it has revolutionised the social deduction genre in multiple great ways, converts, multiple abilities the list goes on! But I feel right now the game has been mishandled and the situation sometimes have been highly exaggerated..This game is good nobody is saying it isn&#39;t, but the devs are clearly dealing with this in a wrong manner, everyone should be up to be criticised nobody&#39;s perfect.Why do you think we do this in the first place? Because we hate your guts and want your game to fail and you to meet a terrible fate? No! We want to make the current game better and expand it, right now this game has got a great sense of community probably one of the best in the gaming industry all together, major class reforms/added into the game were sometimes made by the community, and right now we have been pretty unified with no real controversy except for like allies I guess. The point is I am making is please stop censor us, please! I really like this game and I really want to see it prosper, but with the direction the Devs have taken I don&#39;t know if I should keep supporting it, but I will try my best. 

P.S please don&#39;t take this offensively I don&#39;t hate any of the devs personally, why would I? I just think personally some of their actions they have made
may have not been the best choice and I just want them to realise that.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 23:32:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Qwert]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In before this thread gets locked. Just going to drop my 2 cents on the situation.</p>
<p>I can understand when feedback threads talk about the same or similar issues/mechanics, they can look bad and messy. Maybe we should been looking into creating megathreads for one issue and focus on redirecting similar threads back into a main one. By doing this developers won’t look bad locking threads and limiting feedback.</p>
<p>Bos/Ellie seemed to take things personally? I understand there are tons of feedback/complaints out there and it’s difficult to keep everyone happy. But feedback/suggestions/complaints are not unique to this game and most game communities behave similarly from what I see.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 23:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73848-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848.rss">Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[invoker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah, but I guess mind warp would be better to say actually</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 21:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73848-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848.rss">Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Unless you are saying Devs and Community</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 21:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73848-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848.rss">Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="invoker" data-post="1" data-topic="73848">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/invoker/40/10751_2.png" class="avatar"> invoker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>right now we have been pretty unified with no real controversy except for like allies I guess</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>other way around</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 21:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73848-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848.rss">Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[invoker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let me be straight to the point… I LOVE THIS GAME, it has revolutionised the social deduction genre in multiple great ways, converts, multiple abilities the list goes on! But I feel right now the game has been mishandled and the situation sometimes have been highly exaggerated…This game is good nobody is saying it isn’t, but the devs are clearly dealing with this in a wrong manner, everyone should be up to be criticised nobody’s perfect.Why do you think we do this in the first place? Because we hate your guts and want your game to fail and you to meet a terrible fate? No! We want to make the current game better and expand it, right now this game has got a great sense of community probably one of the best in the gaming industry all together, major class reforms/added into the game were sometimes made by the community, and right now we have been pretty unified with no real controversy except for like allies I guess. The point is I am making is please stop censor us, please! I really like this game and I really want to see it prosper, but with the direction the Devs have taken I don’t know if I should keep supporting it, but I will try my best.</p>
<p>P.S please don’t take this offensively I don’t hate any of the devs personally, why would I? I just think personally some of their actions they have made<br>
may have not been the best choice and I just want them to realise that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 21:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-73848-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/devs-please-stop-censoring-us/73848.rss">Dev&#39;s Please stop censoring us</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
