<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Coward (Neutral Offensive)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-coward-neutral-offensive/23750</link>
    <description>&gt;**The Coward**
&gt;Neutral, Offensive
&gt;
&gt;**Goal:** Survive.
&gt;
&gt;**Passive Ability 1**
&gt;Anyone who kills you at night will gain 1 extra charge of their limited use abilities. (Doesn&#39;t include being executed by the prince). 
&gt;
&gt; **Passive Ability 2**
&gt; Immune to occupation.
&gt;
&gt;**Day ability 1**
&gt;Swap your name and position with another player for the rest of the day. They will not be notified about it. Cannot be used while on trial. 1 use. (doesn&#39;t work with the king)
&gt;
&gt;(Explanation: Basically you and your target &quot;swap bodies&quot; for the rest of the day, like a two-way possessor jump)
&gt;
&gt;**Night ability 1**
&gt;Target a player and hide in their room, making everyone who tries to visit them visit you instead (this works against occupy immune roles). Players attempting to visit you directly will be prevented. Infinite uses.
&gt;(Everyone redirected towards you will not be notified of your number, they will only get a message saying &quot;You were forced to target a coward hiding in their room.&quot;). 
&gt;
&gt;**Night ability 2**
&gt;If at least one person dies tonight, you will swap bodies and logs with them and it will appear as if you died. If more than one person died you will pick one at random. 1 use. (doesn&#39;t work with the king)
&gt;This is basically a possessor jump but without the killing part and random.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 04:15:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-coward-neutral-offensive/23750.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Coward (Neutral Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p><strong>The Coward</strong><br>
Neutral, Offensive</p>
<p><strong>Goal:</strong> Survive.</p>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 1</strong><br>
Anyone who kills you at night will gain 1 extra charge of their limited use abilities. (Doesn’t include being executed by the prince).</p>
<p><strong>Passive Ability 2</strong><br>
Immune to occupation.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability 1</strong><br>
Swap your name and position with another player for the rest of the day. They will not be notified about it. Cannot be used while on trial. 1 use. (doesn’t work with the king)</p>
<p>(Explanation: Basically you and your target “swap bodies” for the rest of the day, like a two-way possessor jump)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 1</strong><br>
Target a player and hide in their room, making everyone who tries to visit them visit you instead (this works against occupy immune roles). Players attempting to visit you directly will be prevented. Infinite uses.<br>
(Everyone redirected towards you will not be notified of your number, they will only get a message saying “You were forced to target a coward hiding in their room.”).</p>
<p><strong>Night ability 2</strong><br>
If at least one person dies tonight, you will swap bodies and logs with them and it will appear as if you died. If more than one person died you will pick one at random. 1 use. (doesn’t work with the king)<br>
This is basically a possessor jump but without the killing part and random.</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-coward-neutral-offensive/23750/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-coward-neutral-offensive/23750/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 04:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-23750-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-coward-neutral-offensive/23750.rss">The Coward (Neutral Offensive)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
