<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342</link>
    <description>**Version 1.1**

Sometimes the evil in souls stretches so far that a person&#39;s birth is corrupted from the beginning. Before the twins ever knew love, they knew loss, and through some blasphemous miracle they managed to live. Not much is known about the serial murderers except that the only thing that outmatches their bloodlust is their loyalty to each other. Town to town, kingdom to kingdom, the two wandered; eliminating townsfolk with their depraved tactics and innocent smiles. It wasn&#39;t until they heard whispers of a cult in the Kingdom of Adiart that they had any particular goals. _Mithras, Corax_. Those two names resonated with them, why? As they sat in the barn of a now dead farming family, they understood. That could be them. Why settle with farmers and peasants when they could become a king and queen in their own right? Gods even? Who would deny them love and blood then? Without a word to each other, they knew, and made their way to the castle to ensure that their dreams could become a reality. Together.

The Twins are 2 Neutral Killers who&#39;s goal is to be the last two standing in the game. Unlike most Neutral Killers the Twins have allies in themselves and must rely on their wits and each other to stay alive. The Twins always spawn together. 

**Disclaimer: I know it isn&#39;t a unique idea, but it is an interesting design space to toy with and I wanted to try my hand at a common game trope.**

&gt; Class Card Name : The Twins
&gt; Class Card Faction : Neutral
&gt; Class Card Type : Killer
&gt; 
&gt; Win Condition: Eliminate all factions that don&#39;t need to survive, or win with a Psycho King.
&gt; 
&gt; **Passives:**
&gt; A Bond Forged in Blood: The Twins share a night chat as long as one isn&#39;t Jailed. If one Twin dies, the other one commits suicide that same phase. The Twins can never be forced to kill each other. 
&gt; _This passive transfers over even when becoming King._
&gt; 
&gt; Sadistic Glee: If someone is executed during the day with no Pardons, reset the cool down of Killing Spree.
&gt; 
&gt; **Day Abilities**
&gt; Sense Motive (Day, 2/Game)
&gt; Allows you to send Private Whispers today to and from the other Twin. 
_Disables if used by the other Twin that day._
&gt; 
&gt; False Innocence (Day, 2/Game)
&gt; Target a player. Their abilities have no effects on you or your Twin tonight.
&gt; 
&gt; **Night Abilities**
&gt; Killing Spree (Night, Unlimited)
&gt; Kill a target tonight. If your Twin kills the same target, the effect is not preventable. This has a 1 Night cool down.
&gt; 
&gt; We Have Each Other (Night, Unlimited)
&gt; Protects your Twin from harmful effects and night kills tonight and Heals them from Bleeding and Poison. Does not protect yourself. 


**Design Decisions**
When designing the Twins, I was wondering what kind of design space could be filled. I was having a conversation with people about why NK&#39;s have such low win rates and I made the comment about them having 15 enemies; so I wondered to myself what would happen if they only had 14? Of course having twin Neutral Killers presented problems and asked questions: How could you balance two night kills a night at minimum with a potential extra one? How much is an ally actually worth for a NK? How could we make them interesting? What was missing in ToL? I had always been infatuated with a Serial Killer who had an unsuspecting Lover attached to them, thinking it was a great (albeit) dangerous dynamic so I started with that. 

While the Twins have massive killing strength (if they get resets with **Sadistic Glee**) they also have issues where if one dies, so does the other, making you extremely reliant on another player to stay alive and make it to the end. To remedy this I gave them two protective abilities, **False Innocence** and **We Have Each Other** which allows them to control the pace of the game for them, while avoiding detection and kills from dangerous roles such as the Drunk and Assassin. Of course this requires some coordination, as you&#39;re limited to how many you have and while they aren&#39;t shared you don&#39;t want to waste the uses of **False Innocence** on low priority targets, making changing information and pre-planning crucial to success.

In terms of their killing power, they have the ability to break through night defenses by doubling up on **Killing Spree**, though they still must watch for stray Knights (and hopefully neuter their power with **False Innocence**). Alternatively they can attack multiple targets to make the game seem Cultish in nature or to just speed up the death clock. As a final option, they can even just alternate night kills, always having one cover the other&#39;s back for a safer and slower game. Either use does put the ability on cool down, whether it succeeds or fails. In order to have it revert quickly, they need to hope for a hard execution to trigger **Sadistic Glee** so they can continue their spree. Having **Sadistic Glee** opens up more bluffing for people &quot;I only voted Pardon in case of Twins!&quot; and makes the voting game an interesting little sub game of chicken.

If a Twin seems to be under fire that night by various effects they can always choose to not kill and lay low, protecting their _other_ twin with **We Have Each Other**, biding time until **Killing Spree** comes off of cool down. 

A unique aspect of the Twins is that their **A Bond Forged in Blood** passive carries over if one of them becomes King, allowing them to nearly secure the game as long as they still trust each other and manage to avoid daytime executions and detection. While this may seem incredibly strong, Psycho Kings are extremely rare already and this ultimately is a win-more situation.

With their protective abilities, I decided to not give them a blanket death immunity, as they can do it them self at the expense of killing. Their lack of redirection and occupation immunity also makes them less suspect, though they can _toggle_ it somewhat with **We Have Each Other**. I&#39;ll be thinking about how dangerous it is to have two targets linked together, but for now they won&#39;t have any immunity.

Please leave some feedback and comments, I always love to hear them.

**Change Log**
&gt; 1.1 Added a Poison/Bleed Heal to **We Have Each Other**</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 21:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubaris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Except you can both choose to protect each other N1.<br>
No one is forcing you to Kill right off the bat.<br>
<img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Burst kill with zero protection <strong>OR</strong> a slow, single kill with a 50/50 <strong>OR</strong> no night kill with guaranteed safety.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 20:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The fact that a NK can die N1 to me is just wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 20:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubaris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Twil1ight" data-post="9" data-topic="58342" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/twil1ight/40/15561_2.png" class="avatar"> Twil1ight:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No killing abillity is okay (It’s already have 1-day cooldown which is good). But immunity to bleeding/poison would be nice since there is no counterplay to it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Added a Bleed/Poison heal to <strong>We Have Each Other</strong>. Might be more dynamic than pure invulnerability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 20:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubaris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="methomps" data-post="5" data-topic="58342" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> methomps:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What message would a drunk/butler get?  That the twin was occ immune?  What would the flirt result be?  I assume this would not impact Prince execute?  What about knight guard?  Merc guard?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Haven’t thought of messaging for Drunks and Butlers yet. Still playing around with the idea, maybe have them like the Mastermind where they think they succeeded, but they didn’t.</p>
<p>Not sure about Flirt, was thinking more Will O’ Wisp.</p>
<p>It would not stop Prince due to Prince kind of breaking the rules (as well as being a Day Ability).</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 20:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No killing abillity is okay (It’s already have 1-day cooldown which is good). But immunity to bleeding/poison would be nice since there is no counterplay to it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 20:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubaris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What would you do to amplify their power without making them a strictly better Night Killer? Its definitely not an easy task balancing a potential 2 extra kills a night; which is why I had them be able to protect on off-nights or nights they want to take less risk. They can even both protect each other, being virtually unkillable if they desire.</p>
<p>Once per game protection a la Inquisitor perhaps? Maybe tie a buff to <strong>Sadistic Glee</strong> for a night?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 20:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[methomps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My opinion, sure, but one I feel fairly confident in.  In addition to being the only NK vulnerable to dying to an assassin/alch n1, it is also the only NK without any natural defense to poison/bleed.</p>
<p>I get the concept of having to work together, which is why each alone is an underpowered NK.  But I don’t think you can have them both be individually underpowered AND have one suicide on the death of the other.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 20:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="methomps" data-post="5" data-topic="58342">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> methomps:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think the suicide aspect of this is too punishing and would make the Twins the hardest NK to win as.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You forgot mention it’s just a <strong>theory</strong>. Right now we can’t determine if this statement is true or not unless that type of idea would be tested.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="methomps" data-post="5" data-topic="58342">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/alchemist-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> methomps:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Without inherent death immunity, twins face a lot of danger: assassin attacks, eradicate, knight guard/CS, bear, alch bomb, etc.  The assassin alone has a 15.3% chance to target one of the twins n1.  Plus two NKs mean two different claims that have to hold up.  I would think about allowing the second twin to forge on, perhaps with some changes upon the death of the first one.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This literally core aspect in this case. An NK who need relly on their teammate.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[methomps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>A Bond Forged in Blood: The Twins share a night chat as long as one isn’t Jailed. If one Twin dies, the other one commits suicide that same phase. The Twins can never be forced to kill each other.<br>
This passive transfers over even when becoming King.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I think the suicide aspect of this is too punishing and would make the Twins the hardest NK to win as.  Without inherent death immunity, twins face a lot of danger: assassin attacks, eradicate, knight guard/CS, bear, alch bomb, etc.  The assassin alone has a 15.3% chance to target one of the twins n1.  Plus two NKs mean two different claims that have to hold up.  I would think about allowing the second twin to forge on, perhaps with some changes upon the death of the first one.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Sadistic Glee: If someone is executed during the day with no Pardons, reset the cool down of Killing Spree.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I really like this.  Will people start explaining away stray pardons as just breaking up twins refresh?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>False Innocence (Day, 2/Game)<br>
Target a player. Their abilities have no effects on you or your Twin tonight.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>What message would a drunk/butler get?  That the twin was occ immune?  What would the flirt result be?  I assume this would not impact Prince execute?  What about knight guard?  Merc guard?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was talking about more common situations.<br>
But yes it is true indeed. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorc can win with inquistor.</p>
<p>Inquistor becomes king.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twil1ight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hubaris" data-post="1" data-topic="58342">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hubaris/40/3990_2.png" class="avatar"> Hubaris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A Bond Forged in Blood: The Twins share a night chat as long as one isn’t Jailed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just want be clear here. It’s not passive abillity. You can just write in notes.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hubaris" data-post="1" data-topic="58342">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hubaris/40/3990_2.png" class="avatar"> Hubaris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>why NK’s have such low win rates and I made the comment about them having 15 enemies</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Generally speaking, Neutral’s are not NK’s enemies and they can win with him. (Except Sorc vs Inq).</p>
<p>But back to the topic, it is solid suggestion with unique concept. Good job mister!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubaris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Version 1.1</strong></p>
<p>Sometimes the evil in souls stretches so far that a person’s birth is corrupted from the beginning. Before the twins ever knew love, they knew loss, and through some blasphemous miracle they managed to live. Not much is known about the serial murderers except that the only thing that outmatches their bloodlust is their loyalty to each other. Town to town, kingdom to kingdom, the two wandered; eliminating townsfolk with their depraved tactics and innocent smiles. It wasn’t until they heard whispers of a cult in the Kingdom of Adiart that they had any particular goals. <em>Mithras, Corax</em>. Those two names resonated with them, why? As they sat in the barn of a now dead farming family, they understood. That could be them. Why settle with farmers and peasants when they could become a king and queen in their own right? Gods even? Who would deny them love and blood then? Without a word to each other, they knew, and made their way to the castle to ensure that their dreams could become a reality. Together.</p>
<p>The Twins are 2 Neutral Killers who’s goal is to be the last two standing in the game. Unlike most Neutral Killers the Twins have allies in themselves and must rely on their wits and each other to stay alive. The Twins always spawn together.</p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer: I know it isn’t a unique idea, but it is an interesting design space to toy with and I wanted to try my hand at a common game trope.</strong></p>
<blockquote>
<p>Class Card Name : The Twins<br>
Class Card Faction : Neutral<br>
Class Card Type : Killer</p>
<p>Win Condition: Eliminate all factions that don’t need to survive, or win with a Psycho King.</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
A Bond Forged in Blood: The Twins share a night chat as long as one isn’t Jailed. If one Twin dies, the other one commits suicide that same phase. The Twins can never be forced to kill each other.<br>
<em>This passive transfers over even when becoming King.</em></p>
<p>Sadistic Glee: If someone is executed during the day with no Pardons, reset the cool down of Killing Spree.</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities</strong><br>
Sense Motive (Day, 2/Game)<br>
Allows you to send Private Whispers today to and from the other Twin.<br>
<em>Disables if used by the other Twin that day.</em></p>
<p>False Innocence (Day, 2/Game)<br>
Target a player. Their abilities have no effects on you or your Twin tonight.</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities</strong><br>
Killing Spree (Night, Unlimited)<br>
Kill a target tonight. If your Twin kills the same target, the effect is not preventable. This has a 1 Night cool down.</p>
<p>We Have Each Other (Night, Unlimited)<br>
Protects your Twin from harmful effects and night kills tonight and Heals them from Bleeding and Poison. Does not protect yourself.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Design Decisions</strong><br>
When designing the Twins, I was wondering what kind of design space could be filled. I was having a conversation with people about why NK’s have such low win rates and I made the comment about them having 15 enemies; so I wondered to myself what would happen if they only had 14? Of course having twin Neutral Killers presented problems and asked questions: How could you balance two night kills a night at minimum with a potential extra one? How much is an ally actually worth for a NK? How could we make them interesting? What was missing in ToL? I had always been infatuated with a Serial Killer who had an unsuspecting Lover attached to them, thinking it was a great (albeit) dangerous dynamic so I started with that.</p>
<p>While the Twins have massive killing strength (if they get resets with <strong>Sadistic Glee</strong>) they also have issues where if one dies, so does the other, making you extremely reliant on another player to stay alive and make it to the end. To remedy this I gave them two protective abilities, <strong>False Innocence</strong> and <strong>We Have Each Other</strong> which allows them to control the pace of the game for them, while avoiding detection and kills from dangerous roles such as the Drunk and Assassin. Of course this requires some coordination, as you’re limited to how many you have and while they aren’t shared you don’t want to waste the uses of <strong>False Innocence</strong> on low priority targets, making changing information and pre-planning crucial to success.</p>
<p>In terms of their killing power, they have the ability to break through night defenses by doubling up on <strong>Killing Spree</strong>, though they still must watch for stray Knights (and hopefully neuter their power with <strong>False Innocence</strong>). Alternatively they can attack multiple targets to make the game seem Cultish in nature or to just speed up the death clock. As a final option, they can even just alternate night kills, always having one cover the other’s back for a safer and slower game. Either use does put the ability on cool down, whether it succeeds or fails. In order to have it revert quickly, they need to hope for a hard execution to trigger <strong>Sadistic Glee</strong> so they can continue their spree. Having <strong>Sadistic Glee</strong> opens up more bluffing for people “I only voted Pardon in case of Twins!” and makes the voting game an interesting little sub game of chicken.</p>
<p>If a Twin seems to be under fire that night by various effects they can always choose to not kill and lay low, protecting their <em>other</em> twin with <strong>We Have Each Other</strong>, biding time until <strong>Killing Spree</strong> comes off of cool down.</p>
<p>A unique aspect of the Twins is that their <strong>A Bond Forged in Blood</strong> passive carries over if one of them becomes King, allowing them to nearly secure the game as long as they still trust each other and manage to avoid daytime executions and detection. While this may seem incredibly strong, Psycho Kings are extremely rare already and this ultimately is a win-more situation.</p>
<p>With their protective abilities, I decided to not give them a blanket death immunity, as they can do it them self at the expense of killing. Their lack of redirection and occupation immunity also makes them less suspect, though they can <em>toggle</em> it somewhat with <strong>We Have Each Other</strong>. I’ll be thinking about how dangerous it is to have two targets linked together, but for now they won’t have any immunity.</p>
<p>Please leave some feedback and comments, I always love to hear them.</p>
<p><strong>Change Log</strong></p>
<blockquote>
<p>1.1 Added a Poison/Bleed Heal to <strong>We Have Each Other</strong></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-58342-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-class-the-twins-neutral-killer/58342.rss">[New Class] The Twins - Neutral Killer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
