<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Feedback/Suggestions - Forum of Lies | Throne of Lies | by Imperium42</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/c/feedback/12</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Feedback/Suggestions&#39; category What can we reasonably do to improve your experience?</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 05:56:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/c/feedback/12.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Ongoing games notification</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[_torino]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please add a message to lobbies about the number of ongoing games</p>
<p>If a player joins a lobby while there is one ongoing game, it should say something like<br>
“There is currently 1 game in progress - people will likely join when it ends.”<br>
If a player joins a lobby while there is no ongoing games, prompt them to join the Discord and get a game started. (that’s how most games are started now, and new players should be <strong>told</strong> that)</p>
<p>If there are games going, the thing which stops people from leaving when they see only a few players in the lobby is someone saying “hey there is a game going, just wait for it to end and people will join”.<br>
If someone doesn’t know that and sees like 3/16 people in a lobby and they’re not on the discord they’ll just go “oh nobody is online i’ll leave”</p>
<p>New players who join without being on the discord should know how to get a game started.</p>
<p>This change would likely improve player retention which is obviously needed right now</p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 05:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88679</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/ongoing-games-notification/88679.rss">Ongoing games notification</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Noble Gossip Buff</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I propose reducing feedback in general, but increasing it in particular for Nobles.  For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Physicians are still informed when they heal an attack or cure a bleed, but not whether it was an attack or a bleed.  Only a Noble’s Gossip can tell.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Butlers and Drunks are not informed whether their target was immune.  Only cooperation with a Noble can determine this.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Etc.</p>
</li>
</ul>
            <p><small>5 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/noble-gossip-buff/88205">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/noble-gossip-buff/88205</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-88205</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/noble-gossip-buff/88205.rss">Noble Gossip Buff</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Feedback as a new player</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Helz]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My limited understanding is that Mafia is a sub-forum here but I just wanted to communicate my thoughts on my experience playing a game here.</p>
<p>-The password limitations suck. I get that its considered a normal thing these days but honestly as a user on a website I wish I could literally make my password “1”. On some sites security just does not matter imo and making crazy password obligations just makes the site a pain in the ass to access while doing nothing for the user.</p>
<p>-The lack of a post number on posts really hurt my experience. May not be an issue for other areas of this forum but it was painful in many respects and absolutely brutal when you went into an Iso as that the slider did not even give you a guestimate.</p>
<p>-This may be the absolute best site I have ever played a game on for mobile use. I would highly encourage this site to embrace ‘Turbos’ as that I feel its made for them between the site meta and the post style.</p>
<p>-The ‘like’ function working for dead players could be used to cheat. Not sure if thats tracked by mods and such but it may be worth a look (and would be better to be disabled)</p>
<p>-The lack of ability to create a quote text after the thread closed hurt night planning for me. Would be nice to be able to grab quote text even if posting is not a thing to build cases at night.</p>
<p>-The search function was cool but I kinda wish the normal Ctrl+F worked. There were plenty of times I needed it to grab something specific in a post but just couldn’t.</p>
<p>-I feel like the buttons could be expanded to include more of what the code allows. Simple things like spoilers were confusing to use so I ended up just spamming the thread with wall posts while I normally would have put them behind a spoiler simply because I did not have access to the function and did not feel I had access to the information. I am sure I could figure it out but I do not feel my ability to figure things out represents the ‘average user’ who functions should be created for.</p>
<p>Anyways, Had a great time playing here and I hope to do so in the future. This is just a bit of feedback on what I feel would make this site even better.</p>
<p>-edit<br>
Forgot to mention, Please please please implement a vote count system. The lack of it was terrible to deal with and undoubtedly AIDS to the hosts. That in itself would make me never want to host a game here.</p>
            <p><small>14 posts - 9 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/feedback-as-a-new-player/87863">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/feedback-as-a-new-player/87863</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 18:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87863</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/feedback-as-a-new-player/87863.rss">Feedback as a new player</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>ToL All Any Mode</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(Suggested by Intensify)</p>
<h1>
<a name="minimum-requirements-1" class="anchor" href="#minimum-requirements-1"></a>Minimum requirements</h1>
<p>10 players<br>
1x MM or CL<br>
1x NK<br>
1x King (does not count towards BD count)<br>
1x Prince (Does count towards BD count)<br>
1x Constable (Does count towards BD count, more info below)<br>
BD must be greater than or equal to the number of non-BD plus three.</p>
<h1>
<a name="general-spawning-and-wincon-rules-2" class="anchor" href="#general-spawning-and-wincon-rules-2"></a>General spawning and wincon rules</h1>
<p>MM, assa, CL, scorned, merc, SS, inq, prince, Mystic, and hunter are unique. Unseen cap at three, while Cult caps at four but can start with any number so long as it complies with the above requirements. Anything else can spawn without a cap unless the rand does not comply with the requirements set above.</p>
<p>Sheriff and Paladin are merged to become Constable, with Scout to detect Unseen visits and Smite to stop CL (no surv). Expert Investigation will not tell you whether or not your target was Unseen or Cult.</p>
<p>Cult and unseen do NOT win with each other. They cannot convert each other either. NKs do not win with each other.</p>
<h1>
<a name="interaction-details-3" class="anchor" href="#interaction-details-3"></a>Interaction details</h1>
<p>If a possessor jumps a reaper with souls, the Reaper will consume a soul and switch bodies with the poss.<br>
If a MM and CL convert the same person, they will become unseen and CL will get a “cannot convert” result.<br>
Unseen and Cult are incompatible with each other, framed people are compatible with both (except for In the Shadows MM).</p>
<h2>
<a name="i-think-that-sums-up-all-the-interactions-4" class="anchor" href="#i-think-that-sums-up-all-the-interactions-4"></a>I think that sums up all the interactions.</h2>
            <p><small>22 posts - 10 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tol-all-any-mode/87805">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tol-all-any-mode/87805</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87805</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/tol-all-any-mode/87805.rss">ToL All Any Mode</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Suggestion] Massive nerf to Inquisitor</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zubumafu]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi fellow liars,<br>
I am suggesting the following 3 changes -</p>
<ol>
<li>Inquisitor needs to kill only 2 targets (and can only attack twice),</li>
<li>The targets are notified if the inq finds them in investigation</li>
<li>If the inq attacks and kills someone who is not an heretic, he losses the remaining attack charges (He can continue his work like a scorned would, convincing others to kill his target).</li>
</ol>
            <p><small>7 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-massive-nerf-to-inquisitor/87252">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-massive-nerf-to-inquisitor/87252</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87252</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-massive-nerf-to-inquisitor/87252.rss">[Suggestion] Massive nerf to Inquisitor</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Addressing the Cult/Unseen chat window</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[_torino]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is a window of time where after your action is processed you can quickly say what happened to you on that night or what your results were.<br>
For example, a Seeker can say “12 is Offensive”, or MM can say “conv immune”</p>
<p>I know that the devs already know about this, but I just wanted to bring it back into the public eye</p>
<p>If you are on an old/slow computer, you cannot make use of this small window of time because the screen fades to black right after your action is processed and you might actually end up saying “convert immune” in the day chat (if the computer is super slow, happened to me once on my old laptop)</p>
<p>The window of time between your action being processed and the night actually ending should be increased by say, 5 seconds.</p>
<p>This would allow easier communication between cult/unseen members, and also make it easier for people with old and slow computers to communicate with their team members.</p>
            <p><small>3 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/addressing-the-cult-unseen-chat-window/86993">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/addressing-the-cult-unseen-chat-window/86993</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 08:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86993</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/addressing-the-cult-unseen-chat-window/86993.rss">Addressing the Cult/Unseen chat window</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral class: caliph</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so i played some other game about medieval times and apparently back then they had muslims and muslims follower a guy called the caliph. so i thought in a medieval game it would be cool to add the caliph</p>
<p>goal: be alive at end of game, and all winning players should be converted<br>
passive abilities:</p>
<p>haram - cannot be occupied</p>
<p>day abilities<br>
sharia - 1 use. force an execution on the target player who is on trial. to other players it will seem like just enough people voted execute in order to execute them<br>
hadj (1 use) - tonight you will leave the castle. you will be immune to attack and healed of bleeding, but cant do any night ability</p>
<p>night abilties<br>
send preacher (infinite) - send a preacher to target player converting them to islam. if they were occupied by someone else they cant be converted. occupies them. members of the cult/unseen cant be converted this way, but if you convert the mastermind/cult leader then the evil faction will all become muslim</p>
<p>jihad (3 uses) - attacks against target player will bypass death immunity tonight.</p>
<p>u like it idea? im try not be controversial on it</p>
            <p><small>13 posts - 5 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-class-caliph/86276">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-class-caliph/86276</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 05:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86276</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/neutral-class-caliph/86276.rss">Neutral class: caliph</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>CATHARS (evil faction suggestion)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hello good friends so i was recently playing a good game of ck2 and the cathars took control of soutern france through a secret religious cult (ck2 is a videogame about medieval kind of like throne of lies).</p>
<p>whats a cathar? they were an evil gnostic church that taught celibacy, creation is evil, god of old testament is evil, heresy about the trinity, etc. i think they would make an excellent evil faction</p>
<p>there would be only 1 role, the cathar</p>
<p>passive - cant be occupied (they are too focused on heresy)<br>
night action - make celibate (the opponent will die in 1 turn)<br>
night action - cooldown two nights (conver them to catharism)</p>
<p>when the blue dragon wins the screen will say “Caedite eos. Novit enim Dominus qui sunt eius.”</p>
<p>what u think</p>
            <p><small>4 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cathars-evil-faction-suggestion/86274">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cathars-evil-faction-suggestion/86274</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 04:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86274</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cathars-evil-faction-suggestion/86274.rss">CATHARS (evil faction suggestion)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Gunslinger (Unique Neutral Offensive)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunica]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p><strong>Win Condition:</strong> Kill 3 players</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
<strong>Battle Armor</strong> - Become death immune for 1 night if attacked, then you lose this passive. Lose this passive when you achieve your objective</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities:</strong><br>
<strong>Lethal Bullet</strong> - The next time you use shoot, it will bypass healing and death immunity. Cannot be used until day 3 (1 use).<br>
<strong>Rogue</strong> - The next time you use shoot, you will not let anybody know (1 use).</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities:</strong><br>
<strong>Shoot</strong> - Attack target player with your gun. Target player and anyone visiting them will be notified you shot them (Can’t target the King) (Infinite uses).<br>
<strong>Reload</strong> - Gain a charge of Rogue (Infinite uses).</p>
</blockquote>
<p>(loses abilities upon winning)</p>
            <p><small>10 posts - 5 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/gunslinger-unique-neutral-offensive/86076">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/gunslinger-unique-neutral-offensive/86076</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 10:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86076</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/gunslinger-unique-neutral-offensive/86076.rss">Gunslinger (Unique Neutral Offensive)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>FM Cult - Skylanders</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChopChop]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Skylander Cult (FM Cult)</p>
<p>Hello. I am Chop Chop.<br>
I used to be known as someone else, but no more. As I am loyal and now known as Chop Chop.<br>
You see I used be known as a “Not Good” or a “Weak” even though I KNOW I’m a “Strong” and a “Good”. I wish I could be liked the way I want to be. The way I know I can be.<br>
So I said Enough is Enough! Time for a change!<br>
Time to better myself! Permanently!<br>
So it doesn’t matter who I was, it matters who I am.</p>
<p>And I am a Skylander but not any Skylander, I am known as “Chop Chop”. “Chop” for short.<br>
But then I decided, maybe there are others like me that want to better themselves and become like as I have become. To become a Skylander.</p>
<p><strong>How does one become a Skylander?</strong><br>
Simple, just type below the Skylander you want to be and say “I hereby pledge myself as this Skylander”<br>
Then you must change your Username and Discord Name to that Skylander and never EVER change your Username and Discord name for as long as you live just like me.<br>
I’ll also then invite you to the Special Private Skylanders only Discord Server.</p>
<p>(P.S. would love to have a Dino-Rang in the Cult)</p>
            <p><small>29 posts - 11 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-cult-skylanders/85855">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-cult-skylanders/85855</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85855</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/fm-cult-skylanders/85855.rss">FM Cult - Skylanders</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Triple Threat Mode</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1x King (60% BD, 20% Unseen, 20% Cult)<br>
1x MM (First convert gains Apprentice, N1 convert is randomized and guaranteed if no one else is converted. Foresight is unusable N1.)<br>
1x CL (N1 convert is randomized and guaranteed if no one else is converted. Eradicate is unusable N1.)<br>
1x Prince<br>
1x Sheriff/Paladin mixture (Infinite Test Faith, Infinite Expert Investigation, Infinite Scout)<br>
8-9x Other BD<br>
2-3x Non-NK neuts</p>
<p>Idk why I created this. Give feedback anyway.</p>
            <p><small>24 posts - 8 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/triple-threat-mode/85666">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/triple-threat-mode/85666</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85666</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/triple-threat-mode/85666.rss">Triple Threat Mode</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Achievements For Each Class (And Other Achievements)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[GameShroomBoy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not saying it should be the exact same but something like the achievements from that other social deduction game that begins with a T. Maybe like you have the main achievements like get 1 win as this class so each class has one achievement but there are also other achievements that you can get for doing certain things as some classes or having something happen. You know? Also maybe the reward for completing an achievement could be 100 GP or something (also with the percent completed on Steam). Also maybe some achievements can be more rare then others by its task or just you know people not getting it.</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/achievements-for-each-class-and-other-achievements/85512">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/achievements-for-each-class-and-other-achievements/85512</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 14:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85512</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/achievements-for-each-class-and-other-achievements/85512.rss">Achievements For Each Class (And Other Achievements)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Logs are only posting on one line as of the new patch - please revert this</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[_torino]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As of the new patch, when you copy/paste logs it pastes only on one line, as opposed to multiple lines. For example, before this patch you could post these logs (below) and they would appear as you see them here<br>
John Smith - Physician<br>
N1 - Heal 3 | DNR<br>
N2 - Heal 4 | DNR</p>
<p>But with this new patch, logs are posting on only one line. So the above logs would appear as:<br>
John Smith - Physician N1 - Heal 3 | DNR N2 - Heal 4 | DNR</p>
<p>Logs appearing on only one line is extremely annoying, it makes other peoples logs hard to read if they post them in full, likewise, people are less likely to understand logs that you post.</p>
<p>Please revert log posting to the former example.</p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/logs-are-only-posting-on-one-line-as-of-the-new-patch-please-revert-this/85460">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/logs-are-only-posting-on-one-line-as-of-the-new-patch-please-revert-this/85460</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 04:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85460</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/logs-are-only-posting-on-one-line-as-of-the-new-patch-please-revert-this/85460.rss">Logs are only posting on one line as of the new patch - please revert this</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Cultseen (new mode)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[GameShroomBoy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t know if somebody has typed this out already but here’s a game mode idea I thought of:</p>
<p>Cultseen: (idk about name)</p>
<p>Game starts off with CL and MM with no starting members.</p>
<p>There will be 1-3 Neutrals per game. If there is only 1 Neutral then the other 2 will just spawn in as members of the Blue Dragon. Same goes for if there’s only 2 Neutrals the 3rd will spawn as a member of the Blue Dragon. (Only 1-2 Neutrals now. 3rd is BD)</p>
<p>For the NK it’s a 35% chance of an NK spawning. Otherwise it will have a 65% to be a member of BD. (Now there is no NK)</p>
<p>The King will always 100% be a Good King.</p>
<p>There will guaranteed be at least 1 Paladin and 1 Sheriff per game.</p>
<p>Playerlist: (note these are just if all the roles added not in any order)</p>
<p>1 - Good King<br>
2 - Cult Leader<br>
3 - Blue Dragon<br>
4 - Mastermind<br>
5 - Blue Dragon<br>
6 - Blue Dragon (Used to be NK)<br>
7 - Neutral 1<br>
8 - Neutral 2 / Blue Dragon<br>
9 - Blue Dragon<br>
10 - Prince<br>
11 - Sheriff<br>
12 - Paladin<br>
13 - Blue Dragon<br>
14 - Blue Dragon<br>
15 - Blue Dragon<br>
16 - Blue Dragon<br>
17 - Possible new slot? (If these are added then these 2 should possibly be starting Assassin and 2nd cult member)<br>
18 - Possible new slot?</p>
<p>Description: (Could be changed)</p>
<p>A battle of the factions! Which faction will be the first to fall, and which will come on top?</p>
<p>Stats:</p>
<p>Inq:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Now any role except for Neutrals can be a heretic. (And the King)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cannot attack anyone expect heretics.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If attacking a non heretic the attack will result a fail.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Cult Leader:</p>
<ul>
<li>Must now wait 2 days before they can use “Eradicate”.</li>
</ul>
<p>Assassin:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Must now wait 2 days before they can use “2 for 1”.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Will be forced to wait 1 day before they can use “Assassinate”.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Changes: (To “Cultseen”)</p>
<p>Cult Leader:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>When converting a Sheriff they will be unable to as they have a new passive “dedicated”.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When converting Paladin they must attempt to convert them twice. The first convert will count towards a pity convert.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Mastermind:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>When attempting to convert a Sheriff you must attempt to convert them twice.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Shen trying to convert the Paladin the Mastermind will be told “You could not convert them as there dedication to finding the Cult was to strong” because of there New passive “Dedication”.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The first convert will count towards a pity convert</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Sheriff:</p>
<ul>
<li>New passive “Dedicated” you will not be able to be converted by the Cult. You will have to have the Mastermind attempt to convert you twice to become a Marshal. You will not know if you had an attempted convert.</li>
</ul>
<p>Paladin:</p>
<ul>
<li>New passive “Dedication” when the Mastermind tries to convert you, you will not be converted. You will have to have the Cult Leader attempt to convert you twice to make you a Seeker. When a convert attempt is used on you, you will not know.</li>
</ul>
<p>Neutral Killing:</p>
<ul>
<li>Now 65% chance to be Blue Dragon and 35% chance to be NK. (New change lower)</li>
</ul>
<p>More changes: (To “Cultseen”)</p>
<p>Mastermind:</p>
<ul>
<li>As you start alone the first person you convert will gain the passive “Apprentice”.</li>
</ul>
<p>Cult Leader</p>
<ul>
<li>Starts alone.</li>
</ul>
<p>Neutral Killing:</p>
<ul>
<li>Removed</li>
</ul>
<p>Possible 18 player games? (2 extras can be BD)</p>
<p>Even more changes: (To “Cultseen”)</p>
<p>Neutral chance:<br>
-Now only 1-2 Neutrals per game. (Or should it stay 1-3?)</p>
<p>Please think about adding this mode just for fun. Also if you have any ideas/changes that would be great! This is also an mode I thought of on my own with some suggested changes. Feel free to make more suggestions!</p>
            <p><small>20 posts - 10 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cultseen-new-mode/85396">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cultseen-new-mode/85396</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 18:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85396</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cultseen-new-mode/85396.rss">Cultseen (new mode)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Butler needs to be nerfed</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[_torino]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s a lot to talk about with Butler so I’ll just mention the parts that I feel are most important</p>
<p>Butler is an extremely powerful BD, to the point of it being overpowered, it needs to be nerfed. Butler is almost on the level of the Prince in terms of power, because Butler:</p>
<ul>
<li>Is very easy to confirm (except in cult games)</li>
<li>Can deny kills + conversions just like Prince by occupying the killers/converters</li>
</ul>
<p>But in addition to this, Butler:</p>
<ul>
<li>Is non-unique, meaning up to three of this pseudo-Prince can spawn in a game</li>
<li>Can protect himself twice from almost all attacks/conversion by partying (unless they are sorc bombed, or the killer/converter is occ immune, which is quite rare)</li>
<li>Can confirm himself as a 100% BD King without a shadow of a doubt by poisoning the king + partying and stepping if the king was EK/neut/PK</li>
</ul>
<p>The problem I have with Butler’s direct occupation is that he can completely cripple evils, and there really isn’t anything that they can do about it, if Butler makes the decision to chain occupy them. Prince can do the same thing, but it’s balanced out by the fact that Prince is unique, and a number of other factors. Drunk at least has some counterplay, most killers can choose to not attack if they think they are going to get debauched/HHed, Sorceror can detonate, and Reaper can CoD to kill the Drunk.</p>
<p>Just kill/convert the Butler right? Well no, because if the Butler has outed his claim and drawn attention to himself then it’s likely that he’ll just decide to party. He can do this twice in a row if he wants, or in the most critical moments so that he can ensure his existence in the late game. Why should the (arguably) second most powerful BD member be able to protect himself from basically everything, twice?</p>
<p>And if the Butler thinks that King is evil, poisons him, parties, steps, and Prince/another Butler or Drunk is alive so it isn’t too much of a loss to king him, BD can have a 100% BD king - there is very, very little counterplay to this.</p>
<p>So basically, Butler has the power of Prince (minus the axes), plus 2 charges of “you can’t kill or convert me”, plus “i am 100% confirmed by poisoning EK, i partied elect me for king”. This power is also non-unique, good luck trying to get anything done as starting evil when there is 2 or more butlers + living prince (even worse if there is a Mercenary or other living offensives)</p>
<p>I think it’s ridiculous to give Butler this much power and I would like to see it nerfed slightly, somehow.</p>
            <p><small>45 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/butler-needs-to-be-nerfed/85385">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/butler-needs-to-be-nerfed/85385</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 08:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85385</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/butler-needs-to-be-nerfed/85385.rss">Butler needs to be nerfed</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>👳 The Monk &amp; The Hedonist (Royal Social)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another “guess someone else’s class” class.</p>
<h1>
<font color="steblue"><strong>The Monk</strong></font> (Social)</h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/sunrise_over_mountains.png?v=9" title=":sunrise_over_mountains:" class="emoji" alt=":sunrise_over_mountains:"> <strong>Ascending (Passive) -</strong> If you survive to the end, your team wins even if 1 opponent remains.</p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"> <strong>Royal Blood (Passive)</strong></p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/eye.png?v=9" title=":eye:" class="emoji" alt=":eye:"> <strong>Discern (Night) -</strong> Earn a charge of <font color="yellow"><strong>Patience</strong></font> by correctly identifying the exact class of a player who is either <font color="purple"><strong>Unseen</strong></font>, <font color="red"><strong>Cult</strong></font>, <font color="gray"><strong>Neutral Killer</strong></font>, <strong>Fool</strong>, <strong>Scorned</strong>, <strong>Inquisitor</strong>, or <strong>Sellsword</strong>.</p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/person_in_lotus_position.png?v=9" title=":person_in_lotus_position:" class="emoji" alt=":person_in_lotus_position:"> <strong>Meditate (Night) -</strong> Become death immune by consuming a charge of <font color="yellow"><strong>Patience</strong></font>, if you have any.</p>
<p><em>You will never be explicitly informed of how many <font color="yellow"><strong>Patience</strong></font> charges you have.  If you use <strong>Meditate</strong> but get attacked and have no <font color="yellow"><strong>Patience</strong></font>, you’ll simply die.</em></p>
<h1>
<font color="Purple"><strong>The Hedonist</strong></font> (Social)</h1>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"> <strong>Royal Blood (Passive)</strong></p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/pill.png?v=9" title=":pill:" class="emoji" alt=":pill:"> <strong>Chill Pill (Night) -</strong> <em>The opposite of <strong>Mind Warp</strong></em>. Target an investigative to make them see everyone as “not suspicious” and “social or support” and “matching everyone”.</p>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/lollipop.png?v=9" title=":lollipop:" class="emoji" alt=":lollipop:"> <strong>Dulcify (Day) -</strong> Force someone to cast their vote as pardon.</p>
            <p><small>7 posts - 5 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-monk-the-hedonist-royal-social/85359">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-monk-the-hedonist-royal-social/85359</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 05:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85359</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-monk-the-hedonist-royal-social/85359.rss">👳 The Monk &amp; The Hedonist (Royal Social)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The problem with &quot;Neuts In&quot; and &quot;Neuts Out&quot;</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arctic]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Having a preconceived idea of the way you are going to treat neutral classes <em>before even entering the game</em> is anti-wincon and unhealthy for the game. People need to treat each game separately with a clear and neutral state of mind. You can’t go holding grudges against alchemists because they didn’t side with you last game, and execute them N3 if you roll Prince just for the sake of it. Likewise, you can’t refuse to kill an alch that was found to be killer/offensive because you are ‘neuts in’. These mindsets that people have going into games simply contributes to the problems neutral classes already have related to kingmaking and the survivor wincon.</p>
<p>People need to evaluate each situation and consider what the most optimal play is when it comes to deciding what to do with a neutral. <strong>The choice you make in regards to a neutral should be made with the intention to further your wincon as far as possible</strong>. Imagine this from a BD perspective. If someone claims alchemist and there are no other neutral claims, with the current ‘D1 alch claim’ meta, chances are they are probably real. If they aren’t bombing people, there is not much of a reason to kill them at an early stage in the game when there are much bigger fish to fry. The situation is different to say, there are 3 neutral claims including an unconfirmed alchemist (3 neuts is not guaranteed), and many people are confirmed. Killing the alchemist when starting evils are still alive is perfectly fine and should not be considering ‘neuts out’ behaviour.</p>
<p>In a different situation, say there are multiple neutral claims already, and you have just upped someone on the second trial and they claim alchemist, and they are unconfirmed with no heals. Executing this would be completely viable to get information on which neutral claims are actually real.</p>
<p>Now consider a situation where it would be unideal to kill an Alchemist as BD. Last game, it came down to a 1v1 and the alchemist helped the other faction over you. This game, you are Prince, and N3 there are several more suspicious people with NK and starting evils alive, but you jail and execute the alchemist who was the only neutral claim and had not been bombing anyone. This is not a good play this early in the game when you need to be getting claims and eliminating the most suspicious slots.</p>
<p>I’ve used alchemist in a lot of these examples, but it applies for most neutrals (except sellsword really, since it is always anti-BD and you shouldn’t rely on the chance of neut king in any serious game). Consider it’s the second trial and the guy on stand claims scorned with a confirmed TB and confirmed frames - there is not much reason to keep this alive when no other trial can happen. For the most part scorned messes up investigative results and since they have confirmed frames, they have already been doing so. Keeping this alive would not further your wincon as BD.</p>
<p>Things get a little more complicated as an evil when you decide what to do with neutrals. Killing an alchemist before they have even healed/bombed is questionable. You miss the chance to see if they would end up siding evils and bombing prince for you later in the game. It becomes a different story once you’ve discovered that the alch (and merc, for this example) is sitting on the prince and clearly have no intention of helping you. In a cult game, if you were to consider the chance that you hit a merc stand guard when eradicating or converting, you may decide that it would be in your best interest to kill them as soon as possible. <em>This is fine, so long as the judgement arises based on this consideration, rather than just resulting from neuts out thinking because you dislike mercs.</em></p>
<p>Something we all need to understand is that it’s pretty much impossible to view neutral classes with complete objectivity when we have all won or lost games because of them. As much as we would like to act independently, our subconscious will always influence what we want to do with neutrals and our preconceived ideas about them. I’m just hoping that people can try to be less biased when it comes to deciding how to deal with neutrals. Ultimately, it’s a matter of judgement but a good way of doing this is considering which course of action is most likely to further your wincon, and act accordingly.</p>
<p>TL;DR - Don’t be “neuts in” or “neuts out” just for the sake of it. Consider each game to be a different situation and make your decision based on what helps you to reach your wincon the most.</p>
            <p><small>63 posts - 17 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-problem-with-neuts-in-and-neuts-out/85090">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-problem-with-neuts-in-and-neuts-out/85090</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 15:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85090</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-problem-with-neuts-in-and-neuts-out/85090.rss">The problem with &quot;Neuts In&quot; and &quot;Neuts Out&quot;</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Classes that are good where they&#39;re at</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We always talk about what classes need fixing but never talk about which classes are fine <img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
<p>I would like to share my personal list:</p>
<ul>
<li>Chronomancer</li>
<li>Court Wizard</li>
<li>Drunk</li>
<li>Hunter</li>
<li>Knight</li>
<li>Observer</li>
<li>Physician</li>
<li>Reaper</li>
<li>Possessor</li>
<li>Sorcerer</li>
<li>Inquisitor</li>
<li>Sellsword</li>
<li>Unseen converts</li>
<li>Cult converts</li>
<li>Cult Leader</li>
</ul>
<p>Actually, there are some things I don’t like.</p>
<p>Like decide fate killing king with arrow.</p>
<p>Exhume revealing NK and saying “alch” when NK is king.</p>
<p>Sorcerer not being able to use both day abilities in the same day (which makes the class the most frustrating to use).</p>
<p>But they are minor.</p>
            <p><small>110 posts - 14 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/classes-that-are-good-where-theyre-at/85084">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/classes-that-are-good-where-theyre-at/85084</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 20:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85084</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/classes-that-are-good-where-theyre-at/85084.rss">Classes that are good where they&#39;re at</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Rebalancing the game</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m hoping to make every class pretty equal here. So let’s begin:</p>
<h1><font color="gold">The King</font></h1>
<p>The main problems with this is its sheer political power and imbalance between the factions and starting/elected king. So:</p>
<ul>
<li>Make Royal Finger 2 uses.
<ul>
<li>This is for two reasons: 1. So EKs have a reason not to point and 2. To make it worthwhile to jump into king</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Give regular Safeguard three uses, and Improved Safeguard four (starting kings)
<ul>
<li>Good king is just a little more powerful on the protection front</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Add one-use regular Safeguard to elected Good kings, and give elected Evil kings three uses of Improved Safeguard
<ul>
<li>This is so there isn’t a huge gap between the power levels of elected and starting kings (big YIKES when your starting good king dies N1 to NK)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Forget formatting, this post is long</p>
<p>Remove poison from butler. It encourages gamethrowing and trolling, and isn’t particularly advantageous to exing the king. This ability also does not belong on butler, it isn’t an occupation ability.</p>
<p>Drunk is pretty balanced right now, so congrats.</p>
<p>Hunter should have unlimited uses of HM (why not?) and have bear not protect against conversion. This is because conversion should be more reliable (it already has a cooldown)</p>
<p>Knight is fine.</p>
<p>Prince. No one knows what to do with this. <a href="https://discord.com/channels/261525739617255424/340696386150596619/783377184390905877" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://discord.com/channels/261525739617255424/340696386150596619/783377184390905877</a> is my idea.</p>
<p>Sheriff and paladin should be merged and scout nipped. Smite will attack the MM, but not kill, but the conv will not succeed. This is because we don’t want someone to know whether it is unseen or cult, just like that.</p>
<p>Observer. I’m going to address this class’s problems later.</p>
<p>Maid should have themselves as a starter. This removes the problem of “start with NK” while also not introducing the problem of “confirmed non-NK” or “nothing to do N1”.</p>
<p>Princess is actually quite good. If people are going to complain, then make flirt reveal target’s <em>exact</em> class type, with the exception of S/I staying together, due to the fact that only MM and CL are Special.</p>
<p>Physician should be removed. Chronomancer is good, but it can’t shine due to healing. Also, exhume contributes to the NK problem.</p>
<p>Alchemist should be removed because it’s bad for the game as a whole.</p>
<p>Mystic: <a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mystic-illusionist-and-apostle-rework-new-nk/85055" class="inline-onebox">Mystic Illusionist, and Apostle Rework + New NK</a> or my prince suggestion works for this.</p>
<p>Noble should be removed. No matter its iteration, it’s OP, UP or unfun.</p>
<p>Magic missile should not count as visiting, in order to counter obs’s power.</p>
<p><s>Poss jump should get an extra use (refund mechanic stays)</s></p>
<p>Into the Shadows should apply to every unseen member.</p>
<p>Phew.</p>
            <p><small>47 posts - 11 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rebalancing-the-game/85070">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rebalancing-the-game/85070</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 21:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85070</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rebalancing-the-game/85070.rss">Rebalancing the game</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>2 converts in 1 night</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>                    <a href="https://i.imgur.com/kAtB1N7.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc" class="onebox">
            <img src="https://i.imgur.com/kAtB1N7.png" width="690" height="387">
          </a>

</p>
            <p><small>5 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/2-converts-in-1-night/85026">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/2-converts-in-1-night/85026</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 05:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85026</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/2-converts-in-1-night/85026.rss">2 converts in 1 night</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>🧙‍♀️ The Priestess &amp; Necromancer</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><font color="steblue"><strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/woman_mage.png?v=9" title=":woman_mage:" class="emoji" alt=":woman_mage:"> The Priestess</strong></font><br>
<strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/innocent.png?v=9" title=":innocent:" class="emoji" alt=":innocent:"> Resurrect</strong> (Night) - Use a dead player’s <strong>non-attacking</strong> night ability.  <font color="FFF333">Cannot use the same player more than once.</font></p>
<hr>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/woman_mage.png?v=9" title=":woman_mage:" class="emoji" alt=":woman_mage:"> The Necromancer</strong></font><br>
<strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/zombie.png?v=9" title=":zombie:" class="emoji" alt=":zombie:"> Reanimate</strong> (Night) - Use a dead player’s night ability.  <font color="FFF333">Cannot use the same player more than once.</font></p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-priestess-necromancer/85018">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-priestess-necromancer/85018</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 06:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85018</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-priestess-necromancer/85018.rss">🧙‍♀️ The Priestess &amp; Necromancer</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>🤺 The Templario</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1><font color="steblue"><strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/person_fencing.png?v=9" title=":person_fencing:" class="emoji" alt=":person_fencing:"> The Templar</strong></font></h1>
<p><strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:"> Protect</strong> (Night) - Protect a player from visits from any specific non-<font color="steblue"><strong>BD</strong></font> class.  <font color="FFF666">For example, if you protect someone from <font color="D72A28"><strong>The Apostle</strong></font>, and <font color="D72A28"><strong>The Apostle</strong></font> actually visits them, you will occupy and attack <font color="D72A28"><strong>The Apostle</strong></font>.  Cannot protect from the same class more than once.</font> <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crossed_swords.png?v=9" title=":crossed_swords:" class="emoji" alt=":crossed_swords:"> Duel</strong> (Night) - Identify a player’s non-<font color="steblue"><strong>BD</strong></font> class.  Kill them if you are correct, bypassing <strong>everything</strong>.  Otherwise, suicide.  <font color="FFF666">For example, if you duel someone you identify as <font color="purple"><strong>The Mastermind</strong></font> you will kill them.  But if they were <font color="steblue"><strong>The Sheriff</strong></font>, you’d die instead.</font> <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong></p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-templario/85017">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-templario/85017</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 06:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85017</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-templario/85017.rss">🤺 The Templario</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>🧞 mys / illu 2.0</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1><font color="steblue"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/genie.png?v=9" title=":genie:" class="emoji" alt=":genie:"> The Mystic</font></h1>
<p><strong>🗩 Telepathy</strong> (Day) - Trollbox someone except your message is automatically prefixed with the word <strong><font color="ED3407B"><span class="bbcode-u">Telepathy</span></font>:</strong>. <font color="FFFF80">This allows anyone to fake telepathy themselves, and anyone with <strong>Trollbox</strong> can fake telepathy anybody.</font> <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong><br>
<strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/innocent.png?v=9" title=":innocent:" class="emoji" alt=":innocent:"> Resurrect</strong> (Night) - Use a dead player’s <strong>non-attacking</strong> night ability.  <font color="FFF333">Cannot use the same player more than once.</font><br>
<strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crystal_ball.png?v=9" title=":crystal_ball:" class="emoji" alt=":crystal_ball:"> Seance</strong> (Night) - Target a dead player to learn what feedback they received the night they died. <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<h1><font color="purple"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/genie.png?v=9" title=":genie:" class="emoji" alt=":genie:"> The Illusionist</font></h1>
<p><strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/speech_balloon.png?v=9" title=":speech_balloon:" class="emoji" alt=":speech_balloon:"> Trollbox</strong> (Day) - Make someone say something. <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong><br>
<strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/man_juggling.png?v=9" title=":man_juggling:" class="emoji" alt=":man_juggling:"> Sleight of Hand</strong> (Night) - Permanently swap the name and number of any 2 players. <strong>(1 use)</strong><br>
<strong><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/zombie.png?v=9" title=":zombie:" class="emoji" alt=":zombie:"> Reanimate</strong> (Night) - Use a dead player’s night ability.  <font color="FFF333">Cannot use the same player more than once.</font></p>
            <p><small>5 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mys-illu-2-0/85016">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mys-illu-2-0/85016</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 05:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85016</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/mys-illu-2-0/85016.rss">🧞 mys / illu 2.0</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>King &amp; Butler &amp; Servant (Rework)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h1><font color="FFA000"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:"> The King</font></h1>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/fu.png?v=9" title=":fu:" class="emoji" alt=":fu:"> <strong>Royal Finger</strong> (Day) - Immediately put someone on trial. <strong>(1 use)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/balance_scale.png?v=9" title=":balance_scale:" class="emoji" alt=":balance_scale:"> <strong>Decide Fate</strong> (Day) - Immediately decide the outcome of the current trial. <strong>(1 use)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p>🗪 <strong>Conspire</strong> (Night) - Talk privately with a player. <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/clinking_glasses.png?v=9" title=":clinking_glasses:" class="emoji" alt=":clinking_glasses:"> <strong>To Your Health!</strong> (Night) - Toast the Butler and drink a chalice of choice wine.  Specifically, <strong>their</strong> choice of wine. <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<h1><font color="deepskyblue"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/older_man.png?v=9" title=":older_man:" class="emoji" alt=":older_man:"> The Butler</font></h1>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/grapes.png?v=9" title=":grapes:" class="emoji" alt=":grapes:"> <strong>Invigorating Wine</strong> (Day) - Grant <font color="FFA000"><strong>The King</strong></font> death immunity, if he chooses to partake. <strong>(3 uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/skull_and_crossbones.png?v=9" title=":skull_and_crossbones:" class="emoji" alt=":skull_and_crossbones:"> <strong>Poisoned Wine</strong> (Day) - Kill <font color="FFA000"><strong>The King</strong></font>, if he is so foolish as to partake. <strong>(1 use)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/wine_glass.png?v=9" title=":wine_glass:" class="emoji" alt=":wine_glass:"> <strong>Serve Wine</strong> (Night) - Occupy a player tonight with wine. <font color="FFFF80">Cannot target the same player 2 nights in a row.</font> <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/champagne.png?v=9" title=":champagne:" class="emoji" alt=":champagne:"> <strong>Concentrated Wine</strong> (Night) - Throw a party, occupying everyone that targets you. <strong>(2 uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<h1><font color="purple"><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/older_man.png?v=9" title=":older_man:" class="emoji" alt=":older_man:"> The Servant</font></h1>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/dizzy_face.png?v=9" title=":dizzy_face:" class="emoji" alt=":dizzy_face:"> <strong>Intoxicating Wine</strong> (Day) - Render <font color="FFA000"><strong>The King</strong></font> so drunk that he is unable to use his day abilities, if he chooses to drink up. <strong>(3 uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/skull_and_crossbones.png?v=9" title=":skull_and_crossbones:" class="emoji" alt=":skull_and_crossbones:"> <strong>Poisoned Wine</strong> (Day) - Kill <font color="FFA000"><strong>The King</strong></font>, if he is so foolish as to partake. <strong>(1 use)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/wine_glass.png?v=9" title=":wine_glass:" class="emoji" alt=":wine_glass:"> <strong>Serve Wine</strong> (Night) - Occupy a player tonight with wine. <font color="FFFF80">Cannot target the same player 2 nights in a row.</font> <strong>(Infinite uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/images/emoji/twitter/champagne.png?v=9" title=":champagne:" class="emoji" alt=":champagne:"> <strong>Concentrated Wine</strong> (Night) - Throw a party, occupying everyone that targets you. <strong>(2 uses)</strong></p>
<hr>
            <p><small>11 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/king-butler-servant-rework/85009">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/king-butler-servant-rework/85009</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 09:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85009</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/king-butler-servant-rework/85009.rss">King &amp; Butler &amp; Servant (Rework)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Templar &amp; King Revamp &amp; Butler Revamp</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Templar</strong></p>
<p>Has a single night ability that works exactly like <strong>Defile</strong> except instead of defiling the target:</p>
<ul>
<li>If he selects their class, he attacks them</li>
<li>If he selects the wrong class, he suicides</li>
<li>Is infinite use and usable <strong>N1</strong>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Advantages over <strong>Coldsteel</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>Can’t kill Blue Dragon</li>
<li>Can’t confirm Blue Dragon</li>
</ul>
<p>I did post this once before long ago.  Of course Blue Dragon classes aren’t selectable.</p>
<h1>King v4.34.7 Beta</h1>
<p>Night ability that replaces <strong>Allies</strong> on Evil King and <strong>Safeguard</strong> on Good King:</p>
<h1><strong>Conspire</strong></h1>
<p>Allow private whispers between yourself and the target player tomorrow with the <code>/c</code> command.</p>
<p>Benefit of replacing Allies on Evil King:</p>
<ul>
<li>In the endgame Blue Dragon can claim Unseen to confuse Evil King.  You can’t do this currently because he already knows who his allies are.</li>
</ul>
<h1>Butler Rework</h1>
<p>Replace <strong>Poison Wine</strong> with <strong>Poison Wine</strong>, which kills the Butler without harming the King.</p>
<p>The info for this ability will not change so that Butlers will eventually learn through trial and error that clicking this button isn’t going to hurt anyone but themselves.</p>
<p>If they don’t learn by the 13th use of <strong>Poison Wine</strong> the window closes and Throne of Lies uninstalls itself from their machine then bluescreens their computer permanenly.</p>
            <p><small>7 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/templar-king-revamp-butler-revamp/84695">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/templar-king-revamp-butler-revamp/84695</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 01:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-84695</guid>
          <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/templar-king-revamp-butler-revamp/84695.rss">Templar &amp; King Revamp &amp; Butler Revamp</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
