<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Scouts, Spy&#39;s and infiltration</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779</link>
    <description>Contrary to popular belief the Blue Dragon faction values secrecy as much if not more so than the Unseen. Much of the kingdom is run by a secret network of scouts and spy&#39;s designed to keep Information out of the wrong hands.

Meny kingdoms that didn&#39;t do this would have their most important members assassinated immediately. An Unseen with no reason to approach the courts at all is a terrifying thing indeed. The spy network stops this because attempts to get in from the outside are thwarted by a lack of information of anyone.

The network&#39;s actualy existence is not nearly as much of a secret. They are called when a new king steps up to verify his legitimacy to the throne. Meny official&#39;s work directly with the network. The Nobles used them as their ears and the sheriff as their eyes. The Princess convays commands and Information through her wisp (those not in the network don&#39;t recognize it) Other responsibilities include keeping track of who dies in the Castle and revealing their identity now that descriteness is unnecessary. The Herbalist and Illusionist are among the few along with the Scorned, Possessor and Fool who can consistently fool them.

So dispite all of this how did the Unseen get in there? Well having been driven out of another kingdom using a similar idea they got an idea to exploit the system they set up. The Mastermind went to the Castle to meet directly with the king, the one man with full control over the Spy network. The plan was to convert him but Incase negotiations turned sour his trusty Assassin was on standby looking for places the spy&#39;s couldn&#39;t find them and learning the ways to move around without being seen. 

The negotiations went well at first. Getting documents explaining his presence for example and setting up the private meetings themselves was easy enough. The Mastermind never expected him to be as unwilling to use the Spy network as he was, the king would not be wavering any time soon. luckily the assassin had found a suitable meeting location and a way to get there without being seen. The next day the King was found dead.

This was a problem but the line of succession was clear. The Oldest son of the old king stepped up uncontested. Unlike the previous king however the Mastermind had no history with him as the Older Prince had very little relationships with even his own younger brother who maintained the Dungeons. One thing he did know is that he was much harsher than his father and just as unwavering. When he went to talk to the new king he found his room was locked. The Spy&#39;s were staying away from him as he had his own Private guard keep Intruders out. 

Things only got worse when the court was calling for blood. An emergency meeting was held after the Kings funeral. The Castle went on lockdown letting no one in or out. The famed Scout network made damn sure to enforce it.

With no way in or out the Mastermind had no choice but to Sabatoge the meetings. The Anonymous nature of the members was coming back to bite them as they had no idea who was who and the Spy&#39;s weren&#39;t revealing much during the lockdown. 

So will paranoia get the Blue Dragon killed or will clever Investigators reveal what happened that night?

**Ever wondered why no one knows who the royals are? Or why the King doesn&#39;t know who the Prince is? Or why the Unseen even bothers with showing up during the day at all? Now you know!**</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 19:38:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Scouts, Spy&#39;s and infiltration</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This was my first lore Suggestion and is supposed to cover everything done behind the scenes in game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 19:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39779-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Scouts, Spy&#39;s and infiltration</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Scouts, Spy&#39;s and infiltration</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Contrary to popular belief the Blue Dragon faction values secrecy as much if not more so than the Unseen. Much of the kingdom is run by a secret network of scouts and spy’s designed to keep Information out of the wrong hands.</p>
<p>Meny kingdoms that didn’t do this would have their most important members assassinated immediately. An Unseen with no reason to approach the courts at all is a terrifying thing indeed. The spy network stops this because attempts to get in from the outside are thwarted by a lack of information of anyone.</p>
<p>The network’s actualy existence is not nearly as much of a secret. They are called when a new king steps up to verify his legitimacy to the throne. Meny official’s work directly with the network. The Nobles used them as their ears and the sheriff as their eyes. The Princess convays commands and Information through her wisp (those not in the network don’t recognize it) Other responsibilities include keeping track of who dies in the Castle and revealing their identity now that descriteness is unnecessary. The Herbalist and Illusionist are among the few along with the Scorned, Possessor and Fool who can consistently fool them.</p>
<p>So dispite all of this how did the Unseen get in there? Well having been driven out of another kingdom using a similar idea they got an idea to exploit the system they set up. The Mastermind went to the Castle to meet directly with the king, the one man with full control over the Spy network. The plan was to convert him but Incase negotiations turned sour his trusty Assassin was on standby looking for places the spy’s couldn’t find them and learning the ways to move around without being seen.</p>
<p>The negotiations went well at first. Getting documents explaining his presence for example and setting up the private meetings themselves was easy enough. The Mastermind never expected him to be as unwilling to use the Spy network as he was, the king would not be wavering any time soon. luckily the assassin had found a suitable meeting location and a way to get there without being seen. The next day the King was found dead.</p>
<p>This was a problem but the line of succession was clear. The Oldest son of the old king stepped up uncontested. Unlike the previous king however the Mastermind had no history with him as the Older Prince had very little relationships with even his own younger brother who maintained the Dungeons. One thing he did know is that he was much harsher than his father and just as unwavering. When he went to talk to the new king he found his room was locked. The Spy’s were staying away from him as he had his own Private guard keep Intruders out.</p>
<p>Things only got worse when the court was calling for blood. An emergency meeting was held after the Kings funeral. The Castle went on lockdown letting no one in or out. The famed Scout network made damn sure to enforce it.</p>
<p>With no way in or out the Mastermind had no choice but to Sabatoge the meetings. The Anonymous nature of the members was coming back to bite them as they had no idea who was who and the Spy’s weren’t revealing much during the lockdown.</p>
<p>So will paranoia get the Blue Dragon killed or will clever Investigators reveal what happened that night?</p>
<p><strong>Ever wondered why no one knows who the royals are? Or why the King doesn’t know who the Prince is? Or why the Unseen even bothers with showing up during the day at all? Now you know!</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 19:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39779-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-scouts-spys-and-infiltration/39779.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Scouts, Spy&#39;s and infiltration</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
