<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847</link>
    <description>Fake Journal Guide
=
This Guide will help people lie better for the  [color=red]&quot;Evil&quot;[/color] Classes, and a second section on lying as Neutral Classes.


- Never know what to claim as a &quot;Evil&quot; Class? (Unseen/ Cult) 
- Keep getting executed by the court/ Prince?
- Fear no more! 

**Classes to fake ranked from worst to best** 
Some classes you should never do and you will instantly die, others might let you live another day or two, and some are possible to be totally convincing.

**Disclaimer**
This is my opinion and I have put a lot of time/ thought into this, I have found success with these ideas and am always looking to improve my lies as well. I hope this helps gives beginners a kick start and veterans good ideas to try out for themselves as well.

**Beginner**
Anything written in &quot;[color=gold]Gold Writing[/color]&quot; is a good claim for a beginner just starting off their lying

[color=purple]**Unseen**[/color] and [color=red]Cult[/color]
=
If you start off as a Blue Dragon and get converted in the middle of the game, it is not always a good idea to keep that classes claim. If you have already claimed publicly what your class is, then you obviously have to stick with it. Many classes that get converted do not keep the same qualities as their Blue Dragon equivalent. I will state the classes that you SHOULD stick to the same as also.


Classes to NEVER CLAIM:
-
[color=Blue]Hunter[/color]: Never claim this 
- Bleeding is a unique mechanic to the hunter so if this never occurs in a game, it would be impossible for people to believe you.
- Poacher (converted Hunter) should still NOT claim this, unless you confirm yourself with bleeding someone already as a real hunter before you were converted.

[color=Blue]Prince[/color]: Never claim this
- This isn&#39;t even a short term claim, you will either get countered claimed (CC) by the Prince... or more than likely jailed and executed the following day by the real Prince.

Classes to ONLY claim if you were converted:
-
[color=Blue]Drunk[/color]: Only claim if you were a Drunk that turned into Alcoholic/ Invoker

- There are only 3 classes that can &quot;redirect&quot; people and you should never claim this if you cant do that action.

[color=Blue]Noble[/color]: Only claim if you were a Noble turned into Aristocrat
- No other class in the game can read whispers sent by everyone. 

[color=Blue]Butler[/color]: Only claim if you are a role that can still occupy people
- Servant/ Invoker/ Fool/ Poacher
- Do not claim a role blocker if you can not role block people yourself, your journal will not be accurate and if nobody says they were role blocked/ backs you up, you are screwed.

[color=Blue]Psychic[/color]: Only claim if you were a Psychic that got turned into Illusionist
- Illusionists still have the same day abilities to confirm themselves, but people still would think that you could be converted
- You can no longer &quot;Mind Link&quot; to confirm that you are BD (Blue Dragon) 
- If you are converted make sure you keep your journal going, just only mind link people that turn out to be dead later, but this is hard to do. 

Classes to claim for SHORT TERM survival/ last resort
-
These work but only for a short period of time, since you will either be counter claimed, or be asked to prove yourself and you cant.

[color=Blue]Sheriff / Paladin[/color]: With the latest patch (9.13) the Sheriff and Paladin are both convertible now. I have had only a small handful of gameplay with this huge change, so I will need more time before journal advice can be given. This also will change based on if there can be 2 or if they are unique still?
- Still experimenting with new update, but here is a test claim of Paladin I did in a game
- I was Cult Leader and claimed Paladin, I made a journal of people who were &quot;not suspicious&quot;. As a Cult is is very easy to make a perfect Paladin role... because you literally know who is &quot;ns&quot; and who is Cult. This worked very well actually and there ended up not even being a Paladin in the game. Everyone was shocked when the proclaimed Paladin turned out to be the Cult Leader.

[color=Blue]Physician[/color]: Although this can save you in the short term, you will need to always heal/cure poisons and bleeds in order to be confirmed as it is a suspicious class.
- **How to Make Journal:**  Mainly make a log of healing random people at first, if there are any confirmed BD, or people who were poisoned and healed from it, also edit your journal to where you say that YOU were the one who healed those people. Also healing a confirmed BD makes it look more believable. If you have time, write why you haven&#39;t revived yet, if you are dealing with smart BD
- Will fall apart completely if someone dies of poison and is not healed. Use this claim with care.

BEST Classes to Fake
-
These are the classes (from worst to best) that you need to get good at writing journals for. Anyone can write journals for these classes, and it takes skill to make them look &quot;legit&quot;. I will talk more in the next section about Journal Editing throughout the game.

[color=gold]**Good Beginner Claim**[/color]
[color=blue]Knight[/color]: Very easy to claim, but also the weakest of the &quot;good claims&quot;

-  **How to Make Journal:** Just fill your journal up with &quot;guarded #&quot; for every night (as long as you don&#39;t say you guard someone that died that night, super easy
- Since its so easy to make, its also going to look suspicious since its probably the #1 Assassin claim. 
- Adding to the assassin claim, if you find a person immune to death, it might be good to claim you cold steeled them and they were immune to confirm yourself as a &quot;true&quot; Knight.
- Knight claim is better than no claim, once you get good at this start working on others.

[color=Blue]Court Wizard[/color]: empower and tornado do not tell the target that the ability was used on them... but it does tell anyone visiting them that they were swapped by something. The only thing you have to be careful of is making sure you didn&#39;t say that you swap someone that was visited.
- **How to Make Journal:** Just say that you empowered random people (or confirmed BD), but just make sure you won&#39;t be executed, try to put in a swap that you have found out by your visits.
- Empowering a target has a different effect on different class types. So anyone that tries to kill your target will go through empower (except when empowering an offensive class type) and anyone who tries to convert your target will still go through (unless empowering a social class type). So in your journal, you can say that you empowered a dead person... but be careful of what classes they are or you will be executed for lying.
- Always the chance that someone did an action that could prove your empower wrong.
- Overall, decent class to fake claim, but semi risky.



[color=Blue]Observer[/color]: Following/ Peeking are not detectable and if you put enough real information in your journal nobody will be able to tell the difference.
- **How to Make Journal:** If people start coming forward that they did something or visited whoever, USE THAT in your journal and write it down for that night. If you have good &quot;fake&quot; information for early nights, just use those &quot;Peek&quot; claims for later on in the game.
- You can use your evil teammates visiting information in your journal as long as they are already dead/ you don&#39;t out them.
- Put information about peoples class (Peek) in your will since that is the easiest information to get correct. If you are an &quot;Evil&quot; then you can pretty much say that you Peeked at ANYONE else and say they are BD. (maybe an Alch or Merc will call you out, but not likely)
- Difficult to gather enough correct information on some quieter/ slower games, but if done right, very believable.
- The mastermind has 3 nights of usual grace from the sheriff, so if you are claiming this as mastermind get as much info as possible.

[color=Blue]Princess[/color]: a risky class to claim. Getting peoples class types is very simple to &quot;fake&quot; especially as the game goes on and people start coming out with what they are.
- **How to Make Journal:** attempt to delay BD and try to find how people act. If they whispers to the king a decent amount, it may mean they have info, like an investigative class. However, from the first nights you will usually be wrong in your &quot;flirts&quot;. How I handle this is to constantly go back and move information around if I need to. the new wisp is much harder to prove, but if you fake finding a killer/offensive class, you could say you wisped them and they did not attack.
- Flirt gives the following results: Killer/ Offensive.... Support/ Social... Special/ Investigative
- Very easy to fill in gaps in journal with dead people and people who are your evil teammates (don&#39;t out your MM/ CL as Special/ Invest), although people will get suspicious of all dead checks.
- Your journal should be made up of mostly flirting (which is better information anyway)
- Cover will be blown if they ask you to step up for king as royalty and you cant

Claiming Neutral Roles as  &quot;Evil&quot; Classes
-
This is always a dangerous thing to do... since some people who play the game kill all neutrals on sight. If things are looking grim for the BD, they will be less likely to hang the neutrals. (except Reaper and Possessor) I have had some fun/ successful times with these.

**Alchemist:** (can only claim this if you are a killing role) You could sell that you are an alchemist (or that there is one in the game) by killing someone early game with a death note that has a dagger of some kind on it... then later drawing a new one with a vial of poison and a message saying &quot;Alch working for BD&quot; or something like that. Most alchemists will often out themselves early so they are not dealt with.
- Make sure the target you &quot;fake kill&quot; as the Alchemist is quiet or someone who seemed suspicious.
- Will still fall appart if you need to heal someone and cant

**Mercenary:** This class is very risky, not to mention serves no purpose to BD, so play this cautiously.
- VERY risky to do, but if you can somehow prevent visitors it can be done.
- Will fall apart if you cannot successfully guard and prevent something.

**Scorned:** this is a bad claim now since scorned has the option to leave with no penalty after winning.

[color=grey]Neutral Classes[/color]
=
These classes all play very different from one another. I will probably do another guide in the future on more in depth guides on how to play each class. This will be more so for if you want to lie in your journal/ claim that you are something else. 

[color=grey]**Alchemist**[/color]: As stated above, you could claim that you truly are an Alchemist but this can be dangerous. 
- If you can get an early game Evil kill the BD will be far more likely to befriend you. Again, I would make sure your death note stands out as an Alchemist type death note, unless you want to play the lay low style of Alch.
- Winning with the Evils is also possible if you can get a late game BD kill off, and establish a majority with the Evils.
- With new update, the Alch might want to lay low and use his abilities to have night immunity to get into the back half of the game, then try siding with whoever the current &quot;winning team&quot; is. 
 

[color=grey]**Mercenary**[/color]: Some people kill on sight, and some people don&#39;t care at all about a Merc in the game. I usually do claim Merc in the game but will wait till mid game or so before I come out with that info. Very hard to confirm that you are Merc because BD will usually putyour guard on someone, and letting someone confirm your guard.
- Knight is easy claim, but a Knight claim can be more suspicious than Merc sometimes.

[color=grey]**Scorned**[/color]: I will be making a Scorned/ Fool guide soon. As scorned I usually always claim Sheriff/ Paladin/ Observer. These classes have &quot;instant accusal information&quot; and if you time it right, with a good fake journal, you can get an easy win. Whichever of your two targets is the most suspicious, throw them under the bus hard and commit to it. 
- Can also claim that you are whatever one of your targets is also, if they are a unique role, so always have a fake Sheriff/ Paladin journal on hand.
- When I play Scorned I usually have multiple journals that I fill out every night so I have it on hand instantly when one of the 2 targets of mine looks suspicious.

[color=grey]**Fool**[/color]: Journal for this class is very different, you almost want it to be fishy and not possible. You could claim anything as long as you purposefully make it not 100% accurate. I will say that I always have a LEGIT butler journal ready for if I get jailed, so I don&#39;t die at night to Prince.
- Example of a purposefully flawed journal: Princess journal that says &quot;Killer / Support&quot;... since that is not a possible feedback you get from the Flirt ability, I have gotten hung purely from that &quot;on purpose mistake&quot;
- Make sure to come out early in the day if you are going to &quot;go for the hanging&quot; that day. You don&#39;t want people to still be indecisive and then not hang you... then you get jailed and die from being so suspicious the day before.
- Fool is not as much about your journal, so I will save the rest of the discussion for the Neutral Guide.

[color=grey]**Reaper**[/color]: Any class that you could claim in the above section as an Assassin would work for the Reaper.
- Knight/ Merc/ Alch/ or even other classes like Obs/ Princess could work too (just harder since you have less info)

[color=grey]**Possessor**[/color]: Journal play should be very advanced and you&#39;d have to keep track of what class everyone is saying they are and keep up to date with their journals once you hop into their body. I have played SO many games since the Possessor rework and only got him once... and died night one to a YOLO Knight Cold Steel... sigh.
- Keep track of others classes and check their journals once you are in their body

The End
-
You have made it through this LONG Journal Faking guide I had fun making it and I hope this helps some people or inspires new ideas. I would love to hear what the community thinks and I am always trying to improve my own lying game as well. The best way to get better is to collaborate with others. See ya in the Throne Room!


**Inspiration**
Moleland made a guide 5 months ago that helped me a lot, so I figure I&#39;d give back the same. 


[color=red]-Alkander[/color]
=</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 23:33:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 15:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GRIZLEDORF]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The cult leader can bleed. Bleeding is not unique to Hunters. I find Hunter a decent claim, there’s only one of them, they’re sort of rare and can’t be occupied.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 23:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hippolytus" data-post="26" data-topic="2847" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hippolytus/40/34066_2.png" class="avatar"> Hippolytus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This guide said claiming Priest is a good idea for beginners so I did it yesterday and got hung immediately.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>New note that should be added, always check patch notes for any changes to classes before claiming them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 17:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hippolytus" data-post="26" data-topic="2847" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/hippolytus/40/34066_2.png" class="avatar"> Hippolytus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This guide said claiming Priest is a good idea for beginners so I did it yesterday and got hung immediately.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fool strats <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 16:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Rip <a class="mention" href="/u/alkander">@Alkander</a>…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 14:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Icibalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mad a few quick edits.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 17:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This guide said claiming Priest is a good idea for beginners so I did it yesterday and got hung immediately.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 16:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That is true. But if you want to do that then you need someone to claim CW on you. I guess you could get one of the other unseen to do it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 11:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just say a court wizard or a drunk did for you . All stories have weakness . With butler you are killer/offensive but as mm you will show as special/investigative .<br>
There’s no perfect claim just try and kill anyone that might be able to piss on your fireworks asap .</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 10:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Navi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Great guide <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Also, am a grammar/spelling freak. Went through and made minor changes to spelling and added apostrophes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 05:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The problem is that you have Occupy immunity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 14:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="18" data-topic="2847">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(you can claim it as fool, but it leads tot he outcome of not being lynched or being suspected as fool)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, as fool you don’t need to claim to RB the same people you actually rbed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 01:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I fake claim princess all the time on mm . why would butler be the only option ?<br>
I have claimed Sheriff Paladin and Butler  too .<br>
Each has weakness but all are fairly easy to tell a half decent story</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 14:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can claim it as a servant.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 23:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>butler claim fails for all evils but invoker (you can claim it as fool, but it leads tot he outcome of not being lynched or being suspected as fool)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 23:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m just saying that the Butler claim fails faster than the Hunter claim. I wouldn’t recommend either.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 21:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zarlath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Alkander" data-post="1" data-topic="2847">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/alkander/40/1403_2.png" class="avatar"> Alkander:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hunter: Never claim this</p>
<p>Bleeding is a unique mechanic to the hunter so if this never occurs in a game, it would be impossible for people to believe you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with OP on that. The hunter claim can fall really quick.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 20:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually it’s hunter. You can’t fake butler or hunter but a hunter has a reason to do nothing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 20:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zarlath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is the Butler your only legit Fake Journal choice when you’re the Mastermind?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 20:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="12" data-topic="2847">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If it can work for an actual scorned, maybe it can work for an evil.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What’s the difference?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 22:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Other claim: claim scorned already won.</p>
<p>I haven’t seen this work for an evil, <strong>but</strong> I have seen BD not execute a scorned that had 1 target left. Of course, that target wanted to kill them. After the target died, the entire court allowed them to become neutral king (and in the end they made the deciding guard that won BD the game)</p>
<p>If it can work for an actual scorned, maybe it can work for an evil.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 12:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“I am i42-Xblade, don’t lynch me1!1111!”</p>
<h6>/s</h6>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 06:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alternative fake claim: Claim a popular person in the community and maybe you will live.<br>
Has never worked for me, personally, but still <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 05:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alkander]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I will make an update on it within the next few hours!<br>
Didnt think about that!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-Admin" data-username="í42-Xblade" data-post="3" data-topic="2847">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/%C3%AD42-xblade/40/2827_2.png" class="avatar"> í42-Xblade:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Pinned, and turned into a “Wiki Post” (anyone can edit)!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="7" data-topic="2847">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this is outdated</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>By all means, update it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2847-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/wiki-fake-journal-guided/2847.rss">[Wiki] Fake Journal Guided</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
