<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Priest (Co-written with Fadeblade)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-priest-co-written-with-fadeblade/585</link>
    <description>Lore Link: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Priest

Lore Subject: The Church of Eternal Renewal (Name subject to change)

Lore: An entry in the grand library.

An advantage the Blue dragon hold over their adversaries is an affinity with the world around them. Magic and science find their way into the minds of those who would follow the righteous path but those with faith for a long time found themselves at a loss. In a world corrupted by Mithras and his deception to follow a god based in reality or myth can lead to the same dark premise. Thus arose the priest one day blessed with the power to return those to life. Confused the people claimed sacrilege determining the corruption of Mithras to have dropped the pretence of stealth. The priests prepared revealed their powers source to the public. A small bird of the crimson flame designated a phoenix by itself made a rousing speech to the people. It proclaimed itself to have wisdom of eternity and have lived as long reviving itself from it&#39;s own ashes. Learned speech through sheer force of will over eons it proclaimed it&#39;s powers were based in nothing other than pacifism. As it stands he created the church of eternal renewal using his own body as a catalyst for the chosen members. A feather pressed against the heart embodies the host with a special type of soul doted a &quot;Tabula rasa&quot; That can merge with the memories still harboured in a human body to refresh it and bring a person to life at the expense of the raw power stored within the priest. Priests as such do not serve a god but the church with phoenix as master. Their holy mission is simply to extend the potential of humanity whatever way they can be it through good works, positivism or revival. &quot;The world must be saved from corruption but we cannot corrupt ourselves in the process&quot; -Priest motto

Commets and explanation: So me and Fadeblade came up with this concept in the discord a while back deciding on how a priest would work without gods. We decided on a superior being rather than a god and decided to go with a phoenix based on it&#39;s lore being steeped in reviving itself from death. I wrote this while I had the flu so feel free to make comments on what to alter.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 20:18:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-priest-co-written-with-fadeblade/585.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Priest (Co-written with Fadeblade)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore Link: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Priest" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Priest</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: The Church of Eternal Renewal (Name subject to change)</p>
<p>Lore: An entry in the grand library.</p>
<p>An advantage the Blue dragon hold over their adversaries is an affinity with the world around them. Magic and science find their way into the minds of those who would follow the righteous path but those with faith for a long time found themselves at a loss. In a world corrupted by Mithras and his deception to follow a god based in reality or myth can lead to the same dark premise. Thus arose the priest one day blessed with the power to return those to life. Confused the people claimed sacrilege determining the corruption of Mithras to have dropped the pretence of stealth. The priests prepared revealed their powers source to the public. A small bird of the crimson flame designated a phoenix by itself made a rousing speech to the people. It proclaimed itself to have wisdom of eternity and have lived as long reviving itself from it’s own ashes. Learned speech through sheer force of will over eons it proclaimed it’s powers were based in nothing other than pacifism. As it stands he created the church of eternal renewal using his own body as a catalyst for the chosen members. A feather pressed against the heart embodies the host with a special type of soul doted a “Tabula rasa” That can merge with the memories still harboured in a human body to refresh it and bring a person to life at the expense of the raw power stored within the priest. Priests as such do not serve a god but the church with phoenix as master. Their holy mission is simply to extend the potential of humanity whatever way they can be it through good works, positivism or revival. “The world must be saved from corruption but we cannot corrupt ourselves in the process” -Priest motto</p>
<p>Commets and explanation: So me and Fadeblade came up with this concept in the discord a while back deciding on how a priest would work without gods. We decided on a superior being rather than a god and decided to go with a phoenix based on it’s lore being steeped in reviving itself from death. I wrote this while I had the flu so feel free to make comments on what to alter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-priest-co-written-with-fadeblade/585/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-priest-co-written-with-fadeblade/585/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-585-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-priest-co-written-with-fadeblade/585.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Priest (Co-written with Fadeblade)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
