<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alchemist rework</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399</link>
    <description>I think currently alchemist has some problems since they usually side with BD and only change sides when they are losing. It also leads to some unfun games where alchemist outs d1 and everyone leaves them alone for the whole game. With these changes, the alch should be more &quot;neutral&quot; and will make alchemists think twice before outing themselves early.

**The Alchemist**
**Coagulate (Passive)** - You are immune to bleeding and nightshade poison. 
**Stoneskin potion (Day ability)** - You are immune to death the following night. 2 uses.
**Amethyst Potion (Day ability)** - Poison a player with Nightshade. They will die in 2 days unless healed. 0 uses.
**Crimson potion (Night ability)** - Heal a target player, preventing their death and curing any poison or bleeding. Healing a player that was bleeding or poisoned will give you a use of Amethyst potion. Unlimited uses.
**Emerald potion (Night ability)** - Poisons a target player with a lethal dosage, instantly killing them. If you successfully kill a player you will gain 1 use of Stoneskin potion. 2 uses.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 05:53:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aquillion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just had an idea to fix this (<span class="bbcode-i">and</span> the confirmability of Physicians) by adding a new role.  They’d be called Hag or something along that line, a witchy-type, with the Witchgoal (live to see the BD lose.)</p>
<p>Their primary ability would be False Cure.  It acts as a heal, but anyone successfully healed by it dies the next night, unless you heal them again.  (<span class="bbcode-i">Only</span> you can keep them alive.  Other heals cannot.)  They would probably need a little more than that to be viable, but that would be the main purpose of the role.</p>
<p>The message the victim receives when they die to a Hag’s False Cure is the generic “you were attacked” message; this prevents them from outing the Hag to the Psychic.</p>
<p>There’s a lot of intricacies to this that aren’t immediately obvious.  One very important thing is that if you False Cure someone who has been poisoned, they will die the next night <span class="bbcode-i">even if they’re also healed by someone else</span>.  In other words, if there’s another healer claim, you can frame them as a Hag by curing someone who was poisoned / bled and not saying anything yourself; they’ll very likely get lynched in your place when the victim dies the next night.  Even if you don’t go through with this, a Hag can cancel out an actual healer.</p>
<p>(Remember that at least one healer is guaranteed, and poison / bleeding is guaranteed as well via the Assassin / Cult Leader.)</p>
<p>If almost completely canceling out other healers is too powerful, the Hag could be balanced by letting a healer save the person the next night.  (Of course, you can False Cure them the next night, and there’s no easy way for the court to determine who the healer is and who the Hag is.)</p>
<p>If that’s <span class="bbcode-i">still</span> too powerful, I suppose it could just not take effect if someone else healed them at the same time you did.  That would make the role much less fun, but would avoid the danger of directly countering healers.</p>
<p>Another option is to let a Hag heal as normal, but give them a “Collect the Price” night ability that unstoppably kills everyone they’ve successfully healed, so they can choose when they want to revoke their false cure.</p>
<p>(Alternatively, I suppose we could give False Cure to the Herbalist, but they don’t show up enough for it to be a big deal in the meta, whereas the existence of a Hag would discredit healer claims in the same way that a .)</p>
<p>Granted, some people might object to the killer-ish feeling of what’s supposed to be a non-killer role, but remember, they can only kill people who would have died earlier anyway without their intervention (and possibly negate some healers in the process, depending on the implementation), so their practical purpose is to fake a healer claim by “saving” people only temporarily, and to make all other healers a bit more suspicious by extension.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 05:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We shouldn’t have methods at all to out neutrals. Observer Peak should be turned into a Sheriff/Pally check.</p>
<p>And if we make Merc guards silent, that’s something to claim when you’re immune.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 19:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There needs to be a BD-sided neutral, so outed neutrals/death immunes can claim something at least. Every other neutral except inquisitor is scum-sided, so why is it so bad that alchemist is BD-sided? I must say I do like the twist on emerald potion/stoneskin.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He still has 4 stoneskins but he needs to bomb people to gain the other 2. He can still be helpful for the bd but this should make him a bit more harmful which I think makes him more “neutral”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do want Alch to be less BD sided.</p>
<p>Reducing Stoneskin doesn’t help, though.</p>
<p>It still has full heals, so it’s still an asset.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alch could be more useful to the bd than before if they want. They can redirect poison from the bd to potential scum</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lily]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="psychoneirik" data-post="1" data-topic="52399">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/psychoneirik/40/12950_2.png" class="avatar"> psychoneirik:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think currently alchemist has some problems since they usually side with BD</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well duh the Blue Dragon has the most members so Alchs side with them to not get executed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 17:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>and now all alchs will die no matter what <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 17:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Alchemist rework</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think currently alchemist has some problems since they usually side with BD and only change sides when they are losing. It also leads to some unfun games where alchemist outs d1 and everyone leaves them alone for the whole game. With these changes, the alch should be more “neutral” and will make alchemists think twice before outing themselves early.</p>
<p><strong>The Alchemist</strong><br>
<strong>Coagulate (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to bleeding and nightshade poison.<br>
<strong>Stoneskin potion (Day ability)</strong> - You are immune to death the following night. 2 uses.<br>
<strong>Amethyst Potion (Day ability)</strong> - Poison a player with Nightshade. They will die in 2 days unless healed. 0 uses.<br>
<strong>Crimson potion (Night ability)</strong> - Heal a target player, preventing their death and curing any poison or bleeding. Healing a player that was bleeding or poisoned will give you a use of Amethyst potion. Unlimited uses.<br>
<strong>Emerald potion (Night ability)</strong> - Poisons a target player with a lethal dosage, instantly killing them. If you successfully kill a player you will gain 1 use of Stoneskin potion. 2 uses.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 15:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-52399-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/alchemist-rework/52399.rss">Alchemist rework</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
