<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>(class suggestion): The schemer/plotter</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-schemer-plotter/2084</link>
    <description>Name: Schemer
Alignment: Neutral
Type: Offensive
Special: Cannot be present if original king is neutral)

Goal: Take the crown for yourself; and live to the following night; you will then kill yourself and all unguarded/unhealed royals (Including converted royals)

**Passive abilities:**

**Charismatic:** If you put your name forward in an election for king (not the royal election, as you can&#39;t put your name forward in this one,) and someone else also puts their name forward, all abstaining votes will count towards you instead.

**Unassuming:** You are immune to death at night (except by poison) as long as the original king is alive

**Night abilities:**

**Assassinate:** (1 use) Attack to kill the king. If the king used a guard this night, you will die. Anyone else who visited the king will be informed you are his killer.

**Vote Intimidation** (Infinite) target will not be able to vote guilty/innocent on any trials the following day. They will not be informed of this; other players will see they abstained, but your target will see whatever vote they selected when the summary of who voted what shows up, even if this would have thrown the vote.

**Day abilities:** 

**Stack jury:** (3 uses) The next trial in the same day, the target will be forced to vote the same as you. If the next trial is yours, they will be forced to vote innocent.


**Unseen converted class:** The Plotter
Type: Offensive

**Passive abilities:**

**In the king&#39;s shadow** If the original king is still alive, you will appear as The schemer to investigators.

**Determined** Immune to non-magic occupation at night (I.E. wizard can still ice ward you, but you will decline the butler&#39;s wine)

**Night abilities:** 

**Anarchist&#39;s gaze:** (Infinite uses) determine if the player has royal blood; The rest of the unseen will be informed of the result as well

**Fence:** (3 uses) Give the assassin one extra use of the &quot;Night shade&quot; ability, and gain one uses of &quot;Subliminal messages&quot;

**Subliminal messages** (0 uses) Targeted player (Cannot be king) will vote the same as you in all trials the following day (If you die this night, they will abstain)

No day abilities.

If you think either role is too overpowered, please tell me in replies how to fix it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 16:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-schemer-plotter/2084.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>(class suggestion): The schemer/plotter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Name: Schemer<br>
Alignment: Neutral<br>
Type: Offensive<br>
Special: Cannot be present if original king is neutral)</p>
<p>Goal: Take the crown for yourself; and live to the following night; you will then kill yourself and all unguarded/unhealed royals (Including converted royals)</p>
<p><strong>Passive abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Charismatic:</strong> If you put your name forward in an election for king (not the royal election, as you can’t put your name forward in this one,) and someone else also puts their name forward, all abstaining votes will count towards you instead.</p>
<p><strong>Unassuming:</strong> You are immune to death at night (except by poison) as long as the original king is alive</p>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Assassinate:</strong> (1 use) Attack to kill the king. If the king used a guard this night, you will die. Anyone else who visited the king will be informed you are his killer.</p>
<p><strong>Vote Intimidation</strong> (Infinite) target will not be able to vote guilty/innocent on any trials the following day. They will not be informed of this; other players will see they abstained, but your target will see whatever vote they selected when the summary of who voted what shows up, even if this would have thrown the vote.</p>
<p><strong>Day abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stack jury:</strong> (3 uses) The next trial in the same day, the target will be forced to vote the same as you. If the next trial is yours, they will be forced to vote innocent.</p>
<p><strong>Unseen converted class:</strong> The Plotter<br>
Type: Offensive</p>
<p><strong>Passive abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>In the king’s shadow</strong> If the original king is still alive, you will appear as The schemer to investigators.</p>
<p><strong>Determined</strong> Immune to non-magic occupation at night (I.E. wizard can still ice ward you, but you will decline the butler’s wine)</p>
<p><strong>Night abilities:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Anarchist’s gaze:</strong> (Infinite uses) determine if the player has royal blood; The rest of the unseen will be informed of the result as well</p>
<p><strong>Fence:</strong> (3 uses) Give the assassin one extra use of the “Night shade” ability, and gain one uses of “Subliminal messages”</p>
<p><strong>Subliminal messages</strong> (0 uses) Targeted player (Cannot be king) will vote the same as you in all trials the following day (If you die this night, they will abstain)</p>
<p>No day abilities.</p>
<p>If you think either role is too overpowered, please tell me in replies how to fix it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-schemer-plotter/2084/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-schemer-plotter/2084/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2084-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-schemer-plotter/2084.rss">(class suggestion): The schemer/plotter</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
