<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Class/Lore/Fanfic - Forum of Lies | Throne of Lies | by Imperium42</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/c/classes-lore/5</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Class/Lore/Fanfic&#39; category Use this category to discuss lore/fanfic/class suggestions related to &lt;em&gt;Throne of Lies&lt;/em&gt;.</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 04:58:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/c/classes-lore/5.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Perhaps A new Mystic Ability. (Possible dead gossip)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[SabreOverdrive]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Give this ability to mystic:</p>
<p>Abyssal Dreams:<br>
1 Use, Day Ability</p>
<blockquote>
<p>See all gossip results of the dead players found the night before the day this ability was used. Unable to be used before D3. But also can’t read any evil or neutral feedback. Any defiled targets still will not show their results.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Reason Why I feel like this should be a ability.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I Feel sorry for the investigatives and everyone else with leads that die. That is of the blue dragon factions. I know. No dead interaction. But I felt like this would be mainly a very interesting ability to add. I know. These are horrible. But, I wanted to try and make a possible chance to make BD investigatives die with the possibility of hope</p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/perhaps-a-new-mystic-ability-possible-dead-gossip/87948">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/perhaps-a-new-mystic-ability-possible-dead-gossip/87948</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 04:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87948</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/perhaps-a-new-mystic-ability-possible-dead-gossip/87948.rss">Perhaps A new Mystic Ability. (Possible dead gossip)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Crow (Blue Dragon Special Social)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crow_is_dead]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Win Condition: Defeat all who oppose the Blue Dragon.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
<strong>Mimicry</strong> - Your vote counts twice. It still shows up as 1 next to the name but actually will count twice, this is so it is harder to prove yourself.</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities:</strong><br>
<strong>Crow’s Mark</strong> - Remove someones ability to vote for the day (3 uses)<br>
<strong>Helping Hand</strong> - Give someone else the ability to vote twice. Similar to Mimicry to where it will still show up as 1 vote but actually counts twice. (2 uses)</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities:</strong><br>
<strong>Crow on the shoulder</strong> - Pick a target, you will then see any whispers that include them (Inf uses)<br>
<strong>Trust me</strong> - Pick a target, the next day they will immediately be executed (1 use)</p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/crow-blue-dragon-special-social/87578">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/crow-blue-dragon-special-social/87578</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 02:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87578</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/crow-blue-dragon-special-social/87578.rss">Crow (Blue Dragon Special Social)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Lunatic [Neutral Special]</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kape]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1><strong>The Lunatic</strong></h1>
<p><strong>Neutral Special</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
<strong>Curse Of La Luna:</strong> You are compulsive to perform an action each night. If you don’t perform an action you will automatically use &lt; Moon Phase &gt;<br>
<strong>Lunar Legacy:</strong> The Moon will start in the Waning Crescent Phase. At the end of each night it will advance to the next one.</p>
<p><strong>Day:</strong><br>
<strong>Moon Ritual (2 use):</strong> Prevent the Moon from advancing to the next Phase tonight. Usable day 1. You cannot delay the same Phase twice.<br>
<strong>Splendor Casei (2 use):</strong> Become Death Immune tonight.</p>
<p><strong>Night:</strong><br>
<strong>&lt; Moon Phase &gt; (inf use):</strong> Perform an action based on the current Moon Phase.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Waning Crescent: Intensify everyone’s action.<br>
New Moon: Heal everyone.<br>
Waxing Crescent: Do nothing.<br>
First Quarter: Frame everyone.<br>
Waxing Gibbous: Anyone executed the next day will appear as their converted class. Unconvertable players show up as Assassin or Cult Leader.<br>
Full Moon: Commit suicide.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Syzygy Sacrifice (1 use):</strong> Only usable during a New Moon or Full Moon. Attack a player. If successful the Moon will return to the previous Phase.</p>
<p><em>Win Con: Survive.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<p>Just your casual 9 ability class, nothing special or unique to be honest.<br>
&lt; Moon Phase &gt; is a placeholder name. The actual ability name changes based on the current Phase as referenced in the list below it.</p>
            <p><small>18 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-lunatic-neutral-special/87558">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-lunatic-neutral-special/87558</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-87558</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-lunatic-neutral-special/87558.rss">The Lunatic [Neutral Special]</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Class Making Tutorial</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[heccy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tutorial for making your own classes with slates!<br>
Follow these steps to make a custom class with ease (it does take time though)</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Download the .psd file linked below.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go to <a href="http://photopea.com" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">photopea.com</a>. You should see a page like this: <a href="https://gyazo.com/6c78c32badb11566e25e6b0915e7172b" class="inline-onebox" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Screenshot - 6c78c32badb11566e25e6b0915e7172b - Gyazo</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click “Open from computer” and navigate to the Downloads folder. Select the classSlate-v2.psd file.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click on the Text tool in the sidebar on the left. Its the large T.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click on the text that says “THE CLASS NAME”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You should see that you opened a textbox. Click on the box that is filled white to the right of the text size changer in the bar at the top that appeared. Try to make the color of the text as close to the color of the faction you are making the class for as possible. When you are done, type in the name of your class and click the check mark.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do this process for the rest of the text. Worry about images later.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Turn your attention to this section: <a href="https://gyazo.com/9720e7e3af74a7a9055b138114275311" class="inline-onebox" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Screenshot - 9720e7e3af74a7a9055b138114275311 - Gyazo</a> Click on the arrow to open the drop-down menu called “Left Info”. If your class cannot be converted, click on the Eye next to “PortraitConvertedSrr” to make it invisible. Now click on “PortaitMain”. Click the eye next to the Border that has the faction of your class (example: I want to make a Blue Dragon class. I will click the eye next to Border-BD.)</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>8.5. If your class can be converted, do the exact same as step 9 except with INSERT_CONVERT.</p>
<ol start="9">
<li>
<p>Click on the drop-down menu of INSERT-PORTRAIT. Make “Unknown-Portrait” Invisible. Click on Unknown-Portrait and paste in the image of what you want to be your classes portrait. If you need to move around the image, press v to select the Move tool and drag it around.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once you’re finished, revert the drop-down menus and open FactionIcons and TypeIcons. IconBD and TypeSocial are selected by default. Make the icon of your faction and type visible, and make all others invisible.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Open the drop-down menu for Right Info. Go into Passive abil slots, and do the same steps as 8.5 and 9 for the ability slots. If you only have one passive, disable one ability slot and disable its corresponding passive. These will be Passive 1 and Passive 2 underneath the passive abil slots.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do the same steps as 11 for Day Abilities and Night Abilities.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once everything is finished, click File, then Export As, then PNG (or jpg if you want it doesnt matter). And click Save. If this class is a meme, post the .png out of your downloads folder into <span class="hashtag">#tol-memes</span>. If its a legitimate class idea that you want to be balanced, post it in this channel (<span class="hashtag">#class-lore-fanfic</span>)</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Enjoy class making!</p>
<p><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1oLy4t0WJqqyX4mUg8Wczl8I63CczW0Hj/view?usp=sharing" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://drive.google.com/file/d/1oLy4t0WJqqyX4mUg8Wczl8I63CczW0Hj/view?usp=sharing</a><br>
and remember, hail Giles!</p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-making-tutorial/86867">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-making-tutorial/86867</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 13:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86867</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-making-tutorial/86867.rss">Class Making Tutorial</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Frostfire (Neutral Killer)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Oogway]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>The Frostfire</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>The Frostfire is a “Killer” class that belongs to Neutral subfaction.<br>
The Frostfire has the ability to collect Frost energy with each kill by “Icy Shot”.<br>
Can use the “Dark Ice” to gain upgrades.<br>
Can use “Mysterious Gift” to gain information about your target and kill them.<br>
Starts the game with 1 bars of Frost energy<br>
<em>Win Condition:</em> Must kill all members of the main factions in order to win.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><em>Passives</em>:<br>
<strong>Baron of Winter</strong>: You have a freeze meter which has maximum 3 bars. each successful kill, fills a bar of Freeze meter with Frost energy. (Only the attacks made by Icy Shot fills the Freeze Meter.)<br>
<strong>Ice Coat</strong>: Death Immune. Immune to bleeding.<br>
Consumes a bar if you get attacked by a Knight “Defend” or Hunter’s “Bear Companion”.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><em>Day Abilities:</em><br>
<strong>Silence of Cold:</strong> Silence a player and block their voting for the day. (2 uses)<br>
<strong>Dark Ice:</strong> Empowers your ice with dark magic. once used you can choose one of the upgrades:<br>
use 3 bars to become occupy and redirect immune<br>
use 2 bars to make Ice Shot bypass death immunity.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><em>Night Abilities</em><br>
<strong>Icy Shot:</strong> Shoot an Ice missile at your target, attacking them.<br>
<strong>Mysterious Gift:</strong> Consume 1 bar to place an Ice statue that reveals who visits your target into your target’s room. if used again (to detonate), you will consume a bar and the statue will explode, attacking your target (doesn’t count as visiting while detonating. The attack with the statue does not fill the Freeze meter.).</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Ice Statue will reveal who visits your target everynight unless you detonate it.</p>
<p>Freeze meter shows how many bars of Frost energy you have, you start the game with 1 bars of Frost energy. You can gain a bar of Frost energy by succesfully killing someone with “Ice Shot”. This Frost energy can be used to empower your abilities, add yourself some passives and put a spy (the ice statue) that shows who visits your target everynight and can be detonated anytime.</p>
<p><em>I know it might sound a little like the Reaper but i want to know what you think. The abilities might be polished as well.</em></p>
<p><strong>ANOTHER VERSION</strong></p>
<blockquote>
<p>The Frostfire (Neutral killer)<br>
<em>Passives:</em><br>
<strong>Ice Coat:</strong> Death Immune. Bleed Immune. You will not attack Death Immune players. You will also not attack the players who are defended by a Knight but mark the Knight instead.<br>
<strong>Baron of Winter:</strong> you will level up with successfull kills<br>
<span class="hashtag">#1</span> Level <strong>(1 kill needed for level 1)</strong> : you ll now mark who visits you. If you attack someone death Immune, you will also mark them. Marks stay on a player until they die<br>
<span class="hashtag">#2</span> Level <strong>(2 kills needed after first level for level 2)</strong> : aditionally, ice statue will show the feedbacks of the abilities used on your target and bypass death immunity when detonated.<br>
<span class="hashtag">#3</span> Level <strong>(3 kills needed after second level for level 3)</strong> : your attacks will now bypass healing<br>
<em>Day Abilities:</em><br>
<strong>Cold Embrace:</strong> Marked players will be freezed, silencing them and blocking their voting for the day. Marks gets cleared on use (3 uses)<br>
<strong>Mysterious Gift:</strong> Place an Ice statue that reveals who visits your target <em>everynight</em> into your target’s room. Marks everyone who visits your target (Unlimited uses. can’t place another until you detonate the remaining ice statue)<br>
<em>Night Abilities:</em><br>
<strong>Icy Shot:</strong> Shoot an Ice missile at your target, attacking them.<br>
<strong>Suprise!:</strong> Detonate the Ice statue, attacking your target</p>
</blockquote>
<p>you kill someone &gt; leveled up to first level<br>
after you level up to first level you need to kill 2 players to level up to second level<br>
after you level up to second level you need to kill 3 players to level up to final level (3rd)</p>
<p>you ll know the marked players</p>
            <p><small>20 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-frostfire-neutral-killer/86838">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-frostfire-neutral-killer/86838</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 15:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86838</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-frostfire-neutral-killer/86838.rss">The Frostfire (Neutral Killer)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Puppet Master (Neutral Killer)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunica]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p><strong>The Puppet Master (Neutral Killer)</strong><br>
<strong>Win Condtion: Must kill all members of the main factions in order to win.</strong><br>
(see Master of Puppets (night ability) first)</p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
<strong>Master of Fate</strong> - Death immune at night. You may speak in the place of your puppet if they are imprisoned by the prince.<br>
<strong>Master of Trickery</strong> - If you die with a puppet still alive, you will be moved into the place of the puppet and consume one use of Master of Puppets. Activates only once.</p>
<p><strong>Day Abilities:</strong><br>
<strong>Master of Control</strong> - Swap between the chat and voting of you and your puppet. (Unlimited uses, can be used multiple times in a day and during elections)</p>
<p><strong>Night Abilities:</strong><br>
<strong>Master of Agony</strong> - Send you or your puppet out to kill target player. (Unlimited uses)<br>
<strong>Master of Puppets</strong> - Kill target player and raise them into your puppet. They will show as their class from before becoming a puppet and keep their passives. Upon the puppet dying, their class will show as The Puppet. Cannot have more than 1 puppet. Only consumes a charge upon success. (3 uses)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>A few interactions I will clear up:</p>
<p>-The Puppet will commit suicide the night of The Puppet Master becoming The Psycho King.<br>
-The Puppet will show as the class they were before they became the puppet when committing suicide.<br>
-The Puppet crowns into The Puppet King, with The Royal Finger and Decide Fate, but still counts as a puppet.</p>
<p>-The King can be turned into a puppet, however it won’t become The Puppet King, much like how The Possessor doesn’t become The Psycho King upon jumping the king.</p>
<p>-If Master of Trickery triggers while The Puppet King is up, you become The Psycho King.<br>
-If Master of Trickery triggers while The Puppet is in the king, you become The Puppet Master in the slot of the King.<br>
-Master of Trickery can still trigger even with 0 uses of Master of Puppets.</p>
            <p><small>3 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-puppet-master-neutral-killer/86710">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-puppet-master-neutral-killer/86710</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 06:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86710</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-puppet-master-neutral-killer/86710.rss">The Puppet Master (Neutral Killer)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Tutor: neutral social</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the kings tutor<br>
goal: survive</p>
<p>passive: captive kids: people with royal blood cant vote exe on u<br>
day ability: kill kings kids: lose ur passive. the king commits surcide. the pricne and princess will bleed. (1 use)<br>
night ability: teach: target will gain1 use of their ability (9 uses)<br>
night ability whiskey: u will be immune to occupation tonight (7 uses)</p>
            <p><small>9 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tutor-neutral-social/86674">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tutor-neutral-social/86674</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 18:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86674</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tutor-neutral-social/86674.rss">Tutor: neutral social</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral class: bill gates</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>goal: reduce the population to 3 or less people (including yourself) by the end of the game</p>
<p>passive: billions of dollars: as long as you havent run out of uses of any of your abilities, you will be death immune</p>
<p>day ability: vaccinate: target player will be healed at night for the next 2 nights. on the third they will die (3 uses)</p>
<p>day ability: microchip: target player will be microchipped, telling you who they visit for the rest of the game (inf uses)</p>
<p>night ability: kill switch: kill target player with a microchip (2 uses)</p>
<p>night ability: reduce emissions: reduce emissions by throwing target into a pit with no food at the bottom. they wont be able to make accusations of treason the following day (4 uses)</p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-bill-gates/86672">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-bill-gates/86672</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 13:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86672</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-bill-gates/86672.rss">Neutral class: bill gates</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral offensive class: Condottiere</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Goal: gain 5 bridles<br>
Day ability: offer contract (Infinite uses): cannot be used on same target more then once. Target will receive pop-up asking who they want dead. whoever they select will be marked.<br>
Day ability: cloak and dagger (2 uses): slice a marked player of your choice, making them bleed. if they die from the bleeding, gain a bridle.<br>
Night ability: Stab (inf uses): attack a marked player. if successfully kill them, gain a bridle.<br>
Night ability: Better gear (costs 1 bridle): gain death immunity for the rest of the game.</p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-offensive-class-condottiere/86603">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-offensive-class-condottiere/86603</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 16:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86603</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-offensive-class-condottiere/86603.rss">Neutral offensive class: Condottiere</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Killer class: The General/warlord</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The General<br>
Faction: Blue dragon<br>
Unique<br>
If the general is not present in a game, the starting unseen/cult and NK will be informed (because  he is out on campaign and they killed him before he could return to court)</p>
<p><strong>Passive 1</strong>: <em>Strongarm Succession</em>: when voting for a new king, your vote counts twice (stacks when voting for someone with royal blood so the vote counts as 4 votes)<br>
<strong>Passive 2</strong>: <em>Coup d’etat</em>: if the king attempts to decide fate execute you, you will kill him and be pardoned instead.<br>
<strong>Day</strong>: <em>Strategize</em> (2 uses): gain a use of each of your night abilities. you will be unable to accuse of treason or vote for the rest of the day (rescinds any accusations you have made at that point). cannot be used if a trial has occurred that day already.<br>
<strong>Night 1</strong>: <em>Court martial</em> (1 uses): Kill target player who was put on trial the previous day but not executed. if the king or sorcerer decided fate pardon on them, bypass death immunity.<br>
<strong>Night 2</strong>: <em>Convene with troops</em> (0 use): Gain death immunity for the night, and the next day if there are too few people to elect a new king and there is no king, become king. You will appear as evil to investigators for the night.</p>
<p>The Warlord<br>
Faction: unseen<br>
<strong>Passive 1</strong>: <em>Strongarm Succession</em>: when voting for a new king, your vote counts twice (stacks when voting for someone with royal blood so the vote counts as 4 votes)<br>
<strong>Passive 2</strong>: <em>Coup d’etat</em>: if the king attempts to decide fate execute you, you will kill him and be pardoned instead.<br>
Day: Putsch (1 use): immediately put the king on trial. votes to execute will count twice. If he is not executed, you will be put on trial, and votes will count double against you as well. usable even during the trial of someone else (including yourself).<br>
<strong>Night 1</strong>: <em>Court martial</em> (1 uses): Kill target player who was put on trial the previous day but not executed. if the king or sorcerer decided fate pardon on them, bypass death immunity.<br>
<strong>Night 2</strong>: <em>Topple Government</em> (1 uses): attack the king. If you successfully kill him, all players will lose the royal blood passive (they will not be informed). If there are too few players left for a new king to be elected and you succeed in killing the king, the unseen will immediately win the game.</p>
<p>Notes:<br>
1: it could be argued that the general/warlord is more of a social class rather then a killer class. However, I wanted the general to be a good claim for evil killers without princess investigate screwing them over. But maybe people think that it should be a social class, so that the princess can threaten anyone who try to use general as an “easy” claim (easy in quotation since the general can confirm themselves at the end of the game by becoming king, though by then it might not matter)<br>
2: the warlord has the ability to kill, which some might object to since the assassin is meant to be the killer for the unseen. However, I think here it is appropriate since court martial can only be used on people who were put on trial the previous day, and topple government may only target the king (who often has death immunity from guards night ability).<br>
3: general considerations: The general can snatch victory from the jaws of defeat if they are still alive at the end of the game by becoming king, but the warlord can do the same if the king wasted his guards earlier and the warlord uses topple government. The general also acts as a counter balance to whichever faction got the starting king on their side (the unseen will have to convert the general of course), since he has anti-king abilities.</p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/killer-class-the-general-warlord/86543">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/killer-class-the-general-warlord/86543</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 03:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86543</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/killer-class-the-general-warlord/86543.rss">Killer class: The General/warlord</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral class: The Harbinger</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Goal: on day 1, you will prophesize (be told) the time of death for all other players (ex: player 1 die day 3, player 2 die night 6, etc.) You win if, before your death, x of these prophecies are true (I am not sure what the amount should be)</p>
<p>passive 1: Calendar of doom: 2 nights of death immunity. After successfully completing your goal, gain 10 gold for every other player whos prophecy is also fulfilled, and lose death immunity</p>
<p>Day ability 1: Align (3 uses): select target player. For the next 3 days, if they vote execute on a player who was not prophesized to die that day, you will have the option to kill them. Their body will be a husk for the rest of the day (like the reaper effect), and they will be revealed dead at the end of the following night. The death will count for your goal if they were meant to die that day or the following night. If they have death immunity, you will instead remove their death immunity. If they kill a player at night who was not prophesied to die that night, yuo will have the option to kill them at the start of the next day in the same manner. target will not be informed you used this ability on them unless you remove their death immunity.</p>
<p>day ability 2: Ward off death (3 uses): target player will have death immunity the following night.  the king will be unable to to force execute on them (if they try they will instead force pardon them).  if they are executed by the court or prince, regain a use of this ability. target is not informed when this ability is used on them.</p>
<p>night ability 1: fulfill prophecy (2 uses): kill target player who is prophesized to die tonight.</p>
<p>night ability 2: guarantee prophecy: (infinite uses): occupy anyone who attempts to kill target player that is not prophesized to die tonight.</p>
<p>Maid compatibility: incompatible with anyone who is prophesized to die that night or the next day, compatible with everyone else.</p>
<p>commentary: A neutral that will probably want to hide their class from blue dragon, but perhaps not. I tried to give them abilities that cannot confirm who they are, though there are ways to confirm through killing people.</p>
            <p><small>7 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-the-harbinger/86541">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-the-harbinger/86541</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 02:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86541</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-the-harbinger/86541.rss">Neutral class: The Harbinger</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Arachne [Neutral Killer]</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kape]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p><strong>The Arachne</strong><br>
<strong>Neutral Killer</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passives:</strong><br>
<strong>Cocoon Retreat:</strong> If you would die, heal yourself and transform into a Cocoon for one day. In this state you are unable to accuse anyone and use your day abilities.<br>
<strong>Arachnid Gaze:</strong> You will be told the classes of all players that visit you.</p>
<p><strong>Day:</strong><br>
<strong>Marionette Strings (2 use):</strong> Force a player to accuse another and prevent them from further voting.<br>
<strong>Spider Toxin (2 use):</strong> Poison a player with a deadly toxin. It will end their life bypassing death immunity the next time they fail to perform a night action. Can be healed on the night of the attack.</p>
<p><strong>Night:</strong><br>
<strong>Deadly Fangs (inf use):</strong> Attack a player. Gain 1 use of Lay Webs if you kill someone this way.<br>
<strong>Lay Webs (1 use):</strong> Occupy your target and everyone visiting you tonight. You will be intensified while performing this action. (Max 2 use)</p>
<p><em>Goal: Do the thing yo</em></p>
</blockquote>
            <p><small>20 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-arachne-neutral-killer/86441">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-arachne-neutral-killer/86441</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 01:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86441</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-arachne-neutral-killer/86441.rss">The Arachne [Neutral Killer]</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral class: royal guard</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the royal guard is loyal to the starting king, having the same victory conditions as him. However, he does not know what the kings victory conditions are at the start of the game.</p>
<p>passive: loyal lowborn: if the starting king was neutral and dies, you will kill yourself. you cannot whisper to the king. if the king dies, you cannot step forward to become the next king.</p>
<p>passive: secret tunnels: you can see the prisoner’s/prince’s conversation at night, though you will not know who the prisoner is (their name will be shown as “prisoner”)</p>
<p>day: off with his head (1) - target player who is accusing the king will immediately die in front of everyone else, and everyone will be informed you are the royal guard.</p>
<p>day: torture (2) - you and the king will immediately be informed of target player’s class, unless they are death immune, in which case only you will be informed that they are death immune (reaper is shown as death immune only if he has no souls left)</p>
<p>night: crossbow (1) - attack target character. if they are the prince, princess, or duchess, the attack will not go through.</p>
<p>night: intimidate (2) - target player will not be able to speak the following day, except as whispers to the king.</p>
            <p><small>42 posts - 9 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-royal-guard/86297">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-royal-guard/86297</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 05:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86297</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-royal-guard/86297.rss">Neutral class: royal guard</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral class: pope</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the pope needs order restored to the kingdom, he wants the game to end within 7 turns. if it doesnt then there will be an outbreak of protestantism. the pope cannot be in the same game as the caliph.</p>
<p>passive: gout - the pope will die if the game isnt over in time for victory from obesity/syphilis</p>
<p>day: excommunicate (3) - target player cannot speak to other players or see what they say for the remainder of the day, can only communicate through whispers. anyone who whispers to an excommunicated person will also become excommunicated</p>
<p>day: call crusade (2) - target player will lose death immunity the following night, if they have it. all non-bd classes with the ability to kill we be informed of this.</p>
<p>night: heresy trial (2) - the following day, after bodies are revealed there will be a trial of the target, before normal voting. if they are executed, the court will still be able to execute someone else.</p>
<p>night: call swiss guards) (2) - you will be death immune tonight, and will attack the target</p>
            <p><small>14 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-pope/86296">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-pope/86296</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-86296</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-class-pope/86296.rss">Neutral class: pope</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Priest and Soulcatcher Comeback</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1><font color="steblue">The Priest</font></h1>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Blue Dragon Special</strong></font><br>
<strong>Godly Info (Passive)</strong> - You will learn the class of everyone who dies no matter what, but you will not know that the flip was tampered with. Possessor jumps will flip as Possessor.<br>
<strong>Limited Power (Passive)</strong> - You may only use the ability of a player once.<br>
<strong>Pray (Day)</strong> - Use target player’s main ability on yourself tonight. Can target dead players. You will only receive feedback if your target is dead. Two uses.<br>
<strong>Living Souls (Night)</strong> - Use target player’s main ability on another player. Can target dead players in the first slot. You will only receive feedback if your first target is dead. Cannot target self in either slot. Does not count as visiting. Unlimited uses.<br>
<strong>Speak with Dead (Night)</strong> - Learn what feedback your target received on the night they died. Does not count as visiting. Three uses.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="purple">The Soulcatcher</font></h1>
<p><font color="purple"><strong>Unseen Special</strong></font><br>
<strong>Godly Info (Passive)</strong> - You will learn the class of everyone who dies no matter what, and you will also know what they flipped as to everyone else. Possessor jumps will flip as Possessor.<br>
<strong>Limited Power (Passive)</strong> - You may only use the ability of a player once.<br>
<strong>To Darkness We Hail (Day)</strong>: Use target player’s main ability on all of the Unseen tonight. Can target dead players. You will receive feedback. Costs 1 soul.<br>
<strong>Collect Souls (Night)</strong> - The Assassin’s kill target will instead be reaped and you will gain one soul. The unseen will be aware of their class. Unlimited uses.<br>
<strong>Living Souls (Night)</strong> - Learn all actions and results of your first target and use their ability on your second. You will receive feedback as if you used the ability. Cannot target self. Can target dead players. Does not count as visiting. Costs one soul.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Cult conversion: If someone wants to design a Cabalist, go ahead, but I’ll currently have it as Seeker</p>
<details>
<summary>
Clarifications and Exceptions</summary>
<p>Drunk = Happy Hour<br>
Hunter and Prince = Normal Kill<br>
Kill Knight = Defend<br>
Non-knight Killer and Offensive abilities will only target the Soulcatcher<br>
NK = Normal Kill<br>
MM = Foresight as if the game just started (ie, Sage would not show up as conv immune)<br>
CL = Normal Kill<br>
Cult convert = Ability with more uses<br>
Ritualist = Brotherhood</p>
</details>
            <p><small>8 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/priest-and-soulcatcher-comeback/85821">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/priest-and-soulcatcher-comeback/85821</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 19:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85821</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/priest-and-soulcatcher-comeback/85821.rss">Priest and Soulcatcher Comeback</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>JoaT King + PK Buff</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tenacity and Loyal Subjects stay the same<br>
PK gains the following passive: <strong>In Other Shoes</strong>: When you are crowned, you will be prompted with a menu of different class types. Choose a class type, you will count as being crowned from this one for the rest of the game.<br>
Royal Finger uses reduced to three, elected king one use, unless you were crowned from a Social class, in which case you get three (Point meta ew)<br>
Decide Fate stays the same<br>
Night Ability: <strong>Head of State</strong> (replaces Guards, SG, and ISG, but not Fatal Guards): Use one of the following abilities. If you are elected, you will only get to use the one corresponding to your class type:<br>
<strong>Order Execution (Killer)</strong> : Attack target player. Two uses, lose this ability when you attack an ally. If you are the starting King, you only get one use.<br>
<strong>Duties (Offensive)</strong> : Occupy target player. Unlimited uses. If you are the starting King, you only get two uses.<br>
<strong>Close Allies (Investigative and Special)</strong> : Learn if target player is a member of your faction. Three uses, starting King only gets one use.<br>
<strong>Improved Safeguard (Support)</strong> : Make target player immune to death. Can target self. Three uses (No reduction for starting king)</p>
            <p><small>14 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/joat-king-pk-buff/85795">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/joat-king-pk-buff/85795</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85795</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/joat-king-pk-buff/85795.rss">JoaT King + PK Buff</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Evil Faction - Vampire</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[SweetyCake]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First, we will have</p>
<details>
<summary>
Vampire Lord</summary>
<p><strong><big><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire Lord</font></big></strong></p>
<p><strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire Special</font></strong></p>
<p><strong>Blood Connect (Passive)</strong> - All <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire</font></strong> can hear you and see your action but can’t speak up. Oldest <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire</font></strong> take your place if you die.</p>
<p><strong>Vampire Lust (Passive)</strong> - Your Faction have no members limit.</p>
<p><strong>Bat (Day)</strong> - Bleed a player. [3 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Vampire Energy (Day)</strong> - Occupy a player tonight. [1 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Bite (Night)</strong> - Convert a target player, if they are convert immune, attack them instead. Can’t target people you have learned to be convert immune. [Unlimited Use]</p>
<p><strong>Blood Ritual (Night)</strong> - Occupy all <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire</font></strong> and attack a target player. [Unlimited Use]</p>
</details>
<p>Then:</p>
<details>
<summary>
Vampire</summary>
<p><strong><big><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire</font></big></strong></p>
<p><strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire Special</font></strong></p>
<p><strong>Hidden (Day)</strong> - Appear as Not Vampire to the <strong><font color="2A7AFC">Vampire Hunter</font></strong> tonight. Not use if Occupied. Disable <strong>Harden</strong> if this is used. [1 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Harden (Night)</strong> - Grant yourself Death Immune tonight. Disable <strong>Hidden</strong> if this is used. [1 Use]</p>
</details>
<p>And ofc, a counter class</p>
<details>
<summary>
Vampire Hunter</summary>
<p><big><strong><font color="2A7AFC">Vampire Hunter</font></strong></big></p>
<p><strong><font color="2A7AFC">Unique BD Killer</font></strong></p>
<p><strong>Blood Hunt (Passive)</strong> - Immune to Convert. Immune to attack from <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire Lord</font></strong> once.</p>
<p><strong>Silver Ring (Day)</strong> - Grant a player Convert Immune for the night. [2 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Blood Test (Night)</strong> - Check if a player is <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire</font></strong> or <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire Lord</font></strong>. If they are, attack them. Your attack will be unhealable. [Unlimited Use]</p>
<p><strong>Follow (Night)</strong> - Follow a player, if they visit  <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire</font></strong>, attack the <strong><font color="4d4d4d">Vampire</font></strong>. [Unlimited Use]</p>
</details>
            <p><small>15 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/evil-faction-vampire/85485">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/evil-faction-vampire/85485</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85485</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/evil-faction-vampire/85485.rss">Evil Faction - Vampire</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral Killer - The Depender</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[SweetyCake]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>(Female :D)<br>
<big><strong><font color="B8B6B6">The Depender</font></strong></big><br>
<font color="B8B6B6"><strong>Neutral Killer</strong></font></p>
<p><strong>Royal Rival (Passive)</strong> - Triple the vote to you during King Select. Appear to be Occupy and Redirect immune to Offensive Classes.</p>
<p><strong>I accidentally killed your friend (Passive)</strong> - Her first kill faction with <strong>Backstab</strong> will choose which faction will she along with.  Also death immune and bleed immune!</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong><font color="2A7AFC">Blue Dragon</font></strong> - She will lose bleed immune and death immune.</li>
<li>
<strong><font color="EE1212">Cult</font></strong> - Fill up a Convert slot and <font color="B8B6B6"><strong>Depender</strong></font> will know other <strong><font color="EE1212">Cult</font></strong>’s but unable to talk with them.</li>
<li>
<strong><font color="8012D6">Unseen</font></strong> - Join the <strong><font color="8012D6">Unseen</font></strong> and filling the <strong><font color="8012D6">Assassin</font></strong> slot. Death immune will only work once. The <strong><font color="8012D6">Assassin</font></strong> will die in the place of the <strong><font color="8012D6">Converted Unseen</font></strong>.</li>
<li>
<strong><font color="B8B6B6">Neutral</font></strong> - She will play as normal <strong><font color="B8B6B6">Neutral Killer</font></strong>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Flirty (Day)</strong> - Occupy the target tonight. [4 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Daughter Revenge (Day)</strong> - Poison the King and they will die that night unless healed. [1 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Backstab (Night)</strong> - Kill your target. Reduce to 2 Use as choosing <strong><font color="2A7AFC">Blue Dragon</font></strong> or <strong><font color="EE1212">Cult</font></strong>. [Unlimited Use]</p>
<p><strong>An End to a Start (Night)</strong> - Heal a target while killing everyone visiting them. Have 0 Use if choose <strong><font color="EE1212">Cult</font></strong>. [1 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Win condition:</strong><br>
<em>You have the same win condition as the faction you chose. You will have <strong><font color="B8B6B6">Neutral Killer</font></strong> win condition if you didnt kill that round.</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If she become King, she will become Psycho King. <strong>Fatal Guard</strong> will be disabled if she did not choose <strong><font color="B8B6B6">Neutral</font></strong> .</p>
            <p><small>5 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-the-depender/85464">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-the-depender/85464</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 14:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85464</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-the-depender/85464.rss">Neutral Killer - The Depender</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Neutral Special - The Magician</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[SweetyCake]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <details>
<summary>
The Magician</summary>
<p><big><span class="bbcode-b"><font color="lightgrey">The Magician </font></span></big> <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/star.png?v=9" title=":star:" class="emoji" alt=":star:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Neutral Special</span><br>
Can only spawn when 3 or more player being Magic Original classes appear (Court Wizard, Sorcerer, Alchemist)</p>
<p>Passives:<br>
+<strong>Magic Source</strong>: You will know when Magic Original visited you. Additionally, immune to Occupy only, and Occupier won’t know you are immune!<br>
+<strong>Hat Trick</strong>: If you die at night, you will make 1 random Magic Original die instead of you, bypass death immunity. Disabled when this ability successfully killed Magic Original.</p>
<p>Day abilities:<br>
+<strong>Card Trick</strong>: Occupy everyone visit you tonight. [1 Use]<br>
+<strong>Full Moon Night</strong>: Know who was targetted by Magic Ability at the end of tonight. [3 Use]<br>
-Magic Abilities: CW/Sage/Ritualist Swap, CW Intensify, both of Alch and Sorc abilities.</p>
<p>Night abilities:<br>
+<strong>Hypnosis</strong>: Occupy the target player. If they are Magic Original, they won’t know and receive fake feedback. [Unlimited Use]<br>
+<strong>Magic Stare</strong>: If you are targetted by Magic Abilities tonight, kill the user. Guarantee Death. Work even if they are occupied. [2 Use]</p>
<p><strong>Win conditions</strong>:<br>
You win when all Magic Original is dead.</p>
</details>
<p>Forgot to say, if Sorc using Missile when being occ’d by this girl, Sorc will receive “You know something was off…”</p>
<p>P/s: after 14 months of being offline lol</p>
            <p><small>10 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-special-the-magician/85463">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-special-the-magician/85463</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 12:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85463</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-special-the-magician/85463.rss">Neutral Special - The Magician</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Explorer (Blue Dragon Support) and The Cartographer (Unseen Support)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Conduit]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>The Explorer [BD Support]</h2>
<p><strong>Telescope (Day)</strong> - Scout someone out with your telescope. Any day abilities used (except Imprison) on them will be used on you instead. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>New Treasures (Night)</strong> - “Explore and claim” another person’s belongings, making all positive and negative effects that happens on them, happens on both of you. You are immune to any occupation abilities when using this ability. - <strong>Infinite uses</strong><br>
<strong>Black Marketer (Night)</strong> - Transfer all negative abilities from one player to another. If a player has their death prevented with this ability, they’ll be notified. First player can’t be target consecutively. - <strong>3 uses</strong></p>
<h2>The Cartographer [Unseen Support]</h2>
<p><strong>Efficient Travel (Passive)</strong> - You are occupation and redirect immune.<br>
<strong>Misleading Map (Night)</strong> - Everyone that visits your first target is secretly redirected to your second target. - <strong>4 uses</strong><br>
<strong>Sail Ship (Night)</strong> - With a top quality ship, you can ensure EVERYTHING negative that happens to one person will happen to another person as well! Amazing! - <strong>1 use</strong></p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-explorer-blue-dragon-support-and-the-cartographer-unseen-support/85448">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-explorer-blue-dragon-support-and-the-cartographer-unseen-support/85448</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85448</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-explorer-blue-dragon-support-and-the-cartographer-unseen-support/85448.rss">The Explorer (Blue Dragon Support) and The Cartographer (Unseen Support)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Paladins (Lore)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zipkick_Seaspook]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“I should have known”, the Paladin mutters to themselves. The Paladin clutches their blade while watching another person within the castle’s cellar. The unknown person quickly looks around the cellar before speaking a passphrase, “Rak’tu Vallah”, to a wall causing it to change into a wooden door. The Paladin peaks around the corner seeing the suddenly appearing door. They then watches as the unknown person enters the door. As soon as the door shuts the wall morphs back to it original cobblestone look.</p>
<p>The Paladin takes another look around the cellar not noticing anyone. After making sure the coast is clear, they step out from their corner and began walking to the spot in the wall. “Fortunately I found you quickly”, the Paladin says to themselves and continues, “I mean the odds that another paladin was in court today was nearly impossible, at least now I can finish you off quickly.” The Paladin draws their sword and speaks the passphrase they heard, “Rak’tu Vallah”, after being said the wall again changes into a door. The Paladin while gripping their sword tighter opens the door.</p>
<p>The Paladin steps through the now open doorway and after fully making it through the doorway the door shuts behind them. The Paladin now stands in a hallway with another door at the end sounds can be heard behind it and light shimmering from underneath the door. Sweat forms on the Paladin’s brow as they begin to walk down the hall. As the Paladin approaches the door the sounds become more clear it seems more like chanting and that there is only one person within the room. “Only one of you, good”, the Paladin whispers to themselves as they prepare to do their duty.</p>
<p>After a very short moment the Paladin bursts through the door coming into the small room. The person the Paladin had been stalking now standing at the other side of an altar in the room. However; the Paladin notices the person is not surprised but is instead smiling. A large blow knocks the Paladin from behind causing them to drop to their weapon and drop to the floor. The Paladin quickly rolls over to see another person within the room. The other person who is also smiling says, “I’m glad the plan worked.”  Before the Paladin could react they began to feel themselves being bound by magic.</p>
<p>“Well good job my Ritualist for being such good bait”, the person says in a taunting manor now standing over the Paladin. The Ritualist still standing behind the altar responds, “of course my leader.” “So what should we do with the paladin”, says a third person now entering the room. They continue to say, “I suggest we should kill them they are dangerous.” “A good suggestion, but I think I may have a better idea”, The Cult Leader responds. The Cult Leader waves their hands, as this happens the Paladin feels their body being forced into a sitting position. The Cult Leader now looking upon the sitting Paladin asks, “why don’t you join us?” In response to the question the Paladin spits in the Cult Leader face. “How dare you, he offers you mercy and you spit at him” The Ritualist yells. The Cult Leader wiping their face responds in a calm manner, “Calm yourself, I would be surprised if he had taken the offer so easily.” The Cult Leader then reaches down hold the Paladin’s head with both of their hands and says, “Now then this may hurt a bit.”</p>
<p>Even after a few hours the pain felt just the same to the Paladin as it did when it began. It still felt like their blood was on fire and the headache was unbearable, but their will had not broken. The Paladin with a grimace on their face says, “How much longer do you plan on keeping this useless plan up?” The Cult Leader responds, “until you have what you deserve.” “Well your going to have to hurry up it will be day soon” The Paladin says now slightly grinning. As if in response to what they said the Paladin felt even more pain than before. The Paladin’s grin was wiped from their face and in exchange they began to scream in pain. The pain now, completely unbearable for the Paladin, knocks them unconscious.</p>
<p>When the Paladin regains conscious they realize they are not where they were before. They are in what looks like a black and red swirling void. However; the Paladin realizes they are not alone noticing another figure within the void with them. The Paladin yells out, “who is their?” In response the figure begins to silently approach the Paladin. Noticing this they reach for their sword or at least where it should have been, but in fact it is not their nor is its holster. The Paladin now also realizes that they are not wearing their armor but instead common clothes that they would generally wear to court. Panicking realizing they have no defense they instead raise their hands as if to punch the being. “Calm, you will find no harm here Paladin”, the being says in a deep, dark voice now stopping their stride. The being then says, “In fact I’m only here to talk, my name is Mithras.”</p>
<p>The Paladin finding no comfort in the words that were just spoken to them keeps their hands up and says, “Feeling safe around you would be a fool’s folly.” Mithras laughs at The Paladins remark and says, “A fair thing to say indeed, however; if I wanted to harm you it would be more apparent already.” The Paladin realizing their words are true lowers their hands and asks, “So what do you want to know demon?” Mithras composing themselves takes a more calm demeanor and responds, “Why you are so resistant to serve me?” The Paladin chuckles slightly at this question and say, “why do you think, you are a demon an enemy of the God and are supposed to be destroyed.” “Why”, Mithras says and then continues, “Those that serve me face no harm and in fact grow in power while your god does nothing for you-”, The paladin interrupts, “My god protects me and gives me power far greater than what you could offer.” Mithras shifts their head sideways and says, “Then why are you here, defenseless and alone, without any help or power that your god supposedly gives you?” The Paladin stays silent for a moment before retorting, “Because this is a test of my faith and if I prove you true then I will have the power to defeat you and your followers.” “One hell of a test I would say leading you to your death”, Mithras responds. “I know it is hard to believe that your god does not care for you but it is the truth and my followers know this”, Mithras says now stepping closer to the Paladin. The Paladin takes a steps back and says shakily, “He does care.” “He does not, nor will he ever” Mithras responds continuing to step closer, they then says “I however do care and offer you a second chance at life, one that your god will never offer, I offer you my power to save yourself and the rest of the world from your god’s corruption.” MIthras then reaches out their hand and states, “take my hand and start your new life.” The Paladin stays silent and unmoving before stepping forward and taking Mithras’s hand and saying “I accept your offer.” MIthras smiles as light begins to piece the void blinding the Paladin.</p>
<p>When the Paladin’s vision recovers they realize they are slumped on a stone altar in a room the remember well. They are back in their own room sunlight shining through the stained glass. The Paladin looks around noticing they are wearing their armor with sword now firmly in their holster. They also notice a note on the stone altar it reads “I name you Seeker, meet tonight at the same place you found us before, after reading this destroy this note.” The Paladin sits their for a moment then destroys the note and gets ready for Court remembering that they still have to keep up the paladin persona even though they are now Seeker.</p>
<p>Please let me know what you think. this took over an hour to write so if you see any spelling or grammar mistakes please let me know and I will fix as soon as possible.</p>
            <p><small>4 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/paladins-lore/85384">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/paladins-lore/85384</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 06:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85384</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/paladins-lore/85384.rss">Paladins (Lore)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Crone [Neutral Special]</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Conduit]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h3>Crone [Neutral Special] <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/skull_and_crossbones.png?v=9" title=":skull_and_crossbones:" class="emoji" alt=":skull_and_crossbones:">
</h3>
<p><strong>Magical Evasion (Passive)</strong> - You are death immune once.<br>
<strong>Crone’s Madness (Passive)</strong> - Your abilities are disabled once you win.<br>
<strong>Dark Touch (Day)</strong> - Corrupt a players soul, causing them to bleed. They will die in 2 nights unless healed. Gain a use of this when you steal a soul. - <strong>0 uses</strong><br>
<strong>Herbicidal Remedy (Day)</strong> - Remove all immunities to death and bleeding, tonight and today. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>Necrostaff (Night)</strong> - Use your staff prevent healers from healing your target tonight. You will gain their soul if they die at night. If they are BD and are executed/arrowed tomorrow, you will also get their soul. (Can’t be used on the same person consecutively) - <strong>Inf uses</strong><br>
<strong>Ultimate Ritual (Night)</strong> - Attempt to violently suck the life out of your target, preventing healing and defiling/disguising them as a different class if they die or get executed. (Same soul rules as Necrostaff) - <strong>1 use</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>WINCON:</strong> Live to gain 3 souls.</p>
</blockquote>
            <p><small>7 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/crone-neutral-special/85096">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/crone-neutral-special/85096</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 00:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85096</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/crone-neutral-special/85096.rss">Crone [Neutral Special]</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mystic Illusionist, and Apostle Rework + New NK</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[thepigeonnyc]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1><font color="steblue">The Mystic</font></h1>
<p><font color="steblue"><strong>Blue Dragon Social</strong></font></p>
<p>Passive: Busy Mind: You are immune to occupation and redirection. This is kept upon changing class.<br>
Passive: Linked: You may anonymously speak with anyone else with this passive. At the beginning of every night, you know how many people have this passive. This is kept upon changing class. (People with this passive are distinguishable, however the people originally linked will be randomly given numbers, and then anyone who is added will get a subsequent number. Ex. There are two mystics and a seer at game start. They will each be randomly assigned a number 1-3. They each use their day ability. Their targets will be randomly assigned numbers 4-6)<br>
Day ability: Link: Give target player the <em>Linked</em> passive. Only you will know their identity. Usable Day 1. Unlimited uses.<br>
Night ability: Power of the Mind: Grant a player with the <em>Linked</em> passive a slight buff  tonight based on class type. Unlimited uses.<br>
Night ability: Protect Minds: Heal everyone with the <em>Linked</em> passive. 1 use.</p>
<p><strong>Power of the Mind Buffs:</strong><br>
Killer: Target player’s attacks bypass death immunity.<br>
Offensive: Your target’s ability bypasses immunity to occupation and redirection. They will know whether or not their target was immune to occupation and redirection, but not that this ability was used on them. Their ability will not bypass the Court Wizard’s <em>Intensify</em> ability. You cannot be occupied or redirected by using this.<br>
Support: Your target will be redirected to themselves.<br>
Social: Your target will be immune to conversion.<br>
Investigative: Your target will always receive correct information with their ability.<br>
Special: Your target will be aided if they are occupied or redirected (same as Intensify)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="purple">The Illusionist</font></h1>
<p><font color="purple"><strong>Unseen Social</strong></font></p>
<p>Passive: Busy Mind: You are immune to occupation and redirection.<br>
Passive: Linked: You may anonymously speak with anyone else with this passive. At the beginning of every night, you know how many people have this passive. This is kept upon changing class.<br>
Day ability: Link: Give target player the <em>Linked</em> passive. Only you will know their identity. Unlimited uses.<br>
Night ability: The Illusion: Target player with the <em>Linked</em> passive receives a debuff based on their class type tonight. Unlimited uses.</p>
<p><strong>Illusion Debuffs:</strong><br>
Killer: Target player’s attacks can be stopped by anything, regardless of buffs or the ability. Note that on the night after someone is reaped, that person cannot be saved, even by this ability.<br>
Offensive: Target player is no longer immune to occupation and redirection.<br>
Support: Target player is redirected to you.<br>
Social: Nothing happens.<br>
Investigative: Target player will receive results as if their target was framed.<br>
Special: Nothing happens.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="darkred">The Apostle</font></h1>
<p><font color="darkred"><strong>Cult Social</strong></font></p>
<p>Passive: Busy Mind: You are immune to occupation and redirection.<br>
Passive: Linked: You may anonymously speak with anyone else with this passive. At the beginning of every night, you know how many people have this passive. This is kept upon changing class.<br>
Day ability: Cult Pressure: Force your first target to accuse your second of treason and prevent them from voting or accusing for the rest of the day. 2 uses.<br>
Day ability: Link: Give target player the <em>Linked</em> passive. Only you will know their identity. Usable Day 1. 1 use.<br>
Night ability: Intrigue: Frame target player and receive feedback for any abilities used on them. 3 uses.<br>
Night ability: Silence Minds: Debuff target player with the <em>Linked</em> passive tonight based on their class type (check Illusionist debuffs)</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1>The Seer</h1>
<p><strong>Neutral Killer</strong><br>
Passive: Linked: You may anonymously speak with anyone else with this passive. At the beginning of every night, you know how many people have this passive. This is kept upon changing class.<br>
Passive: Foresee Attacks: You are immune to death at night and bleeding.<br>
Day ability: Link: Give target player the <em>Linked</em> passive. Only you will know their identity. Usable Day 1. Unlimited uses.<br>
Day ability: Isolate: You cannot be accused of treason today. 1 use.<br>
Night ability: Mental Force: Attack target player. Unlimited uses.<br>
Night ability: End Links: Attack two players with the <em>Linked</em> passive. Bypasses death immunity. 4 use.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Changelog:<br>
Isolate now has 1 use.<br>
Added bleed immunity to Seer.<br>
Made End Links bypass death immunity.<br>
Changed Social buff to make target player be immune to conversion.<br>
Apostle now has 1 use of <em>Link</em><br>
End Links now attacks two linked players, uses raised to 4.<br>
Changed Offensive buff to not make your target receive incorrect feedback.<br>
End Links once again bypasses death immunity.</p>
            <p><small>107 posts - 9 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mystic-illusionist-and-apostle-rework-new-nk/85055">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mystic-illusionist-and-apostle-rework-new-nk/85055</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 16:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85055</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mystic-illusionist-and-apostle-rework-new-nk/85055.rss">Mystic Illusionist, and Apostle Rework + New NK</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Some King Remakes I Made</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Conduit]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>Paranoid King <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<h3>Alchemist Crown</h3>
<p><strong>Tenacity (Passive)</strong> - Occupy and redirect immune. Can talk at all points in a trial.<br>
<strong>The Royal Finger (Day)</strong> - Your next nomination for treason will count twice. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - Decide an accused player’s fate. If used to trigger Hunter’s <strong>Retribution</strong>, King will be targeted with the arrow. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>Guards! (Night)</strong> - Become death immune for the night. - <strong>Stoneskin Potion Use + 1 use(s)</strong><br>
<strong>Order Execution (Night)</strong> - Send a guard to attack target player. <em>You</em> will die if the player is protected. - <strong>Emerald Potion Use(s)</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1>Foolish King <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<h3>Fool Crown</h3>
<p><strong>Poor Tenacity (Passive)</strong> - Occupy and redirect immune. Can talk at all points in a trial. If you are executed, all those who voted to execute you will lose <strong>1</strong> charge from all limited-use abilities and there can be no trials the next day.<br>
<strong>Cowardice (Passive)</strong> - You hide in your chambers every night, giving you death immunity and telling your attackers that you are the Foolish King.<br>
<strong>The Royal Finger (Day)</strong> - Your next nomination for treason will count twice. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - Decide an accused player’s fate. If used to trigger Hunter’s <strong>Retribution</strong>, King will be targeted with the arrow. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>Bloodied Crown (Night)</strong> - If you are voted up to the stand tomorrow, you will be instantly executed. There will still be trials tomorrow, but everyone who voted you up will lose will lose <strong>1</strong> charge from all limited-use abilities - <strong>1 use</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1>Zealot King <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<h3>Inquisitor Crown</h3>
<p><strong>Relentless Tenacity (Passive)</strong> - Occupy and redirect immune. Death immune. Can talk at all points in a trial.<br>
<strong>The Royal Finger (Day)</strong> - Your next nomination for treason will count twice. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - Decide an accused player’s fate. If used to trigger Hunter’s <strong>Retribution</strong>, King will be targeted with the arrow. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>Adiart Inquisitors (Night)</strong> - Determine target player’s class if marked as a <em>Heretic</em>. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Ruthless Efficiency</strong> - Have guards kill a player, only if they are a heretic. - <strong>Ruthless Efficiency Use(s)</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1>Contracted King <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<h3>Mercenary Crown</h3>
<p><strong>Tenacity (Passive)</strong> - Occupy and redirect immune. Can talk at all points in a trial.<br>
<strong>The Royal Finger (Day)</strong> - Your next nomination for treason will count twice. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - Decide an accused player’s fate. If used to trigger Hunter’s <strong>Retribution</strong>, King will be targeted with the arrow. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>Guards! (Night)</strong> - Become death immune for the night. - <strong>2 uses</strong><br>
<strong>Mercantile Safeguard (Night)</strong> - Occupy everyone targeting your target. You cannot target the same target 2 nights in a row. Gain 1 brilder for each ability prevented, and 3 brilders for a prevented death. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1>Vengeful King <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<h3>Scorned Crown</h3>
<p><strong>Vengence (Passive)</strong> - Occupy and redirect immune. Death immune. Can talk at all points in a trial.<br>
<strong>The Royal Finger (Day)</strong> - Your next nomination for treason will count twice. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - Decide an accused player’s fate. If used to trigger Hunter’s <strong>Retribution</strong>, King will be targeted with the arrow. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>Incriminate (Night)</strong> - Make TWO targets appear framed tonight. They will also be marked for 1 day. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Disguise (Night)</strong> - TWO Players will appear as chosen class, if executed tomorrow. They will also be marked for 1 day. - <strong>Disguise Uses</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h1>Puppet King <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/crown.png?v=9" title=":crown:" class="emoji" alt=":crown:">
</h1>
<h3>Sellsword Crown</h3>
<p><strong>Tenacity (Passive)</strong> - Occupy and redirect immune. Can talk at all points in a trial.<br>
<strong>The Royal Finger (Day)</strong> - Your next nomination for treason will count twice. - <strong>Infinite Uses</strong><br>
<strong>Decide Fate (Day)</strong> - Decide an accused player’s fate. If used to trigger Hunter’s <strong>Retribution</strong>, King will be targeted with the arrow. - <strong>1 use</strong><br>
<strong>Guards! (Night)</strong> -   Become death immune for the night. - <strong>2 uses</strong><br>
<strong>Privy Conversation</strong> - Force your first target into someone else. All visits on the first target will be occupied, except those attacking or converting your target. Also find out if the first target is an ally. - <strong>4 uses</strong></p>
</blockquote>
            <p><small>9 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/some-king-remakes-i-made/85051">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/some-king-remakes-i-made/85051</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 05:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85051</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/some-king-remakes-i-made/85051.rss">Some King Remakes I Made</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Seeker [Lore]</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[WindwardAway]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The dungeon was dank and smelled of mildew. Holding his nose, the observer meandered through the passages in pursuit of the prince, who had brought his prisoner in for interrogation. A starved-looking rat scuttled across the floor, and the squeamish observer suppressed a shriek as he peered around the corner to overlook the prince. Shortly after, a knight arrived to stand guard in the hall; he was soon followed by a shy-looking woman who seemed only to linger nearby without venturing closer.</p>
<p>Scribbling the details in his logbook, the observer watched with concern as the knight drew his sword. With a smirk, the woman pushed the knight against the wall and flipped his helmet open to expose his face. The knight froze, his own blade held against his throat. “I’m sorry,” crooned the invoker, “but you’re in our way.”</p>
<p>Soundlessly, the cult leader emerged from the shadows, his dagger gleaming in the torchlight. “Much appreciated,” he told the invoker as he pulled off the knight’s helmet.<br>
The knight crumpled to the ground as the cult leader slit his throat, coughing and gasping for air. The older cultist grinned as he whispered to the dying knight. “You, my friend, have been eradicated.”<br>
He then sailed toward the prince, his crimson robes flowing in his wake. It seemed the young royal was preoccupied with his thoughts, and he didn’t hear the nearing footsteps as he bade his prisoner farewell. He hadn’t so much as the chance to turn his head before the cult leader’s dagger pierced his heart, and the prince fell without so much as a word.<br>
Beckoning for the invoker to follow, the cult leader slipped out of the dungeon. As the observer clenched his fists in frustration, he swore revenge on the cultists for murdering his fellow Blue Dragon members.</p>
<p>~</p>
<p>The court assembled the next day, a somber mood upon them as they realized the prince was gone. “May I speak?” asked the observer, withdrawing his logbook and opening it. “Last night, I overlooked the prince and saw two visitors. One of them was a knight, who incidentally is also dead. The other one…” he lifted a finger and pointed at the man across the table, “…is right here.”<br>
At his words, the cult leader shifted nervously. All eyes were on him, and he cleared his throat. “I believe the observer is lying,” he accused. “After all, that knight was on the prince. How would the killer have bypassed the knight?”<br>
The court turned to the observer for an answer. “I suspect there was an invoker or a sellsword,” he replied. “Wouldn’t that be logical? Occupy the knight and attack the prince?”<br>
“No! Well… yes. But you’re feeding the court with your lies. Who can say you’re not a sorcerer and you bombed them last night? The cult leader may have been imprisoned,” the cultist covered, but he sensed he was on thin ice.<br>
With a sigh, the king waved at the cult leader. “Get this man out of here,” he ordered. “If we’re wrong, we execute the observer tomorrow.”<br>
“That won’t be necessary, Your Majesty,” the observer assured him. “I know what I saw, and I saw this man kill the prince.”<br>
As the cult leader was forced on stand, the invoker stood back and watched. She knew already that her leader would be executed, and she was prepared for it.</p>
<p>The court cheered as the cult leader was executed, and the observer breathed a small sigh of relief; he would no longer be under any suspicion. He would simply have to undertake the task of finding the rest of the cult before they found him.</p>
<p>~</p>
<p>Night fell over Castle Adiart, and the observer prepared for his next task. He suspected the invoker was masquerading as a drunk claim, so he intended to track him tonight. As he left the walls of Castle Adiart to make his way toward the tavern, he heard a whisper. There was nobody in sight, however, and the observer felt a slight chill creeping up his spine. Surveying his surroundings, he peered cautiously into a dimly lit alley. Afraid of stepping into the secluded area, he lingered only for a minute before continuing on his way. But the farther he walked, the more lost in thought he became, until he had completely passed by the tavern. The whispers came again, nearer and nearer, distracting him from finding his target. He picked up the pace and strode briskly toward the tavern as the whispers grew louder and clearer.</p>
<p>As he reached for the door, a hand grabbed onto his arm and pulled him around the side. His assailant slapped a hand over his mouth before he could speak. She drew back the hood of her blood-red cloak and brandished a dagger. “Ah, yes,” she said, a carefree laugh gliding after her words as she mocked the observer. “You knew what you saw, and you saw our leader kill the prince.”<br>
Struggling to free himself of the former invoker’s grasp, the observer pushed the dagger away. “Oh, don’t worry. I’m not here to kill you,” she reassured him as she moved the dagger out of his reach, “I’m only here to take your eyes.”</p>
<p>The whispers came from all directions now, begging and pleading the observer to join them. They overwhelmed him, drowning his every thought in a sea of promises of ancient gods and unearthly powers. He could scarcely feel the dagger as the cultist worked, and a strange, comforting peace blanketed him as he succumbed to the voices in his head - his world had gone dark, but his mind had achieved a new level of enlightenment.</p>
<p>“Remember,” said the cult leader as she led her new convert away, “Your eyes belong to Mithras now.”</p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-seeker-lore/85041">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-seeker-lore/85041</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 02:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-topic-85041</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-seeker-lore/85041.rss">The Seeker [Lore]</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
