<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502</link>
    <description>## [color=#447294]W[/color][color=#487698]h[/color][color=#4c7a9c]a[/color][color=#517ea0]t[/color] [color=#5987a8]i[/color][color=#5d8bac]s[/color] [color=#6593b4]t[/color][color=#6a97b8]h[/color][color=#6e9bbb]i[/color][color=#729fbf]s[/color] [color=#7aa7c7]S[/color][color=#7eaccb]i[/color][color=#83b0cf]e[/color][color=#87b4d3]g[/color][color=#8bb8d7]e[/color] [color=#95bdd9]o[/color][color=#9abfd8]n[/color] [color=#a5c2d4]t[/color][color=#abc3d2]h[/color][color=#b1c5d1]e[/color] [color=#bcc8cd]X[/color][color=#c2c9cb]e[/color][color=#c7caca]d[/color] [color=#d2cdc6]t[/color][color=#d8cfc5]h[/color][color=#ded0c3]i[/color][color=#e3d2c1]n[/color][color=#e9d3bf]g[/color][color=#eed5be]y[/color][color=#f4d6bc]?[/color] ![gkicon|32x32](upload://2uDGm1OKtVgMO39Ttx0mWrKCgTp.png)

You are not in Castle Adiart and everything is completely rethemed.
All aboard. Ship Xed, which houses the Green Kraken. A pirate faction that is friendly towards the Blue Dragon. With similar classes to BD (and some unique ones)

Well, the Unseen or Cult have decided that Castle Adiart is out of their reach to conquer, so what is the second best option to take over? None other than a pirate ship. Pirate ships are cool.

There are entirely new threats on this pirate ship. Venomous snakes that poison you, the idea of giving evils their special abilities.

## [color=#f77933]G[/color][color=#f77a45]a[/color][color=#f87b57]m[/color][color=#f87b69]e[/color][color=#f87c7b]p[/color][color=#f97d8d]l[/color][color=#f97e9f]a[/color][color=#f97caa]y[/color] [color=#fa79c0]a[/color][color=#fa78cb]n[/color][color=#fa76d6]d[/color] [color=#fb73ec]N[/color][color=#ec69ef]a[/color][color=#dd60f1]m[/color][color=#ce56f4]e[/color] [color=#b043f9]C[/color][color=#a139fb]h[/color][color=#9342fa]a[/color][color=#844cfa]n[/color][color=#7655f9]g[/color][color=#685ef8]e[/color][color=#5968f8]s[/color][color=#4b71f7]:[/color]
* The King is now named The Captain.
* Royal Blood is no longer a concept here and has been replaced with a different concept.
* The game is now set on a Pirate Ship instead of the usual Castle.
* There is no Blue Dragon, instead having a new main faction called the Green Kraken.
* All new classes.
* Plunder Abilities which are 1 time use special abilities which you gain from being given the ability from somebody else. You must use plunder abilities at night.
* You may use abilities on trial.
* Day occupation and day redirection are both concepts here.
* Starting Cowardly King/Captain has been removed in favor for 65/35.
* Spiritualist/Revenant and Fool have both been disabled.

## [color=#e98a2b]W[/color][color=#efa230]h[/color][color=#f4b935]a[/color][color=#fad139]t[/color] [color=#fbe860]i[/color][color=#f6e882]s[/color] [color=#ede9c7]a[/color] [color=#efe9be]P[/color][color=#f4e994]l[/color][color=#fae869]u[/color][color=#ffe83e]n[/color][color=#fad139]d[/color][color=#f4b935]e[/color][color=#efa230]r[/color][color=#e98a2b]?[/color]

Plunder Abilities are a new feature to this gamemode. The Captain or Plunder Organiser (even when converted) may give a targeted player the ability to use their plunder ability. Which is a one time use ability that is more powerful than their regular abilities. They will only be able to gain and use it once in a game unless stated otherwise.

Plunder abilities are always free regarding Cult Points.

# [color=#ff0000]C[/color][color=#ff4000]l[/color][color=#ff7f00]a[/color][color=#ffff00]s[/color][color=#80ff00]s[/color] [color=#00ff80]C[/color][color=#00ffff]a[/color][color=#0000ff]r[/color][color=#4600ff]d[/color][color=#8b00ff]s[/color]

### [color=#00a150]T[/color][color=#00af57]h[/color][color=#00bd5e]e[/color] [color=#00dc6e]G[/color][color=#00ee76]r[/color][color=#00ff7f]e[/color][color=#00ff7f]e[/color][color=#00ff7f]n[/color] [color=#00ee76]K[/color][color=#00dc6e]r[/color][color=#00cb65]a[/color][color=#00bd5e]k[/color][color=#00af57]e[/color][color=#00a150]n[/color]


[details=&quot;Show&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Bard[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Social[/color]**
&gt; **Musical Network (Passive)** - You will start the game with 2 random players in your network. Players will have access to your network for one more day if they die. You will always have access to your musical network if it exists, even upon class change.
&gt; **In Space, No One Can Hear You Scream (Passive)** - Once you die or become Captain. Your network will cease to exist. This passive will carry over upon class change even if you already have 2 passives as that class.
&gt; **Song of Connections (Day)** - Targeted living or dead player will be added to the network chat tonight. - Infinite uses - 1 night cooldown
&gt; **Song of Disapproval (Night)** - Remove target player from the network chat at the end of tonight. - 4 uses
&gt; **Song of Modifications (Plunder)** - You may modify 3 living player&#39;s access to your network chat.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Credit to @Hippolytus as I pulled abilities from his Mystic rework and Marl/eevee as I also pulled abilities from the NuclearBurrito class in i42 Forum Member Mafia.

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Versifier[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Apostle[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 1 - Each ability costs: varies**[/color]
&gt; **[color=darkred]Free and Forced[/color]**
&gt; (Musical Network)
&gt; (In Space, No One Can Hear You Scream)
&gt; **[color=darkred]1 Point[/color]**
&gt; (Song of Connections)
&gt; (Song of Disapproval)

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Cooper[/color]
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Offensive[/color]**
&gt; **Wall of Barrels (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Roast Pork (Day)** - Targeted player will be occupied today and tonight. - 4 uses
&gt; **Nightly Preparations (Night)** - Roast Pork will bypass occupy immunity tomorrow. - 2 uses
&gt; **Barrel Drop (Night)** - Kill the Captain tonight. If you kill a Good Captain, you will commit suicide. Cannot be used until Night 3. - 1 use
&gt; **All You Can Eat Buffet (Plunder)** - Targeted player will be occupied all of tomorrow and the day after tomorrow.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Credit to @Firelitten for helping with this class.

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Steward[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Invoker[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(Barrel Drop) Mithras Infused Barrel** - Kill the Captain tonight. If you kill a Devout Captain, you will commit suicide. - 1 use

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Deck Hand[/color]
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Support[/color]**
&gt;**Wall Off (Day)** - The targeted player will not be able to be visited tonight. - 2 uses - Self targetable
&gt; **Loose Plank (Night)** - If there is a player attempting to convert, occupy, redirect, frame, warp targeted player, etc they will be occupied bypassing occupy immunity. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Quality Materials (Night)** - Make sure the player&#39;s night ability will work no matter what. This will have no affect on Special or Killing classes. This will not make players bypass immunities on their target. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Dispenser (Plunder)** - All the targeted player’s abilities with charges will be fully recharged to the starting amount. (Doesn’t work on Plunder Abilities)
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Engineer[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Ritualist[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(Quality Materials) Timber of Corax** - Make sure the targeted player&#39;s night ability will work no matter what. (Does not bypass convert immunity for Cult Leader) - 1 use

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The First Mate[/color] :shield: :crossed_swords:  
&gt; [color=springgreen]**Green Kraken Offensive**[/color]
&gt; **Get Out (Passive)** - Cannot be occupied or redirected in any way, shape or form. Including means which usually bypass this.
&gt; **Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two.
&gt; **Punishment (Day)** - Punish targeted player to scrub the deck. You and them may send eachother two different 1000 character messages, visits to them will be prevented and they will be prevented from doing any actions.
&gt; **Shark&#39;s Curse (Night)** - Force punished player to target a specific player tomorrow night, bypassing redirection immunity. - 3 uses
&gt; **Shark&#39;s Gift (Night)** - Punished player will be allowed to use their abilities tonight. - 1 use
&gt; **Lie Detector (Plunder)** - If the punished player lies about anything in their messages (who they targeted, actions, class, etc.), you will be sent a positive outcome.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; **Convert Immune**

&gt; Credit to @Whammerist for Plunder Abil

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Good Captain[/color]  :shield: :crossed_swords:  
&gt; [color=springgreen]**Green Kraken Special**[/color]
&gt; **Leader of the Crew (Passive)** - There must always be a captain. If you are killed, a new captain must be voted for the following day. If you are executed for treason, all future captains will be unable to use ‘Plunder yer Booty’.
**My Word is Law (Passive)** - Your votes to accuse players passively count as 2.
**Plunder yer Booty (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - Unlimited Uses, 1 Day Cooldown.
**Coup de Grace (Day)** - Decide the fate of the player currently on the plank. - 1 use.
**Keep Watch (Night)** - Protect a player, making them immune to attacks tonight. - 3 Uses.
**Into the Brig! (Night)** - Unseen/Cult will be unable to visit targeted player tonight. - 2 uses
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Credit to @Marluxion 
&gt; Crowned from:
&gt; Green Kraken Classes

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Gunslinger :shield: [/color]
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Killer [/color]**
&gt; **A Pirate’s Life (Passive)** - Immune to redirection but not occupation. Every three nights, you will gain a usage of Barrel Explosion
&gt; **Only At My Best (Passive)** - After a successful use of Aboard the Mary Jane, you may not use night abilities until you are healed.
&gt; **Barrel Explosion (Day)** - Kill a target player amidst the chaos of the current execution. You will lose the passive, A Pirate’s Life if you kill a Green Kraken with this ability. - 0 Uses
&gt;**Aboard the Mary Jane (Night)** - Protect a target player. If a Cult/Unseen tries to visit the target, you will kill them. Does not bypass immunity. If you successfully attack a player (even if immune) you will be poisoned sometime the next day and die in two nights unless you are healed. - 3 Uses
&gt; **Blight of Insanity (Night)** - Protect a target player. If the Neutral Killer tries to visit the target, the host will reveal who they are at the start of the second next day phase. You will die if the Neutral Killer visits your target. Your target will also die if they are a member of the Unseen/Cult. - 2 uses
&gt; **Cannon’s Away (Plunder)** - Target a player. If any Killers or Unseen/Cult visit, they will be killed. Bypasses night immunity. The youngest Unseen/Cult&#39;s name will be revealed to you only tomorrow morning.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Outlaw[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Invoker[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(A Pirate&#39;s Life) A Cultist&#39;s Life** - Every three nights, you will gain a usage of Voodoo Doll
&gt; **(Barrel Explosion) Voodoo Doll** - Prevent the current lynch from occurring. You will kill a target player amidst the chaos. - 0 Uses
&gt; **(Aboard the Mary Jane) Aboard the Mithras Jane** - Protect a target player. If a Green Kraken tries to visit the target, you will kill them. Does not bypass immunity. - 1 use
&gt; **(Blight of Insanity) Blight of Mithras** - Protect a target player. If the Neutral Killer tries to visit the target, the host will reveal who they are at the start of the second next day phase. You will die. Your target will also die if they are a member of the Green Kraken. - 2 uses
&gt; **(Cannons Away) - Select a Green Kraken/Neutral class from the class list, you will be able to kill everyone who is that specific class. Bypassing night immunity**

&gt; Credit to @Margaret 

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Navigator[/color] 
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Investigative[/color]**
&gt; **Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
&gt; **Parrot&#39;s Sight (Day)** - See the result of target dead player&#39;s final ability tonight. Even if they would not be notified normally. You will not know who was targeted. - 3 uses
&gt; **Crow&#39;s Nest (Day)** - Learn if target player used a day ability at the start of tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Telescope (Night)** - See who target player targeted tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Extra Crackers (Plunder)** - You may see who target player targeted tonight and who visited them.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Onlooker[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Seeker[/color]**
&gt; **[color=darkred]Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1[/color]**

&gt; Credit to @Firelitten for helping with this class.

&gt;## [color=springgreen]The Plunder Organiser :shield: [/color]
&gt;[color=springgreen]**Green Kraken Offensive**[/color]
**Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
**Secretive Plunder (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - 2 uses - One day cooldown.
**Authority (Night)** - See if targeted player used their plunder ability today - Infinite uses
**Hijack (Night)** - Remove target player&#39;s privilege to use a plunder ability - 1 use
**Prestige (Plunder)** - Give targeted player who already has used their plunder ability the ability to plunder (cannot target self)
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Entrepreneur[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Invoker[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(Authority) Mithras&#39; Influence (Night)** - Occupy targeted player - Unlimited uses

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Private Investigator[/color] :crossed_swords: 
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Investigative[/color]**
&gt; **Searchlight (Day)** - You will see if targeted player is a member of the Unseen at the start of tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Additional Interrogation (Night)** - Check if target player is the same faction as your day target. - 2 uses
&gt; **Coffee Overdose (Plunder)** - See if two targeted players are the same faction.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Fraud[/color]**. Does not appear in Cult games.

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Quarter Master[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Social[/color]**
**Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
**Peer Pressure (Day)** - Force target player to vote whatever you vote while somebody is on trial. - 2 uses
**Higher Identity (Day)** - Add an extra vote by the name of &quot;Quarter Master&quot; to whoever you are currently voting. - 2 uses
**Rank Change (Night)** - Give/remove targeted player&#39;s leadership qualities. - 3 uses
**Chinese Whispers (Night)** - You and targeted player will be able to send a 1000 character message to eachother for the day. - 2 uses
**Argggh You Kidding Me? (Plunder)** - If a Green Kraken player is supposed to be executed tomorrow, they will not be executed and there will instead be another execution.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Dictator[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Apostle[/color]**
&gt; **[color=darkred]Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1[/color]**
&gt; **(Argggh You Kidding Me?) Reversal of Corax** - If a Cultist would be executed tomorrow, they will not be executed and there will instead be another execution.
&gt; **(Rank Change)** Corax&#39;s Influence - Give/remove targeted player&#39;s leadership qualities. - 2 uses

&gt; Credit to @psychoneirik as I pretty much ripped off Golden Dragon Queen&#39;s royal blood giving idea.

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Sailor[/color] 
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Investigative[/color]**
&gt; **Sonar System (Day)** - Choose what you are going to find using Green Flare/Bright Flare tonight. Killer/Offensive, Support/Social, Investigative/Special or Neutral/Unseen/Cult. By default this ability will start on Killer/Offensive. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Green Flare (Night)** - Find out if targeted player fits the criteria of your Sonar System ability. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Bright Flare (Night)** - If targeted player fits the criteria, find out what specific part of it they match. - 2 uses
&gt; **Expedition (Plunder)** - Find out target player&#39;s exact class type and faction.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Buccaneer[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Seeker[/color]**
&gt; **[color=darkred]Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1[/color]**

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Scientist[/color]
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Support[/color]**
&gt; **Experimental (Passive)** - Immune to poison and bleeding.
&gt; **Robotic Spiders (Night)** - Heal a player from attacks, poison or bleeding. - Infinte uses
&gt; **Malfunction (Night)** - Targeted player will be healed when they need it. This will only take affect while you are living and it may only take affect once. - 1 use
&gt; **Portal Gun (Plunder)** - Select a dead Green Kraken player from the graveyard. They will be revived as a Skeletal Snakekeeper.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Plagiarist[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Ritualist[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(Portal Gun) Portal of Corax** - Targeted dead Cultist will be revived as a Blood Skeleton. - 1 use

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Skeletal Snakekeeper[/color]
&gt; [color=springgreen]**Green Kraken Killing**[/color]
**Undead (Passive)** - You appear dead to all other forum members. You cannot talk to the living or vote.
**Rotting (Passive)** - You will die in 2 nights after being revived.
**Serpent&#39;s Guard (Night)** - Kill any attackers who attack targeted player. - 2 uses
**Skeletal Fangs (Night)** - Kill target player. - 1 use
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; **Convert Immune**

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Snakekeeper[/color]
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Killer[/color]**
**Snake&#39;s Retaliation (Day)** - Kill yourself and target player, bypassing death immunity. - 1 use
**Snake&#39;s Venom (Day)** - Poison target player, they will die in 2 nights. - 2 uses
**Snake&#39;s Delay (Night)** - If targeted player is supposed to die tonight, they will instead die tomorrow. - Infinite uses
**Snake&#39;s Distraction (Night)** - If an attacker attacks target player, their attack will be redirected into themself, bypassing death immunity. - 3 uses
**Snake Army (Plunder)** - If target player has killed or converted anybody, you will kill them, bypassing everything.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Serpent[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Invoker[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(Snake&#39;s Venom) Worm&#39;s Venom** - Poison target player. They will die in 2 nights. The second use of this ability will expend a use of the Cult Leader’s “Injection” - 2 uses
&gt; **(Snake Army) Worm Army** - The Cult Leader&#39;s eradicate will bypass everything tonight.

&gt; Credit to @psychoneirik as I pretty much ripped off Golden Dragon Royal Guard&#39;s day ability.

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Stealthy[/color] :crossed_swords: 
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Investigative[/color]**
&gt; **Cultist&#39;s Scent (Day)** - Find out who the Cult Leader killed at the end of the day. - 2 uses
&gt; **Nightly Hideout (Day)** - Find out if any Cultists attempted to visit target player tonight. This will stay on targeted player until you use Smoke Bomb or change your target with this ability. This does not count as a visit. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Swift Judgement (Night)** - Find out if targeted player is a member of the Cult. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Ambush (Plunder)** - Select a target, you and them will be death and convert immune tonight. Any Cult members visiting them tonight will die.
*Your objective is to defeat the Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=darkred]The Seeker[/color]**. Does not appear in Unseen games.
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 1 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(Cultist&#39;s Scent) Smoke Bomb** - If targeted player gets Investigated, they will show up with incorrect results. - Infinite uses
&gt; **(Nightly Hideout) Blood Hideout** - You may see the First Mate&#39;s conversation logs tonight. - 1 use
&gt; **(Swift Judgement) Mithras&#39; Judgement** - If targeted player is part of the Green Kraken, learn of their class. - Infinite uses
&gt; **(Ambush) Ambush of Corax** - Instantly kill any player, bypassing night immunity and heals.

&gt; ## [color=springgreen]The Treasure Keeper[/color]
&gt; **[color=springgreen]Green Kraken Offensive[/color]**
**Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
&gt; **Rich (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Money Bags (Day)** - If targeted player uses a day ability, they will target themself. - 2 uses
&gt; **Bribe (Night)** - Make a player target another player. Any conversions you redirect will not work. Attacks that get redirected into other players will also not work. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Full House (Night)** - Targeted player will be redirected into themself tonight, bypassing redirection immunity. - 2 uses
&gt; **Straight Flush (Plunder)** - You may redirect a player bypassing redirect immunity, any attacks or conversions you redirect will be nullified.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen or Cult and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Converts into **[color=purple]The Scrooge[/color]** or **[color=darkred]The Invoker[/color]**
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]

[/details]

## [color=#560156]T[/color][color=#610161]h[/color][color=#6b006b]e[/color] [color=#800080]U[/color][color=#800080]n[/color][color=#760076]s[/color][color=#6b006b]e[/color][color=#610161]e[/color][color=#560156]n[/color]
[details=&quot;Show&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=purple]The Assassin[/color] :crossed_swords: :shield: 
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Killer**[/color]
**Nightshade (Day)** - Poison target player, they will die after 2 nights. Bypassing death immunity unless they are healed. - 4 uses (shared)
**Distract (Day)** - - Distract a player, rendering them unable to any day abilities for the rest of the day. - 1 use
**Assassinate (Night)** - Kill a player. - Infinite uses
**2-For-1 (Night):** - Kill two players tonight. - 1 use (shared)
**No Limits (Plunder)** - Kill a player bypassing everything that could prevent you from killing them.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Buccaneer[/color] 
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Investigative[/color]**
&gt; **Sonar System (Day)** - Choose what you are going to find using Purple Flare/Shadelight Flare tonight. Killer/Offensive, Support/Social, Investigative/Special. By default this ability will start on Killer/Offensive.
&gt; **Purple Flare (Night)** - Find out what classtype target player is if they match your Sonar System Criteria. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Shadelight Flare (Night)** - If targeted player fits the criteria, find out their exact class. Additionally, this will frame the target to Investigators. - 3 uses
&gt; **Expedition (Plunder)** - Find out two target player&#39;s exact classes.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Dictator[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Social[/color]**
**Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
**Peer Pressure (Day)** - Force target player to vote whatever you vote while somebody is on trial. - 2 uses
**Higher Identity (Day)** - Add an extra vote by the name of &quot;Quarter Master&quot; to whoever you are currently voting. - 2 uses
**Rank Change (Night)** - Give/remove targeted player&#39;s leadership qualities. - 3 uses
**Secretive Gossip (Night)** - You and targeted player will be able to send a 1000 character message to eachother for the day. - 2 uses
**Argggh You Kidding Me? (Plunder)** - If an Unseen player is supposed to be executed tomorrow, they will not be executed and there will instead be another execution.
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken and any Neutrals who stand against you*

&gt;## [color=purple]The Engineer[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Offensive**[/color]
&gt; **Wall Off (Day)** - Only Unseen members will have the ability to visit targeted player tonight - 2 uses
&gt; **Flimsy Tools (Night)** - Targeted player will unknowingly occupy player they targeted if their targeted player is not Unseen. If they are already occupying a player. They will occupy another random player - Infinite uses
&gt; **Jumpscare (Night)** - Anybody visiting targeted player will be redirected to the other targeted player - 4 uses
**Launch Trap (Plunder)** - Anybody visiting target player will be redirected to one of the two adjacent players on the list.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Entrepreneur :shield: [/color]
&gt;[color=purple]**Unseen Offensive**[/color]
**Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
**Secretive Plunder (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - 2 uses - One day cooldown.
**Economical Corruption (Night)** - Only the Assassin will be able to visit target player if they are using a plunder ability. This ability will fail on attempt to use it if they die tonight - 1 use
**Hijack (Night)** - Remove target player&#39;s privilege to use a plunder ability - 1 use
**Prestige (Plunder)** - Give targeted player who already has used their plunder ability the ability to plunder.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Evil Captain[/color] :shield: :crossed_swords:  
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Special**[/color]
&gt; **Leader of the Crew (Passive)** - There must always be a captain. If you are killed, a new captain must be voted for the following day. If you are executed for treason, all future captains will be unable to use ‘Plunder yer Booty’. (starting Green Kraken Captain only)
**My Word is Law (Passive)** - Your votes to accuse players passively count as 2.
**Plunder yer Booty (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - Unlimited Uses, 1 Day Cooldown.
**Coup de Grace (Day)** - Decide the fate of the player currently on the plank. - 1 use.
**Keep Watch (Night)** - Protect a player, making them immune to attacks tonight. - 3 Uses.
**Cursed Treasure (Night)** - If the targeted player tries to use their plunder ability tonight, they will die and the ability will fail - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Credit to @Marluxion
&gt; Crowned from:
&gt; Unseen classes
&gt; Warlock (In an Unseen Game)

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Fraud[/color]
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Investigative[/color]**
&gt; **Underdeck (Day)** - You will see The First Mate&#39;s conversation tonight. - 1 uses
&gt; **Nightly Research (Night)** - If targeted player is Green Kraken. You will be able to see their class. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Test of Skills (Night)** - You may see the night result of targeted player. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Forged Documents (Plunder)** - Target player&#39;s logbook will only be able to be read by the Unseen if they die at night, it will appear blank to everybody else. Their class will show up as a random non unique Green Kraken class on death.
*Your objective is to defeat the Unseen and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Mastermind[/color] :crossed_swords: :shield: 
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Special**[/color]
**Can&#39;t Touch This (Passive)** - You cannot be killed at night. Additionally, you are occupy immune. You will be alerted upon occupy and redirect attempts. You will know if someone tries to occupy you or change your target.
**Lurking Presence (Passive)** - If you are killed within the first 3 nights your next in line will take your place as the Mastermind, you appear as a Green Kraken to investigators for those 3 nights.
**Dirty Work (Day)** - If there are no Unseen members left, you can become the Assassin at the beginning of the night. - May only use if you are the only living Unseen member.
**Foresight (Day)** - Find out targeted player&#39;s classtype if they can be converted. - 4 uses (shared)
**Convert (Night)** - Convert a player to the Unseen. - Infinite uses - 1 night cooldown on success
**Advanced Convert (Plunder)** - If you are executed on trial tomorrow, targeted Unseen member will become the new Mastermind. This Mastermind will not have Can&#39;t Touch This or Lurking Presence.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Onlooker[/color] 
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Investigative[/color]**
&gt; **Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
&gt; **Hawk&#39;s Sight (Day)** - See the result of target dead player&#39;s final ability tonight. Even if they would not be notified normally. You will know who they targeted. - 3 uses
&gt; **Crow&#39;s Nest (Day)** - Learn if target player used a day ability at the start of tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Telescope (Night)** - See who target player targeted tonight. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Extra Crackers (Plunder)** - You may see who target player targeted tonight and who visited them.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Outlaw :shield: [/color]
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Killer [/color]**
&gt; **A Pirate’s Life (Passive)** - Immune to redirection but not occupation. Every three nights, you will gain a usage of Barrel Explosion.
&gt; **Barrel Explosion (Day)** - Prevent the current lynch from occurring. You will kill a target player amidst the chaos. - Uses before convert
&gt; **Spinning Wheel (Night)** - An exact class that is in the current game will show to you. (Cannot be a guaranteed class or a class that has already been shown to you) - Infinite uses
&gt; **Hostage (Night)** - Target a player, they will be occupied and the Unseen will be told the target’s exact class - 2 use
&gt; **Wild Shotgun (Plunder)** - Pick a class from the class list, you will know everyone who is that specific class.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Plagiarist[/color]
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Social[/color]**
&gt; **Experimental (Passive)** - Immune to poison and bleeding.
&gt; **Fake Spider Fangs (Day)** - Targeted player will believe that they were poisoned. - 2 uses
&gt; **Confusion Ray (Night)** - Targeted player will believe they were redirected tonight if they would get the notification normally. - 3 uses
&gt; **Robot&#39;s Disguise (Night)** - If target player dies tonight, they will appear as selected class. - 1 use
&gt; **Portal Gun (Plunder)** - Select a dead Unseen player from the graveyard. They will be revived as a Skeletal Serpent.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Scrooge[/color]
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
**Leader Characteristics (Passive)** - Upon voting a new captain, your votes will privately count as two. You will keep this passive upon class change.
&gt; **Rich (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Money Bags (Day)** - If targeted player uses a day ability, they will target themself. - 2 uses
&gt; **Bribe (Night)** - Make a player target another player. Attacks that get redirected into other players will also fail. - Infinite uses
&gt; **Full House (Night)** - Targeted player will be redirected into themself tonight, bypassing redirection immunity. - 2 uses
&gt; **Straight Flush (Plunder)** - You may redirect a player bypassing redirect immunity, any attacks you redirect will be nullified.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Skeletal Serpent[/color]
&gt; [color=purple]**Unseen Killing**[/color]
**Undead (Passive)** - You appear dead to all other forum members. You cannot talk to the living or vote.
**Rotting (Passive)** - You will die in 2 nights after being revived.
**Serpent&#39;s Guard (Night)** - Defend target Unseen member for the night, preventing visitors. - 1 use
**Skeletal Fangs (Night)** - Kill target player. - 1 use
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Serpent[/color]
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
**Serpent&#39;s Venom (Day)** - Poison targeted player. The second use of this ability will expend a use of the Assassin’s “Nightshade” - 2 uses
**Serpent&#39;s Delay (Night)** - If targeted player is supposed to die tonight, they will instead die tomorrow. - Infinite uses
**Serpent&#39;s Distraction (Night)** - Target player will be redirected into themself. - Infinite uses
**Serpent Army (Plunder)** - The Assassin&#39;s kill tonight will work no matter what.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Steward[/color]
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Offensive[/color]**
&gt; **Wall of Barrels (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; **Roast Pork (Day)** - Targeted player will be occupied today and tonight. - 4 uses
&gt; **Nightly Preparations (Night)** - Roast Pork will bypass occupy immunity tomorrow. - 2 uses
&gt; **Barrel Drop (Night)** - Kill the Captain tonight. - 1 use
&gt; **All You Can Eat Buffet (Plunder)** - Targeted player will be occupied all of tomorrow and the day after tomorrow.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; Credit to @Firelitten for helping with this class.

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Versifier[/color] :shield: 
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Social[/color]**
&gt; **Musical Network (Passive)** - You still have access to your Bard network. Players will have access to your network for one more day if they die.
&gt; **In Space, No One Can Hear You Scream (Passive)** - Once you die or become Captain. Your network will cease to exist. This passive will carry over upon class change even if you already have 2 passives as that class.
&gt; **Song of Connections (Day)** - Targeted living or dead player will be added to the network chat tonight. - Infinite uses - 1 night cooldown
&gt; **Song of Disapproval (Night)** - Remove target player from the network chat at the end of tonight. - 4 uses
&gt; **Song of Shade (Night)** - Make all Unseen members appear as Green Kraken in Investigative results tonight - 2 uses
&gt; **Song of Dark Matter (Plunder)** - You will take over the worker’s body tomorrow night. The worker will think that they weren&#39;t working for the First Mate and would appear to be occupied.
&gt; *Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*
[/details]

### [color=#3e0000]T[/color][color=#630000]h[/color][color=#770000]e[/color] [color=#8b0000]C[/color][color=#770000]u[/color][color=#630000]l[/color][color=#3e0000]t[/color]
[details=&quot;Show&quot;]

&gt; Cult Convert Plunder Abilities are dependent on their Converted Class/Starting Cult Class Choice.

&gt; ## [color=darkred]The Apostle[/color]
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Social**[/color]
**Dark Words (Passive)** While you live, living and dead Cult members can communicate at night.
**Mind Warp (Night)** - Cause a player to recieve incorrect feedback with their abilities tonight. - 3 uses
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken and any Neutrals who stand against you*

&gt; ## [color=darkred]The Blood Skeleton[/color]
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Killing**[/color]
**Undead (Passive)** - You appear dead to all other forum members. You cannot talk to the living or vote.
**Rotting (Passive)** - You will die in 2 nights after being revived.
**Skeletal Worm (Night)** - Defend target Cultist for the night, preventing visitors. - 1 use
**Flaming Skull (Night)** - Kill the target player. - 1 use
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken and any Neutrals who stand against you*

&gt; ## [color=darkred]The Cult Leader[/color] :shield: :crossed_swords:  
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Special**[/color]
**Train (Passive)** - At any point before the start of the first night, you may message the GM and choose the Cult alts that the Cult class that spawned with you will receive, based on a non-unique class they can be converted from. If you do not choose the Cult alts, they will receive a random valid set.
**Corax&#39;s Blessing (Passive)** - You will know if you are occupied or redirected while using Brainwash.
**Disguise (Day)** - If the target player dies tonight, they will appear as a class of your choice. - 3 uses
**Inject (Day)** - Poison targeted player. They will die in two nights. - 4 uses (shared)
**Brainwash (Night)** - Attempt to convert a player to the Cult. If you have failed to convert a target twice already and your next conversion would fail it will instead target a random convertible player. - Infinite uses - 1 night cooldown
**Blood of Mithras (Night)** - Kill a Cult player and a non-Cult player. The first use of this will not kill the cult player. - Infinite uses
**Dark God&#39;s Mastermind (Plunder)** - You will become death immune upon using this. Additionally you will gain occupy and redirection immunity. (shared between Cult Leaders)
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken and any Neutrals who stand against you*

&gt; ## [color=darkred]The Devout Captain[/color] :shield: :crossed_swords:  
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Special**[/color]
&gt; **Leader of the Crew (Passive)** - There must always be a captain. If you are killed, a new captain must be voted for the following day. If you are executed for treason, all future captains will be unable to use ‘Plunder yer Booty’. (starting Green Kraken Captain only)
**My Word is Law (Passive)** - Your votes to accuse players passively count as 2.
**Plunder yer Booty (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - Unlimited Uses, 1 Day Cooldown.
**Coup de Grace (Day)** - Decide the fate of the player currently on the plank. - 1 use.
**Keep Watch (Night)** - Protect a player, making them immune to attacks tonight. - 3 Uses.
**Blood Rites (Night)** - Summon the Shade of Mithras upon the Xed. All Cultists will be informed of his presence. After using this ability once, it changes into “Blood Price”. - 1 use
*Your objective is to defeat the Green Kraken and any Neutrals that oppose you*

&gt; **Blood Price (Night)** - Cause the Shade of Mithras to torment a crew member, occupying them tonight. - Unlimited Uses.

&gt; Credit to @Marluxion

&gt; Crowned from:
&gt; Cult classes
&gt; Warlock (In a Cult Game)

&gt; ## [color=AC0300]The Invoker[/color]
&gt; [color=AC0300]**Cult Offensive**[/color]
**Fanatic (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing.
**Bewilder (Day)** - Prevent target player from using day abilities and occupy them tonight. - 1 use
**Strings of Mithras (Night)** - Control a player, choosing who they target tonight. - 2 uses
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken and any Neutrals who stand against you*

&gt; ## [color=AC0300]The Ritualist[/color]
&gt; [color=AC0300]**Cult Support**[/color]
**Will of Mithras (Day)** - Cultists will appear as Green Kraken tonight. - 1 use
**Strength of Corax (Night)** - The Cult Leader’s Blood of Mithras will bypass night immunity tonight. - 1 use
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken and any Neutrals who stand against you*

&gt; ## [color=darkred]The Seeker[/color]
&gt; [color=darkred]**Cult Investigative**[/color]
**Expose (Day)** - Find out the next player to use a day ability. - 1 use
**Gaze (Night)** - Learn a player&#39;s classtype. - 2 uses
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken and any Neutrals who stand against you*

[/details]

## [color=#717171]N[/color][color=#828282]e[/color][color=#929292]u[/color][color=#b6b6b6]t[/color][color=#b6b6b6]r[/color][color=#b6b6b6]a[/color][color=#929292]l[/color][color=#828282]s[/color][color=#717171]:[/color]
[details=&quot;Show&quot;]
&gt; ## [color=darkgreen]The Alchemist[/color]
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Support**[/color]
**Coagulate (Passive)** - Immune to Nightshade.
**Stoneskin Poison (Day)** - Make yourself night immune tonight - 4 uses
**Crimson Potion (Night)** - Heal someone from wounds or poison.
**Emerald Potion (Night)** - Poison a player, killing them - 2 uses
**Gold Creation (Plunder)** - Upon using this, stoneskin potions will be automatically used whenever you are attacked.
*Your objective is to remain alive until the game ends*

&gt; ## [color=red] The Begrudged Captain[/color]
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Special**[/color]
&gt; **Leader of the Crew (Passive)** - There must always be a captain. If you are killed, a new captain must be voted for the following day.
**My Word is Law (Passive)** - Your votes to accuse players passively count as 2.
**Plunder yer Booty (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - Unlimited Uses, 1 Day Cooldown.
**Coup de Grace (Day)** - Decide the fate of the player currently on the plank. - 1 use.
**Keep Watch (Night)** - Protect a player, making them immune to attacks tonight. - 3 Uses.
**Contraband (Night)** - Send a guard to frame your target. They will appear as a member of the Unseen or Cult, depending on which is present in the current game. - 3 uses
*Your objective is your previous wincon.*

&gt; ## [color=lightgrey] The Cowardly Captain[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Special**[/color]
&gt; **Spiteful of the Crew (Passive)** - There must always be a captain. If you are killed, a new captain must be voted for the following day. Additionally, one player of your choice who executed you will be killed out of spite of your death. You must choose a player or a random player will be killed
**My Word is Law (Passive)** - Your votes to accuse players passively count as 2.
**Plunder yer Booty (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - Unlimited Uses, 1 Day Cooldown.
**Coup de Grace (Day)** - Decide the fate of the player currently on the plank. - 1 use.
**Keep Watch (Night)** - Protect a player, making them immune to attacks tonight. - 3 Uses.
*Your objective is to remain alive until the game ends*

&gt; ## [color=darkorange]The Demon[/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color=lightgrey]Neutral Killer[/color]**
&gt;**Cloak Of Mithras (Passive)** - Immune to death and occupation at night, you will be alerted upon occupy and redirect attempts.
**Haemophilia (Day)** - Increases the power of Funeral Pyre at night, - 1 Day Cooldown - 3 uses
**Funeral Pyre (Night)** - Set your target ablaze. If Haemophilia is used, anyone who comes in contact with the target is eaten alive by the half-melted corpse. - Infinite uses
**Hell&#39;s Rupture (Plunder)** - Summon flames from hell, killing your target and causing anybody who is visiting your target to die, bypassing all forms of protection.
&gt;*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken, the Unseen, the Cult and any Neutrals who stand in your way*

&gt; **Convert Immune**

&gt; Credit to Bounty.
&gt; Credit to @Strangle for the Plunder ability 

&gt; ## [color=darkgreen]The Druid[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Killer**[/color]
**Wall of Nature (Passive)** - You are immune to death and poison.
**Root Network (Passive)** - The roots will prevent you from visiting someone if it would lead to your death. Players whose rooms have been rooted will investigate as ‘Your targets room is damaged by roots!’ to all investigatives for the first two nights they are rooted alongside their usual investigative result.
**Judgement of the Wild (Day)** - Publicly mark someone, you will gain a use of Constricting Roots if they aren’t dead by the next day. - Infinite uses, 1 day cooldown
**Rune of Growth (Day)** - Spreading Roots can target two people tonight. - Infinite uses, 1 day cooldown
**Spreading Roots (Night)** - Curl roots around a player’s room. - Infinite uses
**Constricting Roots (Night)** - Kill all players that are rooted. - 0 uses
**Indoor Jungle (Plunder)** - All players who visit target player along with the player tonight will be entangled in vines. They will not know that they were entangled.
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken, the Unseen, the Cult and any Neutrals who stand in your way*

&gt; Credit to @Icibalus

&gt; ## [color=lime]The Electrocutioner[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Killer**[/color]
&gt;**Static Shield (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night.
**Discharge (Day)** - A public announcement will be made to the court that “The Electrocutioner is using Discharge!”. If you are still alive at the end of the night, all charged players will be killed (Bypasses death immunity). - Infinite uses, 2 day cooldown
**Charge (Night)** - Apply a static charge to a player. Anyone they visit tonight will also become charged, and you will know who they are. - Infinite uses
**Composition C-4 (Plunder)** - Kill target player, bypassing night immunity while static charging any players they visit and all players who visit them. You will know who your target visited and who visited them.
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken, the Unseen, the Cult and any Neutrals who stand in your way*

&gt; Credit to Unoski and Vulgard

&gt; ## [color=darkolivegreen] The Fanatical Captain[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Special**[/color]
&gt; **Leader of the Crew (Passive)** - There must always be a captain. If you are killed, a new captain must be voted for the following day.
**My Word is Law (Passive)** - Your votes to accuse players passively count as 2.
**Plunder yer Booty (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - Unlimited Uses, 1 Day Cooldown.
**Coup de Grace (Day)** - Decide the fate of the player currently on the plank. - 1 use.
**Keep Watch (Night)** - Protect a player, making them immune to attacks tonight. - 3 Uses.
**Biased Guard (Night)** - Your target will be death immune tonight. - Infinite uses
*Your objective is to ensure that your target remains alive until the end of the game, your target is [x]*

&gt; ##  [color=darkolivegreen]The Mercenary[/color]
&gt; **Neutral Support**
**Looking For Work (Passive)** - If your original target dies, you have 3 days to find a new target, otherwise you will commit suicide.
**Failure (Passive)** - If both your original target and new target die, you will commit suicide since you can no longer find work.
**Offer Contract (Day)** If your original target dies, you can form a new contract. - 3 uses
**Stand Guard (Night)** - Protect your target from visits, and grant yourself immunity to death tonight. - 4 uses
**Rebound (Night)** - Kill a player who accused your target of treason earlier in the day. - 1 use
**Important Guard (Plunder)** - Kill all players visiting your target, bypassing night immunity. Additionally you will be night immune.
*Your objective is to ensure that your target remains alive until the end of the game, your target is [x]*

&gt;Converts into **[color=632A94]The Sellsword[/color]** or **[color=AC0300]The Ritualist[/color]**
&gt;[color=AC0300]**Cult Alts:**[/color]
&gt;[color=AC0300]**Cult Points: 2 - Each ability costs: 1**[/color]
&gt; **(Offer Contract) Faustian Contract (Day)** - Offer a player a contract. If they accept this contract, later that day they will be poisoned, dying in 2 nights. - 1 use
&gt; **(Stand Guard) Blood Shield (Night)** - Prevent all visits to a Cult player of your choosing. - 3 Uses.
&gt; **(Important Guard) Important Cultist (Plunder)** - Kill all players visiting target Cult player.

&gt; ## [color=darkblue]The Possessor[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Killer**[/color]
**Driven (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing, you will be alerted upon occupy and redirect attempts.
**Blackened Shield (Passive)** - Immune to death at night
**Puppet Strings (Night)** - Control a player, forcing them to kill someone and making it so you can see their whispers tomorrow.
**Possess (Night)** - Kill the target player. Their class will appear as one of your choice, and they will have information in their logbook of your choosing (or no logbook if nothing is specified). You will know what class they truly were, and what their logbook said. - 3 uses
**Split Will (Plunder)** - Change targeted player&#39;s wincon into yours if they are able to be converted. If you die at any time. They will become the new Possessor. These players will be able to talk to you at night and will show up as Neutral to any investigative checks.
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken, the Unseen, the Cult and any Neutrals who stand in your way*

&gt; ## [color=#ff0000]T[/color][color=#ff2000]h[/color][color=#ff4000]e[/color] [color=#ff7f00]P[/color][color=#ff9f00]s[/color][color=#ffbf00]y[/color][color=#ffdf00]c[/color][color=#ffff00]h[/color][color=#bfff00]o[/color][color=#80ff00]p[/color][color=#40ff00]a[/color][color=#00ff00]t[/color][color=#00ff55]h[/color][color=#00ffaa]i[/color][color=#00ffff]c[/color] [color=#0080ff]C[/color][color=#0040ff]a[/color][color=#0000ff]p[/color][color=#2300ff]t[/color][color=#4600ff]a[/color][color=#6800ff]i[/color][color=#8b00ff]n[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Special**[/color]
&gt; **Leader of the Crew (Passive)** - There must always be a captain. If you are killed, a new captain must be voted for the following day.
**Blackmailing Word (Passive)** - Your votes to accuse players passively count as 2. Additionally you are night immune.
**Plunder yer Booty (Day)** - Grant a player treasure. This enables them to use their special plunder ability once. Cannot be used on the same player twice. - Unlimited Uses, 1 Day Cooldown.
**Coup de Grace (Day)** - Decide the fate of the player currently on the plank. - 1 use.
**Keep Watch (Night)** - Kill targeted player - Infinite Uses.
**Possessed Treasure (Night)** - If the targeted player tries to use their plunder ability tonight, they will die and the ability will fail - 3 uses
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken, the Unseen, the Cult and any Neutrals who stand in your way*

&gt; Crowned from:
&gt; Neutral Killers

&gt; ##  [color=black]The Reaper[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Killer**[/color]
**Consume Soul (Passive)** - If you die at night with at least one soul, you will consume it and come back to life. You start with two souls. (Does NOT work if executed by The Prince)
**Icy Touch (Day)** - Consume two souls to prevent a player from using day and night abilities today. The target will only be aware of being prevented if they attempt to use a day ability , and they will appear occupied at night. - Infinite uses
**Reap (Night)** - Reap the soul of a player, killing them and occupying them. The victim can not be healed. You will gain one soul on a successful reap. - Infinite uses
**Gathered Darkness (Night)** - Consume two souls to kill a player. Bypasses death immunity, and the victim can not be healed. They will have information in their logbook of your choosing (or no logbook if nothing is specified), and you will receive their real logbook when they die. - Infinite uses
**Davy Jones&#39; Locker (Plunder)** - Double the amount of souls you have.
*Your objective is to Eliminate the Green Kraken, the Unseen, the Cult and any Neutrals who stand in your way*

&gt; **Convert Immune**

&gt; Credit to @CheesyKnives

&gt; ##  [color=red]The Scorned[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Social**[/color]
**Resolve (Passive)** - Immune to occupation and target changing. Immune to death at night.
**Frame (Night)** - Make a target appear suspicious to investigative abilities.
**Bait and Switch (Night)** - Swap a player with one of your targets, redirecting all actions on one to the other. - 3 uses
**Costume (Plunder)** - You will appear as a Green Kraken class of your choice to investigative checks for the rest of the game.
*Your objective is to live to see 1 of your targets Executed, they are [X], [Y]*

&gt; ## [color=Aquamarine]The Warlock[/color] :shield:
&gt; [color=lightgrey]**Neutral Offensive**[/color]
**Bend Reality (Passive)** - As long as you remain alive, Green Kraken classes that are passively immune to occupation are not.
**Dark Magic (Passive)** - You appear as a member of the Unseen or Cult (depending on which is present in the game) to investigations.
**Detect Thoughts (Day)** - Cast a spell that reveals your target’s last night action to you. - 4 uses
**Carnage (Day)** - Cast a spell that causes all kills tonight to bypass all forms of protection or prevention. - 1 use
**Mind Control (Night)** - Cast a spell that forces your target to target somebody of your choosing. - 3 uses
**Seeming (Night)** - Make yourself and one other person of your choice appear as members of the Green Kraken to investigations. - 2 uses
**The Shadows (Plunder)** - Make yourself and one other person of your choice appear as members of the Green Kraken for 3 nights, if you die. Their shade will be uncovered.
*See the Green Kraken defeated.*

&gt; Credit to @ThePlex
 
[/details]


(note that many classes are still being reworked)




Credit to xicidis for helping with names and @Strangle for helping me come up with some names and plunder abilities. Credit to the FoL team too.
All other credits for specific classes are absolutely fine.

### Dumb quicklinks:

[Vote For What Gets Reworked Next](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/232?u=pug)
[Official Interpretation of Xed Classes](https://forum.imperium42.com/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/233?u=pug)

**Changelogs**
07/21/18 - Ability rewords and updates to make the game more suitable for the minor feedback change.
5/08/18 - Finished everything.
26/08/18 - Changed the name of &quot;Lookout Pole&quot; to Crow&#39;s Nest.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 05:00:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum of Lies</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just want to pack as much new shit possible and balance that new shit so the game isnt just a boring balance patch</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/249">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/249</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 05:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-249</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>its definitely about time for another Xed to arise.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/248">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/248</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-248</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah but thing is are all of them original/swapped abilities?</p>
<p>no.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/247">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/247</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-247</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My SFoL still has more classes than yours <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/246">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/246</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-246</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean if I wasnt so lazy and set my time aside for Xed 4.0 I could do it.</p>
<p>but thing is I’m adding even more classes now.<br>
Expect new NKs, a new scumfaction which plays on gaining plunder abilities and neut reworks</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/245">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/245</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-245</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We need more SFoLs pug</p>
<p><em>wink</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/244">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/244</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-244</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Memesky" data-post="241" data-topic="63502">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/memesky/40/6386_2.png" class="avatar"> Memesky:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>nk called Pirates <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Green Kraken are good pirates lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/243">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/243</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-243</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Livicus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then why not you design it for him</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/242">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/242</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-242</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Memesky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How bouta another scum faction or nk called Pirates <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/thinking.png?v=9" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/241">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/241</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-241</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>thy finnish</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/240">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/240</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-240</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Revived!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/239">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/239</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 04:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-239</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Yes.</h2>
<h3>14 days is tomorrow.</h3>
<h1>Scientist has finally been released.</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/238">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/238</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 05:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-238</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Jokes on youuuuu. Im making it tomorrow because Mental Health &gt; Forum Games</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/237">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/237</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 12:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-237</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>New reworks hopefully coming out today</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/236">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/236</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-236</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/235">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/235</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-235</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ill be removing cabin boy/swabbie</p>
<p>Both are way too gimmicky of classes</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/234">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/234</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 06:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-234</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1><font color="springgreen">Anyway, what class is next?</font></h1>
<p>btw green kraken’s class color is springgreen if you would like it.</p>
<p><s>return of the green kraken coming someday</s></p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-close="2018-06-08T08:26:00.000Z" data-poll-max="3" data-poll-min="1" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-type="multiple" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="ee9fc7ea9c781752141639447f9582ad">Bard/Versifier</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="2c39f2c63b700fc3fb35a3142b0ad3c2">Cooper/Exploiter</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="56f1bfcdc989f7466ecd2c7dcf9645b3">Navigator/Onlooker</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="a44c805f52b9c51f9ee7c8145a549d99">Private Investigator/Information Fraud (PI/IF)</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="d41c9e3822e77b26ea05eecfef050347">Quarter Master/Dictator</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="eca05f1849a99f4fc45be65ac908c9a3">Scientist/Plagiarist and Skeletons</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="776ce16518ea45fb6e197a5e587b0131">Snakekeeper/Serpent</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="93288a3c353a01497f19739faa3e4519">Stealthy</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="39a64842e330582f06839d519c43903c">Treasure Keeper/Scrooge</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/232">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/232</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-232</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll be putting up signups for a new forum mafia in like 5 minutes tho</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/231">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/231</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 07:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-231</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thx Marl.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/230">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/230</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 07:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-230</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marluxion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pug can’t even start until Casino or ROTBD is over</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/229">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/229</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 07:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-229</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Im bored asf so host soon. Im legit making a game with the free time I have and its annoying me</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/228">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/228</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 05:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-228</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/pug">@Pug</a> 3 votes for Offensive lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/227">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/227</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 05:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-227</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I forgot shield and swords so I fixed it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/226">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/226</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 04:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-226</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m going to add offensive now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/225">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/225</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 04:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-225</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would say more… offensive?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/224">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502/224</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 04:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-63502-224</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/siege-on-xed-sfol-3-0-main-thread/63502.rss">Siege on Xed SFoL 3.0 Main Thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
