<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Banshee (Neutral) becomes Poltergeist (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-banshee-neutral-becomes-poltergeist-unseen/34439</link>
    <description>**Banshee** (Neutral Social?)

Passive 1:
**Vengeful Spirit** - You cannot be killed when successfully using either of your night abilities. In other words, you can be killed if you are occupied, don&#39;t use an ability, etc. Otherwise you are immune.

Passive 2:
**Fading Memory** - You cannot be converted after you&#39;ve won.

Day Ability:
**Spectral Shriek** - Send an anonymous message to all players EXCEPT your target. In other words, select one player to be excluded from hearing your anonymous message. (2 uses.)

Night Ability 1:
**Read Aura** - See a player&#39;s exact class. (3 uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**Icy Grip** - Choose two players. If they are different factions, they will both be occupied. (Unlimited use.)

Goal:
Prevent three murders with your **Icy Grip** ability. (Players you choose do not need to be attacking each other, you simply need to prevent ANY type of night time murder by occupying the attacker. It even counts if you stop a Blue Dragon from killing.)

----

Converts to...

----

**Poltergeist** (Unseen)

Day Ability:
**Deafening Howl** - Send an anonymous message to all players EXCEPT your target. You will not be anonymous to fellow Unseen members. (2 uses.)

Night Ability 1:
**Obscure Aura** - Cause anyone investigating your target to be prevented. Can be used on any non-King player, including Unseen. (3 uses.)

Night Ability 2:
**Wall of Noise** - Choose two players. If they are the same faction, they will be prevented from visiting each other. Stop a Physician from healing BD, keep a suspected player from being cleared, etc. (3 uses.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 04:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-banshee-neutral-becomes-poltergeist-unseen/34439.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Banshee (Neutral) becomes Poltergeist (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Banshee</strong> (Neutral Social?)</p>
<p>Passive 1:<br>
<strong>Vengeful Spirit</strong> - You cannot be killed when successfully using either of your night abilities. In other words, you can be killed if you are occupied, don’t use an ability, etc. Otherwise you are immune.</p>
<p>Passive 2:<br>
<strong>Fading Memory</strong> - You cannot be converted after you’ve won.</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Spectral Shriek</strong> - Send an anonymous message to all players EXCEPT your target. In other words, select one player to be excluded from hearing your anonymous message. (2 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Read Aura</strong> - See a player’s exact class. (3 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Icy Grip</strong> - Choose two players. If they are different factions, they will both be occupied. (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p>Goal:<br>
Prevent three murders with your <strong>Icy Grip</strong> ability. (Players you choose do not need to be attacking each other, you simply need to prevent ANY type of night time murder by occupying the attacker. It even counts if you stop a Blue Dragon from killing.)</p>
<hr>
<p>Converts to…</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Poltergeist</strong> (Unseen)</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Deafening Howl</strong> - Send an anonymous message to all players EXCEPT your target. You will not be anonymous to fellow Unseen members. (2 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Obscure Aura</strong> - Cause anyone investigating your target to be prevented. Can be used on any non-King player, including Unseen. (3 uses.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Wall of Noise</strong> - Choose two players. If they are the same faction, they will be prevented from visiting each other. Stop a Physician from healing BD, keep a suspected player from being cleared, etc. (3 uses.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-banshee-neutral-becomes-poltergeist-unseen/34439/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-banshee-neutral-becomes-poltergeist-unseen/34439/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-34439-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-banshee-neutral-becomes-poltergeist-unseen/34439.rss">[Class Suggestion] Banshee (Neutral) becomes Poltergeist (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
