<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Queen (Neutral)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440</link>
    <description>Day Ability 1: The King&#39;s Ear // Private Chambers
Passive: can whisper to the king secretly. // Can whisper with the king privately in both directions

This allows the Queen to share information with the king that the Queen gathered safely.

Day Ability 2: Royal Proceedings
Choose 2 targets, have a secret conversation with them in queen tab. 4 uses

This conversation happens during the day, if that&#39;s too hectic, instead the conversation can happen at night but must be selected during the day.

Night Ability 1: Expose Truth
Reveal the class of target 4 charges

This makes the queen a very powerful neutral role, able to choose sides and narrow down who you want to talk with during the day/night.

Night Ability 2 Promote (can&#39;t think of a better name)
Upgrade target to a more powerful role of their class (in most cases this would add a new ability or amplify an existing abilities to be more powerful) is announced to the players when the next day starts (if announcing to everyone proves to be controversial, only announce to king) 1 charge.

After confirming a players role and choosing a side, the Queen can bolster the forces of the side chosen, however this alerts the king (and maybe others) that the queen has chosen a side.

Win condition: Neutral - Survive. If you promote BD or Unseen/Cult you gain their respective win condition.

Lore:
With the King seeming unsure of the loyalty of his subjects the Queen sought to take matters into her own hands Collecting her most trusted subjects she devised a plan to ensure that the kingdom would thrive... her way...
 
Comments:
I thought it would be interesting to have a neutral character that truly was able to choose a side based on the flow of the game, you want to gain info as quickly as possible to possibly choose a promote target which changes your faction and win condition, however you may also wish to wait to discover which side will be winning, choose too early and perhaps your decision backfires, wait to choose too late and perhaps you become a casualty or choose the wrong side. However a key promote could lead to interesting gameplay mechanics.

If you have suggestions for upgraded classes or abilities feel free to share! Also taking suggestions to improve the Queen&#39;s abilities, if you can think of something better please don&#39;t be afraid to let me know!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 14:12:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Queen (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why would you want to relate info to the king?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 14:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10440-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440.rss">[Class Suggestion] Queen (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Queen (Neutral)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zeprido]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Day Ability 1: The King’s Ear // Private Chambers<br>
Passive: can whisper to the king secretly. // Can whisper with the king privately in both directions</p>
<p>This allows the Queen to share information with the king that the Queen gathered safely.</p>
<p>Day Ability 2: Royal Proceedings<br>
Choose 2 targets, have a secret conversation with them in queen tab. 4 uses</p>
<p>This conversation happens during the day, if that’s too hectic, instead the conversation can happen at night but must be selected during the day.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1: Expose Truth<br>
Reveal the class of target 4 charges</p>
<p>This makes the queen a very powerful neutral role, able to choose sides and narrow down who you want to talk with during the day/night.</p>
<p>Night Ability 2 Promote (can’t think of a better name)<br>
Upgrade target to a more powerful role of their class (in most cases this would add a new ability or amplify an existing abilities to be more powerful) is announced to the players when the next day starts (if announcing to everyone proves to be controversial, only announce to king) 1 charge.</p>
<p>After confirming a players role and choosing a side, the Queen can bolster the forces of the side chosen, however this alerts the king (and maybe others) that the queen has chosen a side.</p>
<p>Win condition: Neutral - Survive. If you promote BD or Unseen/Cult you gain their respective win condition.</p>
<p>Lore:<br>
With the King seeming unsure of the loyalty of his subjects the Queen sought to take matters into her own hands Collecting her most trusted subjects she devised a plan to ensure that the kingdom would thrive… her way…</p>
<p>Comments:<br>
I thought it would be interesting to have a neutral character that truly was able to choose a side based on the flow of the game, you want to gain info as quickly as possible to possibly choose a promote target which changes your faction and win condition, however you may also wish to wait to discover which side will be winning, choose too early and perhaps your decision backfires, wait to choose too late and perhaps you become a casualty or choose the wrong side. However a key promote could lead to interesting gameplay mechanics.</p>
<p>If you have suggestions for upgraded classes or abilities feel free to share! Also taking suggestions to improve the Queen’s abilities, if you can think of something better please don’t be afraid to let me know!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 09:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-10440-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-queen-neutral/10440.rss">[Class Suggestion] Queen (Neutral)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
