<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Dishonored (Cult)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589</link>
    <description>**Class:** The Dishonored (Cult) (Offensive)

**Backstory:** An impeached royal that has fallen into insanity, their grudge against the Blue dragons grew and their insanity lead them to warship mithras.

**Royal Blood:** Yes

**Converts from:** Royal bloods (Noble still converts to Apostle)

**Day ability: Royal Threat (x2)** - Make someone unable to talk for the rest of the day, if they do talk they will be killed from an arrow,  the message&quot;_You have been threatened by a fallen royal_&quot; will appear when this happens.  To prevent accidentally talking when this is used on the player, they are timed out for talking 5 seconds, this gives the CL 1 more use of eradicate.

**Day ability: Kingdom Heist (x1) -** Restock 1 of every person in the cults night abilities (For example, seeker would get +1 gaze and +1 identify) this does not work for the cult leader&#39;s abilities.

**Night ability: Royal sacrifice (x3) -** Sacrifice blood to mithras to gain night immunity for 1 - 2 members of the cult (1 member if there are 2 members of the cult, 2 members if there are 3)

**Night ability: Spiritual protection (x4) -** Summon demon spirits to make anybody who visits you bleed, the person bleeding will die in 2 nights, they will get the notification they would get if a hunter sent wolves after them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 02:44:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Dishonored (Cult)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Htm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>Converts from: Royal bloods (Noble still converts to Apostle)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Wait this is really confusing</p>
<p>so would princess/drunk convert to the dishonoured instead of their previous cult classes?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Day ability: Royal Threat (x2) - Make someone unable to talk for the rest of the day, if they do talk they will be killed from an arrow, the message"You have been threatened by a fallen royal" will appear when this happens. To prevent accidentally talking when this is used on the player, they are timed out for talking 5 seconds, this gives the CL 1 more use of eradicate.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>this is way to OP because you have bleeding plus CL’s killing ability meaning you can kill four people in one night, also if you’re gonna give it killing powers then it’s not really an offensive class, it’s a killer class, only way I can see this working is if you made it kind of like reaper’s chill</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Day ability: Kingdom Heist (x1) - Restock 1 of every person in the cults night abilities (For example, seeker would get +1 gaze and +1 identify) this does not work for the cult leader’s abilities.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Okay this is kind of a support ability so for day abilities I see no offensive abilities but anyway it’s a decent ability to have</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Sacrifice blood to mithras to gain night immunity for 1 - 2 members of the cult (1 member if there are 2 members of the cult, 2 members if there are 3)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>this seems to be an easy OP ability, which is yet again not an offensive ability but a support ability, only way I see that this can work is to give recharge time</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Night ability: Spiritual protection (x4) - Summon demon spirits to make anybody who visits you bleed, the person bleeding will die in 2 nights, they will get the notification they would get if a hunter sent wolves after them.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Again this is a killer ability and an OP one too, also you will get instantly killed if there is no hunter or he is dead, only way I can see this working is if you give it 2 times  not 4</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 02:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51589-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Dishonored (Cult)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Dishonored (Cult)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Class:</strong> The Dishonored (Cult) (Offensive)</p>
<p><strong>Backstory:</strong> An impeached royal that has fallen into insanity, their grudge against the Blue dragons grew and their insanity lead them to warship mithras.</p>
<p><strong>Royal Blood:</strong> Yes</p>
<p><strong>Converts from:</strong> Royal bloods (Noble still converts to Apostle)</p>
<p><strong>Day ability: Royal Threat (x2)</strong> - Make someone unable to talk for the rest of the day, if they do talk they will be killed from an arrow,  the message"<em>You have been threatened by a fallen royal</em>" will appear when this happens.  To prevent accidentally talking when this is used on the player, they are timed out for talking 5 seconds, this gives the CL 1 more use of eradicate.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability: Kingdom Heist (x1) -</strong> Restock 1 of every person in the cults night abilities (For example, seeker would get +1 gaze and +1 identify) this does not work for the cult leader’s abilities.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability: Royal sacrifice (x3) -</strong> Sacrifice blood to mithras to gain night immunity for 1 - 2 members of the cult (1 member if there are 2 members of the cult, 2 members if there are 3)</p>
<p><strong>Night ability: Spiritual protection (x4) -</strong> Summon demon spirits to make anybody who visits you bleed, the person bleeding will die in 2 nights, they will get the notification they would get if a hunter sent wolves after them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 23:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-51589-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-dishonored-cult/51589.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Dishonored (Cult)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
