<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mercenary Re-Work</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401</link>
    <description>Merc games are very slow and RNG dependent. I almost never get to attack my contract&#39;s accuser and I only have four guards. So you have to guess which night they are attacked which is based on a variety of different factors. For example, a drunk outs himself at court for whatever reason, it&#39;s a good idea to guard him. Sometimes you are just unlucky and they die in the first three nights.

A good idea is to save your guards for the second contract with a high priority kill such as the Prince. But that&#39;s no guarantee. 

The neuts out meta means that merc is a hard claim to announce during the execution block. So they may have to either stay under the radar (which is suspicious) OR they have to claim another role which could easily get you killed. If the Unseen/Cult know you&#39;re a merc, they will want to convert you or kill you at night.

Here is a simple solution. Return the Retribution ability but change it to something like False Accusation. 

How this works:

If a Blue Dragon accuses another Blue Dragon of treason and he goes to the chopping block, the Merc will attack the accuser and save the person&#39;s life. This will prove that you are not a neutral killer (reaper/possessor) and the Blue Dragon player lives another day. The King, Cult, and Unseen will not be affected by this ability.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 04:05:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-Work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 04:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9401-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401.rss">Mercenary Re-Work</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-Work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Merc should be convert immune</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 02:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9401-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401.rss">Mercenary Re-Work</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-Work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unknown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I rarely see neuts out being applied to mercs… because they are not true neutrals. That only happens if:</p>
<ol>
<li>their second target is suspicious(if it is the first, get the first target)<br>
2.the merc claim does not add up(but that is similar to any bd)</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9401-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401.rss">Mercenary Re-Work</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mercenary Re-Work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeathSwitch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Merc games are very slow and RNG dependent. I almost never get to attack my contract’s accuser and I only have four guards. So you have to guess which night they are attacked which is based on a variety of different factors. For example, a drunk outs himself at court for whatever reason, it’s a good idea to guard him. Sometimes you are just unlucky and they die in the first three nights.</p>
<p>A good idea is to save your guards for the second contract with a high priority kill such as the Prince. But that’s no guarantee.</p>
<p>The neuts out meta means that merc is a hard claim to announce during the execution block. So they may have to either stay under the radar (which is suspicious) OR they have to claim another role which could easily get you killed. If the Unseen/Cult know you’re a merc, they will want to convert you or kill you at night.</p>
<p>Here is a simple solution. Return the Retribution ability but change it to something like False Accusation.</p>
<p>How this works:</p>
<p>If a Blue Dragon accuses another Blue Dragon of treason and he goes to the chopping block, the Merc will attack the accuser and save the person’s life. This will prove that you are not a neutral killer (reaper/possessor) and the Blue Dragon player lives another day. The King, Cult, and Unseen will not be affected by this ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 22:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-9401-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/mercenary-re-work/9401.rss">Mercenary Re-Work</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
