<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378</link>
    <description>Lore link:
http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Alchemist
Lore subject: The Accident in the castle

Despite Aidart being a large castle, with many other rooms, it wasn&#39;t always so separated as it is now, there used to be a giant lab where many people would gather to prepare potions for the King and townspeople. There were three main people who used this lab to create many types of potions. However, they were not all out for the same purposes. Often, only one of them would be in the lab, while the other two were around the castle.

Occasionally, two of these people were in the same room and they would converse a bit more while working, but, this day was different, all of them were gathered, attempting to create potions, trouble was brewing instead. As the lady amongst ran around, she looked around to see conical flasks bubbling and a small mist being produced. With all of the chemicals in the room, everyone had to be evacuated and the lab was shut down. The lady was the person who seemed to be the most affected by the experience, the chemicals really affecting her, whereas the males were unharmed, frequently scribbling in their notes about experiences in the lab.

The Alchemist was the first to re-enter the lab, annoyed that she had been forced to evacuate before, grabbing some of the components she had used previously and some flasks before bringing them to her room. Which was a fairly bright room after she had started to brew new potions. The King was walking around the castle, when he noticed three fluorescent chemicals in the corner of her room. Red, Yellow and Green ones. Nobody knew what the effects of the weird potions were until she snuck into the King&#39;s room and made him drink her green concoction. The king had been found dead in the morning, one of the males saying that he had been poisoned by an alchemist when they realised he was neutral to them all. 

The male who pointed out the death turned out to be a physician, proud to help everyone, having regretted not healing the king and letting him pass away. A note detailing of the lab and the time spent with his fellow potion makers. He had become immune to the poisonous fumes because of remedy studies and missed his fellow friends, despite having become very scared of them for some reason. Writing that they weren&#39;t to be trusted fully, although, the Alchemist wasn&#39;t bad.

A knight took out a sword and killed someone else. The alchemist quickly running to the room where the victim of the attack had been laying down, pouring her red liquid into his mouth and praying that it worked. The following day, only a noble had died, but, nobody knew why it had happened. The knight called out the man, saying that as he wasn&#39;t Blue Dragon, he could be part of the Black Rose, their enemies, so he was voted for execution. When he died, his note had been discovered &quot;I was a physician, happy to be serving, but the Black Rose have shown me that the Blue Dragon are not to be trusted. I am immune to poison, as I had already completed my studies, but I am a herbalist now. The Alchemist is trustworthy as they have served with us to help. They can harm people too, caution is needed. Sorry to have left you all like this but thank you for the memories and times we spent brewing the potions. They will not be forgotten ever. I just wish.. We could&#39;ve worked together some more&quot;

The Alchemist had been filled with rage after this, running to the room of the court wizard and poisoning him, to take revenge for her friend. Eventually, only three people remained, a mercenary who had been watching over her a bit and a mastermind, who smiled and reached out their hand to them. They used to be a herbalist too, so had used the lab. As the lights slowly dimmed and the Black Rose took over, the Alchemist stood proudly, the lab re-opened and she kept using it for more potion materials. The others used it too when needed, but never again was there an accident in the lab. The Alchemist seen as a hero to some, but an enemy to others. Just a neutral person trying to survive and happily work in Aidart.

Comments/Explanations:
This was made to capture that the Alchemist was always seen as a nice hard working person by many but could also be an enemy at different stages, somewhat being misunderstood, but also, underestimated sometimes. Showing how she can seem to all sides of the equation instead of just being a plain neutral who seems to cause of a lot of chaos all the time.

Tried to edit it down a bit, trying not to get rid of too much. This is going to be a slow process..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 21:26:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Condensed down a bit, not much, just the occasional words.<br>
Will try to do it again, but, I just don’t want to get rid of the main concepts.<br>
A story which shows the power the Alchemist possesses.<br>
It’s different, but also works fairly well, I hope…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 21:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1378-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe it comes off a little too long winded? I mean it is nice it explains the abilities and possible motive of the alchemist, but maybe condense it down a little?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 23:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1378-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks. I thought that the lore is sort of alternative, but it might work well.<br>
Was one of the first things which intrigued me and so went with what I thought.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 19:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1378-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The story is kinda cool, I like it as a story <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 22:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1378-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PokemonKidRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore link:<br>
<a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Alchemist" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Alchemist</a><br>
Lore subject: The Accident in the castle</p>
<p>Despite Aidart being a large castle, with many other rooms, it wasn’t always so separated as it is now, there used to be a giant lab where many people would gather to prepare potions for the King and townspeople. There were three main people who used this lab to create many types of potions. However, they were not all out for the same purposes. Often, only one of them would be in the lab, while the other two were around the castle.</p>
<p>Occasionally, two of these people were in the same room and they would converse a bit more while working, but, this day was different, all of them were gathered, attempting to create potions, trouble was brewing instead. As the lady amongst ran around, she looked around to see conical flasks bubbling and a small mist being produced. With all of the chemicals in the room, everyone had to be evacuated and the lab was shut down. The lady was the person who seemed to be the most affected by the experience, the chemicals really affecting her, whereas the males were unharmed, frequently scribbling in their notes about experiences in the lab.</p>
<p>The Alchemist was the first to re-enter the lab, annoyed that she had been forced to evacuate before, grabbing some of the components she had used previously and some flasks before bringing them to her room. Which was a fairly bright room after she had started to brew new potions. The King was walking around the castle, when he noticed three fluorescent chemicals in the corner of her room. Red, Yellow and Green ones. Nobody knew what the effects of the weird potions were until she snuck into the King’s room and made him drink her green concoction. The king had been found dead in the morning, one of the males saying that he had been poisoned by an alchemist when they realised he was neutral to them all.</p>
<p>The male who pointed out the death turned out to be a physician, proud to help everyone, having regretted not healing the king and letting him pass away. A note detailing of the lab and the time spent with his fellow potion makers. He had become immune to the poisonous fumes because of remedy studies and missed his fellow friends, despite having become very scared of them for some reason. Writing that they weren’t to be trusted fully, although, the Alchemist wasn’t bad.</p>
<p>A knight took out a sword and killed someone else. The alchemist quickly running to the room where the victim of the attack had been laying down, pouring her red liquid into his mouth and praying that it worked. The following day, only a noble had died, but, nobody knew why it had happened. The knight called out the man, saying that as he wasn’t Blue Dragon, he could be part of the Black Rose, their enemies, so he was voted for execution. When he died, his note had been discovered “I was a physician, happy to be serving, but the Black Rose have shown me that the Blue Dragon are not to be trusted. I am immune to poison, as I had already completed my studies, but I am a herbalist now. The Alchemist is trustworthy as they have served with us to help. They can harm people too, caution is needed. Sorry to have left you all like this but thank you for the memories and times we spent brewing the potions. They will not be forgotten ever. I just wish… We could’ve worked together some more”</p>
<p>The Alchemist had been filled with rage after this, running to the room of the court wizard and poisoning him, to take revenge for her friend. Eventually, only three people remained, a mercenary who had been watching over her a bit and a mastermind, who smiled and reached out their hand to them. They used to be a herbalist too, so had used the lab. As the lights slowly dimmed and the Black Rose took over, the Alchemist stood proudly, the lab re-opened and she kept using it for more potion materials. The others used it too when needed, but never again was there an accident in the lab. The Alchemist seen as a hero to some, but an enemy to others. Just a neutral person trying to survive and happily work in Aidart.</p>
<p>Comments/Explanations:<br>
This was made to capture that the Alchemist was always seen as a nice hard working person by many but could also be an enemy at different stages, somewhat being misunderstood, but also, underestimated sometimes. Showing how she can seem to all sides of the equation instead of just being a plain neutral who seems to cause of a lot of chaos all the time.</p>
<p>Tried to edit it down a bit, trying not to get rid of too much. This is going to be a slow process…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 22:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1378-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-alchemist/1378.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Alchemist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
