<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] &quot;A Betrayed, A True Seeker&quot;</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-a-betrayed-a-true-seeker/66109</link>
    <description>**_wrote this on a short amount of time, a lot of stuff could be written wrongly so please, if you see something wrongly spelled (looking at you! those detestable correctioneers), please tell me so that I can fix it_**

This is how I envisioned the conversion from Any Investigative to Seeker. (Don&#39;t judge me) (Ignore former message due to message above) (Too many appendix notes, but another one!)

**A Betrayed, A True Seeker**

Why can’t they understand. Is there no one who will ever understand me?

They all walk past me, not seeing that butler evilly grinning at me and whom is clearly a part of the cult. I can’t understand them at all. Why can’t you just accuse him for trial? Why? The King and The Prince kept ignoring me, calling me a fool. I could still see him that night. That grin, those words naturally flowing through his mouth. Those words that everyone believed. Let them flow through their minds. Not noticing the fact; he was almost out of wine. Everyone who mocked me for being foolish.

The following night &quot;He&quot; came into my room. He gave me a strange mask and told me to cover my eyes. I did as he told me to. He was scary, I was frightened by him, why wouldn&#39;t I do what he said when he had that knife. Wait, scary? What is that? Something not needed?Blood? Mithras accepts me? A new name? Seeker... I like it. Seeker. I am now Seeker. What I was before? I don&#39;t remember and I don&#39;t care. I will follow my leader to the end. I won&#39;t ever take of this mask. Never ever will I take this mask off. Never until I am promoted or I am sacrificed.

The night after, as The Seeker, they walked down the corridor, the rest of the cult welcomed them with open arms. Yet, no one was capable of deducing what gender they are or who they were, since they never show their face. The Seeker then went on his mission to enter a room dedicated to the Inquisitor, who was hired to kill the Cult and the Sorceress. After finishing investigating, he took out his dagger before hesitating, walking back and leaving a little blood on the door. The blood mark giving of a faint glow in the dark.

A few nights later the Inquisitor’s head was found outside of his room, a bloodless corpse.

The Seeker had done their job.
He was now finally understood, though as a part of Cult.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 11:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-a-betrayed-a-true-seeker/66109.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] &quot;A Betrayed, A True Seeker&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mathmods]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong><em>wrote this on a short amount of time, a lot of stuff could be written wrongly so please, if you see something wrongly spelled (looking at you! those detestable correctioneers), please tell me so that I can fix it</em></strong></p>
<p>This is how I envisioned the conversion from Any Investigative to Seeker. (Don’t judge me) (Ignore former message due to message above) (Too many appendix notes, but another one!)</p>
<p><strong>A Betrayed, A True Seeker</strong></p>
<p>Why can’t they understand. Is there no one who will ever understand me?</p>
<p>They all walk past me, not seeing that butler evilly grinning at me and whom is clearly a part of the cult. I can’t understand them at all. Why can’t you just accuse him for trial? Why? The King and The Prince kept ignoring me, calling me a fool. I could still see him that night. That grin, those words naturally flowing through his mouth. Those words that everyone believed. Let them flow through their minds. Not noticing the fact; he was almost out of wine. Everyone who mocked me for being foolish.</p>
<p>The following night “He” came into my room. He gave me a strange mask and told me to cover my eyes. I did as he told me to. He was scary, I was frightened by him, why wouldn’t I do what he said when he had that knife. Wait, scary? What is that? Something not needed?Blood? Mithras accepts me? A new name? Seeker… I like it. Seeker. I am now Seeker. What I was before? I don’t remember and I don’t care. I will follow my leader to the end. I won’t ever take of this mask. Never ever will I take this mask off. Never until I am promoted or I am sacrificed.</p>
<p>The night after, as The Seeker, they walked down the corridor, the rest of the cult welcomed them with open arms. Yet, no one was capable of deducing what gender they are or who they were, since they never show their face. The Seeker then went on his mission to enter a room dedicated to the Inquisitor, who was hired to kill the Cult and the Sorceress. After finishing investigating, he took out his dagger before hesitating, walking back and leaving a little blood on the door. The blood mark giving of a faint glow in the dark.</p>
<p>A few nights later the Inquisitor’s head was found outside of his room, a bloodless corpse.</p>
<p>The Seeker had done their job.<br>
He was now finally understood, though as a part of Cult.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-a-betrayed-a-true-seeker/66109/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-a-betrayed-a-true-seeker/66109/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 11:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-66109-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-a-betrayed-a-true-seeker/66109.rss">[Lore Suggestion] &quot;A Betrayed, A True Seeker&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
