<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603</link>
    <description>First of all let me just say I love this game and I will continue to support this game in the future!  When I first started playing my goal was to collect enough gold to buy the armor and weapon I wanted, which is only 2 items in the game.  I was able to accomplish this goal within a week with moderate playtime.  

Now I find myself unmotivated to play more games because I have no progression or goals to work towards to.  Don&#39;t get me wrong, playing the game to have fun is more than enough to keep playing but I am looking to invest long-term and I would love to see some type of progression system.

Below are my suggestions to improve retention and keep having players to come back.

**Ranking System**

1. The game should have a ranking system based on your stats of W/D/L.  This could be expanded further into the Top 100 players based on W/D/L ratio and even having two separate game modes.  Casual Play vs Ranked Play.  Ranked Play of-course is your &quot;Try Hard&quot; games because your outcomes will get recorded against your competitive score to compete for higher rankings.

2. There should be seasons of rank games where it might last 3 months and at the end of the season based on your current rankings you will get a reward (Armor or Weapon)  Having unique items just for playing Ranked Games would motivate try-hard gamers to play competitively and be rewarded with Unique items you can&#39;t buy in the shop.

Right now I feel like games can be considered as throw away games because it doesn&#39;t affect your stats of winning or losing at this very moment and I would like to see some type of ranking system in the near future.

Please Please Please Devs tell me there is something in the works??? :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 14:07:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1: Somewhere around 50 as a minimum. From there more is better. Btw I mean that for ToL spacificaly not games in general.</p>
<p>2: There are 2 ways. A: The conversation mechanic means that good players are more likely to be on the evil team which you just established is the team that usually wins in low Elo games. It also means that there are often a majority of winners in a BD loss. B: The system overwatch uses in low Elo of tracking more than just winrate. The devs already said that the system they use will involve lots of math so I think they will do this</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 14:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-37</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BD makes up most of the players in most games… odds are if there is a tanker, it will be on BD, and odds are you will be on BD. When a ranked mode is implimented, in the higher skillrates, BD’s winrate will be significantly above BD’s winrate in the lower skill pools. Which will also lead to one of 3 things.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>The game will be balanced around the uper skill ranks, resulting in a ludicriously high evil winrate in low skill tiers.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The game will remain balanced for “average players across the board”, resulting in a very high BD winrate in the upper tier.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The dev’s attempt some kind of seperate rules for seperate levels (not going to happen).</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Whatever the case, in the higher rank/elo/whatever it will be called mode, BD will win more, meaning more average winners per game the higher up you go.</p>
<p>Now they can compensate for that like town of salem does, where winning as town earns fewer points than winning as mafia, and losing as town costs more points than losing as mafia.</p>
<p>But whatever the case… that difference still falls in, at lower skill levels, there’s going to be a much fewer average winners per game, than at higher skill levels. That’s just an unescapable fact. No matter how you slice it, BD will win more in higher skill modes than they do in lower skill modes, and as you have a higher chance of starting on BD per game, you have a higher chance of winning your average game, if you are in the higher skill tier.</p>
<p>My question for people in favor of a ranked system.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>How many games do you think it takes on an even playing field, to get a good estimate of someones skill. 10? 50? 100?.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What mechanism do you think can work for getting people who were misjudged at first to actually get back up to the level they belong in? Or do you really think that a players skill can dig him out when he is constantly with bad teams?</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-36</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not true. There will be plenty of times were the players that are tanking are on the other team if you are good.</p>
<p>If you are the one tanking your team then that is impossible. You are always on your own team after all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/35</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-35</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right, but my point is, the good players that will also ALWAYS be on a team that gets tanked. The qualifiers/starting area that judges skill, will be a grab bag, some people will get lucky and get good teams, some people will get unlucky and get on teams with tankers… and if you were unfortunate enough to be tanked in the placement matches, you then get pulled down with tankers, and continue to always get tankers.</p>
<p>Like I said with town of salem, the ONLY way I was able to get out of ELO hell was to get a new account… I’d rather not have to buy throne of lies again if I get unlucky at the start.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-34</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A player that tanks his team will ALWAYS be on a team that gets tanked. That alone makes being good increase winrate a ton</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-33</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="newarkinvaders" data-post="27" data-topic="4603" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/newarkinvaders/40/2154_2.png" class="avatar"> newarkinvaders:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if skill doesn’t increase your win percentage significantly then the game is pointless .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No one is saying skill doesn’t increase your win percentage, over a significant number of games across an even playing field. The point I’m making is</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>In a small scale, say 50ish games or so. Variables outside a players control, will still have a larger impact than his own skill.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>After you divide people up, the playing field stops being even. People who are put on the worse ranks, will lose more games, while people in the upper ranks will win more games, regardless of their skill level. If you took someone from the depths of elo hell with 10 wins 90 losses, and someone at the peak of the games records with 90 wins 10 losses, and inverted who went in which games, you’d see the former winner lose most of his games, and the former loser winning most of his games. Maybe not to the same extent eachother had, maybe it would turn to 70/30s for each. But trust me it’s a huge difference.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>In town of salem, I sank down to 600 ELO when I started out, I tried for 4 months, I occasionally climbed up to 1100 before getting shot down over and over again. I made a new account (which starts at 1200), and happened to win my first few games. I absolutely breezed in 1300 ELO range and easilly had a near 90% winrate as town.</p>
<p>Then for giggles I went and tried to see if I could dig myself out on the old account… 8 losses in a row. I wasn’t magically great when playing on the 1400 ELO account and terrible on the 700 account. I simply was good enough not to be a deterant to my team at 1400s, so the teams usually won, while with unskilled teams there was just no way I could turn them around most of the time.</p>
<p>Skill plays a factor, but when you divide up the playing fields, which field you are in is a much bigger factor than yourself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 22:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-32</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NuclearBurrito" data-post="30" data-topic="4603">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nuclearburrito/40/4723_2.png" class="avatar"> NuclearBurrito:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Good players increase the chances of a given team winning and bad players reduce the chances that a team will win. That means that if you are a good player then your team will always have at least one good player thus increasing your chances of winning.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But not on a 1:1 ratio is my point. A bad BD player in a mostly good team, is very likely to get 1 BD executed, then himself killed by the prince, thus taking out 2 BD and crippling the prince. A good BD player… might catch a replacable bad guy earlier… Though not even that as scumreading is virtually impossible when you have bad players in the mix.</p>
<p>One horrible player can tank a solid team with waay more efficiency than one excellent player can carry a bad team. Especially because a great player in a horrible team, effectively has no tools of deduction. Sure you can tell that every single action done by several players has been purely detrimental to the BD… but that doesn’t mean they aren’t just terrible.</p>
<p>My point is no matter what in a social deduction game like this, if you are underestimated early on… you are very unlikely to fix that. Being good is often a detriment if you are on bad teams. I’ve gotten executed several times because when we caught the assasain red handed day 2, I wanted to occupy/jail him instead of execute him immediately and let the MM replace him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 22:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-31</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That would be a problem that extends to casual gameplay however. Plus that is simply not true. Newer players are less likely to be on the winning team because thier team is less likely to win. Let’s put it this way. Good players increase the chances of a given team winning and bad players reduce the chances that a team will win. That means that if you are a good player then your team will always have at least one good player thus increasing your chances of winning.</p>
<p>If you have a ranking system you also are putting all of the best players into one game thus magnifying any differences in skill compared to everyone else. This is an engagement loop that makes it much more likely for a game to be decided by skill simply BECAUSE of a ranked system.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 22:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-30</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zarlath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="newarkinvaders" data-post="27" data-topic="4603" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/newarkinvaders/40/2154_2.png" class="avatar"> newarkinvaders:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if skill doesn’t increase your win percentage significantly then the game is pointless .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My point exactly</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-29</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="newarkinvaders" data-post="27" data-topic="4603" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/newarkinvaders/40/2154_2.png" class="avatar"> newarkinvaders:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if skill doesn’t increase your win percentage significantly then the game is pointless .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>not neccessarily<br>
<strong>points to gambling</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 13:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-28</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if skill doesn’t increase your win percentage significantly then the game is pointless .</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 11:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-27</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zarlath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another question is by how much can skill alone increase your win percentage.<br>
If a highly skilled player has only a slightly bigger win percentage than others, way less skilled, then the system is flawed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 09:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-26</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let’s compare this to a MOBA okay?</p>
<p>Just cause someone gets a lot of kills, doesn’t mean they’d be able to do the same unless they had a good team backing them up.</p>
<p>The support is just as important as the tank or the damage dealer, and vice versa.</p>
<p>But the most important factor of whether a team wins or not is how good they are at working together.</p>
<p>And sometimes you’ll face up against people who work together better.<br>
It’s random chance unless every game you play is with 15 other people you know.<br>
It’d be impossible to show real stats determined on how good you are at the game when the game relies on team work and luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 09:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-25</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A is true, but not perfectly true… Right off the bat if you are BD, you yourself are 10% or less of your team. Look at any sport, how often is the highest rated player on the team that wins the (insert name of big finish game). On just wins/losses it would take several hundred games to fairly compare 2 different people.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 23:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-24</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel like it’s this:<br>
Skill will increase your win percentage, but just not necessarily directly/immediately, due to other players/random chance</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 20:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-23</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you can’t have it both ways.</p>
<p>either</p>
<p>a, individual skill will increase your win percentage</p>
<p>or</p>
<p>b, the game is random and skill has no impact on the game .</p>
<p>If a is true then a win loss ratio is sufficient to rank players .</p>
<p>If b is true then there is no purpose in a ranking system for a game where your actions cannot influence your out come .</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 19:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-22</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Obviously not, I believe we are all in agreement that it is a combination of luck, your teams compound skill vs your opponents skill, as well as your individual skill. But we can squabble all day on what percentage each factor has.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-21</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so we are agreed that if you win or lose is completely random and has nothing to do with player ability ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 17:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-20</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[beo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I fully agree with radarsu, who gave very nice explanation. I can also add that ranked system will very likely lead to more toxicity and flame. Especially taking into account that this game is very RNG dependent and has convert system. And in this game unlike in Dota or LoL there is not possible to mute toxic player. Of course you can report such players, but still overall level of impoliteness of players with strongly rise. And this is definitelty not that this game needs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-19</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eran_Shmuel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, better prince, will win more games.<br>
Better King will win more game<br>
Better MM will win more game .<br>
Same thing about fool,scorned,alchemist</p>
<p>Im not so sure about the others<br>
They might win more games but like 0.5% more<br>
And thats not enough for  rating system</p>
<p>So maybe judge people only for King’s, prince and those classes games?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 09:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-18</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Better players <strong>won’t</strong> win more games.</p>
<p>This is a game built on team play and <em>random</em> chance. You might be killed N1 and that’s GG.<br>
You might be good at lying, but then someone decides to kill you at night or Lynch you or investigate you.</p>
<p>I would like to imagine I’m a very good Reaper player, though my winning is mostly based on not being investigated or attacked early game.</p>
<p>My win rate wouldn’t reflect this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 08:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[newarkinvaders]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>guys I don’t understand why this is so difficult to understand .</p>
<p>better players will win more games .</p>
<p>whatever the game and whatever the rules set . better players will win more games .</p>
<p>did I mention better players will win more games?</p>
<p>just did a bit more research and found out that better players will win more games …</p>
<p>Alert : according to latest  horoscope : he who plays better will win more games .</p>
<p>in the art of war it’s is stated better players will win more games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 07:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s what I see as well</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 05:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eran_Shmuel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this idea, but in my opinion a better tactic for blue dragon that noone is using right now, is choose not to execute investigated bad guys  until the middle-late game.</p>
<p>why? because there is a limit for bad guys but no limit on conversion, so when you execute a bad guy you just help the unseen and give them more space.<br>
Also, killing a mastermind before day 4 is just wasting a mastermind kill.</p>
<p>the best option is to wait until you got like 2-3 bad guys and then start to kill them 1 by 1 before they can convert fast enough</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 01:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Something that comes to my mind, now this may be super complicated to try and code or even fathom, but possibly a semi-hidden scoring system, in which points are awarded for what happens while you are in the faction, rather than which faction you happened to be at the end of the game, as well as bonus points for individual actions for roles. You still continue to gain faction points while dead as your role. Do note none of these points should be visible during the game, whether an actual breakdown of them after the game is debatable.</p>
<p>But overall the games scoring should be more focused on what happens on your watch, rather than which side you happened to be on at the last second.</p>
<p>BD</p>
<ul>
<li>Positive: Execute Unseen/Cult, Reaper, Possesor, scorned, evil king</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Negative: Execute BD, Fool</li>
</ul>
<p>Unseen/cult</p>
<ul>
<li>Positive: Execute BD, Reaper, Possesor, Good king, Fool</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Negative: Execute Unseen/cult</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Positive Kill (done by their members) - BD, Good king</li>
</ul>
<p>Individual things like</p>
<p>Investigatives earn bonus points if a + they checked is executed afterwards<br>
Role blockers gain points for blocking an enemy (again, these points absolutely are invisible during the course of the game).</p>
<p>Knights and hunters gain extra points for killing things that would have earned their faction points for executing.</p>
<p>Court wizards gain points for conversion preventions</p>
<p>etc…</p>
<p>If the majority of the end score is what positive events your faction pulled off while you are in it. that would greatly lessen the flaws to rank that come from say spending 80% of the game as one faction and switching at the last second etc…</p>
<p>If the expected result of the score being<br>
50% team points, 25% individual acts, 25% for the win/loss result.</p>
<p>Obviously this kind of system would be complicated as heck, people will argue on the details etc… But to me that’s the only direction to go which actually could allow some kind of grading in a team game in which players may switch sides.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 01:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-4603-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/suggestion-player-reward-system-and-rankings/4603.rss">[Suggestion] Player Reward System and Rankings</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
