<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581</link>
    <description>(WARNING THIS IS A COMPLEX CLASS THAT MAY NEVER BE ADDED BUT I STILL THINK ITS A COOL UNIQUE TAKE ON AN NK)

Name- The Punisher or The Law enforcer 
Class - Neutral Killing or Neutral Support 

Win Condition: kill all who have served wrong against their own.

New mechanic:
• the punisher see all strikes people gain on the punishers list 
• if a player accuses a member of their own faction and that player goes on trial, then they will gain a strike on the punishers list
• if you vote to execute a member of your own faction, then you will gain 2 strikes
• if a player that has 4 strikes then the punisher can kill you if he pleases to. 
• if a player kills a member of their own faction at night(even if it&#39;s by accident due to the CW switch or on purpose) then you will gain 3 strikes 

{special rules that could be added}:
•  if they kill a fool during the day or night, then the people who have killed the fool will loose 2 strikes from the list. 

What doesn&#39;t count as strikes:
•BD can kill any neutrals or Unseen/Cult
•Cult/Unseen can kill any neutrals or Bd
•Neutrals can kill any BD or Unseen/Cult 


 Night ability 1 -  &quot;serve justice&quot; - kill a player who has 4 strikes {unlimited}. 

Night ability 2) - is called &quot;loyalty guidance&quot; -  prevent anyone from voting against their own team tomorrow(no one will know that this ability is in affect){2 uses}(a Neutral can vote as normal). 

Day ability 1) - is called &quot;learned from past mistakes&quot; -  you will make a player understand what they did wrong and they will completely be erased of all past mistakes{in other words, all strikes will have been removed} (3 uses)

 Day ability 2) - is called &quot;out right Justice&quot; - this allows The Punisher to kill a player that has 4 strikes and everyone will be notified on who did it{this is similar to when the hunter kills someone when they are killed during the day}

 Passive 1) - is called &quot;respect&quot; if you kill two players then it allows you to be immune for the next attack on you. (Does stack)  (The reason is that your loyal followers give there life to see justice live on) 

Passive 2) - is called &quot;loyalty&quot; - if you kill two players then it allows you to survive one execution on you in the morning. (This can stack). (The reason is that your loyal followers give there life to see justice live on)

Notes: This could end up really being an interesting class that changes up the meta of the game. This could prevent random voting and innocent people dying. What I think is cool that the evil faction could want to keep the Punisher alive because he can help kill BD faster, along with the Punishers unique win condition. 

Tell me what you think

Guys the Punisher 2.0 is now out. Go and check it out!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 12:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the feedback about this class idea. It’s something I threw together after a game where almost everyday we killed a BD member on trial. I know this class may seem over powered and needs some reworking. So I might be making a Punisher 2.0 idea or might just edit this one. But again thank you</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 12:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35581-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Punisher’s list can basically tell you the factions of all players who vote in the game, for a start.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="35581">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night ability 2) - is called “loyalty guidance” -  prevent anyone from voting against their own team tomorrow(no one will know that this ability is in affect){2 uses}(a Neutral can vote as normal).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The entire BD could vote players in order until someone is voted to trial, confirming them as non-BD. Neutral and Unseen/Cult players don’t have the numbers to do this so can’t “fake” it and cause mislynches, and if there were people suspect of being Unseen/Cult, they would be asked to vote up other suspects, and if they are unable to then they would be executed. Overall, fairly abusable if a meta were to set in, and overly confusing until one did.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="35581">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Day ability 2) - is called “out right Justice” - this allows The Punisher to kill a player that has 4 strikes and everyone will be notified on who did it{this is similar to when the hunter kills someone when they are killed during the day}</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Uses on this? Also, since most of your strikes would be on BD members, I would expect this ability to be avoided like the plague.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="35581">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Passive 1) - is called “respect” if you kill two players then it allows you to be immune for the next attack on you. (Does stack)  (The reason is that your loyal followers give there life to see justice live on)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>NKs without permanent death immunity tend to have low win rates and be unenjoyable since there is a potential that you can die night one, and you’ve instantly lost. That’s why Alchemist has stoneskin potion and Mercenary’s guard gives them death immunity (even though they can technically win if somehow their target survives the length of the game), because losing n1 <em>sucks</em>.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="35581">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Passive 2) - is called “loyalty” - if you kill two players then it allows you to survive one execution on you in the morning. (This can stack). (The reason is that your loyal followers give there life to see justice live on)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Instantly confirms you as Punisher, but no faction has a good enough reason to want to keep you alive, so it would just get you executed the next day or by the Prince.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NOBLE1" data-post="1" data-topic="35581">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://www.ThroneOfLies.com/images/class-icons/princess-icon-256.jpg" class="avatar"> NOBLE1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Win Condition: kill all who have served wrong against their own.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I assume this means people with 4 strikes, and not just any amount? If it doesn’t, it would be impossible to win as, and if it does, it might have a very low win rate anyways. You would basically have to live to the end to ensure nobody got 4 strikes after your death, so it really wouldn’t differ to a regular NK in practice other than having “killing rules” and being more prone to death.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 01:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35581-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thor_Odinson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This class seems very slow as an NK.</p>
<p>Think about it, there’s so many people who won’t mess up and get any strikes, and the ones that do get strikes will have a very small chance of making more mistakes to reach 4 strikes. I’d suggest reducing the kill threshold for strikes down to 3 or something.</p>
<p>Adding all this, the Punisher’s pool of killable targets is <em>extremely</em> small, and sometimes they might not get a single kill in a game.</p>
<p>Also, I see some problems with “Loyalty Guidance”. If members of the same team can’t vote each other, then BD will immediately go on a voting spree and execute the people they <em>can</em> vote.</p>
<p>What I <em>would</em> suggest however, is that the Punisher be given a Night Ability which allows them to kill any BD who voted against their own team during the Day, this is a better system than the strike system because it really forces BD to ensure that their votes are serious. A class that punished BD for voting their own, would imo, drastically cut down on random exe’s and force the sheep BD to start putting thought into their votes.</p>
<p>The “Loyalty” Passive seems extremely OP however, so I’d recommend that one be scrapped. Being immune to Day execution is downright ludicrous.</p>
<p>I really like the idea of a class that punishes bad voting, but it needs a bit more balance since it has the potential to know exactly who the BD or baddies are (since they can only kill eligible targets).</p>
<p>The only way to counteract this would be to forbid the Punisher from sharing classes/factions with anyone else. And if they do say class to anyone that’s game throwing.</p>
<p>I can see this guy as a Neut, but not as an NK.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 01:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35581-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cannot be NK as it is restricted to the people it can kill. (With the Exception of Sorcerer of course.)<br>
Proves to BD everyone of their faction. Also as the Punisher you instantly know who BD is due to the amount of strikes they will gain.</p>
<p>Interesting idea though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35581-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(WARNING THIS IS A COMPLEX CLASS THAT MAY NEVER BE ADDED BUT I STILL THINK ITS A COOL UNIQUE TAKE ON AN NK)</p>
<p>Name- The Punisher or The Law enforcer<br>
Class - Neutral Killing or Neutral Support</p>
<p>Win Condition: kill all who have served wrong against their own.</p>
<p>New mechanic:<br>
• the punisher see all strikes people gain on the punishers list<br>
• if a player accuses a member of their own faction and that player goes on trial, then they will gain a strike on the punishers list<br>
• if you vote to execute a member of your own faction, then you will gain 2 strikes<br>
• if a player that has 4 strikes then the punisher can kill you if he pleases to.<br>
• if a player kills a member of their own faction at night(even if it’s by accident due to the CW switch or on purpose) then you will gain 3 strikes</p>
<p>{special rules that could be added}:<br>
•  if they kill a fool during the day or night, then the people who have killed the fool will loose 2 strikes from the list.</p>
<p>What doesn’t count as strikes:<br>
•BD can kill any neutrals or Unseen/Cult<br>
•Cult/Unseen can kill any neutrals or Bd<br>
•Neutrals can kill any BD or Unseen/Cult</p>
<p>Night ability 1 -  “serve justice” - kill a player who has 4 strikes {unlimited}.</p>
<p>Night ability 2) - is called “loyalty guidance” -  prevent anyone from voting against their own team tomorrow(no one will know that this ability is in affect){2 uses}(a Neutral can vote as normal).</p>
<p>Day ability 1) - is called “learned from past mistakes” -  you will make a player understand what they did wrong and they will completely be erased of all past mistakes{in other words, all strikes will have been removed} (3 uses)</p>
<p>Day ability 2) - is called “out right Justice” - this allows The Punisher to kill a player that has 4 strikes and everyone will be notified on who did it{this is similar to when the hunter kills someone when they are killed during the day}</p>
<p>Passive 1) - is called “respect” if you kill two players then it allows you to be immune for the next attack on you. (Does stack)  (The reason is that your loyal followers give there life to see justice live on)</p>
<p>Passive 2) - is called “loyalty” - if you kill two players then it allows you to survive one execution on you in the morning. (This can stack). (The reason is that your loyal followers give there life to see justice live on)</p>
<p>Notes: This could end up really being an interesting class that changes up the meta of the game. This could prevent random voting and innocent people dying. What I think is cool that the evil faction could want to keep the Punisher alive because he can help kill BD faster, along with the Punishers unique win condition.</p>
<p>Tell me what you think</p>
<p>Guys the Punisher 2.0 is now out. Go and check it out!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 14:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35581-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-punisher-law-enforcer/35581.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Punisher/ Law Enforcer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
