<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293</link>
    <description>**For me:** EverQuest. This is the only game beside Counter-Strike that I&#39;ve played on-and-off for like ... 15 years lol. It was a hardcore MMO before WoW, but after Ultima. You die and you lose like 2 hours of game time haha, so a huge risk/reward factor. Not many games do that, anymore. 

Well, ToL definitely has inspirations -- we use huge risk/reward factors. If you get converted, will you use your new ability if it means you will get caught as converted? Will you tell the others someone is 100% guilty, if it means you may be revealing your class, risking death the next night? 

Stuff like this. **Risk vs Reward.** _I love it._

Demon Souls is another great example of Risk/Reward.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 15:00:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off-Topic (Thronepass)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wolfy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Meh, for me I’m not much of a pc gamer. I’m ps4 and a massive fan of Attack on Titan.</p>
<p>However, as this asks for fav pc game, I would have to say papers please. I love the panic of a dystopian world, based on the Berlin Wall</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I forgot Plants vs. Zombies. Great tower-defense-style game, love the asthetics and art direction. Each level feels unique and different, the minigames are super fun, and there’s a ton of replayability after you beat the game.</p>
<p>If only PvZ 2 hadn’t been so lackluster in comparison.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 13:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[numberFTW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Minecraft(with mod and servers): Iimitless possibilities, Its a revolution for game industry, it itself is an era.</p>
<p>Rainbow six: siege: Love the strategic part of the game, you dont just use your awesome aim to destroy the opposite team but have you use your head and LOTS of teamwork</p>
<p>Overwatch:… I dunno…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 12:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In that case it easily makes my list, and since I know Halo 2 got a port (and it’s probably the best Halo game) it makes the list as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 11:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>True, it’s XBOX game - But this got ported to PC as well <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 10:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wasn’t aware that Halo CE was a PC game <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 10:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Halo: Combat Evolved! And I still hold the physical dvd case since 2003-2004ish and the disc is not being unreadable yet, thanks for the current unofficial updates I can play without the disk!</p>
<p>Who doesn’t love Halo 1? It’s a treasure amoung sea of gems for me, The ring world and the mystery behind this, killing covenant alien scum left and right, dominate the warzone using the vehicles from both factions and it gets only better with new type of enemy (SPOILERS!), the story is so memorable that won’t let me go out of heart without forgetting some life lessons.</p>
<p>I didn’t play Civilization 3 past one hour, but I adore Civilization 4 with it’s expansion packs which I can shape the history of mankind forever (The highest I can go is Prince Difficulty), did you know I always eradicate the first civilization closest from my capital city before I reach Turn 50? Warrior Rush!</p>
<p>Star Wars: Republic Commando is one of best Star Wars FPS–oooh ok, back then I didn’t know about Dark Forces although I did do Jedi Outcast and Jedi Academy–but Republic Commando has it’s adrenaline kicking moments to outsmart the A.I capabilities to eliminate me and the squad, the squad themselves are also smart to use their survivability, and untold story throughout the Clone Wars will be remembered by many fans.</p>
<p>Same goes for F.E.A.R and it’s expansion packs as well, mixing FPS Action, Japanese Horror, elements of The Matrix’s slow motion and slices of SCI-FI with interesting story and plot twists, the A.I of the enemies is ahead of it’s time and won’t hesitate to adapt based on player’s tactics and use against the players as well. The music won’t leave you calm.</p>
<p>Need For Speed: Most Wanted? Hell yeah, Police chases, illegal street racing with rubberbanding of A.I, customization and selection of cars, hands down for kick-ass soundtrack of licensed songs from several bands that make your adventure in Rockport State worthwhile, let’s see how good you are in daylight. The story behind this game become more clear once you’re closing to reach number <span class="hashtag">#1</span> in the Most Wanted.</p>
<p>I almost forgot about Fable: The Lost Chapters! My favorite Fantasy-RPG PC-ported game of all-time for me, the world and the lore is fascinating! The mobs and monsters you can fight as your renown gets higher, the quests I can take, the choices I will make, The game that can make you good character that won’t hurt a fly can turn into merciless killing demon evil maniac because one villager decide to mock you by calling you “Arse Face” and the british dry humor will cause you to laugh, even silly laughing from your Hero can tempt you to smirk, depending on the situation.</p>
<p>Out of all Assassin’s Creed games I played, Assassin’s Creed 2 stays the favorite for me no matter what. The world of Renaissance Italy and the lore behind this game is historically correct (Except I don’t agree how Ezio doesn’t get any older until in DLCS before end-game finally decide to give you beard), the side-missions and the main storyline goes well with the pace, you can kill civilians and soldiers alike even with the brooms and the best part about brooms I can scare the annoying musicians that causes to drop the flute, the assassination moves and the stealth function of the game!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 08:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I want to play Talos, if you recently discovered awesome puzzle games like this. You definitely need to play Portal, Portal 2 and The Stanley Parable (spelling?)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 07:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[deadfrien]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One of my favs is Tales of the Abyss. Between its strong story and character development, and its combat, it’s definitely one of my favorites, if not the one. While I still have to play most of the games, the Tales of series is one of my favorite franchises.</p>
<p>By hours, Garry’s Mod is a top contender.</p>
<p>Super Mario Galaxy 1 + 2 were just great fun for me, completely dominated over all other 3D platformers in my eyes. A shame that I don’t have my copies any more.</p>
<p>The Talos Principle is one of my most recent entries, and while I’m not a huge puzzle buff, it was an excellent experience overall, and there was some awesome world building.</p>
<p>Some runner ups are Transistor, Insurgency, Super Mario Bros 3 (too many hours wasted when I was young), Gunpoint, Crosscode (still in Beta builds though), and Zak and Wiki.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 07:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Spelunky</p>
<p>FTL</p>
<p>Slime Rancher</p>
<p>Robot Arena 2</p>
<p>Will do explanations later maybe</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Queen_Alfa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Are you asking me to choose a favourite? I can’t… So I’m picking a few</p>
<p>I’ve been really into Overlord lately, it’s like Pikmin but edgier, and judging from my loss count, I suck at it, but I love it to bits, mainly for the fact I can be evil :3, but it’s interesting and it have kept me entertained solving puzzles around the area and battling the bosses. (I love the sudden “ah-ha!” Moment when I figure out where to go)</p>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/1X/cd482f7c925bef6a56d25af604f6aa6e79f92d19.jpg" width="441" height="494"></p>
<p>(Rip my minions tho)</p>
<hr>
<p>Another game I really love is slime rancher, it’s honestly pure stress relief for me and helps me relax when no other game can, I love the exploration factor of it and well slime farming! All the slimes are absolutely adorable, in both design and behaviour (such as tabby slimes booping you!)</p>
<p><img src="/uploads/default/original/1X/a08bb9e5a5166db573de6eac236fbce2eddc06f3.jpg" width="668" height="392"></p>
<p>You can’t say no to that adorable face</p>
<hr>
<p>“A few she says” As she picks only two X3</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 04:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedRosser]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Of course it has to be the masterpiece that is Big Rigs over the road racing,</p>
<p>Im just screwing around it would have to be a mix up between Mass effect trilogy or Knights of the old Republic</p>
<p>Both for the same reason bioware created worlds i wanted to learn more about, it actually peaked my interest and got me into the RPG genre</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 04:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>final fantasy 13 has always held a huge spot in my heart, as it got me into the series because I would always watch my brother play it and it would fascinate me. as much sh*t as people give for it, it will always have a special place in my heart.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ooh, hard one.</p>
<p>Civilization 3 is pretty up there. I poured hours of my life into that game back in the day. Civs 4 and 5 never truly grabbed me like 3 did, but I suspect that’s because I have less time and more to play.</p>
<p>Roller Coaster Tycoon 2 is another one of those games that I got absolutely lost in when I was younger. It is by far the best tycoon-style game I’ve ever played. RCT3 also failed to pull me back into the franchise, probably for the same reasons Civ 4/5 didn’t.</p>
<p>Technically, by hours played, Minecraft has earned a spot on the list. Because Minecraft.</p>
<p>Recently, I’d have to say that my most played game would be Tom Clancy’s Rainbow Six: Siege. The game is far and away the best FPS I’ve ever played, and it’s just the breath of fresh air that the genre needed. I’m kind of cheating by including it here, as school has taken so much of my time since I bought the PC version that I mostly still play it on Xbox, but the game is simply not to be missed by anybody even casually interested in FPS games.</p>
<p>World of Goo is another hot contender. This game may not be infinitely replayable like the first couple, but it is truly amazing in every capacity. Great soundtrack, great level design, great atmosphere, and more - World of Goo has it all.</p>
<p>Considering that Skyrim is also a PC game (like most things, I prefer Xbox), it makes the list. No explanation needed, as a massive RPG fan.</p>
<p>Another game that I loved on Xbox is XCOM: Enemy Unknown (and Enemy Within). The famous Long War mod is the reason I bought the PC version, and it was well worth it.</p>
<p>On a smaller scale, honorable mentions go out to Town of Salem, despite its issues, and Rogue Legacy. Not a huge indie game fan, but these two are pretty fun.</p>
<p>If I think of any more, I’ll be sure to let you know.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hahah I never thought about it as a game, interesting. RL level ups! Definitely risk vs reward too, much like my fav.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rogue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>YouTube probably.<br>
There is a huge risk/reward factor, it uses real life stuff too, you invest real money in to get better recording gear and stuff like that and if people like your videos, you get it big</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[í42-Xblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>For me:</strong> EverQuest. This is the only game beside Counter-Strike that I’ve played on-and-off for like … 15 years lol. It was a hardcore MMO before WoW, but after Ultima. You die and you lose like 2 hours of game time haha, so a huge risk/reward factor. Not many games do that, anymore.</p>
<p>Well, ToL definitely has inspirations – we use huge risk/reward factors. If you get converted, will you use your new ability if it means you will get caught as converted? Will you tell the others someone is 100% guilty, if it means you may be revealing your class, risking death the next night?</p>
<p>Stuff like this. <strong>Risk vs Reward.</strong> <em>I love it.</em></p>
<p>Demon Souls is another great example of Risk/Reward.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1293-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/favorite-pc-game-of-all-time-why-go/1293.rss">Favorite PC game of all-time + why? GO!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
