<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The messenger</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088</link>
    <description>Right now, with the new king changes, information is scarce in the land of the blue dragon. BD can&#39;t trust each other, they risk too much and gain too little. but what if there was a class that could safely convey the information, without risking his life instantly?
in comes in **THE MESSENGER**

**type:** social
**goal:** convey info between the secretive BD without calling them out

**passive** the perks of the job: the messenger will be able to see all the messages he conveys, but not who sends them.

**Day ability**
_royal chatter:_ allows a member of the royal family (prince, princess, ...drunk? and king) to talk to the others safely, without revealing who they are. they will only talk to each other as their titles, so there won&#39;t be a need to reveal who they are. only a few charges, its a pretty strong ability.

_utmost secrecy:_ the messenger allows for a secretive meeting between 3 players he chooses at night. he can hear what is being said, but not who is saying it.  allows to organize tactics or call out someone without needing to reveal them to the whole world. can be turned against him if he uses it with the wrong people.

**Night ability**
_mail routes_ reveal the whispers of the selected character to the royal character of his choice the next day.


while this is obviously a very rough concept, I just wanted to bring it up to see how we can shape this class up together. I think BD has a lack of safe routes for communication, as psychic is the only one currently filling that position and its hard to convey messages through the psychic, due to the links being only between the psychic and one other, and the fact that the psychic can&#39;t really trust if the man who claims to be prince really is one.

there could obviously be an unseen version that actually tampers the communication between the BD, being able to pretend to be whispering someone as a different character, changing who receives the whispers of X character, or even making public the previous whispers of someone.

thanks for reading.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 05:56:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The messenger</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NagoGiovanna" data-post="1" data-topic="41088">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/nagogiovanna/40/2971_2.png" class="avatar"> NagoGiovanna:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and one other, and the fact that the psychic can’t really trust if the man who claims to be prince really is one.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>a prince claim is more trustworhthy than a psychic imo</p>
<p>however i like theprenise of this idea . ill dig deeper later.</p>
<p><strong>leaves</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 05:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41088-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088.rss">[Class Suggestion] The messenger</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The messenger</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NagoGiovanna]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought it was clear that he is a BD class that assists the communication between the other crucial BDs. his converted version could be “the disruptor” and as I said, he could " tampers the communication between the BD, being able to pretend to be whispering someone as a different character, changing who receives the whispers of X character, or even making public the previous whispers of someone."</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41088-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088.rss">[Class Suggestion] The messenger</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The messenger</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What alignment is this? If neutral whats its win condition? If BD then whats its converted version?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 22:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41088-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088.rss">[Class Suggestion] The messenger</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The messenger</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NagoGiovanna]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right now, with the new king changes, information is scarce in the land of the blue dragon. BD can’t trust each other, they risk too much and gain too little. but what if there was a class that could safely convey the information, without risking his life instantly?<br>
in comes in <strong>THE MESSENGER</strong></p>
<p><strong>type:</strong> social<br>
<strong>goal:</strong> convey info between the secretive BD without calling them out</p>
<p><strong>passive</strong> the perks of the job: the messenger will be able to see all the messages he conveys, but not who sends them.</p>
<p><strong>Day ability</strong><br>
<em>royal chatter:</em> allows a member of the royal family (prince, princess, …drunk? and king) to talk to the others safely, without revealing who they are. they will only talk to each other as their titles, so there won’t be a need to reveal who they are. only a few charges, its a pretty strong ability.</p>
<p><em>utmost secrecy:</em> the messenger allows for a secretive meeting between 3 players he chooses at night. he can hear what is being said, but not who is saying it.  allows to organize tactics or call out someone without needing to reveal them to the whole world. can be turned against him if he uses it with the wrong people.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability</strong><br>
<em>mail routes</em> reveal the whispers of the selected character to the royal character of his choice the next day.</p>
<p>while this is obviously a very rough concept, I just wanted to bring it up to see how we can shape this class up together. I think BD has a lack of safe routes for communication, as psychic is the only one currently filling that position and its hard to convey messages through the psychic, due to the links being only between the psychic and one other, and the fact that the psychic can’t really trust if the man who claims to be prince really is one.</p>
<p>there could obviously be an unseen version that actually tampers the communication between the BD, being able to pretend to be whispering someone as a different character, changing who receives the whispers of X character, or even making public the previous whispers of someone.</p>
<p>thanks for reading.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 21:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-41088-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-messenger/41088.rss">[Class Suggestion] The messenger</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
