<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[class suggestions] the apprentices</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-the-apprentices/2753</link>
    <description>only one per game, not guranteed

-------------------------------
**The prince&#39;s apprentice**
Blue dragon support

**Prince&#39;s aid** (passive)
knows who the prince imprisoned. Can listen in on the conversation between the prince and the prisoner. Can speak to the prince at night (text appears like the dead do to priest). Prince will see you as &quot;Apprentice (your name).&quot; E.x: Apprentice lewis harte

**In his foot steps** (passive)
if the prince dies night 1, 2, or 3, you shall replace him as prince with one use of &quot;execute&quot; left. If he dies another night, you shall become a knight.

**Spare cell** (day, 2 uses) your target will be thrown in the dungeon tonight, but no one will be there to talk to them or execute them. The prince&#39;s target is in another cell.

goal: Defeat the unseen/cult and any neutral who would seek to do you harm.
converts into the enforcer, but still speaks with the prince at night as &quot;Apprentice (your name)&quot;

----------------------------------
**The alchemist&#39;s apprentice**
neutral support

**Alchemist&#39;s aid** (passive)
If the alchemist is occupied, you will carry out whatever task they attempted to do. You can speak with the alchemist at night, being seen as &quot;Apprentice (your name)&quot;

**Apply potion** (night, infinite uses)
Inject your target with a potion. There is a 50 percent chance it will be a crimson potion, and a 50 percent chance it will be an emerald potion.

**First-aid** (night, 2 uses)
the alchemist will be immune to death tonight, and if she is bleeding, you will stop the bleeding. 

goal: see the alchemist survive. you don&#39;t need to survive to win.

-------------------------
**The killer&#39;s apprentice**
Neutral support

**The killer&#39;s aid** (passive)
You can speak with your neutral killer master at night, being seen as &quot;Apprentice (your name).&quot;

**In their bloody foot steps** (passive)
you shall replace your master if they die as a neutral killer, becoming the mortician (see below).

**Pay-off** (night, 2 uses)
you will pay off any investigators who visit your master tonight, making your master appear as a blue dragon support to them.

goal: win with your master. you don&#39;t need to survive to win.

------------------------------
**The Mortician**
Neutral killing
you tried to make like your master, but you are not magical....

**Overdose** (night, infinite uses)
give your target an overdose of drugs. There screen will be blurry of and on the next day (fifteen second intervals) and will speak gibberish only, and then will die the next day.

**Dissect** (night, infinite uses)
gain a use of _transplant_

**Transplant** (day, 1 uses)
If you are the target, you will be immune to death the next time you are attacked. If the target is someone else, they will hemorrhage and gain the bleeding effect (same as what hunter causes to other players).

goal: kill everyone who does not need to survive. If you win, so does your previous master.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 16:00:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-the-apprentices/2753.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[class suggestions] the apprentices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>only one per game, not guranteed</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>The prince’s apprentice</strong><br>
Blue dragon support</p>
<p><strong>Prince’s aid</strong> (passive)<br>
knows who the prince imprisoned. Can listen in on the conversation between the prince and the prisoner. Can speak to the prince at night (text appears like the dead do to priest). Prince will see you as “Apprentice (your name).” E.x: Apprentice lewis harte</p>
<p><strong>In his foot steps</strong> (passive)<br>
if the prince dies night 1, 2, or 3, you shall replace him as prince with one use of “execute” left. If he dies another night, you shall become a knight.</p>
<p><strong>Spare cell</strong> (day, 2 uses) your target will be thrown in the dungeon tonight, but no one will be there to talk to them or execute them. The prince’s target is in another cell.</p>
<p>goal: Defeat the unseen/cult and any neutral who would seek to do you harm.<br>
converts into the enforcer, but still speaks with the prince at night as “Apprentice (your name)”</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>The alchemist’s apprentice</strong><br>
neutral support</p>
<p><strong>Alchemist’s aid</strong> (passive)<br>
If the alchemist is occupied, you will carry out whatever task they attempted to do. You can speak with the alchemist at night, being seen as “Apprentice (your name)”</p>
<p><strong>Apply potion</strong> (night, infinite uses)<br>
Inject your target with a potion. There is a 50 percent chance it will be a crimson potion, and a 50 percent chance it will be an emerald potion.</p>
<p><strong>First-aid</strong> (night, 2 uses)<br>
the alchemist will be immune to death tonight, and if she is bleeding, you will stop the bleeding.</p>
<p>goal: see the alchemist survive. you don’t need to survive to win.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>The killer’s apprentice</strong><br>
Neutral support</p>
<p><strong>The killer’s aid</strong> (passive)<br>
You can speak with your neutral killer master at night, being seen as “Apprentice (your name).”</p>
<p><strong>In their bloody foot steps</strong> (passive)<br>
you shall replace your master if they die as a neutral killer, becoming the mortician (see below).</p>
<p><strong>Pay-off</strong> (night, 2 uses)<br>
you will pay off any investigators who visit your master tonight, making your master appear as a blue dragon support to them.</p>
<p>goal: win with your master. you don’t need to survive to win.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>The Mortician</strong><br>
Neutral killing<br>
you tried to make like your master, but you are not magical…</p>
<p><strong>Overdose</strong> (night, infinite uses)<br>
give your target an overdose of drugs. There screen will be blurry of and on the next day (fifteen second intervals) and will speak gibberish only, and then will die the next day.</p>
<p><strong>Dissect</strong> (night, infinite uses)<br>
gain a use of <em>transplant</em></p>
<p><strong>Transplant</strong> (day, 1 uses)<br>
If you are the target, you will be immune to death the next time you are attacked. If the target is someone else, they will hemorrhage and gain the bleeding effect (same as what hunter causes to other players).</p>
<p>goal: kill everyone who does not need to survive. If you win, so does your previous master.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-the-apprentices/2753/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-the-apprentices/2753/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2753-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestions-the-apprentices/2753.rss">[class suggestions] the apprentices</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
