<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453</link>
    <description>I try my best as Alchemist to help but every game a Prince kills me in jail or the table goes &quot;NEUTS OUT&quot; and kills me.

It&#39;s an incredibly frustrating role to play.

I think every other Neutral role is interesting.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 11:28:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[slappy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/2X/d/db84323f04298ea0e8bc31e1ff9825ced39e5e74.jpg" alt="zzzzzzz" data-base62-sha1="vjVNiTMuTm08PkKEisvBvpOZKXq" width="227" height="225"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 11:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is a social deduction game. Would you play it if you were never questioned of your class?</p>
<p>Not only that, but with new update you can easily pretend to be a physician</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 11:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When you get to late game there is always the crimson potion. Use it on a few scum and close the game before the BD can think to execute you. If you find the MM then you can wait and out him to buy time and trust if needed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 19:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not hard or easy, it’s largely beyond your control.  You need to survive the entire game, but as the game goes on the list of suspects narrows.  Someone steps on a trap and outs the Hunter.  The Butler poisons the king and confirms.  The psychic tells the Prince who they are.  The Noble confirms via invisible whispers.  The Priest reveals and isn’t counterclaimed or revives someone who becomes confirmed.  The Sheriff/Paladin get the MM/Cult and everyone trusts them.  Your acting like there’s always 10+ options and the Alchemist will never get picked unless the alchemist themselves does something to make themselves get picked, but that isn’t the case.  In a game with good BD, an Alchemist is going to end up on a very short list of suspects and there really isn’t much an alchemist can do to prevent it.  Yes, there are things you can do that are dumb and will get you checked but even if you do none of those things unless BD has leads, it’s likely at some point in the game you’ll get checked or at least voted up for your role.</p>
<p>But okay, let’s take a step back and take Allies and other checks out of the equation.  Would you agree that if the majority of BD is of the opinion that Alchemists shouldn’t be lynched, especially Prince and King, that the game becomes much more difficult for the Alchemist?  Because my main point is still that the attitude of others towards Alchemists in general, especially the BD power roles, is the biggest factor of an Alchemist’s success.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually, you do. You can kill the only 2 people who can find your factions (and out you)</p>
<p>I don’t see why it is so hard to avoid 4/6/8 uses of an ability, the only one that will reveal you</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 12:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The advice of ‘just don’t get checked’ isn’t really a counter-argument to how good or bad a class is.  You can say that about literally every evil and most neutral classes.  Everyone is trying not to be suspicious (Except the fool), it’s a social deduction game. Saying don’t be suspicious is like saying “Win a football game by having more points at the end.”  You’re not wrong, but it’s also not really useful advice.</p>
<p>Other classes have tools to assist them not getting caught, which the Alchemist doesn’t.  Most of those classes have a team so even if they die they can still win, which the Alchemist doesn’t.  Scorned and Fool have goals that means they don’t have to survive the entire game, the Alchemist doesn’t.  If BD is hostile to Alchemists then being an Alchemist is almost like being an NK but without the benefits.</p>
<p>Which means that surviving as an Alchemist if BD is hostile to you is much, much, harder than surviving when they are not.  Not impossible, and good play can certainly nudge your odds up, but the single greatest factor in if you’ll win as an Alchemist is the attitude other players have toward Alchemists before the game even starts.  I’ve seen people win as Alchemist, but 9 times out of 10 people knew they were an Alchemist before the end of the game and let them live.  And in the small time this wasn’t the case, it was mostly that the game ended very quickly.  I’ve never seen an Alch survive a 10+ day game without being outed.</p>
<p>I know players who say you should keep Alchemists around and I know players who say you should always kill them. Those players have made their minds up in advance and there is very little an Alchemist can do to change their mind.  All they can do is hope they get lucky and end up with the people who keep Alchemists around. No class should have it’s biggest (Not only, but biggest) factor in their winning or not winning be the strategy of the <em>other</em> players.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 07:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t do it kids</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 01:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>just played a game where BD allows alch to live all game, alch ends up siding with evil as king maker</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 01:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>huh, master mind is <em>also</em> free prince exe when caught…</p>
<p>and they both happen to be not BD, what are the odds?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frostwolf103]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So Alchemist need fake claim of Investigative class with ‘creative’ way to play.</p>
<p>It does make you look more like Scorned or Fool in theory, basically free prince exe when caught.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 22:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sketch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Never claim Alchemist…</p>
<p>…unless you truly believe evils have a majority.</p>
<p>Alchemist used to have an interesting day ability that literally blurred a player’s screen during the day for 10 seconds and they would NEVER get hanged or die by evils at night since it’d be a waste of time for both factions. It was almost a literal “I win” button.</p>
<p>Alchemist, while more difficult to play, is much better in this current iteration. Claim Physician, or get more creative with Princess, Sheriff/Paly or Observer claims.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 22:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael_Tawney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s a great way for a possessor or reaper to run train on everyone while BD thinks you’re throwing heals. That’s why I say “statistically speaking” it’s better to just kill them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 21:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eran_Shmuel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The best way to play alchemist is to claim it before somone ask.<br>
usually im just wishpering the king on day 1 and tell him im healing him the whole game.</p>
<p>Somtimes they even tell me to kill somone and prove my loyalty</p>
<p>Say it on town chat is also very good, because no evil players will want you dead.</p>
<p>As a Prince, I tend not to kill a proved alchemist players for the simple reason: alchemists can not be converted, they are wasting convert chances for evil players and can help you just execute every convertable players left</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 12:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="EvadableMoxie" data-post="7" data-topic="7453">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/evadablemoxie/40/2001_2.png" class="avatar"> EvadableMoxie:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So, typically when you win by lying it’s because you were lucky enough not to get checked and the game moved quickly enough that you slid under the radar.  Which again means you won not on your own merits, but because BD was kicking so much ass they never needed to really look into you, or Unseen murdered BD so quickly they never had a chance. And if it’s a cult game? Good fucking luck surviving one of those, there are so many days you’re getting executed at some point for sure.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, the way to survive is:</p>
<ol>
<li>avoid the king’s allies ability (4 uses), possibly by killing them</li>
<li>avoid observer’s window peak (2 uses)</li>
<li>use stone skin as you think you will be attacked</li>
</ol>
<p>both the king and observer have few uses, so just act not suspicious and they won’t waste time on you. Alternatively, murder them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 11:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“If the king checks you, you are dead”</p>
<p>The king only has 4 uses of ability, so act normal enough and he won’t waste one on you.</p>
<p>In fact, this is the exact same with sheriff and the unseen…</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 11:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Michael_Tawney" data-post="14" data-topic="7453" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/michael_tawney/40/2198_2.png" class="avatar"> Michael_Tawney:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If I were king and someone whispered me saying they were alch I would get them prince executed on the spot. Don’t want to risk leaving a reaper, scorned, fool, or poss on the field.</p>
<p>Alch has it bad because all other neuts are negative to BD so statistically better to just off the alch every time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t agree or disagree with this behavior but I believe it cements the point I was originally making.</p>
<p>The current state of the game has most people that I’ve come across to say “NEUTS OUT” and kill them on the spot.</p>
<p>People suggesting to make a pact with the king, it’s a bandaid to the problem and it doesn’t work 100% of the time.</p>
<p>Alch, and to a lesser extent, neutrals in general, need a lot of love in the current state of the game.</p>
<p>Even as BD it sucks when my team kills an Alch because of this mentaility and we lose somebody late game because we don’t have a heal, but they just can’t risk posessor/scorned/reapers/fools interfering with the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 11:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s the point of Neutrals???</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 10:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael_Tawney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If I were king and someone whispered me saying they were alch I would get them prince executed on the spot. Don’t want to risk leaving a reaper, scorned, fool, or poss on the field.</p>
<p>Alch has it bad because all other neuts are negative to BD so statistically better to just off the alch every time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 03:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Again, you’re taking the game out of your own hands by allying with the King.  Maybe he lets you live. Maybe he throws you to the wolves because BD is getting restless about him not finding any unseen and stating you’re not an ally and letting you burn helps his cause.  Maybe he’s worried about the Reaper/Poessessor and decides to kill you just to make sure you aren’t fake claiming.  Either way, you didn’t win or lose by cleverness or good gameplay.  You won or lost because the King made a decision to keep you around or kill you all on his own.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 03:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[livejamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well said EvadableMoxie.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 22:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The moral of the story is the starting king is either your best friend or your worst enemy</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 22:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CN73DRUMMER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If nobody is yelling neuts out I make a pact with the king that I will be on his side whether he is good neutral or evil. That I will heal him every night unless he says otherwise, and I remind him I have two emerald potions at his disposal. A king loves hearing that he can silently kill off two people that he wants during the game without having to execute them, just by whispering to you.</p>
<p>If people are yelling neuts out, I give the first two that yell it an emerald potion and then stay quiet and usually the rest of the BD get killed or executed and I vote with whoever has majority at the end of the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 22:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always just poison relatively quiet people. Kill Prince? Great job! Kill cult? Great job! Hit immune? Great job!</p>
<p>You can’t go wrong with killing indiscriminately as alch. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 21:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So make a pact with the King or something</p>
<p>Now you only need to convince one person instead of the whole town</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 21:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Being an Alchemist is Awful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[EvadableMoxie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My problem with Alchemist isn’t so much the win rate, but how you win or lose.</p>
<p>Basically you have 2 options:</p>
<p>1: Claim Alchemist.</p>
<p>2: Lie.</p>
<p>Option 1: You are now fully at the Mercy of BD.  You’ve basically taken the game out of your own hands and into someone elses and asked nicely to win.  And when you win, you didn’t win because you outsmarted anyone, you didn’t win because you played well, you didn’t win due to any plays you made… you won because someone else allowed you to do so.</p>
<p>Option 2: Lie.  Okay, well… If the King checks you? You’re dead.  If you claim Phys and then 2 actual Phys die? You’re dead. One Phys died and the other counter claims you? Dead. If you claim anything else and can’t back it up with a good journal? Dead. You don’t get any evil versions of abilities like converted Unseen, nor do you have anyone to plot with and help your claims.  The only possible ability that can confirm you is your heal, but again, if you claim Phys and someone gets poisoned? Yea, you’re dead.</p>
<p>Hell, just when it gets down to the wire you’re often dead because both BD and Unseen/Cult are happy to lynch you since you have nothing to confirm with and very little ways to fake other roles. When unseen/cult get to that critical point where they just have to dodge getting one of them executed for 1 or 2 more days to win, they’ll throw you right under the bus because the BD love killing neutrals, and that’s one more day they don’t have to worry about getting one of them lynched.</p>
<p>So, typically when you win by lying it’s because you were lucky enough not to get checked and the game moved quickly enough that you slid under the radar.  Which <em>again</em> means you won not on your own merits, but because BD was kicking so much ass they never needed to really look into you, or Unseen murdered BD so quickly they never had a chance. And if it’s a cult game? Good fucking luck surviving one of those, there are so many days you’re getting executed at some point for sure.</p>
<p>That’s what bothers me about Alchemist.  A balanced Win rate doesn’t mean a class is good, if you had a class that literally flipped a coin Night 1 and then won on heads and lost on tails it would have a 50% win rate but it would be a shitty class.</p>
<p>Alchemist does have <em>some</em> agency and every now and then you can make plays as an alchemist to speed up the game but in general, you’re playing a game that is mostly out of your hands.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 20:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-7453-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/being-an-alchemist-is-awful/7453.rss">Being an Alchemist is Awful</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
