<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] Harpy (Neutral Killing)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-harpy-neutral-killing/39380</link>
    <description>**Harpy** (Neutral Killing) - A FREAKIN&#39; BIRD WOMAN, Y&#39;ALL.

Passive 1:
**Invasive Species** - Every two successful kills you make give you one additional use of your &quot;Broodling&quot; day ability.

Passive 2:
**Mommy Dearest** - You are immune to murder at night while you have a &quot;Broodling&quot; egg in play. (IE: There is at least one player still alive that you gave an egg to.)

Day Ability:
**Broodling** - Place an egg with a target player. It stays with them permanently. If that target visits you on a future night, the egg will &quot;hatch&quot;, killing them. Acts as a normal kill, can be healed, etc. (Single use, recharged with your &quot;Invasive Species&quot; passive.)

Night Ability 1:
**Live Prey** - Kill a player and feed them to your children, keeping them from joining dead chat  for **1 additional night**. (Victim can&#39;t speak to Ghosts or Psychic, can&#39;t be made Death Knight, etc. but only for that 1 extra night.) (Unlimited use.)

Night Ability 2:
**Home to Roost** - Retreat to your nest, protecting yourself from murder and healing bleeding/poison. (3 uses. For when you don&#39;t have an egg in play and need emergency safety or you have been bled/poisoned, etc.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 05:56:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-harpy-neutral-killing/39380.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] Harpy (Neutral Killing)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Harpy</strong> (Neutral Killing) - A FREAKIN’ BIRD WOMAN, Y’ALL.</p>
<p>Passive 1:<br>
<strong>Invasive Species</strong> - Every two successful kills you make give you one additional use of your “Broodling” day ability.</p>
<p>Passive 2:<br>
<strong>Mommy Dearest</strong> - You are immune to murder at night while you have a “Broodling” egg in play. (IE: There is at least one player still alive that you gave an egg to.)</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Broodling</strong> - Place an egg with a target player. It stays with them permanently. If that target visits you on a future night, the egg will “hatch”, killing them. Acts as a normal kill, can be healed, etc. (Single use, recharged with your “Invasive Species” passive.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Live Prey</strong> - Kill a player and feed them to your children, keeping them from joining dead chat  for <strong>1 additional night</strong>. (Victim can’t speak to Ghosts or Psychic, can’t be made Death Knight, etc. but only for that 1 extra night.) (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Home to Roost</strong> - Retreat to your nest, protecting yourself from murder and healing bleeding/poison. (3 uses. For when you don’t have an egg in play and need emergency safety or you have been bled/poisoned, etc.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-harpy-neutral-killing/39380/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-harpy-neutral-killing/39380/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 05:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39380-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-harpy-neutral-killing/39380.rss">[Class Suggestion] Harpy (Neutral Killing)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
