<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530</link>
    <description>Once a kind little girl that grew up surrounded by thieves she learned that in order to stay alive she must first protect others, but at a price. After several contracts after another she gained a trust for her clients, this is something she will turn to regret. But seeing as though she was doing well she moved to a castle in a far distant land.

Once she arrived she began contracting others in the kingdom, and standing guard by there doors. But as the mercenary found out, they were all cruel. None of them payed and if she was to do any thing about it she would be executed for treason. She gave up her contracts, seeing as though there was nothing else she could do, and regretted putting her trust in others in the first place.

At this night in the pale moonlight, she tied a noose and stood on a chair ready to make it all go away. Then she saw a person come from the corner of her room. &quot;You still have some use&quot;. The Figure said. &quot;You could serve some use for my group, we will not betray you like the others did.&quot; She stepped down from the stool and landed on the ground, she walked toward the figure. &quot;Come and we will make you great. You will not regret joining the unseen.&quot; She gladly accepted the man&#39;s invitation and became a sell-sword, seeking vengeance for the sadness that the Blue Dragon caused her.   
------------------------------------------------------------------------
Comments/Explanations
This sellsword lore is I think fits the lore of the unseen in general.
For I see that all the members of the unseen had to have felt betrayed by the blue dragon, then felt as out-casts 
But I also feel as though the mercenary before she became the sellsword should have gained trust with her clients in order to set up something for blue dragon to betray. Which they did, although I also feel like she should not be familiar to the kingdom, residing her in the neutral category, all in all I feel like this is relevant as a lore suggestion due to the fact that I first gives a portion of her life before the becoming a sellsword, but ends when she became a sellsword, leaving it to the reader to envision what happens next.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:09:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>True</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2530-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530.rss">[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insanity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess u guys make too much lore lol.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 07:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2530-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530.rss">[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I rewrote it.</p>
<p>Once, a kind little girl was born, that grew up surround by thieves and brigands. She learned quickly that in order to protect herself, she must earn her keep by protecting others, and would come to be known as the Mercenary. After several repeat contracts, she gained trust in her clients. She would then learn to regret this as one by one they betrayed her or wouldn’t pay up. Seeing as though she had earned a lump sum anyways, she decided to move to the far distant land of Adiart, and found she could make a contract in the castle.</p>
<p>Once she arrived, she began contracting others in the court, standing guard and making sure nothing went awry. But as the Mercenary soon learned, they were all bitter people due to the tensions within the court, and would not pay her fees. There was nothing she could do, as even the King would not help her. She gave up her contracts, and without a single penny left to her name, she gave up.</p>
<p>Under the pale moonlight as she pondered what she would do, a fearsome looking person revealed themselves from the shadows. Although the Mercenary was taken aback, she was calmed after the person spoke “They all let you down, didn’t they.” The person said “There is still use for you in this castle, as a member of my organisation, the Unseen.” She got up and walked towards the person, shaking their hand. “You will not regret the choice you have made. Come with me,” said the person. She gladly accepted the invitation and became known as the “Sellsword”, seeking vengeance on the Blue Dragon for how she had suffered.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 04:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2530-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530.rss">[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Once a kind little girl that grew up surrounded by thieves she learned that in order to stay alive she must first protect others, but at a price. After several contracts after another she gained a trust for her clients, this is something she will turn to regret. But seeing as though she was doing well she moved to a castle in a far distant land.</p>
<p>Once she arrived she began contracting others in the kingdom, and standing guard by there doors. But as the mercenary found out, they were all cruel. None of them payed and if she was to do any thing about it she would be executed for treason. She gave up her contracts, seeing as though there was nothing else she could do, and regretted putting her trust in others in the first place.</p>
<h2>At this night in the pale moonlight, she tied a noose and stood on a chair ready to make it all go away. Then she saw a person come from the corner of her room. “You still have some use”. The Figure said. “You could serve some use for my group, we will not betray you like the others did.” She stepped down from the stool and landed on the ground, she walked toward the figure. “Come and we will make you great. You will not regret joining the unseen.” She gladly accepted the man’s invitation and became a sell-sword, seeking vengeance for the sadness that the Blue Dragon caused her.</h2>
<p>Comments/Explanations<br>
This sellsword lore is I think fits the lore of the unseen in general.<br>
For I see that all the members of the unseen had to have felt betrayed by the blue dragon, then felt as out-casts<br>
But I also feel as though the mercenary before she became the sellsword should have gained trust with her clients in order to set up something for blue dragon to betray. Which they did, although I also feel like she should not be familiar to the kingdom, residing her in the neutral category, all in all I feel like this is relevant as a lore suggestion due to the fact that I first gives a portion of her life before the becoming a sellsword, but ends when she became a sellsword, leaving it to the reader to envision what happens next.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2530-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-sellsword/2530.rss">[Lore suggestion] Sellsword</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
