<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910</link>
    <description># [color=024A0D]VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa[/color]
Hosted by sulit, cohosted by katze

### How to Play
The game will shift through three cycles, Discussion, Roaming, and Ambidex, until it is over. Note that this game is complex and has many elements and factors. Please read all of the below before signing up.

[details=Discussion]
During Discussion all players can speak in the main thread. All players will be in the same room, so actions can be performed on other players during this time. You can also choose to end Discussion early by leaving the room. After you have left you can no longer talk in the main thread, and players can no longer perform actions on you. 

Discussion will last for 24 hours, or until 3/4 of the total players have left the room.
[/details]
[details=Roaming]
During roaming all players can move about and perform actions, search for items, attack other players, and explore in a pre-made map via PMs. If two or more people are in the same place they will be added to a PM in which they can talk privately.

There will likely be different puzzles you can solve to get better and upgraded gear.

Roaming lasts 48 hours or until all players say in their PM that they would like Roaming to end.
[/details]
[details=Ambidex]
During Ambidex all players will return to the room Discussion takes place. However, no actions can be performed at this time. Players will publicly vote on 1 of 3 lists that say which players will be paired with whom during the Ambidex Games.

After pairings have been voted on, the main thread will be closed and all players must decide whether to ally or betray their partner in their PM. If a player doesn&#39;t cast a vote they will ally by default. If both partners don&#39;t cast a vote they will both betray by default.

**Ally vs. Ally:** Both players gain 2 Ambidex Points.
**Ally vs. Betray:** The person who allied will lose 2 points, and the betrayer will gain 3.
**Betray vs. Betray:** Both players will earn zero Amdidex Points.

Ambidex Phase will last 48 hours, 24 for voting, 24 to submit Ally or Betray.
[/details]
[details=Stats]
If an action a player performs has a chance to fail, a 1d20 will be rolled with discobot. Depending on the action, the player will have one or more of their stats added to the roll. This will determine how successful it is. There are five different stats that can be applied to actions.

**Strength (STR):** Lifting or pushing heavy things, pulling things, attacking with melee-based weapons, etc.
**Precision (PRC):** Throwing items, attacking with ranged weapons, doing actions with items that are hard to maneuver, etc.
**Endurance (END):** How much hits you can, how much you can withstand harmful effects, etc.
**Intelligence (INT):** Searching rooms, gaining information, healing, building things, etc.
**Agility (AGI):** Dodging hits, running, attacking with melee weapons, etc.
[/details]
[details=Inventory and Items]
During the game, players may find useful items they want to keep with them, or take them from other players. 

Players have a limited inventory space. They have 5 public inventory slots that can be seen by anyone looking into their inventory, and 1 private slot that no one can see unless the player is unconscious or specifically shows it to someone.

In addition, some players may start with an addition private role slot, in which a role item can be stored.
[/details]
[details=Roles]
Before the game starts, players will be assigned a role via PM. Roles will dictate unique abilities, stats, items you might start with, your alignment, and your win condition.

**CLAIMING YOUR ROLE, STATS, OR WIN CONDITION TO ANYONE ELSE IS STRICTLY NOT ALLOWED AND WILL RESULT IN A MODKILL. SPECULATION ABOUT OTHERS ROLES IS NOT ALLOWED EXCEPT UNDER VERY SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES.**

However, claiming and speculating on alignment is allowed.

The four alignments are Good, Evil, Wildcard and Neutral.

**Good** players need to help others, and help as many people escape as possible.
**Neutral** players need to escape at all costs.
**Wildcard** players have a more flexible win condition and can end up being any of the other three alignments.
**Evil** players are there to sabotage others, cause chaos, and cause conflict and potentially death.

There is no role list.

**Roles and alignments will not be flipped upon death.**
[/details]
[details=Actions]
Players submit actions to the moderator in order to interact with other players and the map. These can be anything; picking up an item, punching another player, doing a backflip.

To perform an action, type **/action,** for example **/call Arete a nerd.** Actions can be submitted in your PM, in chats with other players, or in the main thread during discussion. You can submit actions anytime except during the Ambidex phase.

Players can set automatic actions for when they are AFK in case something happens to them while they are gone. If they have nothing set I will generally do something for them. I&#39;m not just going to let someone get stabbed because they were AFK.

During roaming, every player will start with 10 Energy. Everytime a player performs an action one of their Energy Points will deplete. If a player runs out, they will still be able to do an automatic action for when they are AFK or counterattack an attacker, but they will not be able to perform anymore actions. If an action fails it will still take away an Energy Point. Energy Points replenish every 24 hours. Energy Points players have every phase will increase as more players die.

In addition to the above, I might add certain time frames where Energy Points do not matter. I will decide this if there is a good time for all players in the game that I would be able to rapidly process actions during.
[/details]
[details=Combat]
All weapons will have a certain damage amount. When a player attacks another, I will take the weapons damage amount and add it to the attacks strength. For example, if a player with a strength stat of 4 attacks a player with a weapon that does four damage, they will do eight damage.

If a player attempts to dodge an attack I will roll a 1d20 and choose a number depending on how the player is attacked. If the number rolled is more than that number the player will successfully dodge.

I am flexible processing combat actions and might award more damage points for creativity.

Health is calculated by 20+(5*END stat). If a player takes more damage than this they will be knocked out. If a player is hit after that they will die.

Medical items will have a flat healing amount, and extra healing will be added on by the INT stat*2.
[/details]
[details=Ambidex Points and Winning]
Every player will start with 4 Ambidex Points. Ambidex Point totals will be visible at all times in the OP. If a player ever has less than one Ambidex Point they will immediately die.

If a player has more than or equal to 11 Ambidex Points, they can access the Door Number 11 that is located in the map. When the door is opened, it will remain open for 11 seconds, then it will close forever and the game will end. Only players with 11 points or more can exit the door.

**The Ambidex Game is the only way to earn Ambidex Points, and the Door Number 11 is the only way to escape.**
[/details]

### Game Maps And Room Descriptions
[details=Map 1]
![image|690x455](upload://VfaPqJzwTSP2EVvqGTXkJnDz6P.png) 

Medic Cabin: *A small, clean cabin, looking recently abandoned. Has a long table in the middle and many cabinets, with a counter running along the wall*

Ruins:  *What looks like large stone pillars and broken down buildings. Is that… writing?*

Prison:  *An abandoned, rusty looking building. Inside there are 3 cells in a desk, however most of the doors are off their hinges and only one seems to be functioning.*

Treehouse 1:  *A cozy little home with a fire place in the corner, burnt out. There’s a small living area and a bedroom, as well as a kitchen.*

Treehouse 2:  *Almost identical to the first treehouse, except there is no fireplace.*

Lake:  *A large lake with sandy shores. Who knows what could be lurking in its depths.*

Greenhouse:  *A large greenhouse. The windows are fogged up but you can see a lot of green hues.*

Clearing:  *Just a large clearing. The group agreed to meet here every 4 days.*


[/details]
[details=Map 2]
![image|690x381](upload://8Fm3tZSIVl1p5RfrDYSf2uGIknb.png) 
[/details]

### Rules
Breaking any of the below will first give you a warning, and breaking them again will result in a force replacement or a modkill.
1. Follow all Global Forum Rules
2. Do not discuss the game outside this thread or in your PM(s)
3.  Do not copy and paste, directly quote, or screenshot anything sent by me.
4. Do not game throw, or go directly against your win condition.
5. Do not angleshoot.
6. Do not edit or delete any posts in the main thread or in any PMs.
7. Do your best to be active, doing actions and posting every phase, getting Ambidex actions in.
8. **Claiming role, win condition, and stats is strictly not allowed, as is speculating on them. This will result in a immediate mod kill. Alignment speculation is allowed.**
9. Mod has the right to add, change, or remove rules.

### Signing Up
To sign up, do /in, /join, just express interest in joining in the thread. **Also please say your timezone and a time frame(s) that you would be able to be the most active for you/would be the most convenient for you. You can convert it to EST for brownie points.**

### Players
1) NetherNitro - **10 AP**
2) DatBird - **Dead**
**3) Marshal - **11 AP****
4) Moleland - **Dead**
5) Magnus  - **8 AP**
6) Zone_Q11 - **Dead**
7) Mist - **Dead**
8) Italy - **Dead**
9) KyoDaz - **Dead**
10) Trustworthy Liberal - **Dead**
11) Alice - **Dead**
12) Simon - **8 AP**

### Backups
1. Apprentice
2. PKR
3. 

### Spectators
1. Napoleon
2. Jane
3. Geyde

## Please read the whole OP before joining. This is extremely important. This is not a game where you can just ignore the OP.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:41:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Completed</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll do so now.</p>
<p>Edit: Done <a class="mention" href="/u/zone_q11">@Zone_Q11</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1212">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1212</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1212</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zone_Q11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>By the way, can the tag change from Ongoing to Completed?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1211">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1211</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1211</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marshal" data-post="1202" data-topic="81910">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marshal/40/32698_2.png" class="avatar"> Marshal:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>it does stop me from getting TL3</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>it’s okay the site settings are such that it has to be manually granted anyway</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1210">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1210</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1210</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Rip. I don’t have trouble with my typing.<br>
Except for minor issues such as typing a ; instead of an ).</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1209">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1209</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1209</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If I didn’t know better I would think that I had dyslexia with how frequently this shit happens</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1208">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1208</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1208</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>why does my brain not connect with my hands when I’m typing</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1207">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1207</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1207</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geyde]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t say that to your face without getting closer</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1206">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1206</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1206</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marshal" data-post="896" data-topic="81910" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marshal/40/32698_2.png" class="avatar"> Marshal:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>simon the player is a real epic gamer™ and I hope both him and his family not only win the lottery but also have good luck for the next 9 and a half years <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/sunglasses.png?v=9" title=":sunglasses:" class="emoji" alt=":sunglasses:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>SAY THAT TO MY FACE!<br>
</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1205">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1205</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1205</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i mean<br>
if they’re reusable icepacks<br>
they’re already toxic, venom or no</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1204">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1204</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1204</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marshal" data-post="896" data-topic="81910" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marshal/40/32698_2.png" class="avatar"> Marshal:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>simon the player is a real epic gamer™ and I hope both him and his family not only win the lottery but also have good luck for the next 9 and a half years <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/sunglasses.png?v=9" title=":sunglasses:" class="emoji" alt=":sunglasses:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well I edited it<br>
now much better</p>
<p>thank you system</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1203">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1203</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1203</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe?</p>
<p>I guess out of the 100s of shadow the hedgehog meme posts with the target clearly not being uncomfortable someone decided that one was the real evil</p>
<p><img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/man_shrugging.png?v=9" title=":man_shrugging:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":man_shrugging:"></p>
<p>could just be someone who didn’t get the context ig not that upset but ik it does stop me from  getting TL3 which is like mildly annoying</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1202">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1202</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1202</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KyoDaz" data-post="1199" data-topic="81910">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/kyodaz/40/30587_2.png" class="avatar"> KyoDaz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>TessA</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Dangerous articles intensifies.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1201">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1201</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1201</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zone_Q11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe some guest or user read the game and didn’t know about the meme?</p>
<p>Otherwise it wouldn’t make sense for me either.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1200">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1200</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1200</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Having to settle for venom-infused icepacks is definitely something KyoDaz would do</p>
<p>Or TessA</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1199">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1199</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1199</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marshal" data-post="895" data-topic="81910">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/marshal/40/32698_2.png" class="avatar"> Marshal:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>why is simon still alive</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>because i promised that i would not die, on threat of a community chosen replacement pfp and one other thing.<br>
i was serious about that yeah</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1198">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1198</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1198</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what?<br>
i mean if it helps i was the targeted individual and im cool with it being there  as is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1197">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1197</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1197</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>w…why was this post flagged?</p>
<p>it wasn’t an attack at simon it was clearly a joke on the shadow the hedgehog meme everyone knows it</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1196">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1196</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1196</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hm</p>
<p>ask me again closer to the end of that, then</p>
<p>im not good at planning far ahead</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1195">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1195</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1195</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ayaya</p>
<p>probably after Danagnronpa ends</p>
<p>if you don’t want to thats ok</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1194">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1194</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1194</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>but like</p>
<p>not with the game itself</p>
<p>although if we did it again i’d probably do most of the discord stuff which is probably not easy</p>
<p>uhh</p>
<p>maybe</p>
<p>idk</p>
<p>it kinda depends on when this happens</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1193">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1193</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1193</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I tagged kat because they helped this game smh</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1192">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1192</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1192</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You helped ):&lt;</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1191">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1191</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1191</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[katze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>do you want a cohost that’ll actually help you  run the game</p>
<p>the answer to that question is the inverse answer to whether or not i’ll cohost <img src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/images/emoji/twitter/eyes.png?v=9" title=":eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1190">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1190</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1190</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sulit" data-post="1188" data-topic="81910">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/sulit/40/32765_2.png" class="avatar"> sulit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyone wanna try cohosting?</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/katze">@katze</a>?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><s>I was <em>right here</em> and you didn’t ask me</s></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1189">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1189</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1189</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Probably gonna start working on there next one</p>
<p>Anyone wanna try cohosting?</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/katze">@katze</a>?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1188">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910/1188</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-81910-1188</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/misc-vldr-virtues-last-danganronpa-marshal-wins/81910.rss">[MISC] VLDR: Virtues Last Danganronpa [MARSHAL WINS]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
