<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138</link>
    <description>Hmm, I was going to base it off the current CW lore, but I wasn&#39;t feeling it. What I&#39;m trying for here is a Court Wizard who&#39;s still suspicious as all hell, still causes chaos for the BD.


Night Abilities
Induce Visions: Your target will see a confirmation of their ability as if nobody could inhibit them. _If occupied, redirected, or prevented, they will not receive a message. They still attempt to perform the action._
Tornado: (3 uses) unchanged

Notifications:
Induce Visions: _target_ was given a vision of their actions.

Sage:
Tornado: unchanged
Induce Doubt (3 uses): Your target receives a message of being prevented from visiting their target. _If occupied or redirected, they will not receive a message._

Notification:
Induce Doubt: _target_ was given false visions of their actions.


Induce Visions from the target&#39;s perspective: No notice that you were the target. This bypasses everything (occupied, redirected, merc guard, jail, frame/hide) to show you the message you&#39;d get. This does not give immunity, so if occupied or prevented, your target will not be healed, attacked, occupied, etc.
Induce Doubt simply does the same effect, but the message will always be prevented from visiting.

EDIT: cleaned up wording. I jumped between lots of ideas on the ability...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 23:06:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[squidgyxombie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The idea was keeping CW still horribly suspicious. It only screws with messages people receive. Make CW something bad guys can still claim, but if you put multiple logs together… you can prove a person was having visions.</p>
<p>If Butler does an Occ on 2, and 2 is in jail. The butler will not occupy the jailed person and see the message<br>
“You were prevented from visiting 2.”<br>
If Butler does an Occ on 2 with Induce Visions and 2 is in jail. The butler will not occupy the jailed person, but the Butler now sees “You occupied 2” or “2 was immune, this could be due to blah blah” based on 2’s class.</p>
<p>The biggest thing this does is make a CW have synergy with both real and fake investigators. If the CW visions a person faking logs, they will know when the person claims they were prevented or occupied. If they vision a real investigator, then the information is gathered regardless of occupy, swap, etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 23:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-55138-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138.rss">Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So it doesn’t actually make their action take effect? And it confirms the CW? I don’t like confirmability and you only gave CW a worse version of Barrier that sorta bypasses prevention in a way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-55138-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138.rss">Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>WOF is the sage greatness</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 21:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-55138-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138.rss">Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nerfed sage so much</p>
<p>I don’t want him</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 21:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-55138-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138.rss">Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[squidgyxombie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm, I was going to base it off the current CW lore, but I wasn’t feeling it. What I’m trying for here is a Court Wizard who’s still suspicious as all hell, still causes chaos for the BD.</p>
<p>Night Abilities<br>
Induce Visions: Your target will see a confirmation of their ability as if nobody could inhibit them. <em>If occupied, redirected, or prevented, they will not receive a message. They still attempt to perform the action.</em><br>
Tornado: (3 uses) unchanged</p>
<p>Notifications:<br>
Induce Visions: <em>target</em> was given a vision of their actions.</p>
<p>Sage:<br>
Tornado: unchanged<br>
Induce Doubt (3 uses): Your target receives a message of being prevented from visiting their target. <em>If occupied or redirected, they will not receive a message.</em></p>
<p>Notification:<br>
Induce Doubt: <em>target</em> was given false visions of their actions.</p>
<p>Induce Visions from the target’s perspective: No notice that you were the target. This bypasses everything (occupied, redirected, merc guard, jail, frame/hide) to show you the message you’d get. This does not give immunity, so if occupied or prevented, your target will not be healed, attacked, occupied, etc.<br>
Induce Doubt simply does the same effect, but the message will always be prevented from visiting.</p>
<p>EDIT: cleaned up wording. I jumped between lots of ideas on the ability…</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 21:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-55138-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/court-wizard-suggestion-by-squidgy/55138.rss">Court Wizard Suggestion by Squidgy</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
