<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum of Lies-General Post</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709</link>
    <description>HI and I know I popped up here and than vanished, but ignore that. If you don&#39;t know me then hi, and in this post I&#39;ll be discussing a few things about FoL(Forum of Lies, ToL but here) and while some of the following can be applicable to ToL as well, I&#39;m mainly addressing the forum&#39;s meta, balance, and etc.

Firstly, the meta. What I noticed in FoL 7 at least it seems to be highly claim and role centric, there isn&#39;t much actual discussion outside of the role mechanics, interactions, claims, you name it. While I know this is hard to change, this itself is highly unproductive in the end goal and gives scum an advantage. Scum know who&#39;s lying in the claim battles 99% of the time(excluding neutrals) and while they might not kill a CC&#39;er(assuming that it is one) they will kill a claim they see as a threat, thus eliminating a helpful power role.

&quot;But they help us solve the game!&quot;

Yes, that is true, but having no set massclaim and claiming randomly just makes this worse-you only want to massclaim when town is in MyLo or all out of places and things to discuss. Furthermore, plans made revolving around roles are often highly revolving around scum&#39;s members, but that in itself is unknown. Finally, given how the game revolves around conversion(another thing that is awful, but since it&#39;s the core concept I wonn&#39;t bother) claiming is worse than usual.

Then we have some roles in the game. In general, for newer players, it&#39;s convoluted and confusing(like me, even after reading a few i still mixed and forgot). Let&#39;s look at ToS for an example-all the roles are simple, and clean cut. Investigator? Narrows down roles. Godfather? Commands the kill? You get the point. But let&#39;s look at ToL. Observer? Trakcer/Lookout/Motion Detector. Court Wizard? Rolestopper/Redirector/Ascetizer. The first and last are so similar, and rolestopper completely trumps Ascetizer(unless the rolestopper also protects which I didn&#39;t see). While Observer isnn&#39;t awful keep in mind it&#39;s one of the simpler roles.

Then, we have roles such as Squire, Noble, and Priest, all of which are night immune. Yes, while there is conversion, town should never have night immunity(outside of protection roles doling out protection). It&#39;s extremely unfair to scum, especially given how members must die to get past their night immunity.

There are other problematic roles that at the core are unbalanced but point made.

Last thing, FoL shouldn&#39;t be sticking to heritage, it should be focused on balance. ToL not so much, since it&#39;s a quickshot game but FoL is longer(drastically) and thus should have a different focus. This ultimately, combined with everything else, makes a confusing and sometimes unpleasant experience for new players. Thank you for reading this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 23:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum of Lies</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies-General Post</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Queen_Alfa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ingeel" data-post="1" data-topic="2709">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ingeel/40/935_2.png" class="avatar"> Ingeel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Firstly, the meta. What I noticed in FoL 7 at least it seems to be highly claim and role centric, there isn’t much actual discussion outside of the role mechanics, interactions, claims, you name it. While I know this is hard to change, this itself is highly unproductive in the end goal and gives scum an advantage. Scum know who’s lying in the claim battles 99% of the time(excluding neutrals) and while they might not kill a CC’er(assuming that it is one) they will kill a claim they see as a threat, thus eliminating a helpful power role.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah yes, the dreaded mass claims, can’t really fix that <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> unless we add some type of rule that kills people when they mass claim (which is no fun)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ingeel" data-post="1" data-topic="2709">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ingeel/40/935_2.png" class="avatar"> Ingeel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Then we have some roles in the game. In general, for newer players, it’s convoluted and confusing(like me, even after reading a few i still mixed and forgot). Let’s look at ToS for an example-all the roles are simple, and clean cut. Investigator? Narrows down roles. Godfather? Commands the kill? You get the point. But let’s look at ToL. Observer? Trakcer/Lookout/Motion Detector. Court Wizard? Rolestopper/Redirector/Ascetizer. The first and last are so similar, and rolestopper completely trumps Ascetizer(unless the rolestopper also protects which I didn’t see). While Observer isnn’t awful keep in mind it’s one of the simpler roles.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Motion detector lel. Anyways, I say the complexity is a good thing, it’s interesting ;D</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ingeel" data-post="1" data-topic="2709">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ingeel/40/935_2.png" class="avatar"> Ingeel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>we have roles such as Squire, Noble, and Priest, all of which are night immune</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Priest is only night immune once<br>
Noble is no longer immune now ;D<br>
Squire is squire .-. and can be can be easily converted instead of killed, the fascinating thing about all these night immune class, is that they can be converrrted! Not to mention That squire still keeps it’s night immunity when converted.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ingeel" data-post="1" data-topic="2709">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ingeel/40/935_2.png" class="avatar"> Ingeel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Last thing, FoL shouldn’t be sticking to heritage, it should be focused on balance. ToL not so much, since it’s a quickshot game but FoL is longer(drastically) and thus should have a different focus. This ultimately, combined with everything else, makes a confusing and sometimes unpleasant experience for new players.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We want to try to stay as close to ToL as possible because well, Forum of lies. We have however moved away from ToL on a few different things (Cult, Noble, unofficial classes). But balance is being worked on ;D</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 23:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2709-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709.rss">Forum of Lies-General Post</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies-General Post</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Problem: ToL’s classes make claiming BD-sided, so claiming it’s a meta issue doesn’t really work when it’s the meta because of an issue and not really an issue with the meta</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 21:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2709-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709.rss">Forum of Lies-General Post</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum of Lies-General Post</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ingeel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>HI and I know I popped up here and than vanished, but ignore that. If you don’t know me then hi, and in this post I’ll be discussing a few things about FoL(Forum of Lies, ToL but here) and while some of the following can be applicable to ToL as well, I’m mainly addressing the forum’s meta, balance, and etc.</p>
<p>Firstly, the meta. What I noticed in FoL 7 at least it seems to be highly claim and role centric, there isn’t much actual discussion outside of the role mechanics, interactions, claims, you name it. While I know this is hard to change, this itself is highly unproductive in the end goal and gives scum an advantage. Scum know who’s lying in the claim battles 99% of the time(excluding neutrals) and while they might not kill a CC’er(assuming that it is one) they will kill a claim they see as a threat, thus eliminating a helpful power role.</p>
<p>“But they help us solve the game!”</p>
<p>Yes, that is true, but having no set massclaim and claiming randomly just makes this worse-you only want to massclaim when town is in MyLo or all out of places and things to discuss. Furthermore, plans made revolving around roles are often highly revolving around scum’s members, but that in itself is unknown. Finally, given how the game revolves around conversion(another thing that is awful, but since it’s the core concept I wonn’t bother) claiming is worse than usual.</p>
<p>Then we have some roles in the game. In general, for newer players, it’s convoluted and confusing(like me, even after reading a few i still mixed and forgot). Let’s look at ToS for an example-all the roles are simple, and clean cut. Investigator? Narrows down roles. Godfather? Commands the kill? You get the point. But let’s look at ToL. Observer? Trakcer/Lookout/Motion Detector. Court Wizard? Rolestopper/Redirector/Ascetizer. The first and last are so similar, and rolestopper completely trumps Ascetizer(unless the rolestopper also protects which I didn’t see). While Observer isnn’t awful keep in mind it’s one of the simpler roles.</p>
<p>Then, we have roles such as Squire, Noble, and Priest, all of which are night immune. Yes, while there is conversion, town should never have night immunity(outside of protection roles doling out protection). It’s extremely unfair to scum, especially given how members must die to get past their night immunity.</p>
<p>There are other problematic roles that at the core are unbalanced but point made.</p>
<p>Last thing, FoL shouldn’t be sticking to heritage, it should be focused on balance. ToL not so much, since it’s a quickshot game but FoL is longer(drastically) and thus should have a different focus. This ultimately, combined with everything else, makes a confusing and sometimes unpleasant experience for new players. Thank you for reading this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 21:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2709-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/forum-of-lies-general-post/2709.rss">Forum of Lies-General Post</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
