<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Faction Suggestion] Revolutionists</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862</link>
    <description>The revolutionist want new order to the kingdom, secretly gaining trust, they must have one of their members become king and kill the rest of the blue dragons, neutrals, and Unseen/Cult

If there are no more killers the last person that isn&#39;t provoker will become serial killer


Classes
-------------
Revolutionary King - This cannot be a starting king, you get this when you get voted king as a revolutionist.  this king has one extra ability, &quot;Secret Execution&quot; you will send one of the revolutionist members to kill a target secretly, so the chat doesn&#39;t see &quot;The king has ordered the execution of [Name/Number]&quot; but there is a catch, they cannot normally execute at player at night, so they will never see the message.

Provoker - The provoker makes people angry at the kingdom, converting them into a revolutionist. this class also comes with the ability &quot;Stand Guard&quot; (x3) which kills everyone who visits them that night. (Unseen/Cult cannot become revolutionists)

Serial Killer - The Serial Killer picks a target to kill, and kills whoever they visit. they can only kill a maximum of 2 people per night, if they hit one of the revolutionists, they will not kill them. (They get converted to this from Killer classes)

Protester - The protester picks one person to occupy each night, anyone who visits the person being occupied will get prevented from visiting them, the protester also has the ability &quot;Burn&quot; which can only be used once, it kills the person they visit, while also occupying them. (They get converted to this from social classes)

Detective - The detective chooses a player and sees 3 possible classes they could be, one of them being the class that they are, they also have have the ability &quot;Thorough investigation&quot; that can only be used once, this finds the targeted players exact class. (They get converted to this from investigative classes)

Barricader - the barricader makes one of the members of the revolutionists immune for a night. (They get converted to this from Support classes)

Trapper - has the ability &quot;bear trap,&quot; anyone who visits the house the bear trap is on gets killed, the bear trap can only be triggered once, you may place a bear trap each night. (They get converted to this from Support classes) (50/50 chance you will get this or barricader)


Hope you like my idea, you can help add more classes if you like :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 04:01:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] Revolutionists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Margaret]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What about offensive classes? You have 1 Killer, 1 Social, 2 Supports, 1 Investigative convert but no offensive convert class. Additionally this may seem a tad bit strong especially since it sounds like four convert classes have the potential to kill. Additionally how many Revolutionists can there be at once? An infinite number? Also do any of the Revolutionists have Royal Blood? Otherwise Revolutionists might not recieve a Revolutionary King the whole game since lets be honest, only times when a non-royal goes up as King is near endgame or late midgame and most convertables are dead by that point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 04:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-49862-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862.rss">[Faction Suggestion] Revolutionists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Faction Suggestion] Revolutionists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The revolutionist want new order to the kingdom, secretly gaining trust, they must have one of their members become king and kill the rest of the blue dragons, neutrals, and Unseen/Cult</p>
<p>If there are no more killers the last person that isn’t provoker will become serial killer</p>
<h2>Classes</h2>
<p>Revolutionary King - This cannot be a starting king, you get this when you get voted king as a revolutionist.  this king has one extra ability, “Secret Execution” you will send one of the revolutionist members to kill a target secretly, so the chat doesn’t see “The king has ordered the execution of [Name/Number]” but there is a catch, they cannot normally execute at player at night, so they will never see the message.</p>
<p>Provoker - The provoker makes people angry at the kingdom, converting them into a revolutionist. this class also comes with the ability “Stand Guard” (x3) which kills everyone who visits them that night. (Unseen/Cult cannot become revolutionists)</p>
<p>Serial Killer - The Serial Killer picks a target to kill, and kills whoever they visit. they can only kill a maximum of 2 people per night, if they hit one of the revolutionists, they will not kill them. (They get converted to this from Killer classes)</p>
<p>Protester - The protester picks one person to occupy each night, anyone who visits the person being occupied will get prevented from visiting them, the protester also has the ability “Burn” which can only be used once, it kills the person they visit, while also occupying them. (They get converted to this from social classes)</p>
<p>Detective - The detective chooses a player and sees 3 possible classes they could be, one of them being the class that they are, they also have have the ability “Thorough investigation” that can only be used once, this finds the targeted players exact class. (They get converted to this from investigative classes)</p>
<p>Barricader - the barricader makes one of the members of the revolutionists immune for a night. (They get converted to this from Support classes)</p>
<p>Trapper - has the ability “bear trap,” anyone who visits the house the bear trap is on gets killed, the bear trap can only be triggered once, you may place a bear trap each night. (They get converted to this from Support classes) (50/50 chance you will get this or barricader)</p>
<p>Hope you like my idea, you can help add more classes if you like <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 02:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-49862-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/faction-suggestion-revolutionists/49862.rss">[Faction Suggestion] Revolutionists</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
