<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The First Psychic, Premona</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-first-psychic-premona/1865</link>
    <description>Lore Page: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Psychic

Lore Subject: Premona, Matriarch of Psychics

Lore: When it is often wondered where such a marvellous gift as telepathy stems from it is actually common knowledge for those in power. They know of the tale of Premona the first psychic and the trouble her life caused. Her extraordinary gifts extended far ahead of the psychics of today some believing that her powers did not infact stem from telepathy at all but a highly focused form of future vision. This of course allowed her to discern the motivations and strategies of those around her. Alas she was alone and began to fear her own gifts. Everybody she looked at she saw their death and weeped for what was to come. However one day she found salvation. For a being by chance took control of her to escape from capture and saw the infinite splendor that she did. He relinquished control and found compassion for what she saw all the time. 

Premona took surprise in that this beings life stretched far beyond her sight and fell in love with the being who in her eyes wasn&#39;t fated to a gruesome end. They would use their talents in tandem saving those in peril and defeating tyrannical figures regardless of their alignment sometimes to even cause the fall of empires. Their children however were left in the hands of strangers as their lives were filled with persecution of those they fought against, how such a union created life we do not know but these orphaned children are the descendants of today&#39;s psychics while not as powerful their mother&#39;s gifts mixed with a possessors guile create a lasting impression of Premona&#39;s hatred of persecution. She died at age 45 presumably killed so to the taxing nature of her powers.

Her Possesor comrade however remains unknown.

Description: I figured that to explain that a psychic can make someone vote they may need to be linked in some form to a possessor. So I decided to write the bloodline of psychics to include a small part of the possesors DNA. Still on the bench about how forbidden love between a woman and a possession demon is.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 13:49:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-first-psychic-premona/1865.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The First Psychic, Premona</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore Page: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Psychic" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Psychic</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: Premona, Matriarch of Psychics</p>
<p>Lore: When it is often wondered where such a marvellous gift as telepathy stems from it is actually common knowledge for those in power. They know of the tale of Premona the first psychic and the trouble her life caused. Her extraordinary gifts extended far ahead of the psychics of today some believing that her powers did not infact stem from telepathy at all but a highly focused form of future vision. This of course allowed her to discern the motivations and strategies of those around her. Alas she was alone and began to fear her own gifts. Everybody she looked at she saw their death and weeped for what was to come. However one day she found salvation. For a being by chance took control of her to escape from capture and saw the infinite splendor that she did. He relinquished control and found compassion for what she saw all the time.</p>
<p>Premona took surprise in that this beings life stretched far beyond her sight and fell in love with the being who in her eyes wasn’t fated to a gruesome end. They would use their talents in tandem saving those in peril and defeating tyrannical figures regardless of their alignment sometimes to even cause the fall of empires. Their children however were left in the hands of strangers as their lives were filled with persecution of those they fought against, how such a union created life we do not know but these orphaned children are the descendants of today’s psychics while not as powerful their mother’s gifts mixed with a possessors guile create a lasting impression of Premona’s hatred of persecution. She died at age 45 presumably killed so to the taxing nature of her powers.</p>
<p>Her Possesor comrade however remains unknown.</p>
<p>Description: I figured that to explain that a psychic can make someone vote they may need to be linked in some form to a possessor. So I decided to write the bloodline of psychics to include a small part of the possesors DNA. Still on the bench about how forbidden love between a woman and a possession demon is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-first-psychic-premona/1865/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-first-psychic-premona/1865/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 13:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-1865-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-first-psychic-premona/1865.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The First Psychic, Premona</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
