<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] - The Trickster</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-trickster/11035</link>
    <description>**The Trickster (Neutral Social) - UNIQUE**

**Passive:** Immune to occupation and death at night.
**Passive:** If you are found guilty of treason during the day, a random goon will die in your place. (one use only)

**Day Ability 1: Rigged Contract (infinite uses)**
Offer a player a contract. (The contract will read exactly like the Mercenary&#39;s contract). If they accept, they will be indebted to you and become _your_ mercenary (which I will refer to as &#39;goons&#39;). You can have a maximum of two goons.

Goons are similar to Mercenary but have some distinct differences; these are:

* Passives are removed, with a version of &#39;Failure&#39; (with the Trickster being the only factor) taking their place
* The class does not have access to stand guard
* The class has two uses of rebound (up from 1)
* The class is a killer class instead of support
* Win Condition: The Trickster wins

**Night Ability 1: Dummy (infinite uses)**
Send a dummy Mercenary to stand outside someone&#39;s room. It will _not_ prevent others visiting but will inform the target they were guarded.

**Night Ability 2: Private Matter (infinite uses)**
Whispers to and from you will be hidden from the public tomorrow.

**Goal:** Must kill all members of the main factions and any other neutral killers in order to win.

**Comments:**
Let&#39;s be real; we need more neutrals, and not ones that can just suit the Blue Dragon or Cult/Unseen on a whim. We need neutrals that play along the game in a unique way.

The Trickster would serve as a quasi-neutral killer. The Trickster&#39;s method of killing would be through his recruited goon&#39;s rebound ability. You won&#39;t be killing very often, but it would become incredibly relevant in the mid-late game and make people very wary of voting for claims or at random.

This also solves the problem of Mercenary being one of the safest Neutral classes to play given how easy it is to prove (via contract). The Trickster adds an interesting dynamic and makes people not just blindly accept any contract offered to them. Mercenaries also do not get a free pass anymore.

Main checks to this class would be Cult leader+Ritualist and Reaper.

Suggestions for improvements are more than welcome</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:25:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-trickster/11035.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] - The Trickster</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neclord]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>The Trickster (Neutral Social) - UNIQUE</strong></p>
<p><strong>Passive:</strong> Immune to occupation and death at night.<br>
<strong>Passive:</strong> If you are found guilty of treason during the day, a random goon will die in your place. (one use only)</p>
<p><strong>Day Ability 1: Rigged Contract (infinite uses)</strong><br>
Offer a player a contract. (The contract will read exactly like the Mercenary’s contract). If they accept, they will be indebted to you and become <em>your</em> mercenary (which I will refer to as ‘goons’). You can have a maximum of two goons.</p>
<p>Goons are similar to Mercenary but have some distinct differences; these are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Passives are removed, with a version of ‘Failure’ (with the Trickster being the only factor) taking their place</li>
<li>The class does not have access to stand guard</li>
<li>The class has two uses of rebound (up from 1)</li>
<li>The class is a killer class instead of support</li>
<li>Win Condition: The Trickster wins</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Night Ability 1: Dummy (infinite uses)</strong><br>
Send a dummy Mercenary to stand outside someone’s room. It will <em>not</em> prevent others visiting but will inform the target they were guarded.</p>
<p><strong>Night Ability 2: Private Matter (infinite uses)</strong><br>
Whispers to and from you will be hidden from the public tomorrow.</p>
<p><strong>Goal:</strong> Must kill all members of the main factions and any other neutral killers in order to win.</p>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong><br>
Let’s be real; we need more neutrals, and not ones that can just suit the Blue Dragon or Cult/Unseen on a whim. We need neutrals that play along the game in a unique way.</p>
<p>The Trickster would serve as a quasi-neutral killer. The Trickster’s method of killing would be through his recruited goon’s rebound ability. You won’t be killing very often, but it would become incredibly relevant in the mid-late game and make people very wary of voting for claims or at random.</p>
<p>This also solves the problem of Mercenary being one of the safest Neutral classes to play given how easy it is to prove (via contract). The Trickster adds an interesting dynamic and makes people not just blindly accept any contract offered to them. Mercenaries also do not get a free pass anymore.</p>
<p>Main checks to this class would be Cult leader+Ritualist and Reaper.</p>
<p>Suggestions for improvements are more than welcome</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-trickster/11035/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-trickster/11035/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11035-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-trickster/11035.rss">[Class Suggestion] - The Trickster</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
