<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928</link>
    <description>Cult Recommendations 
=
If you want to see the new class and new ability recomendations just scroll down. This is why I feel these changes would be good for the game/ the cult.

Cult Issues:
-
The Cult compared to the Unseen have very different strengths and weaknessess. You have to understand these before understanding what changes I am proposing. My changes will address all of these issues.

**Cult Strengths:**
- Can have 4 members

**Unseen Strengths**
- Mastermind is immune to death at night, is not suspicious the first 3 nights, can find out peoples class types, and turn into an Assassin if needed
- Assassin can not only kill at night, but he can poison during the day basically having the most killing power in the game with 2 killing methods.
- Classes converted from Blue Dragon have a wide variety of classes that they could have at their disposal 15 Unseen Classses vs 5 Cult Classes. This gives a more broad potential of things that the BD have to watch out for.


**Cult Weaknesses:**
- Classes ALL have limited use charges on all abilites, and have to be sacrificed to gain more charges of Eradicate so that the leader can kill
- Killing and converting are shared by the same class
- Overall have ZERO classes that can &quot;protect&quot; the cult, where as the Unseen have 3 strong classes that can keep their own members alive (Enforcer, Sellsword, and even Poacher)

**Unseen Weaknesses:** 
- If the Mastermind dies, they lose ability to convert

Cult vs Unseen Unique Abilities
-
I am not trying to be biased... and as you can see from the list I have made, the cult have many weaknesses and few strengths. What I did was write down all abilities that the Cult had... and all abilities that the Unseen had. Then I crossed off abilities from both lists that the other factions shared/ similar. So this list is the &quot;Unique Abilities&quot; that Cult/ Unseen classes have.

Unique Cult Abilities
- 
- Talking to the dead members at night
- Whispering during the day
- King Ability disable
- Group occupy immune 

Unique Unseen Abilities
-
- Royalty (Alcoholic/ Aristocrat/ Duchess)
- Poisoning
- Muting players for 10 seconds
- Stoping a player from voting that day
- Appearing &quot;not suspicious&quot; at night (2 charges)
- Protecting/ Guarding members at night (Enforcer/ Sellsword)
- Defile - changing a players class on death
- Erasing chat history
- Listen to Prince conversation
- Read other players journals
- Make player unable to speak or hear the following day

That is CRAZY that the Unseen have that many more unique abilities. 
These changes I am proposing even out the 2 lists to be balanced. Each Faction will have 4 unique things that they can do but the other cannot. Instead of the Cult being FAR less diverse and overall weaker. 

Cult Current Class Changes
=
Seeker
-
- 2nd Day Ability: (2 charges) target player will appear as not suspicious the following night

The Seeker always starts off with the Cult Leader, so this would be a way of giving the Cult Leader the ability to be &quot;NS&quot; the first 2 nights. This could not only be used later in the game also, but on other members of the Cult. Usually I wold say the Cult Leader is more likely to die and be replaced than the members living long enough to need to sacrifice. 

Apostle
-
- 2nd Night Ability: Prevent target player from speaking the following day

The Unseen have this ability but even more powerful by not letting them hear either (Hangover). They also have a distract for 10 seconds (yes, much shorter). This falls in line with a social class, and if they dont want to do a random mind warp (if they havent found an investigative class yet, they can mute someone (potentially making them look reaped)

Invoker / Ritualist
- 
- I feel like they could use a day ability, but nothing seemed necessary, and after all these changes everything already was more balanced

New Class for Cult
=
The Cult have every &quot;type&quot; of class except for Killer. If you are a Killer Blue Dragon (Knight/ Hunter) you get converted into an Invoker... which is an &quot;offensive&quot; type class. This just feels bad to me simply because it violates the theme of the Cult. Whatever your BD class is... you get converted into the Cults version of that type... except for killers. There are 4 classes that currently turn into Invokers... thats a lot of Invokers. Now I understand that this is because the Cult Leader can kill, and if there were TWO classes for the Cult that could kill, that would be Over Powered! So here is my solution to this

If you are a Knight or Hunter... you will now instead be converted to this

Acolyte (or make a new name)
-
**Cult Killer Class**
- Day Ability: Hemorrhage (1 charge) Put a cure on target player and the following day they will be alerted that they are now bleeding to death. (same message you get when you are bit by a Hunter wolf)
- Night Ability 1: Do Thy Bidding (2 charges) Activate this ability to kill the player that the Cult Leader is Eradicating. This will not consume eradicate charges.
- Night Ability 2: Blood Pact (2 charges) Watch over your Cult members tonight and sacrifice yourself for them if anyone is attacked.

Explanation:
-
- There is not a bleed in the game except for the Hunters 2 night abilities. I have always had an issue with that since its one of the few &quot;100% unique&quot; things in the game. Hunter is one of the WORST claims in the game right now, since if nobody bleeds... then there is no Hunter. This opens up the potential for a Cult to actually claim hunter
- The bleed also gives the Cult something similar to an Unseen poison but its far less powerful since you cant recharge it, and you wont always have this class always.
- Gives the Cult Leader 2 things, the ability to not use up Eradicate charges, and not have to leave his chambers and visit the kill target.
- The Acolyte could use up his killing charges then stand guard over the Cult and let himself die instead of the other members.

Conclusion
=
After reading all of this, look back on the strengths/ weaknessess of each faction. Look at the unique abilities of each faction. These changes not only address ALL the issues I layed out, but closes the gap on the unique abilities of the two factions

Please let me know what you guys think. 

-Alkander
=</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 14:45:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just put this on the affected cult classes on the wiki, thanks for the (indirect) reminder. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 14:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-17</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is the truth though.</p>
<p>I have been converted noble (during the twin era) and stepped up to be king as royal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 20:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-16</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can you tell me where (if anywhere) it says that converted cult classes with noble blood keep it? I can’t find it anywhere</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 18:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-15</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yessir</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Stop it now before I start being a Moderator</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 13:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="11" data-topic="2928">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>passive aggressive = aggressive.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>facepalms</em><br>
Aggressive.</p>
<p>adjective</p>
<p>characterized by or tending toward unprovoked offensives, attacks, invasions, or the like; militantly forward or menacing:<br>
aggressive acts against a neighboring country.<br>
Passive Aggressive</p>
<p>denoting or pertaining to a personality type or behavior marked by the expression of negative emotions in passive, indirect ways, as through manipulation or noncooperation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 13:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>passive aggressive = aggressive.</p>
<p>I am done talking to you, you seem to want to escalate this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="8" data-topic="2928">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t be so aggressive</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>… I’m not being aggressive. I’m not being passive aggressive. I’m stating you didn’t prove your damn point. Act like this then I will be aggressive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Methnor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="6" data-topic="2928">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Night ability: Shred (2 uses)</p>
<p>Attack a cult member and a non cult member. Both will start bleeding and die the next night (bypassing death immunity) if they are not healed by a physician or alchemist.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m actually a huge fan of this because the CL just sacrifices the bleeding person the next day. Makes the whole Cult cooperate.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>Don’t be so aggressive</li>
<li>It kilsl to fast. Cult should never be more kill capable then unseen.</li>
</ol>
<p>multiple acolytes will lead to lots of death specially if CL still eradicates.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RopeStringFace" data-post="6" data-topic="2928">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/ropestringface/40/1106_2.png" class="avatar"> RopeStringFace:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but I don’t think the acolyte you suggested was very good (especially unbalanced with the suggestion i just made</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Prove your point Rope. Plex and Jammy do it all the time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I see his problems, and they look great on paper (or computer or whatever)</p>
<p>However, the cult is able to convert much faster. This gives the ability to convert their paladins easier; and if they do’t, people are more likely to believe the claim that they are.</p>
<p>I agree with two changes you suggested: Eradicate fix and killer conversion</p>
<h2>Eradicate</h2>
<p>I was thinking of a way to fix the balance issue you suggested where the converter and killer are the same class. My suggestion is this: when you select someone to sacrifice, you also select someone for mithras to attack that night, <strong>and</strong> you gain <strong>one</strong> use of eradicate. This way, cult leader could kill without having to slow down the conversions.</p>
<h2>Acolyte</h2>
<p>I think that killers should not be converted to invoker, but I don’t think the acolyte you suggested was very good (especially unbalanced with the suggestion i just made):</p>
<p><strong>Day ability: Blood of Corax</strong> (special uses)<br>
you will expand a use of the cult leader’s eradicate to poison a player. They will die in two nights if they are not healed by a physician. This bypasses death immunity.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability: Shred</strong> (2 uses)<br>
Attack a cult member and a non cult member. Both will start bleeding and die the next night (bypassing death immunity) if they are not healed by a physician or alchemist.</p>
<p><strong>Night ability: Annihilate</strong> (2 uses)<br>
Whoever the cult leader Eradicates tonight will have their journal erased.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 12:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is true. You keep royal blood.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unknown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly…<br>
You didnt see the elephant in the room… congratulations.<br>
The elephant is that the Mastermind, the cornerstone of the Unseen, has to fakeclaim from Day 1 and isn’t replaceable. As soon as the Mastermind dies there is no more than 2 unseen and no conversions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 08:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>also add to Cult Strengths:<br>
Infinitely replaceable converting class<br>
More Class Combination permutations due to the converter and killer being the same class</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 08:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jazz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>royal blood isn’t unique to unseen</p>
<p>if you’re a royal and converted to cult you keep royal blood I’m fairly certain</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 08:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alkander]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h1>Cult Recommendations</h1>
<p>If you want to see the new class and new ability recomendations just scroll down. This is why I feel these changes would be good for the game/ the cult.</p>
<h2>Cult Issues:</h2>
<p>The Cult compared to the Unseen have very different strengths and weaknessess. You have to understand these before understanding what changes I am proposing. My changes will address all of these issues.</p>
<p><strong>Cult Strengths:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Can have 4 members</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Unseen Strengths</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Mastermind is immune to death at night, is not suspicious the first 3 nights, can find out peoples class types, and turn into an Assassin if needed</li>
<li>Assassin can not only kill at night, but he can poison during the day basically having the most killing power in the game with 2 killing methods.</li>
<li>Classes converted from Blue Dragon have a wide variety of classes that they could have at their disposal 15 Unseen Classses vs 5 Cult Classes. This gives a more broad potential of things that the BD have to watch out for.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cult Weaknesses:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Classes ALL have limited use charges on all abilites, and have to be sacrificed to gain more charges of Eradicate so that the leader can kill</li>
<li>Killing and converting are shared by the same class</li>
<li>Overall have ZERO classes that can “protect” the cult, where as the Unseen have 3 strong classes that can keep their own members alive (Enforcer, Sellsword, and even Poacher)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Unseen Weaknesses:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>If the Mastermind dies, they lose ability to convert</li>
</ul>
<h2>Cult vs Unseen Unique Abilities</h2>
<p>I am not trying to be biased… and as you can see from the list I have made, the cult have many weaknesses and few strengths. What I did was write down all abilities that the Cult had… and all abilities that the Unseen had. Then I crossed off abilities from both lists that the other factions shared/ similar. So this list is the “Unique Abilities” that Cult/ Unseen classes have.</p>
<h2>Unique Cult Abilities</h2>
<ul>
<li>Talking to the dead members at night</li>
<li>Whispering during the day</li>
<li>King Ability disable</li>
<li>Group occupy immune</li>
</ul>
<h2>Unique Unseen Abilities</h2>
<ul>
<li>Royalty (Alcoholic/ Aristocrat/ Duchess)</li>
<li>Poisoning</li>
<li>Muting players for 10 seconds</li>
<li>Stoping a player from voting that day</li>
<li>Appearing “not suspicious” at night (2 charges)</li>
<li>Protecting/ Guarding members at night (Enforcer/ Sellsword)</li>
<li>Defile - changing a players class on death</li>
<li>Erasing chat history</li>
<li>Listen to Prince conversation</li>
<li>Read other players journals</li>
<li>Make player unable to speak or hear the following day</li>
</ul>
<p>That is CRAZY that the Unseen have that many more unique abilities.<br>
These changes I am proposing even out the 2 lists to be balanced. Each Faction will have 4 unique things that they can do but the other cannot. Instead of the Cult being FAR less diverse and overall weaker.</p>
<h1>Cult Current Class Changes</h1>
<h2>Seeker</h2>
<ul>
<li>2nd Day Ability: (2 charges) target player will appear as not suspicious the following night</li>
</ul>
<p>The Seeker always starts off with the Cult Leader, so this would be a way of giving the Cult Leader the ability to be “NS” the first 2 nights. This could not only be used later in the game also, but on other members of the Cult. Usually I wold say the Cult Leader is more likely to die and be replaced than the members living long enough to need to sacrifice.</p>
<h2>Apostle</h2>
<ul>
<li>2nd Night Ability: Prevent target player from speaking the following day</li>
</ul>
<p>The Unseen have this ability but even more powerful by not letting them hear either (Hangover). They also have a distract for 10 seconds (yes, much shorter). This falls in line with a social class, and if they dont want to do a random mind warp (if they havent found an investigative class yet, they can mute someone (potentially making them look reaped)</p>
<h2>Invoker / Ritualist</h2>
<ul>
<li>I feel like they could use a day ability, but nothing seemed necessary, and after all these changes everything already was more balanced</li>
</ul>
<h1>New Class for Cult</h1>
<p>The Cult have every “type” of class except for Killer. If you are a Killer Blue Dragon (Knight/ Hunter) you get converted into an Invoker… which is an “offensive” type class. This just feels bad to me simply because it violates the theme of the Cult. Whatever your BD class is… you get converted into the Cults version of that type… except for killers. There are 4 classes that currently turn into Invokers… thats a lot of Invokers. Now I understand that this is because the Cult Leader can kill, and if there were TWO classes for the Cult that could kill, that would be Over Powered! So here is my solution to this</p>
<p>If you are a Knight or Hunter… you will now instead be converted to this</p>
<h2>Acolyte (or make a new name)</h2>
<p><strong>Cult Killer Class</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Day Ability: Hemorrhage (1 charge) Put a cure on target player and the following day they will be alerted that they are now bleeding to death. (same message you get when you are bit by a Hunter wolf)</li>
<li>Night Ability 1: Do Thy Bidding (2 charges) Activate this ability to kill the player that the Cult Leader is Eradicating. This will not consume eradicate charges.</li>
<li>Night Ability 2: Blood Pact (2 charges) Watch over your Cult members tonight and sacrifice yourself for them if anyone is attacked.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Explanation:</h2>
<ul>
<li>There is not a bleed in the game except for the Hunters 2 night abilities. I have always had an issue with that since its one of the few “100% unique” things in the game. Hunter is one of the WORST claims in the game right now, since if nobody bleeds… then there is no Hunter. This opens up the potential for a Cult to actually claim hunter</li>
<li>The bleed also gives the Cult something similar to an Unseen poison but its far less powerful since you cant recharge it, and you wont always have this class always.</li>
<li>Gives the Cult Leader 2 things, the ability to not use up Eradicate charges, and not have to leave his chambers and visit the kill target.</li>
<li>The Acolyte could use up his killing charges then stand guard over the Cult and let himself die instead of the other members.</li>
</ul>
<h1>Conclusion</h1>
<p>After reading all of this, look back on the strengths/ weaknessess of each faction. Look at the unique abilities of each faction. These changes not only address ALL the issues I layed out, but closes the gap on the unique abilities of the two factions</p>
<p>Please let me know what you guys think.</p>
<h1>-Alkander</h1>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2928-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/cult-recommendations-new-class-new-acolyte/2928.rss">Cult Recommendations + New Class (New Acolyte)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
