<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Archduke (NK)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526</link>
    <description>&gt; # [color = &quot;indigo&quot;] The Archduke [/color]:shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Killer [/color]** 
**Megalomaniac (Passive)** - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King. Becomes the Tyrannous King instead of the Psycho King.
**Paranoia (Passive)** - Allows the Archduke to listen on whispers and grants immunity against poison, bleeding, and death at night.
**Tyrant&#39;s Pressure (Day)** - Force a player to accuse another player and prevent them from voting further. - 3 uses 
**Tyrant&#39;s Informant (Day)** - You will know the class type of the target player at the beginning of the night. - 3 uses 
**Political Murder (Night)** - Kills a player without counting as a visit, but has a one-day cooldown period and cannot target the King. - Infinite uses 
**Coup d&#39;Etat (Night)** - Kills the King while bypassing night immunity. Can only be used in the fifth night or later. - 1 use 
*Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.*

Crowns into:

&gt; # [color = &quot;indigo&quot;] The Tyrannous King [/color] :shield:
&gt; **[color = &quot;gray&quot;] Neutral Special [/color]** 
**Reign of Terror (Passive)** - The Tyrannous King’s cruel guards are guaranteed kills against players who did not vote for him during the ballot phase of an election bypassing preventions, night immunity, and healing.
**Tyrant&#39;s Paranoia (Passive)** - Grants immunity from occupation, redirection, bleeding, poison, death at night, and allows the Tyrannous King to read whispers. For the first time the Tyrant King is accused of treason and the majority vote for an execution, the Tyrant King will overrule the vote, pardon himself, and kill his first accuser. The self-pardoning does not work on the same day that the Tyrant King steps up and if this triggers then his cruel guards will only be able to kill one player at night.
**Tyrant&#39;s Finger (Day)** - The King&#39;s next vote for treason will count twice. - Infinite uses 
**Tyrant&#39;s Decision (Day)** - After the final vote, the King can veto the votes and decide if the fate of the person defending themselves. If the King decides to execute, the player on the stand is executed. If the King decides to pardon the player on the stand, they can&#39;t be accused of treason again that day. - 1 use 
**Cruel Guards (Night)** - Allows the Tyrannous King to send guards to two players at once, killing them both. - Infinite uses 


Theme: A neutral killer that has a weak KPN potential but can meld in with the court as a Princess or Noble claim, and then becomes an extremely dangerous NK if he becomes King.
Survivability: Non-visiting attacks allow him to survive bears and Knights, meanwhile he is by default immune to poison and bleeding.
Late-game: Becoming King late-game is essentially GG for the Archduke.

Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:11:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Archduke (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this one also <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  I just hope as soon as Maid Spy is reverted (I’m still waiting) his whisper reading passives are nerfed as well</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70526-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Archduke (NK)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Archduke (NK)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="indigo"> The Archduke </font><img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Megalomaniac (Passive)</strong> - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King. Becomes the Tyrannous King instead of the Psycho King.<br>
<strong>Paranoia (Passive)</strong> - Allows the Archduke to listen on whispers and grants immunity against poison, bleeding, and death at night.<br>
<strong>Tyrant’s Pressure (Day)</strong> - Force a player to accuse another player and prevent them from voting further. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Tyrant’s Informant (Day)</strong> - You will know the class type of the target player at the beginning of the night. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Political Murder (Night)</strong> - Kills a player without counting as a visit, but has a one-day cooldown period and cannot target the King. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Coup d’Etat (Night)</strong> - Kills the King while bypassing night immunity. Can only be used in the fifth night or later. - 1 use<br>
<em>Your objective is to defeat the Blue Dragon, Unseen, Cult and any neutrals that dare stand in your way.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Crowns into:</p>
<blockquote>
<h1>
<font color="indigo"> The Tyrannous King </font> <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/shield.png?v=9" title=":shield:" class="emoji" alt=":shield:">
</h1>
<p><strong><font color="gray"> Neutral Special </font></strong><br>
<strong>Reign of Terror (Passive)</strong> - The Tyrannous King’s cruel guards are guaranteed kills against players who did not vote for him during the ballot phase of an election bypassing preventions, night immunity, and healing.<br>
<strong>Tyrant’s Paranoia (Passive)</strong> - Grants immunity from occupation, redirection, bleeding, poison, death at night, and allows the Tyrannous King to read whispers. For the first time the Tyrant King is accused of treason and the majority vote for an execution, the Tyrant King will overrule the vote, pardon himself, and kill his first accuser. The self-pardoning does not work on the same day that the Tyrant King steps up and if this triggers then his cruel guards will only be able to kill one player at night.<br>
<strong>Tyrant’s Finger (Day)</strong> - The King’s next vote for treason will count twice. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Tyrant’s Decision (Day)</strong> - After the final vote, the King can veto the votes and decide if the fate of the person defending themselves. If the King decides to execute, the player on the stand is executed. If the King decides to pardon the player on the stand, they can’t be accused of treason again that day. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Cruel Guards (Night)</strong> - Allows the Tyrannous King to send guards to two players at once, killing them both. - Infinite uses</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Theme: A neutral killer that has a weak KPN potential but can meld in with the court as a Princess or Noble claim, and then becomes an extremely dangerous NK if he becomes King.<br>
Survivability: Non-visiting attacks allow him to survive bears and Knights, meanwhile he is by default immune to poison and bleeding.<br>
Late-game: Becoming King late-game is essentially GG for the Archduke.</p>
<p>Posting my NKs by Firekitten’s requests.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 01:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-70526-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-the-archduke-nk/70526.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Archduke (NK)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
