<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485</link>
    <description>Since i just spent the day watching reality TV and playing Forum mafia i wanted to put this out there cuz i think it would be fun to combine the two


it&#39;s the apprentice(the show that donald trump hosted&lt;sup&gt;(its not politics it has nothing to do with him as a politician its just how people might know the show plz no ban feds)&lt;/sup&gt;) and i thought y&#39;all might enjoy it





[details=&quot;the genral format is as such for those who&#39;ve never watched it&quot;]
*The Apprentice*  is a reality game show featuring season-long competitions. Each season begins with a new group of contestants vying to earn a place in one of the organizations run by the host. The contestants (who are referred to as &quot;candidates&quot;) have come from business backgrounds in various enterprises, the backgrounds including real estate, accounting, restaurant management, management consulting, sales and marketing.

During the show, the contestants live in a communal dwelling, a &quot;penthouse suite&quot;, in New York City (save for Season 6 which took place in Los Angeles). The candidates are divided into two teams, treated as &quot;corporations&quot; within the show. These corporations select a name they are subsequently referred to through the rest of the show. Each week, the teams are assigned a task and required to select one of their members to lead the team as &quot;project manager&quot;, who is to take responsibility for organizing the team and making executive decisions. Tasks are generally business oriented and tend to highlight one of several business skills. Tasks most commonly revolve around sales (selling the most items or earning the most money) and marketing (producing a specific marketing material or campaign that is judged by a company&#39;s executives). During the tasks, the teams are usually visited by one of the host&#39;s &quot;advisors&quot; for that week. Tasks typically lasted for one or two days. After the completion of the task, the teams meet with the host and his two advisers in &quot;the [boardroom](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boardroom)&quot;.

Boardroom meetings generally proceed in three stages. In the preliminary stage, all of the remaining candidates on both teams gather in the boardroom to be briefed on the task by the host and his advisors. Team members are asked about how the task went and whether there were any strong or weak players. Teams are sometimes asked to comment on materials or products produced by the opposing team. At the end of this stage, the host or his advisors reveal the results of the task and announce which team was the winner. The winning team wins a reward (usually a unique, luxurious experience) and are excused from the boardroom while the losing team returns to the boardroom for an elimination. In later seasons, winning teams have been permitted to view the next stage of the boardroom on the TV in their suite.

The entire losing team remains in the boardroom and are confronted with their loss. They are interrogated as to the reasons for their loss and which players contributed to it or failed at the task. Then, for the final stage of the boardroom meeting, the project manager is asked to select a certain number of teammates (typically two, but on occasion one or three) to bring back into the final-stage boardroom meeting. The remaining teammates return to the suite while the project manager and the selected teammates step out of the boardroom momentarily so the host can consult with his advisors.

Upon returning to the boardroom for the final stage, the host and his advisors continue interrogating the remaining players about their loss. The project manager is sometimes further interrogated about his or her choice of teammates to bring back into the boardroom. Ultimately, at least one project manager and/or remaining teammate is &quot;fired&quot; at the host&#39;s discretion, and leaves the show. The host has broad discretion to fire candidates outside of this usual process, including firing multiple candidates at a time. The eliminated contestants are shown leaving the boardroom with their luggage and entering a taxi cab, during which they are given time to recount on their elimination that is shown over the episode&#39;s credits.

When only three or four candidates (depending on the season) are left, they are interviewed rather than being assigned a task. Executives from various companies interview the finalists and report their assessments to the host. Based on the interviews, a &quot;boardroom meeting&quot; and firing take place, leaving two candidates.

The final two candidates are then each assigned a different final task. Each is given a support team of previously fired candidates. Final tasks generally require the finalists to organize (to various degrees) an event such as a party or a fundraiser which has multiple planning elements. In a final boardroom meeting following the final task, the host &quot;hires&quot; one of the two candidates to become his &quot;apprentice&quot;, winning the show&#39;s prize of a one-year $250,000 starting contract to manage a business project offered by the host.
[/details]



now i&#39;d be changing a few things and adding some twists but here&#39;s how it goes basically



- 2 evenly split teams

- each phase a project manager would be picked by the team

- they would be responsible for leading the team in whatever the &quot;task&quot; is(i have things planned)


- teams would compete in said task

- losing team project manager picks 2 other teammates who he/she/they thinks were mostly responsible for the loss, and  the remaining members of the team would vote between the three of them (i think this is better because it&#39;s less host-discretion and more power to the players)

- most voted player is fired

- at the final 4 it will be a randomly-selected 2v2 match up where the winning team moves on to the final 2

- at the final 2 each player will present their resumé and my advisers and I would decide on who to hire(who wins)



players would be allowed to make any PMs they want to with anyone, on either team(although cross-team relations will be primarily competitive) as long as i am added


***AND IF ANYONE IS CAUGHT &quot;SLACKING OFF&quot; ON THE JOB MORE THEN ONCE, THEY WILL PROMPTLY BE FIRED***

if enough interest is shown i&#39;ll flesh this out more

but it could have success IMO

(also if anyone does want to pre-in you can go ahead)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 16:54:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Forum Matches</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PoisonedSquid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For some reason this reminds me of Hell’s Kitchen</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 16:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80485-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485.rss">Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>even though eh interest has been expressed imma keep working on this cuz i got a lot of ideas</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 16:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80485-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485.rss">Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sulit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 03:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80485-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485.rss">Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shurian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="/uploads/default/original/3X/9/e/9eed2e69106f92e180d801f4774e14e14e002877.gif" alt="tenor (5)" data-base62-sha1="mFVB8bfCBJvuMMuAr8TCiLOgVdJ" width="346" height="428"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80485-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485.rss">Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marshal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since i just spent the day watching reality TV and playing Forum mafia i wanted to put this out there cuz i think it would be fun to combine the two</p>
<p>it’s the apprentice(the show that donald trump hosted<sup>(its not politics it has nothing to do with him as a politician its just how people might know the show plz no ban feds)</sup>) and i thought y’all might enjoy it</p>
<details>
<summary>
the genral format is as such for those who've never watched it</summary>
<p><em>The Apprentice</em>  is a reality game show featuring season-long competitions. Each season begins with a new group of contestants vying to earn a place in one of the organizations run by the host. The contestants (who are referred to as “candidates”) have come from business backgrounds in various enterprises, the backgrounds including real estate, accounting, restaurant management, management consulting, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>During the show, the contestants live in a communal dwelling, a “penthouse suite”, in New York City (save for Season 6 which took place in Los Angeles). The candidates are divided into two teams, treated as “corporations” within the show. These corporations select a name they are subsequently referred to through the rest of the show. Each week, the teams are assigned a task and required to select one of their members to lead the team as “project manager”, who is to take responsibility for organizing the team and making executive decisions. Tasks are generally business oriented and tend to highlight one of several business skills. Tasks most commonly revolve around sales (selling the most items or earning the most money) and marketing (producing a specific marketing material or campaign that is judged by a company’s executives). During the tasks, the teams are usually visited by one of the host’s “advisors” for that week. Tasks typically lasted for one or two days. After the completion of the task, the teams meet with the host and his two advisers in “the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boardroom" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">boardroom</a>”.</p>
<p>Boardroom meetings generally proceed in three stages. In the preliminary stage, all of the remaining candidates on both teams gather in the boardroom to be briefed on the task by the host and his advisors. Team members are asked about how the task went and whether there were any strong or weak players. Teams are sometimes asked to comment on materials or products produced by the opposing team. At the end of this stage, the host or his advisors reveal the results of the task and announce which team was the winner. The winning team wins a reward (usually a unique, luxurious experience) and are excused from the boardroom while the losing team returns to the boardroom for an elimination. In later seasons, winning teams have been permitted to view the next stage of the boardroom on the TV in their suite.</p>
<p>The entire losing team remains in the boardroom and are confronted with their loss. They are interrogated as to the reasons for their loss and which players contributed to it or failed at the task. Then, for the final stage of the boardroom meeting, the project manager is asked to select a certain number of teammates (typically two, but on occasion one or three) to bring back into the final-stage boardroom meeting. The remaining teammates return to the suite while the project manager and the selected teammates step out of the boardroom momentarily so the host can consult with his advisors.</p>
<p>Upon returning to the boardroom for the final stage, the host and his advisors continue interrogating the remaining players about their loss. The project manager is sometimes further interrogated about his or her choice of teammates to bring back into the boardroom. Ultimately, at least one project manager and/or remaining teammate is “fired” at the host’s discretion, and leaves the show. The host has broad discretion to fire candidates outside of this usual process, including firing multiple candidates at a time. The eliminated contestants are shown leaving the boardroom with their luggage and entering a taxi cab, during which they are given time to recount on their elimination that is shown over the episode’s credits.</p>
<p>When only three or four candidates (depending on the season) are left, they are interviewed rather than being assigned a task. Executives from various companies interview the finalists and report their assessments to the host. Based on the interviews, a “boardroom meeting” and firing take place, leaving two candidates.</p>
<p>The final two candidates are then each assigned a different final task. Each is given a support team of previously fired candidates. Final tasks generally require the finalists to organize (to various degrees) an event such as a party or a fundraiser which has multiple planning elements. In a final boardroom meeting following the final task, the host “hires” one of the two candidates to become his “apprentice”, winning the show’s prize of a one-year $250,000 starting contract to manage a business project offered by the host.</p>
</details>
<p>now i’d be changing a few things and adding some twists but here’s how it goes basically</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>2 evenly split teams</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>each phase a project manager would be picked by the team</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>they would be responsible for leading the team in whatever the “task” is(i have things planned)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>teams would compete in said task</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>losing team project manager picks 2 other teammates who he/she/they thinks were mostly responsible for the loss, and  the remaining members of the team would vote between the three of them (i think this is better because it’s less host-discretion and more power to the players)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>most voted player is fired</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>at the final 4 it will be a randomly-selected 2v2 match up where the winning team moves on to the final 2</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>at the final 2 each player will present their resumé and my advisers and I would decide on who to hire(who wins)</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>players would be allowed to make any PMs they want to with anyone, on either team(although cross-team relations will be primarily competitive) as long as i am added</p>
<p><em><strong>AND IF ANYONE IS CAUGHT “SLACKING OFF” ON THE JOB MORE THEN ONCE, THEY WILL PROMPTLY BE FIRED</strong></em></p>
<p>if enough interest is shown i’ll flesh this out more</p>
<p>but it could have success IMO</p>
<p>(also if anyone does want to pre-in you can go ahead)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-80485-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/interest-check-the-apprentice-misc/80485.rss">Interest check - the Apprentice Misc</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
