<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Friend chat in Lobby + ignore function</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782</link>
    <description>When someone invites me to a game or is just in the lobby with me or even in a game, I&#39;d sometimes like to be able to talk to them... Like for example saying that I currently can&#39;t accept their game invitation, ask them for how much longer they are in their current game... or simply just to talk. 
Though I would be glad if one could chat in the Lobby at least since the ingame option would make it easier for those chatting to cheat. (But if they REALLY wanted to their are other options from the get go so...)

the second thing would be some kind of ignore function. at least one when you are dead. It&#39;s already bad enough that you have to endure some of the crap they say while being alive...
I get that you can&#39;t ignore them while playing this game but being dead and having to see the spam on accusations or the &quot;pretending to be fool&quot; stuff is just annoying and would make me wanna leave right away. BUT if I wanna report them, I have to stay until the end of the game...

Either way it destroys the fun while playing</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 20:51:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Friend chat in Lobby + ignore function</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>/support</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 20:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-46782-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782.rss">Friend chat in Lobby + ignore function</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Friend chat in Lobby + ignore function</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arinya]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When someone invites me to a game or is just in the lobby with me or even in a game, I’d sometimes like to be able to talk to them… Like for example saying that I currently can’t accept their game invitation, ask them for how much longer they are in their current game… or simply just to talk.<br>
Though I would be glad if one could chat in the Lobby at least since the ingame option would make it easier for those chatting to cheat. (But if they REALLY wanted to their are other options from the get go so…)</p>
<p>the second thing would be some kind of ignore function. at least one when you are dead. It’s already bad enough that you have to endure some of the crap they say while being alive…<br>
I get that you can’t ignore them while playing this game but being dead and having to see the spam on accusations or the “pretending to be fool” stuff is just annoying and would make me wanna leave right away. BUT if I wanna report them, I have to stay until the end of the game…</p>
<p>Either way it destroys the fun while playing</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 17:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-46782-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/friend-chat-in-lobby-ignore-function/46782.rss">Friend chat in Lobby + ignore function</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
