<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757</link>
    <description>Prepare your potions! It&#39;s time to get yourself a win with **Alchemist!**

**_Introduction:_**
Hello! So you&#39;re playing Throne Of Lies one day, and you get the Neutral class Alchemist. &quot;What is this?&quot; you ask yourself in desperation as the Prince cuts off your head while yelling #NeutsOut!  No worries, the community has got your back! This guide will cover **The Basics** and the **The Strategies** for Alchemist.

**The Basics:**

 You start with 3 types of potions: **_Stoneskin Potion_**, **_Crimson Potion_**, and **_Emerald Potion._**

**Day Ability:**

* **Stoneskin:** 4 uses, - _Drink a potion that will make you immune tonight._ Stoneskin is one of the most important potions that the Alchemist has in his inventory. When used correctly it can be a nuisance for those pesky Neutral Killers and Unseen/Cult. Stoneskin is best used when you feel like you&#39;re going to be attacked (Talked and gave an abundance of info in chat for example.)

**Night Ability:**

* **Crimson:** Unlimited uses, - _Heal a player&#39;s wounds and cure any poison._ Crimson is important for when you need to prove yourself to the Blue Dragon or heal an ally. Just like the **Physician&#39;s Heal** it can be used to cure a Blue Dragon&#39;s poison/bleed to narrow down your class to Physician/Alchemist.

* **Emerald:** 2 uses, - _Poison a player with a lethal dosage, instantly killing them._ Emerald is also important for proving yourself, or killing someone who you feel is a threat to your win condition. However, Emerald should mostly be used as a **LAST RESORT.** The Blue Dragon will have a death sentence for you if you kill one of their members with it. So use Emerald wisely.

**Passive:**

* **Coagulate:** _Immune to **NightShade** and **bleeding**_ - This passive is important for when you&#39;re suspected as a Blue Dragon member to the **Assassin/Cult Leader**, or an evil to the **Hunter**. This passive keeps you from dying early on to a pesky poisoning or wolf/rupture.

**The Strategies:**

Nice! You know what the Alchemist has in his hands, now its time to put those potions to use in a game! This sub-part of the guide will explain the most common strategies as Alchemist, and the highest chance to win as the class!

* **Blue Dragon Route:** The most common route for Alchemist, you declare your allegiance to the Blue Dragon and you will help them win against the Cult/Unseen! When you start out as Alchemist Day 1, it is advised to use a **Stoneskin** potion. However, this is **YOUR DECISION.** Night one is usually the most random night in the game, Unseen/Cult will pick someone random to convert/kill and so will the NK, so its advised to do this. **MAKE A PHYSICIANS JOURNAL**. It&#39;s o&#39; so important to do this step. If you are jailed and NK is still alive, there is a  high chance you will die from the prince execution assuming you claim Alchemist to them. Blue Dragon is usually unaware that Alchemist can be important later on, and they will kill any Neutral possible to kill the NK. Once the NK is dead you have **TWO CHOICES.** You can:

1. Announce to the court that you are indeed **Alchemist.** The Court will most likely acknowledge this, and the Unseen/Cult will stay off of you unless you are blatantly helping the Blue Dragon. **DON&#39;T BE BLATANT**, you will be targeted if you verbally tell everyone that you will help the Blue Dragon, and your game will be over at this point. **USE YOUR STONESKINS WISELY.** If somehow you do end up being blatant, make sure you have those stoneskin potions ready, and keep helping the Blue Dragon till all the evils are executed.

2. Whisper the king that you&#39; are indeed **Alchemist.** This is one of the more riskier plays that you may make. **NOTE: THIS CHOICE MAY BLEED INTO THE UNSEEN/CULT/NEUTRAL ROUTE** it is entirely your decision if you want to side with the king or not. At this point of the game, NK is dead, and the king seems like a **Good King** from the evils he has outed and the checks he has made. If the king seems Evil/Neutral **DON&#39;T WHISPER THEM**. As soon as you whisper the king, they are expecting you to join their side. Make sure 100% that the king is Good through outing, or voting a new king who is confirmed Good. The advantages of having a king at your side is abundant. The King and the Alchemist can make a heal combo, which they can&#39;t die from. This is important for this strategy. **BETRAYING THE KING IS YOUR DECISION DO IT WISELY.** Only do this if you know for a fact that the king&#39;s faction is going to lose.

* **Unseen/Cult/Neutral Route:** You have made your decision. You smile eerily, and you want every Blue Dragon member dead. This is an uncommon route, but is heavily rewarded if successful. Use a **Stoneskin** potion Night 1, again this is your decision, but it is advised. **STILL CREATE A PHYSICIANS JOURNAL.** This will again come in handy if you&#39;re jailed by the **Prince**. Use the **Emerald** Potion on who you think are important classes. **Psychics,** **Sheriff/Paladins**, **Observers**, **Princesses**, and the **Prince** are the best targets for your Emerald Potion. **TARGET ACTIVE VOTERS.** Anyone who votes actively or asks for logs, is a player that needs to be eliminated. If you know that the king is Neutral/Evil **WHISPER HIM** that you&#39;re willing to side with him. He will most likely tell any evils he knows that you&#39;re an ally. **USE YOUR STONESKINS ONLY IF THREATEND BY A KNIGHT OR ANOTHER ALCHEMIST.** Yes, there can be more than one Alchemist. You may not get along together if you both are going opposite routes. Vote with who you think is evil, and actively whisper. (There always may be a few games where the evils will unknowingly kill you, everyone expierences this. It&#39;s ok, start another one!)

**Resolution And Comments:**

Thank you for taking the time to read my Guide, I&#39;m actively open to constructive criticism, and I may edit this to fit what else the community has to offer! Good luck throwing those potions!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 02:50:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I usually go with the Blue Dragon Route since there is a higher chance to win, but I made the Unseen/Cult/Neutral route for people who want the highest chances of winning with them. Sure you can betray the Blue Dragon late game, but that would just bleed into the Unseen/Cult/Neutral route.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 02:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-14</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eran_Shmuel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You don’t have to choose BD/cult/unseen, you can just try and help BD and the soon as unseen/cult have numbers vote exe on prince/king/whatever.</p>
<p>For me, winning with BD/NK is more satisfying so ill rather not betray BD unless i got not choice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 13:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-13</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Weizen1988]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Its not really a matter of open or not open, anyone can make any guides they wish, and we will pin them in the ask a guide channel. We are just seeking people to help write up guides on anything tol related. So sure, we would love to have one for evil kings.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 22:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-12</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t seen one. I just did a hunter guide however.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-11</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Has anyone made a fool guide? That is the only one I think I could do a truly great guide on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 18:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-10</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orangeandblack5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ooh, I can take Evil King! Is that still open?</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 17:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-9</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, I do agree with you. This indeed can be part of the Unseen/Cult/Neutral Route. However, Evils tend to be random with who they kill or convert, so you can’t be 100% sure of when to stoneskin when you do out yourself. I still recommend to wait till the NK is dead to out yourself. There are a lot of blood-thirsty Princes who will take any opportunity they get to execute after you claim a neutral class.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 16:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-8</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey! Thanks for noticing this error, the guide has been edited and corrected to fit the format you have requested. Thank you for this!</p>
<p>If you see any more errors please let me know.</p>
<p>Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 16:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-7</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do actually. I’ll work on it later.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 15:38:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-6</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeathReaperRH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OR try the neutral route<br>
1-Out day 1<br>
2-Spam chat saying your alchemist<br>
3-Prove yourself anytime possible<br>
4-Never need to stoneskin tbh with this strategy(Unless you feel threatened)(I would wait to stoneskin potion until N3 because BD killers cant kill until N3 and evils shouldnt waste a night on you)(They still might though)<br>
With this strat you live most of the time unless prince tells “knight” to CS you making you die.<br>
Totally didnt happen to me and lose BD the game.What is good about this strat is everyone knows your alch and will feel no need to kill you.You NEVER potion on this route unless evils attack you and you want revenge.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 15:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Weizen1988]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah, yeah, thats a mistake far as I know, but that can all be corrected. Incidently nuclear, we are looking for written guides on different classes if you have any you are particularly good with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 15:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The alchemist isn’t Occupy immune. The butler and drunk are not effected by your passive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 12:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Weizen1988]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you dns, Pinning this in <span class="hashtag">#ask-a-guide</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 06:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Prepare your potions! It’s time to get yourself a win with <strong>Alchemist!</strong></p>
<p><strong><em>Introduction:</em></strong><br>
Hello! So you’re playing Throne Of Lies one day, and you get the Neutral class Alchemist. “What is this?” you ask yourself in desperation as the Prince cuts off your head while yelling <span class="hashtag">#NeutsOut</span>!  No worries, the community has got your back! This guide will cover <strong>The Basics</strong> and the <strong>The Strategies</strong> for Alchemist.</p>
<p><strong>The Basics:</strong></p>
<p>You start with 3 types of potions: <strong><em>Stoneskin Potion</em></strong>, <strong><em>Crimson Potion</em></strong>, and <strong><em>Emerald Potion.</em></strong></p>
<p><strong>Day Ability:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Stoneskin:</strong> 4 uses, - <em>Drink a potion that will make you immune tonight.</em> Stoneskin is one of the most important potions that the Alchemist has in his inventory. When used correctly it can be a nuisance for those pesky Neutral Killers and Unseen/Cult. Stoneskin is best used when you feel like you’re going to be attacked (Talked and gave an abundance of info in chat for example.)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Night Ability:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Crimson:</strong> Unlimited uses, - <em>Heal a player’s wounds and cure any poison.</em> Crimson is important for when you need to prove yourself to the Blue Dragon or heal an ally. Just like the <strong>Physician’s Heal</strong> it can be used to cure a Blue Dragon’s poison/bleed to narrow down your class to Physician/Alchemist.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Emerald:</strong> 2 uses, - <em>Poison a player with a lethal dosage, instantly killing them.</em> Emerald is also important for proving yourself, or killing someone who you feel is a threat to your win condition. However, Emerald should mostly be used as a <strong>LAST RESORT.</strong> The Blue Dragon will have a death sentence for you if you kill one of their members with it. So use Emerald wisely.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Passive:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Coagulate:</strong> <em>Immune to <strong>NightShade</strong> and <strong>bleeding</strong></em> - This passive is important for when you’re suspected as a Blue Dragon member to the <strong>Assassin/Cult Leader</strong>, or an evil to the <strong>Hunter</strong>. This passive keeps you from dying early on to a pesky poisoning or wolf/rupture.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>The Strategies:</strong></p>
<p>Nice! You know what the Alchemist has in his hands, now its time to put those potions to use in a game! This sub-part of the guide will explain the most common strategies as Alchemist, and the highest chance to win as the class!</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Blue Dragon Route:</strong> The most common route for Alchemist, you declare your allegiance to the Blue Dragon and you will help them win against the Cult/Unseen! When you start out as Alchemist Day 1, it is advised to use a <strong>Stoneskin</strong> potion. However, this is <strong>YOUR DECISION.</strong> Night one is usually the most random night in the game, Unseen/Cult will pick someone random to convert/kill and so will the NK, so its advised to do this. <strong>MAKE A PHYSICIANS JOURNAL</strong>. It’s o’ so important to do this step. If you are jailed and NK is still alive, there is a  high chance you will die from the prince execution assuming you claim Alchemist to them. Blue Dragon is usually unaware that Alchemist can be important later on, and they will kill any Neutral possible to kill the NK. Once the NK is dead you have <strong>TWO CHOICES.</strong> You can:</li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Announce to the court that you are indeed <strong>Alchemist.</strong> The Court will most likely acknowledge this, and the Unseen/Cult will stay off of you unless you are blatantly helping the Blue Dragon. <strong>DON’T BE BLATANT</strong>, you will be targeted if you verbally tell everyone that you will help the Blue Dragon, and your game will be over at this point. <strong>USE YOUR STONESKINS WISELY.</strong> If somehow you do end up being blatant, make sure you have those stoneskin potions ready, and keep helping the Blue Dragon till all the evils are executed.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Whisper the king that you’ are indeed <strong>Alchemist.</strong> This is one of the more riskier plays that you may make. <strong>NOTE: THIS CHOICE MAY BLEED INTO THE UNSEEN/CULT/NEUTRAL ROUTE</strong> it is entirely your decision if you want to side with the king or not. At this point of the game, NK is dead, and the king seems like a <strong>Good King</strong> from the evils he has outed and the checks he has made. If the king seems Evil/Neutral <strong>DON’T WHISPER THEM</strong>. As soon as you whisper the king, they are expecting you to join their side. Make sure 100% that the king is Good through outing, or voting a new king who is confirmed Good. The advantages of having a king at your side is abundant. The King and the Alchemist can make a heal combo, which they can’t die from. This is important for this strategy. <strong>BETRAYING THE KING IS YOUR DECISION DO IT WISELY.</strong> Only do this if you know for a fact that the king’s faction is going to lose.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Unseen/Cult/Neutral Route:</strong> You have made your decision. You smile eerily, and you want every Blue Dragon member dead. This is an uncommon route, but is heavily rewarded if successful. Use a <strong>Stoneskin</strong> potion Night 1, again this is your decision, but it is advised. <strong>STILL CREATE A PHYSICIANS JOURNAL.</strong> This will again come in handy if you’re jailed by the <strong>Prince</strong>. Use the <strong>Emerald</strong> Potion on who you think are important classes. <strong>Psychics,</strong> <strong>Sheriff/Paladins</strong>, <strong>Observers</strong>, <strong>Princesses</strong>, and the <strong>Prince</strong> are the best targets for your Emerald Potion. <strong>TARGET ACTIVE VOTERS.</strong> Anyone who votes actively or asks for logs, is a player that needs to be eliminated. If you know that the king is Neutral/Evil <strong>WHISPER HIM</strong> that you’re willing to side with him. He will most likely tell any evils he knows that you’re an ally. <strong>USE YOUR STONESKINS ONLY IF THREATEND BY A KNIGHT OR ANOTHER ALCHEMIST.</strong> Yes, there can be more than one Alchemist. You may not get along together if you both are going opposite routes. Vote with who you think is evil, and actively whisper. (There always may be a few games where the evils will unknowingly kill you, everyone expierences this. It’s ok, start another one!)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Resolution And Comments:</strong></p>
<p>Thank you for taking the time to read my Guide, I’m actively open to constructive criticism, and I may edit this to fit what else the community has to offer! Good luck throwing those potions!</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 06:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29757-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/the-alchemist-guide-for-beginners/29757.rss">The Alchemist Guide! (For Beginners)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
