<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Neutral Killer: Mad Scientist</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-neutral-killer-mad-scientist/54734</link>
    <description>Passive:

Break-Through Enhancement: The NK would only have 2 Death Immunes at night and has MM passive on the Occupy Immune.

This is More Fun: If you successfully use Decay Control, you forfeit &quot;Step Up&quot; to be the next King

Night Abilities

Virus Control: This Mad Scientist visits a dead body and reanimates it for that 1 night and makes him attack anyone of this choice. The dead body attacking a player won&#39;t count as the NK visiting, rather, the dead visiting. The player reanimated will still be BD, Neut, Cult/Unseen (as to NOT piss anyone off) and will be oblivious to what&#39;s happening as players would leave sometimes and ruin the NK player. It&#39;s like Possessor, but for dead bodies.

Day Ability

Lethal Drug Control (1 use): The Mad Scientist chooses a living target and infects them, killing them at night and can ONLY use that body from now on to attack at night. The target body will keep his/her current faction and will still remain alive, but unable to speak for himself/herself. You cannot use that body&#39;s abilities.

Vocal Box: The Mad Scientist can make the player affected by Decay Control say anything the NK wants.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 23:03:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-neutral-killer-mad-scientist/54734.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Neutral Killer: Mad Scientist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WolfTico]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Passive:</p>
<p>Break-Through Enhancement: The NK would only have 2 Death Immunes at night and has MM passive on the Occupy Immune.</p>
<p>This is More Fun: If you successfully use Decay Control, you forfeit “Step Up” to be the next King</p>
<p>Night Abilities</p>
<p>Virus Control: This Mad Scientist visits a dead body and reanimates it for that 1 night and makes him attack anyone of this choice. The dead body attacking a player won’t count as the NK visiting, rather, the dead visiting. The player reanimated will still be BD, Neut, Cult/Unseen (as to NOT piss anyone off) and will be oblivious to what’s happening as players would leave sometimes and ruin the NK player. It’s like Possessor, but for dead bodies.</p>
<p>Day Ability</p>
<p>Lethal Drug Control (1 use): The Mad Scientist chooses a living target and infects them, killing them at night and can ONLY use that body from now on to attack at night. The target body will keep his/her current faction and will still remain alive, but unable to speak for himself/herself. You cannot use that body’s abilities.</p>
<p>Vocal Box: The Mad Scientist can make the player affected by Decay Control say anything the NK wants.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-neutral-killer-mad-scientist/54734/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-neutral-killer-mad-scientist/54734/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 23:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54734-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/new-neutral-killer-mad-scientist/54734.rss">New Neutral Killer: Mad Scientist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
