<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore suggestion] The Court Wizard</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-court-wizard/2027</link>
    <description>Lore page: http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Court_Wizard

Lore Subject: The Wizarding way

Lore:

An extract from the Diary of Archmage Thedelus:

&quot;Whatever the world demands there is one truth with our kind. A wizard is always late because if a wizard was early he would never maintain the study and practice that magic desires of her consorts. Our magic holds infinite secrets but to prepare our abilities takes precise and intricate co-ordination. Not with each other but with the forces all around us. Fire energy is gained from the sun and as such can only be used in limited abundance. A simple &quot;Pants on fire&quot; Spell takes at least one year to prepare a use of. The average Wizard will only use a few within his lifetime. Whilst more lunar based skills are abundant the fire spells maintain consistent and decisive effects upon our sworn enemies. It has been said the Unseen hold records of how to utilise fire energy at a far more efficient rate however we have yet to understand their ways.

The moon provides strength for our barriers. Whilst the sun flares it&#39;s energy wildly without care the moon acts as a magnifying lens for our magic allowing for a quick and focused use of our energies. Our magical barriers provide protection for any we deem to be worthy of it. A wizard will always remain undeterred in his judgement however so never ask one for his input unless you have proven yourself to him. This ability will last till the next Lunar cycle it is a tool to ensure the heartiest of debates.

Finally our most Aggressive yet defensive tool. The Ice ward. The cold air around us at night can be utilised in a manner befitting of a paralysis spell caster. We halt the targets movement and actions rendering them unable to both impress and be impressed upon due to the nature of the wards chilling embrace. Some reports of illness due to this ward have flown in yet in the ever evolving state of magic we expect this to be solved post-haste.

This is the Wizards way and while to some it may seem poultry and inefficient know this is only the start of what our potential can lead us.&quot;


_-Taken from Archduke Thedelus&#39; Diary in the event of his departure from severe burn wounds._






Comments; Well I figured that being magical scientists court wizards should be introduced through an introduction to a thesis. In that Vain I also named the archduke after a user named &quot;Theseus&quot; around here due to his overwhelming confidence in his abilities orresponding with what I believe would be a rather stubborn attitude shown by wizards.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:10:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-court-wizard/2027.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore suggestion] The Court Wizard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Magnasword2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lore page: <a href="http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Court_Wizard" class="inline-onebox-loading" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">http://tol.wikia.com/wiki/The_Court_Wizard</a></p>
<p>Lore Subject: The Wizarding way</p>
<p>Lore:</p>
<p>An extract from the Diary of Archmage Thedelus:</p>
<p>"Whatever the world demands there is one truth with our kind. A wizard is always late because if a wizard was early he would never maintain the study and practice that magic desires of her consorts. Our magic holds infinite secrets but to prepare our abilities takes precise and intricate co-ordination. Not with each other but with the forces all around us. Fire energy is gained from the sun and as such can only be used in limited abundance. A simple “Pants on fire” Spell takes at least one year to prepare a use of. The average Wizard will only use a few within his lifetime. Whilst more lunar based skills are abundant the fire spells maintain consistent and decisive effects upon our sworn enemies. It has been said the Unseen hold records of how to utilise fire energy at a far more efficient rate however we have yet to understand their ways.</p>
<p>The moon provides strength for our barriers. Whilst the sun flares it’s energy wildly without care the moon acts as a magnifying lens for our magic allowing for a quick and focused use of our energies. Our magical barriers provide protection for any we deem to be worthy of it. A wizard will always remain undeterred in his judgement however so never ask one for his input unless you have proven yourself to him. This ability will last till the next Lunar cycle it is a tool to ensure the heartiest of debates.</p>
<p>Finally our most Aggressive yet defensive tool. The Ice ward. The cold air around us at night can be utilised in a manner befitting of a paralysis spell caster. We halt the targets movement and actions rendering them unable to both impress and be impressed upon due to the nature of the wards chilling embrace. Some reports of illness due to this ward have flown in yet in the ever evolving state of magic we expect this to be solved post-haste.</p>
<p>This is the Wizards way and while to some it may seem poultry and inefficient know this is only the start of what our potential can lead us."</p>
<p><em>-Taken from Archduke Thedelus’ Diary in the event of his departure from severe burn wounds.</em></p>
<p>Comments; Well I figured that being magical scientists court wizards should be introduced through an introduction to a thesis. In that Vain I also named the archduke after a user named “Theseus” around here due to his overwhelming confidence in his abilities orresponding with what I believe would be a rather stubborn attitude shown by wizards.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-court-wizard/2027/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-court-wizard/2027/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2027-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/lore-suggestion-the-court-wizard/2027.rss">[Lore suggestion] The Court Wizard</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
