<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Madman</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123</link>
    <description>### **The Madman**  - Unique Neutral Killer

**Objective:** Kill all members of the main factions and any other neutral killers to win (same as reaper and possessor).

### Passive Abilities

**Prophetic** - Immune to death, occupation and conversion at night.

* This also includes immunity to attacks caused by the Madman&#39;s Unhinge ability.

### Day Abilities

**Show Fate** [infinite uses] - Target player will be unable to sit idle tonight. If they do not use any abilities tonight, they will take their own life.

* The target will immediately be notified when this has been used on them during the day, and will receive a reminder at night.
* If the target attempts to use an ability and it is prevented by occupation or otherwise, they will not commit suicide. They must only attempt to use an ability.
* Classes without any night abilities to use, either because their abilities are out of uses or they have no night abilities, will have no choice but to commit suicide.
* If a Prince is affected by this, they will have to execute their prisoner tonight or suicide. However, if they are affected by Show Fate and execute a Blue Dragon, they will not lose all of their execute uses.
* The target will not receive a notification of this, and all messages they send will appear normal.
* Their accusations of treason will seem to have worked to them, but will not actually do anything.

### Night Abilities

**Unhinge** [infinite uses]: Target player is forced to attack all players they targeted with their night ability (cannot target the King).

* As well as getting a result for the action, they will receive the message:
_You were forced by a Madman to instead attack_ [players targeted]
* If the target was occupied, they will not attack anyone.
* The Madman will receive a notification of who was attacked.
* Does not affect classes with abilities that do not target, such as Psychic and Prince.
* If this affects a class that is targeting two or more targets that night, such as an Invoker using Strings of Mithras, they will attack all of them.
* If Unhinge would be redirected to a drunk that has used debauch on the intended target, it will have no affect on the drunk.

**Enlighten** [2 uses]: Show target player all you have learned of the future. That player attacks themselves and all players who visit them tonight.

* If the target is night immune, they will be unhurt, but all players visiting them will still be attacked.
* The Madman will be shown as having visited the target, but they will be unaffected.

### Comments
The Madman&#39;s general strategy will be using Unhinge on targets that are Blue Dragon, preventing them from gathering information while also killing players off slowly. Once a Madman is known about, players may be less likely to want to use their abilities, so Show Fate can be used to so that someone will have to use their abilities. If the Madman becomes aware of an important target such as a heavily guarded prince, they can use the Enlighten ability to hopefully get multiple kills.

**Changes**
Removed daytime silence ability.
Removed the failure from the unhinge ability.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 02:59:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Madman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Navi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with both your points. I added the failure to unhinge just to prevent weird interactions like a knight sacrificing himself to stop his own attack, or a drunk being redirected to attack themselves with their own debauch. But what you’ve said makes more sense.</p>
<p>And yeah, the Silence doesn’t fit too well. It was a last minute addition because I was worried that any investigators would immediately wonder why the Madman was immune to the attack, and immediately accuse them. But if that happens, it’s only really fair that players would be suspicious of the Madman anyway.</p>
<p>I’m only really worried about the Madman’s longevity in a long game. It doesn’t have the potential confusion of the reaper with reaps and chills, and doesn’t have the get-out-of-jail-free card that the possessor has when he jumps targets. There’s also a potential lack of unhinge targets that can target others with their night abilities.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 02:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11123-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Madman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Madman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like this. A unique take on a 1 kpn (normaly anyway). I just have 2 suggestions. 1: don’t have Unhinge make the action fail. Instead have them Kill AND do their ability. This is actually a buff in most cases as:</p>
<p>Invest - Kills target and if they were obs then they learn visitors (not you. You didn’t visit their target)<br>
Killer - Most killers are killing anyway. Hunter - Will bleed them if they were immune. Knight - Will kill self instead if he sacrificed and kill self and target if he csed a BD.<br>
Offensive - Drunk/Alcoholic - Redirects potential support. Occupiers - Prevent they’re last action giving them less info for psychic.<br>
Support - CW/Merc - Blocks potential support. Physician/alch - Heals target, the only bad result from this.</p>
<p>Suggestion 2 is to remove Silence. He is already powerful without it and it doesn’t fit the class concept.</p>
<p>Other than that I love this class!</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 02:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11123-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Madman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Madman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Navi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you’re sure someone is not using abilities, then you can use Show Fate on them to either force their abilities or their own death, or just use Enlighten to get rid of them if they are really important.</p>
<p>Made some other changes to the OP as well. Accidentally posted it before I was done oops</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 02:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11123-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Madman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Madman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>nice organization. I also like the class, only suggestion is if you use unhinge and the person willfully does nothing (meaning not including occupies) then they will kill them selves instead</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 01:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11123-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Madman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Madman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Navi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h3>
<strong>The Madman</strong>  - Unique Neutral Killer</h3>
<p><strong>Objective:</strong> Kill all members of the main factions and any other neutral killers to win (same as reaper and possessor).</p>
<h3>Passive Abilities</h3>
<p><strong>Prophetic</strong> - Immune to death, occupation and conversion at night.</p>
<ul>
<li>This also includes immunity to attacks caused by the Madman’s Unhinge ability.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Day Abilities</h3>
<p><strong>Show Fate</strong> [infinite uses] - Target player will be unable to sit idle tonight. If they do not use any abilities tonight, they will take their own life.</p>
<ul>
<li>The target will immediately be notified when this has been used on them during the day, and will receive a reminder at night.</li>
<li>If the target attempts to use an ability and it is prevented by occupation or otherwise, they will not commit suicide. They must only attempt to use an ability.</li>
<li>Classes without any night abilities to use, either because their abilities are out of uses or they have no night abilities, will have no choice but to commit suicide.</li>
<li>If a Prince is affected by this, they will have to execute their prisoner tonight or suicide. However, if they are affected by Show Fate and execute a Blue Dragon, they will not lose all of their execute uses.</li>
<li>The target will not receive a notification of this, and all messages they send will appear normal.</li>
<li>Their accusations of treason will seem to have worked to them, but will not actually do anything.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Night Abilities</h3>
<p><strong>Unhinge</strong> [infinite uses]: Target player is forced to attack all players they targeted with their night ability (cannot target the King).</p>
<ul>
<li>As well as getting a result for the action, they will receive the message:<br>
<em>You were forced by a Madman to instead attack</em> [players targeted]</li>
<li>If the target was occupied, they will not attack anyone.</li>
<li>The Madman will receive a notification of who was attacked.</li>
<li>Does not affect classes with abilities that do not target, such as Psychic and Prince.</li>
<li>If this affects a class that is targeting two or more targets that night, such as an Invoker using Strings of Mithras, they will attack all of them.</li>
<li>If Unhinge would be redirected to a drunk that has used debauch on the intended target, it will have no affect on the drunk.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Enlighten</strong> [2 uses]: Show target player all you have learned of the future. That player attacks themselves and all players who visit them tonight.</p>
<ul>
<li>If the target is night immune, they will be unhurt, but all players visiting them will still be attacked.</li>
<li>The Madman will be shown as having visited the target, but they will be unaffected.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Comments</h3>
<p>The Madman’s general strategy will be using Unhinge on targets that are Blue Dragon, preventing them from gathering information while also killing players off slowly. Once a Madman is known about, players may be less likely to want to use their abilities, so Show Fate can be used to so that someone will have to use their abilities. If the Madman becomes aware of an important target such as a heavily guarded prince, they can use the Enlighten ability to hopefully get multiple kills.</p>
<p><strong>Changes</strong><br>
Removed daytime silence ability.<br>
Removed the failure from the unhinge ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 01:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-11123-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-madman/11123.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Madman</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
