<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Rework Idea] Mercenary</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979</link>
    <description>Note &quot;Idea&quot; as opposed to &quot;Suggestion&quot;, this isn&#39;t something I feel needs to be added, just playing around with the idea of it, but that doesn&#39;t mean I&#39;m not looking for feedback. Also note that the Rogue&#39;s abilities are disabled once they meet their win condition.
&gt; ## [color=gray]The Mercenary[/color]
&gt; **[color=gray]Neutral Support[/color]**
**Looking For Work (Passive)** - You have three days to find a contract, or you will commit suicide. If that contract dies, you will become **[color=gray]The Rogue[/color]**.
**Contact Contract (Passive)** - At night, you can talk with your contract, if you have one.
**Offer Contract (Day)** - Offer a contract to a player, if you do not already have one. - Infinite uses
**Stand Guard (Night)** - Protect your target and prevent others from visiting and make yourself immune to death for the night. - 4 uses
**Rebound (Night)** - Kill a player that accused your target of treason during the previous day. - 1 use
_Contracted player survives._

&gt; ## [color=purple]The Sellsword[/color]
&gt; **[color=purple]Unseen Support[/color]**
**Keeping in Contract (Passive)** - At night, you can talk with the contract you had as a Mercenary, if you had one.
**Stonewall (Night)** - Protect an Unseen player and prevent other visitors from interacting with them. - 3 uses
**Revenge (Night)** - Kill target player that accused an Unseen member of treason the previous day. - 1 use
_Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to harm you._

&gt; ## [color=gray]The Rogue[/color]
&gt; **[color=gray]Neutral Killer[/color]**
**Hardened (Passive)** - Immune to death at night.
**Contract Killing (Day)** - Offer to kill for a player. They can choose a player for you to kill, or can deny the contract. - Infinite uses, can be used on the same day if denied
**True Strike (Day)** - Make your attack tonight pierce death immunity. - Infinite uses
**Exterminate (Night)** - Attack a player that you have been contracted to kill. - Infinite uses
_Kill three contract targets. If you became a Rogue after Day 6, kill two contract targets, or if you became a Rogue after Day 9, kill a single contract target._</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 15:31:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Rework Idea] Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyoDaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good Idea Ashe, but I do not agree with the Neutral Killer class type. I’d put it into Neutral Offensive or back into Support.</p>
<p>All Neutral Killers should not be restricted to who they can kill and should be able to kill who they want and not someone else’s idea. It also messes with the “1 Neutral Killer Limit” thing. It’s win con also is not defeat an opposing faction which is what all NK’s are.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 15:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35979-5</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979.rss">[Rework Idea] Mercenary</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Rework Idea] Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NOBLE1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like this but instead of turning into a NK he should be a Neutral Support. His end goal should be that the Rouge has to kill a certain smoking of player and the only way he can do that is by offering a random play to do so.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35979-4</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979.rss">[Rework Idea] Mercenary</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Rework Idea] Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well when you think about it that is way better that what you have now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 12:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35979-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979.rss">[Rework Idea] Mercenary</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Rework Idea] Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jabba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ultimately I see the change into rogue as an instant exe for BD if your contract dies early, as at that point in the game BD will not have enough information to know the evils exactly, and BD will ultimately be contracting to rando kill each other with the Rogue.  Furthermore, if a merc goes rogue mid-game, BD will be hesitant in the first place to contract for rogue kills with limited info, and if the Rogue ends up killing a BD, he’s gonna get exe’d.  If a merc is strapped for guards and his contract unfortunately dies late game, then there’s not going to be enough time in the rest of the game for him to get 3 contract kills.  Obviously you could look at reducing the number of contract kills required to win, however rogue would inevitably be one of those neutral classes BD would immediately dispose of because it ultimately only hurts BD, like fool and scorned.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 05:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35979-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979.rss">[Rework Idea] Mercenary</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Rework Idea] Mercenary</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Note “Idea” as opposed to “Suggestion”, this isn’t something I feel needs to be added, just playing around with the idea of it, but that doesn’t mean I’m not looking for feedback. Also note that the Rogue’s abilities are disabled once they meet their win condition.</p>
<blockquote>
<h2><font color="gray">The Mercenary</font></h2>
<p><strong><font color="gray">Neutral Support</font></strong><br>
<strong>Looking For Work (Passive)</strong> - You have three days to find a contract, or you will commit suicide. If that contract dies, you will become <strong><font color="gray">The Rogue</font></strong>.<br>
<strong>Contact Contract (Passive)</strong> - At night, you can talk with your contract, if you have one.<br>
<strong>Offer Contract (Day)</strong> - Offer a contract to a player, if you do not already have one. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Stand Guard (Night)</strong> - Protect your target and prevent others from visiting and make yourself immune to death for the night. - 4 uses<br>
<strong>Rebound (Night)</strong> - Kill a player that accused your target of treason during the previous day. - 1 use<br>
<em>Contracted player survives.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><font color="purple">The Sellsword</font></h2>
<p><strong><font color="purple">Unseen Support</font></strong><br>
<strong>Keeping in Contract (Passive)</strong> - At night, you can talk with the contract you had as a Mercenary, if you had one.<br>
<strong>Stonewall (Night)</strong> - Protect an Unseen player and prevent other visitors from interacting with them. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Revenge (Night)</strong> - Kill target player that accused an Unseen member of treason the previous day. - 1 use<br>
<em>Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to harm you.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<h2><font color="gray">The Rogue</font></h2>
<p><strong><font color="gray">Neutral Killer</font></strong><br>
<strong>Hardened (Passive)</strong> - Immune to death at night.<br>
<strong>Contract Killing (Day)</strong> - Offer to kill for a player. They can choose a player for you to kill, or can deny the contract. - Infinite uses, can be used on the same day if denied<br>
<strong>True Strike (Day)</strong> - Make your attack tonight pierce death immunity. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Exterminate (Night)</strong> - Attack a player that you have been contracted to kill. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Kill three contract targets. If you became a Rogue after Day 6, kill two contract targets, or if you became a Rogue after Day 9, kill a single contract target.</em></p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 05:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-35979-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/rework-idea-mercenary/35979.rss">[Rework Idea] Mercenary</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
