<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] CHERUB (Blue Dragon) / BRAT (Unseen)</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-cherub-blue-dragon-brat-unseen/21345</link>
    <description>**Cherub** (Blue Dragon)

Passive:
**Beloved** - If you are executed for treason, players who voted to execute you cannot vote to put anyone on trial the next day.

_^ They can still vote to Pardon or Execute, they simply cannot nominate someone to stand trial._

Day Ability:
**Lilting Voice** - Select two players to prevent them from using day abilities, but only if they are not Blue Dragon. (3 uses.)

_^ You&#39;re not notified of the result, it simply blocks day actions from non-BD if at least one of your targets is non-BD._

Night Ability 1:
**Lucky Cat** - Send your pet to protect a player from death. It will be transferred to the next person that player visits, and so on. You may also call your pet back by choosing to protect someone else entirely. (Unlimited use.)

_^ Explained: You give the cat to Player1. He visits Player2, so Player2 is then protected instead. Player2 visits Player3, so he is then protected instead. If the player DOESN&#39;T visit anyone, he just doesn&#39;t transfer the cat._

Night Ability 2:
**Matchmaker** - Select two players at night. If they are not in direct opposition to each other, they will be told they are possible allies. (3 uses.)

_^ If you select two players who can win together, they will be told &quot;A Cherub has told you that PlayerName is not your enemy.&quot; If the two players cannot win together, they will be told nothing at all. You are not given any information on the result._



**Converts to...**



**Brat** (Unseen)

Passive:
**Spoiled Rotten** - If you are executed for treason, players who voted to execute you cannot use their night abilities on the following night. [Note that this is different from &quot;Beloved&quot;.]

Day Ability:
**Whine** - Force a player to use their night ability on you if they are a healing class. (3 uses.)

_^ In other words, if you know who the Physician/Alchemist is, you can force them to heal your bleeding or just protect you the following night. No need to out yourself as injured, or simply hope they heal you. Simply does nothing if your target is not able to heal._

Night Ability 1:
**Ominous Cat** - Send your pet to block a player&#39;s night actions. It will be transferred to the next person that visits your target, and so on. You may also call your pet back by choosing to block someone else entirely. (2 uses.)

_^ Explained: You sent your pet to Player1. He is visited by Player2, who now picks up the cat and is blocked instead. He is then visited by Player3, who now picks up the cat and is blocked instead. And so it goes. If no one visits the person with the cat, it keeps blocking them._

Night Ability 2:
**Temper Tantrum** - Cause all living, non-Unseen players to randomly change their target. (Single use.)

_^ Only works on people who are actually trying to use a night ability._</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 05:56:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-cherub-blue-dragon-brat-unseen/21345.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] CHERUB (Blue Dragon) / BRAT (Unseen)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tormental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Cherub</strong> (Blue Dragon)</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Beloved</strong> - If you are executed for treason, players who voted to execute you cannot vote to put anyone on trial the next day.</p>
<p><em>^ They can still vote to Pardon or Execute, they simply cannot nominate someone to stand trial.</em></p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Lilting Voice</strong> - Select two players to prevent them from using day abilities, but only if they are not Blue Dragon. (3 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ You’re not notified of the result, it simply blocks day actions from non-BD if at least one of your targets is non-BD.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Lucky Cat</strong> - Send your pet to protect a player from death. It will be transferred to the next person that player visits, and so on. You may also call your pet back by choosing to protect someone else entirely. (Unlimited use.)</p>
<p><em>^ Explained: You give the cat to Player1. He visits Player2, so Player2 is then protected instead. Player2 visits Player3, so he is then protected instead. If the player DOESN’T visit anyone, he just doesn’t transfer the cat.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Matchmaker</strong> - Select two players at night. If they are not in direct opposition to each other, they will be told they are possible allies. (3 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ If you select two players who can win together, they will be told “A Cherub has told you that PlayerName is not your enemy.” If the two players cannot win together, they will be told nothing at all. You are not given any information on the result.</em></p>
<p><strong>Converts to…</strong></p>
<p><strong>Brat</strong> (Unseen)</p>
<p>Passive:<br>
<strong>Spoiled Rotten</strong> - If you are executed for treason, players who voted to execute you cannot use their night abilities on the following night. [Note that this is different from “Beloved”.]</p>
<p>Day Ability:<br>
<strong>Whine</strong> - Force a player to use their night ability on you if they are a healing class. (3 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ In other words, if you know who the Physician/Alchemist is, you can force them to heal your bleeding or just protect you the following night. No need to out yourself as injured, or simply hope they heal you. Simply does nothing if your target is not able to heal.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
<strong>Ominous Cat</strong> - Send your pet to block a player’s night actions. It will be transferred to the next person that visits your target, and so on. You may also call your pet back by choosing to block someone else entirely. (2 uses.)</p>
<p><em>^ Explained: You sent your pet to Player1. He is visited by Player2, who now picks up the cat and is blocked instead. He is then visited by Player3, who now picks up the cat and is blocked instead. And so it goes. If no one visits the person with the cat, it keeps blocking them.</em></p>
<p>Night Ability 2:<br>
<strong>Temper Tantrum</strong> - Cause all living, non-Unseen players to randomly change their target. (Single use.)</p>
<p><em>^ Only works on people who are actually trying to use a night ability.</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-cherub-blue-dragon-brat-unseen/21345/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-cherub-blue-dragon-brat-unseen/21345/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 05:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-21345-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/class-suggestion-cherub-blue-dragon-brat-unseen/21345.rss">[Class Suggestion] CHERUB (Blue Dragon) / BRAT (Unseen)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
