<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tiny thoughts from a tiny brain</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672</link>
    <description>.... 
If you can&#39;t kill the MM* as the king.. What&#39;s the point of the king having a killing ability?.. 

We have some great suggestions about the king here.. 
**NO KING, vote him up day 4.** (Stole that one from the post above ;) )
Yes, people could step up to become king with some actual logs.
No, every royal BD would have to make a claim or show that they are royal.. 

**The king is the king right?**
He should be informed on who the Prince is jailing.. Every night ! Passive ability.

Yes, this would support his investigative abilitys by a landslide! Someone giving the king logs about a fella that was in fact jailed.. Well oops. That fella is lying.
No, .... Why not?

**King is still a king.**
King can force start a trial instead of having two votes. (I would credit the fella who said it but I forgot.)

Yes, the finger isn&#39;t the strongest of abilitys and we&#39;re coming in to actual king actions here. 
No, Time will be wasted during trials for sharing information, but hey, we&#39;re good at starting trials early anyway!


_*MM, Scorned, Merc guarding, Merc guarded target, jailed target (you&#39;re the king), Poss, Sorc, Reaper with souls, and also healed and knight guarded targets.._ 

Oh, and yes, all the other stuff that was supposed to be implemented in to the game but wasn&#39;t. Please give it to us.
:breast_feeding:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 13:04:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tiny thoughts from a tiny brain</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hippolytus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually quite like the idea of the King having a passive where he can see who the Prince jails. Fits thematically, gives a bit of extra power, and would appease all the whiners who are crying now that Prince has no OP investigative ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 13:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40672-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672.rss">Tiny thoughts from a tiny brain</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tiny thoughts from a tiny brain</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tinyneut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…<br>
If you can’t kill the MM* as the king… What’s the point of the king having a killing ability?..</p>
<p>We have some great suggestions about the king here…<br>
<strong>NO KING, vote him up day 4.</strong> (Stole that one from the post above <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> )<br>
Yes, people could step up to become king with some actual logs.<br>
No, every royal BD would have to make a claim or show that they are royal…</p>
<p><strong>The king is the king right?</strong><br>
He should be informed on who the Prince is jailing… Every night ! Passive ability.</p>
<p>Yes, this would support his investigative abilitys by a landslide! Someone giving the king logs about a fella that was in fact jailed… Well oops. That fella is lying.<br>
No, … Why not?</p>
<p><strong>King is still a king.</strong><br>
King can force start a trial instead of having two votes. (I would credit the fella who said it but I forgot.)</p>
<p>Yes, the finger isn’t the strongest of abilitys and we’re coming in to actual king actions here.<br>
No, Time will be wasted during trials for sharing information, but hey, we’re good at starting trials early anyway!</p>
<p><em>*MM, Scorned, Merc guarding, Merc guarded target, jailed target (you’re the king), Poss, Sorc, Reaper with souls, and also healed and knight guarded targets…</em></p>
<p>Oh, and yes, all the other stuff that was supposed to be implemented in to the game but wasn’t. Please give it to us.<br>
<img src="/images/emoji/twitter/breast_feeding.png?v=9" title=":breast_feeding:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":breast_feeding:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 11:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-40672-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/tiny-thoughts-from-a-tiny-brain/40672.rss">Tiny thoughts from a tiny brain</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
