<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[BUG] Drunk debauch ability triggers twice</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bug-drunk-debauch-ability-triggers-twice/39937</link>
    <description>#### What happened?
I was playing as a drunk, and every time I successfully debauched someone (they weren&#39;t immune), I would receive the &quot;You caused X to target you&quot; message twice.

#### What was SUPPOSED to happen?
Should only receive it once.

#### Steps to reproduce:
1. Use Debauch on any target not immune to having their target redirected.

The same nights I received the double message I (as the drunk) was also guarded by my merc, so I&#39;m not sure if that factors into it.

#### Comments:
Have seen a few times when playing as other classes that I&#39;d get redirected twice in one night, so I&#39;m assuming that was due to a drunk&#39;s debauch being doubled? Both debauches count towards the 3 needed to get occupy immunity, so this could be game breaking in some cases.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 04:44:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bug-drunk-debauch-ability-triggers-twice/39937.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[BUG] Drunk debauch ability triggers twice</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Navi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>What happened?</h4>
<p>I was playing as a drunk, and every time I successfully debauched someone (they weren’t immune), I would receive the “You caused X to target you” message twice.</p>
<h4>What was SUPPOSED to happen?</h4>
<p>Should only receive it once.</p>
<h4>Steps to reproduce:</h4>
<ol>
<li>Use Debauch on any target not immune to having their target redirected.</li>
</ol>
<p>The same nights I received the double message I (as the drunk) was also guarded by my merc, so I’m not sure if that factors into it.</p>
<h4>Comments:</h4>
<p>Have seen a few times when playing as other classes that I’d get redirected twice in one night, so I’m assuming that was due to a drunk’s debauch being doubled? Both debauches count towards the 3 needed to get occupy immunity, so this could be game breaking in some cases.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bug-drunk-debauch-ability-triggers-twice/39937/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bug-drunk-debauch-ability-triggers-twice/39937/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 04:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-39937-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/bug-drunk-debauch-ability-triggers-twice/39937.rss">[BUG] Drunk debauch ability triggers twice</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
