<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Terminology/Keyword Suggestions</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-terminology-keyword-suggestions/28811</link>
    <description>In addition to reducing confusion I feel like making and using keywords for more things can help streamline how ability&#39;s work as time goes on and helps better define what things to what. Mainly for class suggestions.


First of all because of confusion on how this works sometimes I would like to propose this Keyword change:

Occupy immunity -&gt; Manipulate immunity - Lots of people don&#39;t understand why Occupy immune people cannot be redirected. This is because Occupy is an actual effect separate from Redirection. This also has the additional effect of being able to give out Occupy immunity and Redirection immunity seperatly in the future.

Now for New Keywords that should be a thing.

Manipulation: Anything that is blocked by Manipulation immunity. Occupation and Redirection are examples right now but other things could be in the future. Jail is not considered manipulation.

Tamper: Any ability that effects ability results. Right now that is Mind Warp and Frame.

Direct attack: Any attack that is explicitly selected. Examples are: Cold Steel, Erraticate, Assassinate, Reap, ect...

Counter attack: Any attack that is in response to something else. Examples are: Sacrafice, Bear, Circle of Death, ect...

Status: Any ability that lingers for a set period of time before doing it&#39;s effect. Examples are: Nightshade, Rapture, Wolf.

Evils: Any and all members of a faction capable of conversion. The NK is not Evil.

Scum: Any class who&#39;s goal requires that they harm the BD. Examples are: All Evils, The NK, Fool, Scorned, Sorcerer.

Faction: A group of 1 or more people that needs all other factions to be eliminated with at least 1 surviving member of their own faction alive to win (is not the same thing as an alignment). Examples are: BD, Evils, NK. Sorcerer is not a Faction member as they only need 1 faction killed and not any others.


If anyone has any suggestions please say them. I might add more as Keywords are useful for streamlining lots of classes and ability&#39;s.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 01:10:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-terminology-keyword-suggestions/28811.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Terminology/Keyword Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In addition to reducing confusion I feel like making and using keywords for more things can help streamline how ability’s work as time goes on and helps better define what things to what. Mainly for class suggestions.</p>
<p>First of all because of confusion on how this works sometimes I would like to propose this Keyword change:</p>
<p>Occupy immunity -&gt; Manipulate immunity - Lots of people don’t understand why Occupy immune people cannot be redirected. This is because Occupy is an actual effect separate from Redirection. This also has the additional effect of being able to give out Occupy immunity and Redirection immunity seperatly in the future.</p>
<p>Now for New Keywords that should be a thing.</p>
<p>Manipulation: Anything that is blocked by Manipulation immunity. Occupation and Redirection are examples right now but other things could be in the future. Jail is not considered manipulation.</p>
<p>Tamper: Any ability that effects ability results. Right now that is Mind Warp and Frame.</p>
<p>Direct attack: Any attack that is explicitly selected. Examples are: Cold Steel, Erraticate, Assassinate, Reap, ect…</p>
<p>Counter attack: Any attack that is in response to something else. Examples are: Sacrafice, Bear, Circle of Death, ect…</p>
<p>Status: Any ability that lingers for a set period of time before doing it’s effect. Examples are: Nightshade, Rapture, Wolf.</p>
<p>Evils: Any and all members of a faction capable of conversion. The NK is not Evil.</p>
<p>Scum: Any class who’s goal requires that they harm the BD. Examples are: All Evils, The NK, Fool, Scorned, Sorcerer.</p>
<p>Faction: A group of 1 or more people that needs all other factions to be eliminated with at least 1 surviving member of their own faction alive to win (is not the same thing as an alignment). Examples are: BD, Evils, NK. Sorcerer is not a Faction member as they only need 1 faction killed and not any others.</p>
<p>If anyone has any suggestions please say them. I might add more as Keywords are useful for streamlining lots of classes and ability’s.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-terminology-keyword-suggestions/28811/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-terminology-keyword-suggestions/28811/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 01:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-28811-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/new-terminology-keyword-suggestions/28811.rss">New Terminology/Keyword Suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
