<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626</link>
    <description>**Counter-Spell**:  Target a player and select an ability (all Unseen, Cult and Neutral Killer abilities are listed). If target is of the evil faction or the Neutral Killer and attempts to use the ability you selected, your Magic Barrier will grant death immunity.

**Divination**: Predict who dies next.  If you are correct and the player was not Blue Dragon, your next use of Magic Barrier will grant death immunity.

**Nature Bender**: Target a player and select an element to infuse them with.  Fire will kill their visitors, Water will heal their visitors, Earth will prevent their visitors, and Air will be the same as current Magic Barrier (this ability would replace Magic Barrier).

The following abilities might be variations on ideas that have already been proposed:

**Wall of Ice:** Select two players.  Only the second player will be able to visit the first; all other visitors will be prevented.

**Empower Spell:** Empower a player&#39;s ability.  Killer/Offensive abilities will bypass immunities.  Investigative abilities will provide more precise feedback and not be fooled by frames or the Mastermind&#39;s passive (Princess flirt will give exact class, Observer follow will identify visits that aren&#39;t technically visits).  Heal will heal Reap and Frenzy.  I can&#39;t think of a way to empower social abilities.

Perhaps Empower, if misused on Mastermind/Cult Leader, could allow them to convert Alchemist, Fool and Scorned.

**Magic Barrier 2.0**:  Super-duper empower a player, making them immune to all negative effects and also allowing their abilities to bypass all of their target&#39;s immunities.  So a Knight could kill a death immune Sorcerer, but if misused on the Mastermind it would allow him to convert Prince :yum:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 19:33:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay instead of reporting him<br>
I suggest to report him and</p>
<p>NUKE HIS HOUSE!!!</p>
<p>Jk No hate just reaping souls</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 19:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54626-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626.rss">Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i just played a game where prince executed cw on purpose to troll</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54626-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626.rss">Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firekitten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel bad for the prince when cw trolls</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 11:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54626-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626.rss">Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>Counter spell is only good if you already know what class and what ability they’re going to use</p>
</blockquote>
<p>That’s intended, the success of the ability is supposed to depend on the skill of the player.  If you want to buff it, have it flat-out kill the target when successful.  <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/sunglasses.png?v=9" title=":sunglasses:" class="emoji" alt=":sunglasses:"></p>
<blockquote>
<p>they also have to be evil and you can just select convert every time to check</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Also if you have multiple sheriff claims it something, you just block convert every time.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I didn’t specify the number of uses.  This can be avoided by limiting the number of uses, and informing evil players if Counter-Spell was used on them.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>MM also needs to stay hidden</p>
</blockquote>
<p>A MM claiming Princess could request an Empower to buff her Flirt when in reality she wants to convert the Alchemist, for instance.  The ability does not expose the Mastermind.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>the rando empower is pretty unreliable and boring as you need to target someone who will be actually doing something with their abilities.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The use of Empower is supposed to be coordinated with the target player, not random (that risks empowering an evil’s ability).  If a Knight wants to kill the Possessor, he can ask for an Empower.  If a Princess wants to flirt a Mastermind suspect, she can ask for an Empower.  If a Physician wants to heal Prince from the Reaper, he can ask for an Empower.  If Sheriff wants to investigate a suspected Scorned target, he can ask for an Empower, etc.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Like how often do you think you’ll be able to heal a reap?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The ability works on much more than just heals in a Reaper game.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Also it makes CW pretty confirmable.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The only significantly confirmable thing about it, that I can tell, is its effect on Princess Flirt.  This can be solved by just not letting it make the Flirt more precise and instead only protecting it against frames.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54626-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626.rss">Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaximusPrime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Counter spell is only good if you already know what class and what ability they’re going to use(they also have to be evil and you can just select convert every time to check. It would also make logs pretty big probably, as they have to state the ability). Also if you have multiple sheriff claims it something, you just block convert every time. MM also needs to stay hidden and the rando empower is pretty unreliable and boring as you need to target someone who will be actually doing something with their abilities. Like how often do you think you’ll be able to heal a reap? Also it makes CW pretty confirmable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54626-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626.rss">Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrimpy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>Counter-Spell</strong>:  Target a player and select an ability (all Unseen, Cult and Neutral Killer abilities are listed). If target is of the evil faction or the Neutral Killer and attempts to use the ability you selected, your Magic Barrier will grant death immunity.</p>
<p><strong>Divination</strong>: Predict who dies next.  If you are correct and the player was not Blue Dragon, your next use of Magic Barrier will grant death immunity.</p>
<p><strong>Nature Bender</strong>: Target a player and select an element to infuse them with.  Fire will kill their visitors, Water will heal their visitors, Earth will prevent their visitors, and Air will be the same as current Magic Barrier (this ability would replace Magic Barrier).</p>
<p>The following abilities might be variations on ideas that have already been proposed:</p>
<p><strong>Wall of Ice:</strong> Select two players.  Only the second player will be able to visit the first; all other visitors will be prevented.</p>
<p><strong>Empower Spell:</strong> Empower a player’s ability.  Killer/Offensive abilities will bypass immunities.  Investigative abilities will provide more precise feedback and not be fooled by frames or the Mastermind’s passive (Princess flirt will give exact class, Observer follow will identify visits that aren’t technically visits).  Heal will heal Reap and Frenzy.  I can’t think of a way to empower social abilities.</p>
<p>Perhaps Empower, if misused on Mastermind/Cult Leader, could allow them to convert Alchemist, Fool and Scorned.</p>
<p><strong>Magic Barrier 2.0</strong>:  Super-duper empower a player, making them immune to all negative effects and also allowing their abilities to bypass all of their target’s immunities.  So a Knight could kill a death immune Sorcerer, but if misused on the Mastermind it would allow him to convert Prince <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/yum.png?v=9" title=":yum:" class="emoji" alt=":yum:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-54626-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/shrimpys-court-wizard-contest-entry/54626.rss">Shrimpy&#39;s Court Wizard Contest Entry</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
