<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class Suggestion] The Siren (Neutral, Offensive)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385</link>
    <description>&gt;**The Siren**
Unique Neutral, Offensive.
&gt;**Goal:** Survive.
&gt;**Day ability 1: Charm**
&gt;Charms a player until he dies. Charmed players will not know they are charmed nor the siren&#39;s identity, but will be forced to pardon her when she is on trial. Unlimited uses but 1 day cool-down. _(You cannot charm the King. You can use this ability on day 1)_
&gt;**Day ability 2: Trollbox**
Trollbox one of your charmed targets. Unlimited uses. _(You can use this even if you used charm the same day. Cannot be used on day 1)_
&gt;**Night ability 1: Personal Bodyguard**
&gt;Choose one of your charmed targets. Everyone attempting to visit you will visit them instead. Unlimited uses, but you can only use this ability once on each charmed target.
&gt;**Night ability 2: Lure**
&gt;Force one of your charmed targets to visit you tonight. They will not know the Siren&#39;s identity, they will only get a message saying &quot;The Siren forced you to target her!&quot;. Doesn&#39;t work on occupy immune players. Unlimited uses.

**Comments:** The Siren is a Neutral class that needs to survive in order to win, however she doesn&#39;t have night immunity. Her survival relies on her charmed targets since she can force them to use protective abilities on her, or redirect attackers into one of her charmed targets.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 17:29:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Siren (Neutral, Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can only use bodyguard once per charmed target so you can’t always use it. I was thinking about making charm tell you the target’s class type (like princess) so lure is safer to use.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 17:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32385-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Siren (Neutral, Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Siren (Neutral, Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Coatsman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice Idea, but I’m not exactly seeing the point of the Lure ability. I can understand in some sense that you could lure a vital faction member to target you, but without knowing their class and with bodyguard being another ability re-directing targets, I feel most of the time you’d be better off just using the initial ability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 16:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32385-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Siren (Neutral, Offensive)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class Suggestion] The Siren (Neutral, Offensive)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p><strong>The Siren</strong><br>
Unique Neutral, Offensive.<br>
<strong>Goal:</strong> Survive.<br>
<strong>Day ability 1: Charm</strong><br>
Charms a player until he dies. Charmed players will not know they are charmed nor the siren’s identity, but will be forced to pardon her when she is on trial. Unlimited uses but 1 day cool-down. <em>(You cannot charm the King. You can use this ability on day 1)</em><br>
<strong>Day ability 2: Trollbox</strong><br>
Trollbox one of your charmed targets. Unlimited uses. <em>(You can use this even if you used charm the same day. Cannot be used on day 1)</em><br>
<strong>Night ability 1: Personal Bodyguard</strong><br>
Choose one of your charmed targets. Everyone attempting to visit you will visit them instead. Unlimited uses, but you can only use this ability once on each charmed target.<br>
<strong>Night ability 2: Lure</strong><br>
Force one of your charmed targets to visit you tonight. They will not know the Siren’s identity, they will only get a message saying “The Siren forced you to target her!”. Doesn’t work on occupy immune players. Unlimited uses.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Comments:</strong> The Siren is a Neutral class that needs to survive in order to win, however she doesn’t have night immunity. Her survival relies on her charmed targets since she can force them to use protective abilities on her, or redirect attackers into one of her charmed targets.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-32385-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-the-siren-neutral-offensive/32385.rss">[Class Suggestion] The Siren (Neutral, Offensive)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
