<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Beast Lord (Neutral Killer)</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-beast-lord-neutral-killer/59135</link>
    <description>&lt;big&gt;[Color=gray]The Beast Lord[/color]&lt;/big&gt;
Neutral, Killer.
Win condition: Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Unseen/Cult.
Description: A shapeshifter and beast tamer able to adapt to every situation.

**Survival Instincts (Passive)** - You are immune to death at night.
**Lion Form (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
**Morph (Day)** - Change your second passive to a different one. You will keep that passive until you change it again. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-day cooldown.
&gt; Available passives:
&gt; * **Lion Form (Passive)** - You are immune to occupation and redirection.
&gt; * **Snake Form (Passive)** - You are immune to poison/bleeding. Doesn&#39;t heal you if you change to this passive while you were already poisoned/bleeding.
&gt; * **Chameleon Form (Passive)** - Your night abilities don&#39;t count as visiting.
&gt; * **Owl Form (Passive)** - You are unaffected by day abilities, except for poison, bleeding or jail. 
&gt; * **Eagle Form (Passive)** - You will know who visits you every night. 

**Rampage (Day)** - Your night ability will be instantly available tonight if its on cooldown. 1 use.
**Tiger companion (Night)** - Kill two players. Unlimited uses, but has a one-night cooldown.
**Tame (Night)** - Change your first night ability to a different one. You will keep that ability until you change it again. Unlimited uses.
&gt; Available night abilities:
&gt; * **Tiger companion (Night)** - Kill two players. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.
&gt; * **Rhinoceros companion (Night)** - Kill a player. Bypasses healing and death immunity. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown. 
&gt; * **Crocodile companion (Night)** - Kill a player and anyone that visits them. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown. 
&gt; * **Bear companion (Night)** - Kill everyone visiting you. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.
&gt; * **Wolf companion (Night)** - Make a player start bleeding. They will die in one day unless healed. Unlimited uses. (This is the only night ability that doesn&#39;t have a cooldown).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 18:52:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-beast-lord-neutral-killer/59135.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Beast Lord (Neutral Killer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[psychoneirik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><big><font color="gray">The Beast Lord</font></big><br>
Neutral, Killer.<br>
Win condition: Defeat the Blue Dragon and the Unseen/Cult.<br>
Description: A shapeshifter and beast tamer able to adapt to every situation.</p>
<p><strong>Survival Instincts (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to death at night.<br>
<strong>Lion Form (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to occupation and redirection.<br>
<strong>Morph (Day)</strong> - Change your second passive to a different one. You will keep that passive until you change it again. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-day cooldown.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Available passives:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Lion Form (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to occupation and redirection.</li>
<li>
<strong>Snake Form (Passive)</strong> - You are immune to poison/bleeding. Doesn’t heal you if you change to this passive while you were already poisoned/bleeding.</li>
<li>
<strong>Chameleon Form (Passive)</strong> - Your night abilities don’t count as visiting.</li>
<li>
<strong>Owl Form (Passive)</strong> - You are unaffected by day abilities, except for poison, bleeding or jail.</li>
<li>
<strong>Eagle Form (Passive)</strong> - You will know who visits you every night.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Rampage (Day)</strong> - Your night ability will be instantly available tonight if its on cooldown. 1 use.<br>
<strong>Tiger companion (Night)</strong> - Kill two players. Unlimited uses, but has a one-night cooldown.<br>
<strong>Tame (Night)</strong> - Change your first night ability to a different one. You will keep that ability until you change it again. Unlimited uses.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Available night abilities:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Tiger companion (Night)</strong> - Kill two players. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.</li>
<li>
<strong>Rhinoceros companion (Night)</strong> - Kill a player. Bypasses healing and death immunity. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.</li>
<li>
<strong>Crocodile companion (Night)</strong> - Kill a player and anyone that visits them. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.</li>
<li>
<strong>Bear companion (Night)</strong> - Kill everyone visiting you. Unlimited uses, but has a 1-night cooldown.</li>
<li>
<strong>Wolf companion (Night)</strong> - Make a player start bleeding. They will die in one day unless healed. Unlimited uses. (This is the only night ability that doesn’t have a cooldown).</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-beast-lord-neutral-killer/59135/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-beast-lord-neutral-killer/59135/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 18:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-59135-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/the-beast-lord-neutral-killer/59135.rss">The Beast Lord (Neutral Killer)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
