<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Saru&#39;s Classes - BD Killer and Converts</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261</link>
    <description>I will probably also be posting the Supports one here later, but so far here are my Killer roles.

&gt; # [color = &quot;steblue&quot;] The Duelist [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;steblue&quot;] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]** 
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.
**Schuld (Passive)** - Disables Royal Blood if the Duelist has killed any Blue Dragon-aligned players in the match.
**Versetzen (Day)** - Grants night immunity for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then the Duelist will gain a use of Zornhau. - 2 uses 
**Mittelhau (Night)** - Redirects the selected player’s action to the Duelist while also granting them immunity to all redirected attacks and conversions, then attacks the player. If the Duelist successfully kills a player then they will gain a use of Zornhau. Disables the Duelist’s night abilities if the target is aligned with the Blue Dragon. - Infinite uses 
**Zornhau (Night)** - Prevents the Duelist from being occupied or redirected, then attacks the Duelist’s target and kills them, bypassing healing and night immunity. Disables the Duelist’s night abilities if the target is aligned with the Blue Dragon. - 0 uses 
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

Converts to:
&gt; # [color = &quot;purple&quot;] The Baronet [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;purple&quot;] Unseen Support [/color]** 
**Royal Blood (Passive)** - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.
**Gerissen (Passive)** - If the Baronet becomes the King, then his guards will also have the additional effect of having faction checks automatically return Blue Dragon on their target.
**Vom Tach (Night)** - Deflects any incoming attack against all members of the Unseen and kills the attacker. Also causes Order Execution to be prevented if used on a member of the Unseen. - Three uses 
**Missgunst (Night)** - Removes Royal Blood from a target for the remainder of the game. - 1 use 
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
--------------------
&gt; # [color = &quot;steblue&quot;] The Warrior [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;steblue&quot;] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]** 
**Combat Ready (Passive)** - If the Warrior is attacked during the first three nights, they will be immune and will counterattack instead of dying. 
**Bloodlust (Passive)** - For every successful kill the Warrior will gain an additional night of Combat Ready.
**Raging Axes (Night)** - Attacks and kills a player. If the target was BD-aligned, then the Warrior will lose his night abilities and they will be shown as Unseen or Cult to faction checks. - Infinite uses 
**Taunt (Night)** - Redirects the target’s night action to the Warrior. Redirects past the third night will trigger Combat Ready. - 2 uses 
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

Converts to:
&gt; # [color = &quot;purple&quot;] The Marauder [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;purple&quot;] Unseen Offensive [/color]** 
**Carnage (Passive)** - The Marauder is immune to occupation, death at night, and will counterattack against attackers. This passive is lost once he is promoted to Assassin.
**Aura of Dread (Day)** - All non-Killer roles will be prevented from visiting the Marauder this coming night. - Two uses 
**Boast (Night)** - Redirects players to the Marauder, while also giving redirected faction checks Blue Dragon as feedback. - Infinite uses 
**Glare (Night)** - Occupies a player for the night. If the Marauder’s target is successfully occupied and is also attacked the same night then they cannot be healed and their night immunity will be bypassed. - 2 uses 
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
-------------------------------
&gt; # [color = &quot;steblue&quot;] The Crusader [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;steblue&quot;] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]** 
**Providence (Day)** - If any player not aligned with the Blue Dragon faction visits the Crusader this coming night, they will be prevented and attacked by the Crusader. This does not kill night immune players. - 2 uses 
**Hand of God (Night)** - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Blue Dragon faction visits them they will be killed by the Crusader. This does not stop their actions and does not kill night immune players. While converting, Cult Leaders will gain immunity against the Crusader- Infinite uses 
**Deus Vult (Night)** - Attacks and kills two targets. The Crusader will also die of exhaustion the night they use this ability regardless of the ability’s outcome. - 1 use 
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*

Converts to:
&gt; # [color = &quot;purple&quot;] The Fanatic [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;purple&quot;] Unseen Support [/color]** 
**Piety (Day)** - The Fanatic will be shown as a member of the Blue Dragon to faction checks if investigated the coming night. - 3 uses 
**Martyrdom (Day)** - If a player is executed this day, the Fanatic can choose to sacrifice themselves in order to stop the execution and save the accused played. - 1 use 
**Malleus Maleficarum (Night)** - Prevents Investigative classes from visiting both the Mastermind and the Assassin for the night. - 3 uses 
**Regicide (Night)** - Attacks and kills the King while bypassing all forms of healing and immunities. Regicide will also kill the Fanatic the same night. - 1 use 
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
-----------------
&gt; # [color = &quot;steblue&quot;] The Thaumaturge [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;steblue&quot;] Blue Dragon Killer [/color]** 
**Thaumaturgic Focus (Passive)** - The Thaumaturge is immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Thunder (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Thunder on the Thaumaturge’s target, causing them to explode and kill the player if they are converted. The Thaumaturge is notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the conversion happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses 
**Sigil of Fire (Night)** - Sets a Sigil of Fire on the Thaumaturge’s target, causing them to explode and kill any player that attacks the target, but does not prevent any actions against them. The Thaumaturge is notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the attack happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses 
*Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
Magic User

Converts to
&gt; # [color = &quot;purple&quot;] The Arcanist [/color] 
&gt; **[color = &quot;purple&quot;] Unseen Social [/color]** 
**Arcane Focus (Passive)** - The Arcanist is immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.
**Sigil of Illusion (Night)** - The Arcanist chooses a class and sets a Sigil on another Unseen player and they will show up as the chosen class to any Investigative roles that visits them. The Sigil is destroyed once the target is visited by an Investigative, requiring them to be recast. - Infinite uses 
**Sigil of Madness (Night)** - Puts a Sigil of Madness on a player, permanently giving them a Mind Warp effect until the Arcanist dies. - 1 use 
*Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.*
Magic User</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 04:57:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Saru&#39;s Classes - BD Killer and Converts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eh, I wanted it to be Offensive in order to still allow MMs to claim Princess without getting tripped over here. Though I imagine that Foresight could also be changed to adapt to these classes and also show the class’ previous type before it becomes converted, so yeah.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 04:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68261-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261.rss">Saru&#39;s Classes - BD Killer and Converts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saru&#39;s Classes - BD Killer and Converts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CheesyKnives]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>quick note arcanist should be social tbh</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 19:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68261-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261.rss">Saru&#39;s Classes - BD Killer and Converts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saru&#39;s Classes - BD Killer and Converts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I will probably also be posting the Supports one here later, but so far here are my Killer roles.</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="steblue"> The Duelist </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="steblue"> Blue Dragon Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Royal Blood (Passive)</strong> - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.<br>
<strong>Schuld (Passive)</strong> - Disables Royal Blood if the Duelist has killed any Blue Dragon-aligned players in the match.<br>
<strong>Versetzen (Day)</strong> - Grants night immunity for the coming night. If any attack is blocked then the Duelist will gain a use of Zornhau. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Mittelhau (Night)</strong> - Redirects the selected player’s action to the Duelist while also granting them immunity to all redirected attacks and conversions, then attacks the player. If the Duelist successfully kills a player then they will gain a use of Zornhau. Disables the Duelist’s night abilities if the target is aligned with the Blue Dragon. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Zornhau (Night)</strong> - Prevents the Duelist from being occupied or redirected, then attacks the Duelist’s target and kills them, bypassing healing and night immunity. Disables the Duelist’s night abilities if the target is aligned with the Blue Dragon. - 0 uses<br>
<em>Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Converts to:</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="purple"> The Baronet </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="purple"> Unseen Support </font></strong><br>
<strong>Royal Blood (Passive)</strong> - As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.<br>
<strong>Gerissen (Passive)</strong> - If the Baronet becomes the King, then his guards will also have the additional effect of having faction checks automatically return Blue Dragon on their target.<br>
<strong>Vom Tach (Night)</strong> - Deflects any incoming attack against all members of the Unseen and kills the attacker. Also causes Order Execution to be prevented if used on a member of the Unseen. - Three uses<br>
<strong>Missgunst (Night)</strong> - Removes Royal Blood from a target for the remainder of the game. - 1 use<br>
<em>Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="steblue"> The Warrior </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="steblue"> Blue Dragon Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Combat Ready (Passive)</strong> - If the Warrior is attacked during the first three nights, they will be immune and will counterattack instead of dying.<br>
<strong>Bloodlust (Passive)</strong> - For every successful kill the Warrior will gain an additional night of Combat Ready.<br>
<strong>Raging Axes (Night)</strong> - Attacks and kills a player. If the target was BD-aligned, then the Warrior will lose his night abilities and they will be shown as Unseen or Cult to faction checks. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Taunt (Night)</strong> - Redirects the target’s night action to the Warrior. Redirects past the third night will trigger Combat Ready. - 2 uses<br>
<em>Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Converts to:</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="purple"> The Marauder </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="purple"> Unseen Offensive </font></strong><br>
<strong>Carnage (Passive)</strong> - The Marauder is immune to occupation, death at night, and will counterattack against attackers. This passive is lost once he is promoted to Assassin.<br>
<strong>Aura of Dread (Day)</strong> - All non-Killer roles will be prevented from visiting the Marauder this coming night. - Two uses<br>
<strong>Boast (Night)</strong> - Redirects players to the Marauder, while also giving redirected faction checks Blue Dragon as feedback. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Glare (Night)</strong> - Occupies a player for the night. If the Marauder’s target is successfully occupied and is also attacked the same night then they cannot be healed and their night immunity will be bypassed. - 2 uses<br>
<em>Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="steblue"> The Crusader </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="steblue"> Blue Dragon Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Providence (Day)</strong> - If any player not aligned with the Blue Dragon faction visits the Crusader this coming night, they will be prevented and attacked by the Crusader. This does not kill night immune players. - 2 uses<br>
<strong>Hand of God (Night)</strong> - Guards a target. If any player not aligned with the Blue Dragon faction visits them they will be killed by the Crusader. This does not stop their actions and does not kill night immune players. While converting, Cult Leaders will gain immunity against the Crusader- Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Deus Vult (Night)</strong> - Attacks and kills two targets. The Crusader will also die of exhaustion the night they use this ability regardless of the ability’s outcome. - 1 use<br>
<em>Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Converts to:</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="purple"> The Fanatic </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="purple"> Unseen Support </font></strong><br>
<strong>Piety (Day)</strong> - The Fanatic will be shown as a member of the Blue Dragon to faction checks if investigated the coming night. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Martyrdom (Day)</strong> - If a player is executed this day, the Fanatic can choose to sacrifice themselves in order to stop the execution and save the accused played. - 1 use<br>
<strong>Malleus Maleficarum (Night)</strong> - Prevents Investigative classes from visiting both the Mastermind and the Assassin for the night. - 3 uses<br>
<strong>Regicide (Night)</strong> - Attacks and kills the King while bypassing all forms of healing and immunities. Regicide will also kill the Fanatic the same night. - 1 use<br>
<em>Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="steblue"> The Thaumaturge </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="steblue"> Blue Dragon Killer </font></strong><br>
<strong>Thaumaturgic Focus (Passive)</strong> - The Thaumaturge is immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.<br>
<strong>Sigil of Thunder (Night)</strong> - Sets a Sigil of Thunder on the Thaumaturge’s target, causing them to explode and kill the player if they are converted. The Thaumaturge is notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the conversion happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Sigil of Fire (Night)</strong> - Sets a Sigil of Fire on the Thaumaturge’s target, causing them to explode and kill any player that attacks the target, but does not prevent any actions against them. The Thaumaturge is notified if the Sigil explodes and recasting this spell will change which player has the Sigil. The Sigil will not activate if the attack happens the same night it is placed. - Infinite uses<br>
<em>Defeat the Unseen or Cult and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em><br>
Magic User</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Converts to</p>
<blockquote>
<h1><font color="purple"> The Arcanist </font></h1>
<p><strong><font color="purple"> Unseen Social </font></strong><br>
<strong>Arcane Focus (Passive)</strong> - The Arcanist is immune to being occupied at night and immune to target changing.<br>
<strong>Sigil of Illusion (Night)</strong> - The Arcanist chooses a class and sets a Sigil on another Unseen player and they will show up as the chosen class to any Investigative roles that visits them. The Sigil is destroyed once the target is visited by an Investigative, requiring them to be recast. - Infinite uses<br>
<strong>Sigil of Madness (Night)</strong> - Puts a Sigil of Madness on a player, permanently giving them a Mind Warp effect until the Arcanist dies. - 1 use<br>
<em>Defeat the Blue Dragon and any neutrals that seek to do you harm.</em><br>
Magic User</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 17:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-68261-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/sarus-classes-bd-killer-and-converts/68261.rss">Saru&#39;s Classes - BD Killer and Converts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
