<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Possessor vs. Knight</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281</link>
    <description>Hey guys, it&#39;s me again with another suggestion!
Nice to see you again, loved the new haircut. :slight_smile:
So, I just had another game where I was Knight (knight claims in 2017 lul), guarded King n1 and got his killer: a possessed CW. Sad story that repeats itself often.
With that Possessor almost always get as many double kills as there are Knights. The Knight dies for nothing, helps BD with nothing and just get frustrated as hell.
I got a suggestion for that:
If a possessed target attacks a King that is guarded by a Knight, the possessed dies. The King gets a message saying a possessed target attacked him but he was guarded. Knight gets a similar message. Possessor gets the message that the attack was prevented by a guard.
If you think that&#39;s too OP, attacking a guarded king could get the Knight &quot;stunned&quot;, occupying him the following night. Or something like that.
I don&#39;t know, what do you guys think? I tried to make it a win-win suggestion, as possessor would still get a kill, so not really losing a lot there. Knight would be happy that he guarded King and King would be happy to be alive. The possessed target was possessed so nothing to do there, tough luck.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 01:50:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Possessor vs. Knight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vandalay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree there… right now there’s balance between the NKs where no one type of protective works for everything… knights weakness is the possesor that has a chance ot double kill… physician’s weakness is the reaper of which he can do nothing against.</p>
<p>IF a buff really were needed (which I do not think it is), I’d say at least to go the route of say the knight only blocking the possesed person with nobody dying… but again I don’t agree with it. Possesor is hard enough as it is.</p>
<p>His weaknesses are… 1. possesing itself is excessively dangerous due to the possibility of a psychic, or information/whispers in which he would not be familiar with that may have been passed through, he has no way to overcome immunity or healing, etc… His only stregnth is that via possesion he can avoid the auto death that comes from attacking a hunter or a knight… that stregnth should not be taken away IMO.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 01:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27281-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281.rss">Possessor vs. Knight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possessor vs. Knight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[methomps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Rather than change the interaction, I simply think knights should not guard king until it is confirmed reaper/sorc game.  Healers can protect king from possessor attacks.  No need to make it harder for NKs at the moment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27281-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281.rss">Possessor vs. Knight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possessor vs. Knight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sheepish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys, it’s me again with another suggestion!<br>
Nice to see you again, loved the new haircut. <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
So, I just had another game where I was Knight (knight claims in 2017 lul), guarded King n1 and got his killer: a possessed CW. Sad story that repeats itself often.<br>
With that Possessor almost always get as many double kills as there are Knights. The Knight dies for nothing, helps BD with nothing and just get frustrated as hell.<br>
I got a suggestion for that:<br>
If a possessed target attacks a King that is guarded by a Knight, the possessed dies. The King gets a message saying a possessed target attacked him but he was guarded. Knight gets a similar message. Possessor gets the message that the attack was prevented by a guard.<br>
If you think that’s too OP, attacking a guarded king could get the Knight “stunned”, occupying him the following night. Or something like that.<br>
I don’t know, what do you guys think? I tried to make it a win-win suggestion, as possessor would still get a kill, so not really losing a lot there. Knight would be happy that he guarded King and King would be happy to be alive. The possessed target was possessed so nothing to do there, tough luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-27281-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/possessor-vs-knight/27281.rss">Possessor vs. Knight</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
