<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Acolyte</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-acolyte/2479</link>
    <description>**__The Spawn of Corax__**

The Cult was failing, Mithras grew tired of their silly games, and yet he still hungered for blood, Corax was much the same, unamused by the antics those pathetic mortals called &#39;progress&#39;, someone was needed to whip those sorry excuses for followers into shape, and Corax knew just the man for the job.

Their prayers and spilled blood would be answered, for their one and only would rise from a wound in reality. He appeared, the spawn sent by Corax. Adorned by a red cloak and his face blistered. He carried with him a small dagger, forged from the bones of Corax himself.

With blood shot eyes and crooked bones, he peered up at the lonesome Cult Leader. The skin on his face began to shift as his mouth curved into a sharp grin. 

He spoke, softly and gently, with a slight deep pitch, &quot;It will be done&quot;

This man did not seek glory, he didn&#39;t care for recognition, he didn&#39;t want to lead the Cult to victory, just give it a few nudges in the right direction, he was not a &#39;people person&#39;, he was barely a person, and the Cult Leader had his doubts, but the man quickly proved his master&#39;s judgement was impeccable, as always.

He did not care what was required of him, he met every demand with a sickening grin and a nightmarish whisper, &quot;...as you wish, my lord&quot;

***Credit to Ruby too for helping with this***</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 07:56:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-acolyte/2479.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] The Acolyte</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePlex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong><strong>The Spawn of Corax</strong></strong></p>
<p>The Cult was failing, Mithras grew tired of their silly games, and yet he still hungered for blood, Corax was much the same, unamused by the antics those pathetic mortals called ‘progress’, someone was needed to whip those sorry excuses for followers into shape, and Corax knew just the man for the job.</p>
<p>Their prayers and spilled blood would be answered, for their one and only would rise from a wound in reality. He appeared, the spawn sent by Corax. Adorned by a red cloak and his face blistered. He carried with him a small dagger, forged from the bones of Corax himself.</p>
<p>With blood shot eyes and crooked bones, he peered up at the lonesome Cult Leader. The skin on his face began to shift as his mouth curved into a sharp grin.</p>
<p>He spoke, softly and gently, with a slight deep pitch, “It will be done”</p>
<p>This man did not seek glory, he didn’t care for recognition, he didn’t want to lead the Cult to victory, just give it a few nudges in the right direction, he was not a ‘people person’, he was barely a person, and the Cult Leader had his doubts, but the man quickly proved his master’s judgement was impeccable, as always.</p>
<p>He did not care what was required of him, he met every demand with a sickening grin and a nightmarish whisper, “…as you wish, my lord”</p>
<p><em><strong>Credit to Ruby too for helping with this</strong></em></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-acolyte/2479/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-acolyte/2479/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 04:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2479-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-the-acolyte/2479.rss">[Lore Suggestion] The Acolyte</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
