<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704</link>
    <description>Playing as a Neutral Killer is hard. Like. Real hard. I think most of the community is generally frustrated with how challenging it is to win as Neutral Killers. As result of that frustration, I&#39;ve seen many Neutral Killers resort to killing the king and then banking their entire game on becoming king by openly claiming what they are and praying that they will win the vote. That&#39;s not how they should be played. I think the Neutral Killers all need some minor buffs... below is what I came up with after some thinking.

REAPER:
What&#39;s wrong with it: My biggest problem with the reaper is that it is incredibly noticeable compared to the other two Neutral Killers. The missing journal entries and lack of immediate death are a surefire indication that a reaper is present, and constant (and frankly - annoying) &quot;reaper checks&quot; that result from this can get in the way of genuine conversation during the day. 

Possible solution: For the reaper, I think it would be interesting and beneficial if you gained the ability to talk as the person you&#39;ve reaped during the day. I imagine it akin to trollbox, but with unlimited use throughout the day - allowing you to talk as both yourself and as your victim. This would prevent anyone from trying &quot;reaper checks&quot; anymore (since the reaped would still be capable of speech, thus rendering it useless) and give the Reaper a chance at misdirection during the day. No one will know that the victim was reaped until they see the journal after they die the following night. That could make for some interesting reaper plays where that could earn false executions during the day or trick people into making poor choices at night - both of which would take the reaper closer to their ultimate goal of winning. 

POSSESSOR:
What&#39;s wrong with it: In my opinion, not much at all. The Possessor is probably the most flexible of the Neutral Killers, with many different strategies that I often see in use surrounding it. If I had any one complaint, it&#39;s that possession seems to happen only near the very end of the game now that the possessor only has 1 possess charge - and many possessors tend to get executed during the day well before they use it. Given that possessing another player is their most interesting ability, I consider this to be a shame.

Possible Solution: Give the possessor 2 possesses? This would make most possessors use their possess a little more freely, I think, while still forcing them to really strategize and weigh when the right time to jump and who the right target to jump into is.

SORCERER:
What&#39;s Wrong with it: The inquisitor is constantly hunting you down - that&#39;s a pressure that none of the other Neutral Killers have.Right now, it feels way too easy for the Inquisitor to win... I think that is, in part, due to how easy it is to find the Sorcerer as the Inquisitor. At present, the only way to safely evade the Inquisitor until you kill them is to mislead them into finding other &quot;magic users&quot; that aren&#39;t you. However, the only means you have of doing so is through magic dust - which is a single target power with a measly single charge. The odds of you picking the target the inquisitor is investigating with your dust seems very low. From my experience, most inquisitors don&#39;t even consider magic dust a great threat to their results. I have yet to see an Inquisitor do a double check to make sure their target was not dusted. That really shouldn&#39;t be the case.

Possible Solution: Make the Sorcerer&#39;s magic dust target 2 people per use... this allows the Sorcerer to gain wider coverage with their magic dust and increases their odds of misleading the inquisitor and keeping them off their trail. This would also make it much easier to falsely claim magic dust when an inquisitor calls you out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feedback/Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moleland]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wish you could use Circle of Death on yourself</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20704-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss">Neutral Killer Buffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just played sorc for the first time. Sorc is nearly impossible to win with. I thought i was going to use circle of death…lol j/k dead n4 from inq. I got random accused d2 and had to claim. Inq could have sat back and did nothing and still win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20704-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss">Neutral Killer Buffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jabba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If it’s late enough in the game for possessor to jump, and it’s to Prince, then hopefully the fool, if there is one, would have died already, bc possessor shouldn’t be jumping in the first 5 days</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20704-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss">Neutral Killer Buffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Possessor.always dies early. Claim knight and get found neutral…dead. Claim but and dead. Jump to someone. Just kidding psychic talked to the guy you jumped too.</p>
<p>NKs are stuck to playing the super late game don’t kill anyone or become king meta. It’s weak and boring as fuck for a killer class. If I wanted to play late game I would join BD.</p>
<p>Also don’t jump to prince. That goes like this. King says prince jail 2 and exe it’s fool. Next day 2 is alive. Ok poss did jump. Exe Prince.  Gg</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20704-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss">Neutral Killer Buffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbiaglla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You had me agreeing 100% until I came to possessor. Nothing wrong with possessor? Try two psychics and code words you can’t possibly know. You can give him unlimited possessions and he still won’t win without becoming king or both sides are extremely autistic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20704-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss">Neutral Killer Buffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jabba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Firstly you have to remember that playing NK is supposed to be hard - they’re supposed to barely ever win, otherwise it would be no fun if one person easily one just by getting the superpowerful killer class and going on a kill streak the whole game.<br>
I actually find reaper to be the easiest NK even with the obviousness of his presence, from personal experience I have seen reapers win plenty but never a sorcerer win.<br>
Possessor I think has the most untapped potential because people think they HAVE to start killing people off just because they’re NK, while possessor is really best played discreetly, as they can cruise through the game with night and occupation immunity, only killing key targets by possessing themselves (a lot of people don’t realize this is a thing); in addition to the fact that once people start suspecting an NK, you as possessor claim that you yourself were possessed some night that you kill someone.  The last tip about possessor is to never possess the king unless it’ll win you the game, as he’s easily the most identifiable due to his finger ability.  It’s better to possess an outed Prince or someone that is known to be trustworthy and unconvertible, so the remaining BD don’t want to risk hanging them during the day.  Prince himself is a really good target because you can just claim that you caught and executed the possessor last night if BD still thinks there’s unseen out there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 03:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20704-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss">Neutral Killer Buffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Neutral Killer Buffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShaneNineOne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Playing as a Neutral Killer is hard. Like. Real hard. I think most of the community is generally frustrated with how challenging it is to win as Neutral Killers. As result of that frustration, I’ve seen many Neutral Killers resort to killing the king and then banking their entire game on becoming king by openly claiming what they are and praying that they will win the vote. That’s not how they should be played. I think the Neutral Killers all need some minor buffs… below is what I came up with after some thinking.</p>
<p>REAPER:<br>
What’s wrong with it: My biggest problem with the reaper is that it is incredibly noticeable compared to the other two Neutral Killers. The missing journal entries and lack of immediate death are a surefire indication that a reaper is present, and constant (and frankly - annoying) “reaper checks” that result from this can get in the way of genuine conversation during the day.</p>
<p>Possible solution: For the reaper, I think it would be interesting and beneficial if you gained the ability to talk as the person you’ve reaped during the day. I imagine it akin to trollbox, but with unlimited use throughout the day - allowing you to talk as both yourself and as your victim. This would prevent anyone from trying “reaper checks” anymore (since the reaped would still be capable of speech, thus rendering it useless) and give the Reaper a chance at misdirection during the day. No one will know that the victim was reaped until they see the journal after they die the following night. That could make for some interesting reaper plays where that could earn false executions during the day or trick people into making poor choices at night - both of which would take the reaper closer to their ultimate goal of winning.</p>
<p>POSSESSOR:<br>
What’s wrong with it: In my opinion, not much at all. The Possessor is probably the most flexible of the Neutral Killers, with many different strategies that I often see in use surrounding it. If I had any one complaint, it’s that possession seems to happen only near the very end of the game now that the possessor only has 1 possess charge - and many possessors tend to get executed during the day well before they use it. Given that possessing another player is their most interesting ability, I consider this to be a shame.</p>
<p>Possible Solution: Give the possessor 2 possesses? This would make most possessors use their possess a little more freely, I think, while still forcing them to really strategize and weigh when the right time to jump and who the right target to jump into is.</p>
<p>SORCERER:<br>
What’s Wrong with it: The inquisitor is constantly hunting you down - that’s a pressure that none of the other Neutral Killers have.Right now, it feels way too easy for the Inquisitor to win… I think that is, in part, due to how easy it is to find the Sorcerer as the Inquisitor. At present, the only way to safely evade the Inquisitor until you kill them is to mislead them into finding other “magic users” that aren’t you. However, the only means you have of doing so is through magic dust - which is a single target power with a measly single charge. The odds of you picking the target the inquisitor is investigating with your dust seems very low. From my experience, most inquisitors don’t even consider magic dust a great threat to their results. I have yet to see an Inquisitor do a double check to make sure their target was not dusted. That really shouldn’t be the case.</p>
<p>Possible Solution: Make the Sorcerer’s magic dust target 2 people per use… this allows the Sorcerer to gain wider coverage with their magic dust and increases their odds of misleading the inquisitor and keeping them off their trail. This would also make it much easier to falsely claim magic dust when an inquisitor calls you out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 03:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-20704-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/neutral-killer-buffs/20704.rss">Neutral Killer Buffs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
