<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Lore Suggestion] Unseen</title>
    <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568</link>
    <description>Once the all mighty Blue Dragon, ruled the land, with none to dare to oppose them. Their king was just and kind, and all lived in harmony one day after another. It was nice times, times in which you could look into the sky and see the sun; a yellow dot. It spread its glorious sunlight all through the kingdom bringing people happiness and joy. Flower were blooming, dandelion&#39;s pedals were floating way in the wind. Water was slowly going down into a pond in which it then vibrated the area that surrounded it, bring it life. For a long time every one was happy, until one day.............

In the pale moonlight, something awful happened. It was during a dark time in the city, each were in fear. Due to the murder of the king. Everyone feared for their lives. Until one man stepped up to the throne, one that wasn&#39;t so kind and nice as the last king. It was his brother. He was not happy about his brothers death, so he demanded the guards to search every house for the murderer, but little did they know the the king, the one that died, killed himself.  Upon entry into the prime suspect&#39;s house, one that did not like the new king. He asked the guards to get out of his house. None of them obeyed, except one, one that was of friend of the man&#39;s. One that despised the king as much has he did. So, that knight left the house and disappeared into the moonlight, he went rogue. See, this knight was the son of an alchemist, one that had a very powerful role in the kingdom. This alchemist, or his father, told him about a poisonous fruit/herb called **nightshade**, this fruit/herb was a banished item from the kingdom, anyone who brought it in without permission from the king would be put on trial and most likely executed. This knight knew that and left the kingdom in search of these herbs/fruits. Then he heard a cry for help.

Meanwhile back at the ranch, the loyal guards to the kingdom dragged the man away. He struggled then stated, &quot;Let me go you idiots, I am not the perpetrator of this crime, It was obviously a suicide, why am I getting charged for murder!&quot;.
The guards responded by saying, &quot;God why did we not gag him?&quot;. The man the pleaded for help. But no one came to his rescue. As they slowly approached the castle in the distance, he started  to try to free himself more and more. Then they walked across the bridge slowly. Then the man noticed something. There was a man on the other side of the bridge. He was dressed in a sort of robe. With red eyes and a bandana, as they approached they castle he could notice that the man didn&#39;t carry a sword, but a dagger, and a small bag of something. The man stayed quite, since he was hiding only in the bushes, a single move would give away his position. As the knights approached the door to the castle with the prisoner, this is when the man in the bushes struck. He took both knights by surprise and the died due to a dagger to the heart. The man saved the falsely accused. The man in robes was a assassin, who was formerly a knight raised by an alchemist. Then forced to turn into a knight by the kings request. Then a army of guards approached from the other side of the bridge since the stabbing of the guards triggered the attention of a observer in the distance, who then called out, &quot;There is a man by the castle murdering people!&quot;. This prompted all of the knights to go to the bridge were they saw a man in robes holding another up. The man in robes, the pulled out his dagger and cut the rope of the bridge, so then the knight couldn&#39;t get over, and jumped into the raging river that awaited below them.

2 hours later.

The man in robes opened his eyes to see they were on a beach, and he saw the person he rescued in the distance. The man in robes ran over to the man, and then held him up. He slowly walked over to a near by tree and put the man down. After a while the man opened his eyes to see the man that rescued him in front of him, he coughed, then stated, &quot;You are the kindest man I&#39;ve met sadly we are most likely being hunted by the blue dragon and our time here is short, we must move if we want to live.&quot; The man in robes then stated, &quot;No.&quot; The other man then stated, &quot;Why, do you want to take down the blue dragon?&#39;. The man in robes replied, &quot;Yes, for I was once trying to become a master alchemist before the king&#39;s guards forced me to become one of them, and destroyed my hopes. For that, I seek vengeance, for now I am a assassin&quot;. The man by the tree replied, &quot;Well if we want to defeat blue dragon we must first infiltrate them gather a army of all of those who also seek to destroy them.&quot; For now until we are ready to fight, we will remain as the unseen of this land, and I will be the mastermind behind it all!&quot;.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 16:43:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Unseen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 16:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2568-3</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Unseen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Unseen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Queen_Alfa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Braixen" data-post="1" data-topic="2568">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/braixen/40/26209_2.png" class="avatar"> Braixen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this knight was the sun of an alchemist</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sun of an alchemist <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Braixen" data-post="1" data-topic="2568">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/braixen/40/26209_2.png" class="avatar"> Braixen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I was obviously a suicide</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was obviously a suicide! I am SUICIDE</p>
<p>I like this lore <img src="/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 09:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2568-2</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Unseen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Lore Suggestion] Unseen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Braixen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Once the all mighty Blue Dragon, ruled the land, with none to dare to oppose them. Their king was just and kind, and all lived in harmony one day after another. It was nice times, times in which you could look into the sky and see the sun; a yellow dot. It spread its glorious sunlight all through the kingdom bringing people happiness and joy. Flower were blooming, dandelion’s pedals were floating way in the wind. Water was slowly going down into a pond in which it then vibrated the area that surrounded it, bring it life. For a long time every one was happy, until one day…</p>
<p>In the pale moonlight, something awful happened. It was during a dark time in the city, each were in fear. Due to the murder of the king. Everyone feared for their lives. Until one man stepped up to the throne, one that wasn’t so kind and nice as the last king. It was his brother. He was not happy about his brothers death, so he demanded the guards to search every house for the murderer, but little did they know the the king, the one that died, killed himself.  Upon entry into the prime suspect’s house, one that did not like the new king. He asked the guards to get out of his house. None of them obeyed, except one, one that was of friend of the man’s. One that despised the king as much has he did. So, that knight left the house and disappeared into the moonlight, he went rogue. See, this knight was the son of an alchemist, one that had a very powerful role in the kingdom. This alchemist, or his father, told him about a poisonous fruit/herb called <strong>nightshade</strong>, this fruit/herb was a banished item from the kingdom, anyone who brought it in without permission from the king would be put on trial and most likely executed. This knight knew that and left the kingdom in search of these herbs/fruits. Then he heard a cry for help.</p>
<p>Meanwhile back at the ranch, the loyal guards to the kingdom dragged the man away. He struggled then stated, “Let me go you idiots, I am not the perpetrator of this crime, It was obviously a suicide, why am I getting charged for murder!”.<br>
The guards responded by saying, “God why did we not gag him?”. The man the pleaded for help. But no one came to his rescue. As they slowly approached the castle in the distance, he started  to try to free himself more and more. Then they walked across the bridge slowly. Then the man noticed something. There was a man on the other side of the bridge. He was dressed in a sort of robe. With red eyes and a bandana, as they approached they castle he could notice that the man didn’t carry a sword, but a dagger, and a small bag of something. The man stayed quite, since he was hiding only in the bushes, a single move would give away his position. As the knights approached the door to the castle with the prisoner, this is when the man in the bushes struck. He took both knights by surprise and the died due to a dagger to the heart. The man saved the falsely accused. The man in robes was a assassin, who was formerly a knight raised by an alchemist. Then forced to turn into a knight by the kings request. Then a army of guards approached from the other side of the bridge since the stabbing of the guards triggered the attention of a observer in the distance, who then called out, “There is a man by the castle murdering people!”. This prompted all of the knights to go to the bridge were they saw a man in robes holding another up. The man in robes, the pulled out his dagger and cut the rope of the bridge, so then the knight couldn’t get over, and jumped into the raging river that awaited below them.</p>
<p>2 hours later.</p>
<p>The man in robes opened his eyes to see they were on a beach, and he saw the person he rescued in the distance. The man in robes ran over to the man, and then held him up. He slowly walked over to a near by tree and put the man down. After a while the man opened his eyes to see the man that rescued him in front of him, he coughed, then stated, “You are the kindest man I’ve met sadly we are most likely being hunted by the blue dragon and our time here is short, we must move if we want to live.” The man in robes then stated, “No.” The other man then stated, “Why, do you want to take down the blue dragon?’. The man in robes replied, “Yes, for I was once trying to become a master alchemist before the king’s guards forced me to become one of them, and destroyed my hopes. For that, I seek vengeance, for now I am a assassin”. The man by the tree replied, “Well if we want to defeat blue dragon we must first infiltrate them gather a army of all of those who also seek to destroy them.” For now until we are ready to fight, we will remain as the unseen of this land, and I will be the mastermind behind it all!”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 05:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-2568-1</guid>
        <source url="https://fol-archive.netlify.app/t/lore-suggestion-unseen/2568.rss">[Lore Suggestion] Unseen</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
