<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</title>
    <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286</link>
    <description>Hey Folks I&#39;ve been racking my brain on classes and it&#39;s really fun to think up some random ideas. Here is some ideas I have come up with. Noble should be like a &quot;Mini king&quot; Much like how psychic is sort of like a &quot;mini prince&quot; Is sort of my idea with the reworked noble.


The Noble (Social) (Unique)  -&gt; The Kings right hand man.

PASSIVES:
Royal Messengers-&gt; Whispers to and from you are hidden from view.
*The Noble never does anything himself. Nobles send messengers to exchange information to allies without endangering themselves.*

Royal Blood-&gt; [Only usable upon the death of a king] As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.

Only 1 Day ability allowed to be used per day*

Day Ability 1:
Maid Spies [infinite]-&gt; Select a player and listen in from all whispers to/from selected player. 

Day Ability 2:
Nobles Word[infinite]-&gt; (only usable after you vote someone for Treason)  Add an extra vote for treason (this does not appear on the chat logs)

Day Ability 3:
Blackmail the King [1] -&gt; (Only usable when someone is being voted for execution of treason) Allows you to veto the decision at the final vote to force pardon the accused player. They will also be immune to accusations for the day. (Appear as &quot;A Noble suddenly whispered in the kings ear, The king cordially pardons the accused.&quot; (Does not spend The King&#39;s &quot;Decide Fate&quot; Ability) 

***If only 2 day abilities are limited then &quot;Nobles word&quot; can work as a double skill if possible? Able to give yourself an extra vote for treason while in the process of voting someone for treason or Force pardon the accused if they are at the Final Vote. 

Only one Night ability allowed per night*

Night Ability 1:
Messengers [2] -&gt; Allows you to anonymously send a message to a selected player. This message will be delivered at the start of the next day.  (It would appear as &quot;A message was left at your door.&quot;)

Night Ability 2 
Secret Service [3] -&gt; Select a player and listen in from all whispers to/from them for the next day.

I think this sort of fits with what the noble originally was as someone who can listen in on the kings whispers. In addition you can now listen to 2 people simultaneously by using secret service at night, And spy maids during the day. Now also added his ability to affect votes for treason by giving him an extra vote (On top of kings vote). The noble can have close connection with King and try and figure out what his faction is by listening in on important information. Your Blackmail ability will allow you to save important BD targets such as the prince who inevitably gets voted up by evil king and force executed. There will be a race to who can decide the fate first :^). 

CONVERTED -&gt; ARISTOCRAT

All abilities are the same except these that are changed:

Day ability 3:
Coerce the King[1]-&gt;  (Only usable when someone is being voted for execution of treason) Allows you to veto the decision at the final vote to force execute the accused player. It will appear as the King decided to execute. (Does not spend The King&#39;s &quot;Decide Fate&quot; Ability)

***Upon review This skill may be overpowered as a converted Noble will most likely force execute the next player on stand.

Night Ability 1:

Royal Spies[2]-&gt; The members of the Unseen can listen in on the Prince&#39;s conversations that night.

***Very similar to other abilities but sort of fits the noble a little bit. (Only one other converted class has this ability (the Marshal)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 21:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Class/Lore/Fanfic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fauker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m thinking maybe just remove the Ability to force execute from the Aristocrat is a better idea. There is no reason not to force execute the next person that goes up on trial that isn’t unseen.</p>
<p>I think there should be some risk reward in playing the noble. You kind of sit behind the scenes and scope information. I really enjoyed the iteration of Noble when he had the maid spies so I tailored this noble around the same thing. The ability to force pardon someone seems interesting but even if though people will find your presence. It’s like the king force executing the prince and instantly you’re outed as evil king. They will know a noble pardoned but they won’t know what number they are unless they’ve outed to other players.</p>
<p>As for “everyone, whisper king so we can find noble” Seems like a stretch. If they are only limited to 2 day abilities I could use “Nobles word” as a double skill? Since you can only use one day ability maybe make a two for one ability?</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 21:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29286-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286.rss">[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wolfy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fauker" data-post="1" data-topic="29286">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.throneoflies.com/user_avatar/forum.throneoflies.com/fauker/40/2457_2.png" class="avatar"> Fauker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Coerce the King[1]-&gt;  (Only usable when someone is being voted for execution of treason) Allows you to veto the decision at the final vote to force execute the accused player. It will appear as the King decided to execute. (Does not spend The King’s “Decide Fate” Ability)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think the Aristocrat and Noble should be given a choice, cuz the execute will out them instantly.</p>
<p>Also another problem, the King can say they didn’t use the decide fate and again, people will find out quickly of the presence.</p>
<p>Idea is good though</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29286-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286.rss">[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devin_Colp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 14:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29286-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286.rss">[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RopeStringFace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“everyone, whisper king so we can find noble”</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 13:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29286-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286.rss">[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NuclearBurrito]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Only 2 day Ability’s</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 11:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29286-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286.rss">[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fauker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey Folks I’ve been racking my brain on classes and it’s really fun to think up some random ideas. Here is some ideas I have come up with. Noble should be like a “Mini king” Much like how psychic is sort of like a “mini prince” Is sort of my idea with the reworked noble.</p>
<p>The Noble (Social) (Unique)  -&gt; The Kings right hand man.</p>
<p>PASSIVES:<br>
Royal Messengers-&gt; Whispers to and from you are hidden from view.<br>
<em>The Noble never does anything himself. Nobles send messengers to exchange information to allies without endangering themselves.</em></p>
<p>Royal Blood-&gt; [Only usable upon the death of a king] As a Royal, you can put your name forward for nominations to become the next King.</p>
<p>Only 1 Day ability allowed to be used per day*</p>
<p>Day Ability 1:<br>
Maid Spies [infinite]-&gt; Select a player and listen in from all whispers to/from selected player.</p>
<p>Day Ability 2:<br>
Nobles Word[infinite]-&gt; (only usable after you vote someone for Treason)  Add an extra vote for treason (this does not appear on the chat logs)</p>
<p>Day Ability 3:<br>
Blackmail the King [1] -&gt; (Only usable when someone is being voted for execution of treason) Allows you to veto the decision at the final vote to force pardon the accused player. They will also be immune to accusations for the day. (Appear as “A Noble suddenly whispered in the kings ear, The king cordially pardons the accused.” (Does not spend The King’s “Decide Fate” Ability)</p>
<p>***If only 2 day abilities are limited then “Nobles word” can work as a double skill if possible? Able to give yourself an extra vote for treason while in the process of voting someone for treason or Force pardon the accused if they are at the Final Vote.</p>
<p>Only one Night ability allowed per night*</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:<br>
Messengers [2] -&gt; Allows you to anonymously send a message to a selected player. This message will be delivered at the start of the next day.  (It would appear as “A message was left at your door.”)</p>
<p>Night Ability 2<br>
Secret Service [3] -&gt; Select a player and listen in from all whispers to/from them for the next day.</p>
<p>I think this sort of fits with what the noble originally was as someone who can listen in on the kings whispers. In addition you can now listen to 2 people simultaneously by using secret service at night, And spy maids during the day. Now also added his ability to affect votes for treason by giving him an extra vote (On top of kings vote). The noble can have close connection with King and try and figure out what his faction is by listening in on important information. Your Blackmail ability will allow you to save important BD targets such as the prince who inevitably gets voted up by evil king and force executed. There will be a race to who can decide the fate first :^).</p>
<p>CONVERTED -&gt; ARISTOCRAT</p>
<p>All abilities are the same except these that are changed:</p>
<p>Day ability 3:<br>
Coerce the King[1]-&gt;  (Only usable when someone is being voted for execution of treason) Allows you to veto the decision at the final vote to force execute the accused player. It will appear as the King decided to execute. (Does not spend The King’s “Decide Fate” Ability)</p>
<p>***Upon review This skill may be overpowered as a converted Noble will most likely force execute the next player on stand.</p>
<p>Night Ability 1:</p>
<p>Royal Spies[2]-&gt; The members of the Unseen can listen in on the Prince’s conversations that night.</p>
<p>***Very similar to other abilities but sort of fits the noble a little bit. (Only one other converted class has this ability (the Marshal)</p>
          <p><a href="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 03:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.throneoflies.com-post-29286-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.throneoflies.com/t/class-suggestion-reworked-noble/29286.rss">[Class suggestion] Reworked Noble</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
